<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medictallaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[This Simple Oral Hygiene Habit May Help Protect You From Stroke]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/this-simple-oral- hygiene-habit-may-help-protect-you-Stroke-473060 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that flossing at least once a week can significantly reduce stroke risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/this-simple-oral- hygiene-habit-may-help-protect-you-Stroke-473060</guid><pubDate> Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:01:00 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Journavx, New Type Of Non-Opioid Pain Relief Drug Gets FDA Approval]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/journavx-new-type-non-opioid-pain-pain-relief-drug-gets-fda-appraval-473058 <description><![CDATA[Suzetrigine, a new non-opioid pain relief drug sold under the brand name Journavx marks the first new class of pain reliever to receive FDA approval in over two decades.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/journavx-new-type-non-opioid-pain-pain-relief-drug-gets-fda-appraval-473058</guid><pubDate> Fri, 31 Jan 2025 04:20:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[You Shouldn't Scratch An Itch—So Why Does It Feel So Good? Are There Benefits?]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/you-shouldt-scratch-scratch-scratchso-why-does-it-feel-so-so-so-so--so-are-are-473056 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that while scratching worsens inflammation and swelling, it also has certain benefits which may explain why the natural urge feels so irresistible.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/you-shouldt-scratch-scratch-scratchso-why-does-it-feel-so-so-so-so--so-are-are-473056</guid><pubDate> Fri, 31 Jan 2025 01:25:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Stick To Your Resolutions? It Takes At Least Two Months To Build A Habit]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/struggling-stick-yresolutions-it-t-least-two-months-build-habit-473055 <description><![CDATA[The researchers believe that the current findings would help "people set realistic expectations" about habit formation, encouraging them to stay committed even if progress feels slow.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/struggling-stick-yresolutions-it-t-least-two-months-build-habit-473055</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Jan 2025 05:10:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Food Noise? Weight Loss Doctor Shares Ways To Manage It Without Medications]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/whatfood-noise-weight-weight-loss-doctor-shares- Quays-Manage-it-Without-Without-Medications 473053 <description><![CDATA[Struggling to lose weight but constantly thinking about food? You might be dealing with "food noise"]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/whatfood-noise-weight-weight-loss-doctor-shares- Quays-Manage-it-Without-Without-Medications 473053</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:23:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Neuroscientist Warns: 3 Drinks That May Harm Your Memory, And What To Sip Instead]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/neuroscientist-warns-3-dogst-wat-may-harm-y-your-memory-memory-memory-memory-memory-473050 <description><![CDATA[What you drink could be quietly affecting your brain health, warns a leading neuroscientist specialized in Alzheimer's prevention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/neuroscientist-warns-3-dogst-wat-may-harm-y-your-memory-memory-memory-memory-memory-473050</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Jan 2025 00:42:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Kansas Tuberculosis Outbreak That Killed Two, Sickened Dozens, Among Largest In U.S. History]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/kansas-tuberculisosis爆发 - 盗用到两次添加的 - 添加添加的dozens-among-among-as-history-History-473048 <description><![CDATA[As of Jan. 24, the Kansas Department of Health and Environment reported 67 confirmed cases of active tuberculosis, along with 79 latent infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/kansas-tuberculisosis爆发 - 盗用到两次添加的 - 添加添加的dozens-among-among-as-history-History-473048</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Jan 2025 04:56:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is 1:1 Diet? Woman Drops 83 Pounds After Declining Gastric Sleeve, Feels Like 'Walking On Air']]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/what-- <description><![CDATA[Instead of opting for gastric sleeve surgery, which she feared due to potential side effects, she chose a simple diet—a decision she calls the "best" she's ever made, completely transforming her life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/what--</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:14:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[29-Year-Old Died After Chiropractor Adjusted 'Crack In Her Neck', Coroner Questions Lack Of Medical History Review]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/29岁的ded-i-water-water-chirractor-pockusted-crack-here-neck-questions-questions-lack-medical-473044 <description><![CDATA[A recent coroner's report on the patient's death is raising concerns over whether chiropractors should be required to review patients' medical histories before treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/29岁的ded-i-water-water-chirractor-pockusted-crack-here-neck-questions-questions-lack-medical-473044</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:59:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Curex Is Making Food Allergy Care Easier Than Ever, Backed by Science]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/curex-making-food--allergy-care-care-sier-eer-ever-basked-Science-473043 <description><![CDATA[Fewer severe reactions and the ability to enjoy meals without fear are two key benefits of using SLIT drops for food allergies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/curex-making-food--allergy-care-care-sier-eer-ever-basked-Science-473043</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 12:29:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Ergin's Holistic Diabetes Care: How SugarMD Is Empowering Women To Take Control]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/dr-ergins-holistic-daibetes-care-how-now-sugarmd-empowering-women-taktake-contake-control-473041 <description><![CDATA[SugarMD offers a lifeline of hope for women seeking a holistic approach. This transformative care is now reaching women worldwide, including those in Australia, where access to innovative diabetes solutions is increasingly vital.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/dr-ergins-holistic-daibetes-care-how-now-sugarmd-empowering-women-taktake-contake-control-473041</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 12:24:51 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>