<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[BMI, Waist Size Aren't Only Risk Factors Of Heart Disease, This Hidden Fat May Matter More]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bmi-waist-size-arent-only-risk-factors-heart-disease-this-hidden-fat-may-matter-more-473007 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that "intermuscular fat", not BMI or waist measurement, may be a more accurate predictor of heart disease risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bmi-waist-size-arent-only-risk-factors-heart-disease-this-hidden-fat-may-matter-more-473007</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 Jan 2025 04:40:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Kids Not Sleeping Well? Not Just Caffeine And Chocolate; Doc Shares Sneaky Culprits That Steal Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kids-not-sleeping-well-not-just-caffeine-chocolate-doc-shares-sneaky-culprits-that-steal-sleep-473004 <description><![CDATA[For parents with light sleepers at home, a sleep doctor suggests paying close attention to what they eat, especially before bedtime.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kids-not-sleeping-well-not-just-caffeine-chocolate-doc-shares-sneaky-culprits-that-steal-sleep-473004</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:25:13 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiac Surgeon's Tips: Detect Heart Blockages At Home Without Tests, Stay Safe If Home Alone During Attack]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-surgeons-tips-detect-heart-blockages-home-without-tests-stay-safe-if-home-alone-during-473002 <description><![CDATA[What if you could spot the body's red flags of a heart attack and act in time? It could save lives.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-surgeons-tips-detect-heart-blockages-home-without-tests-stay-safe-if-home-alone-during-473002</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 Jan 2025 01:22:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Fitness Tracker, Smartwatch Bands May Contain 'Very High Concentrations' Of Harmful Forever Chemicals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-fitness-tracker-smartwatch-bands-may-contain-very-high-concentrations-harmful-forever-473001 <description><![CDATA[The very gadget you trust to track your health may be hiding a silent threat that could slowly seep through your skin and affect your well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-fitness-tracker-smartwatch-bands-may-contain-very-high-concentrations-harmful-forever-473001</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 Jan 2025 05:22:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Most Headaches Are Harmless', But Neuro Warns Not To Ignore These 3 Signs]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/most-headaches-are-harmless-neuro-warns-not-ignore-these-3-signs-473000 <description><![CDATA[While most headaches are harmless, a neurologist warns that certain symptoms could indicate something more serious, like a brain aneurysm.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/most-headaches-are-harmless-neuro-warns-not-ignore-these-3-signs-473000</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 Jan 2025 03:47:54 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Not Worth Your Life': 21-Year-Old Warns After Throwing Up Blood, Falling In Coma From Continuous Vaping]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-worth-your-life-21-year-old-warns-after-throwing-blood-falling-coma-continuous-vaping-472997 <description><![CDATA[The young man, who now lives with one functioning lung after surviving two weeks in a coma and bilateral pneumonia, is now raising awareness about the dangers of vaping.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-worth-your-life-21-year-old-warns-after-throwing-blood-falling-coma-continuous-vaping-472997</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 Jan 2025 01:15:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide to 17 Energy-Boosting Supplements You Need in 2025]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/ultimate-guide-17-energy-boosting-supplements-you-need-2025-472996 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top 17 natural energy boosters for 2025! Perfect for athletes, professionals, and anyone seeking all-day vitality. Unlock your full potential today!]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/ultimate-guide-17-energy-boosting-supplements-you-need-2025-472996</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:51:32 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth Is Price Gouging Cancer Patients by Overcharging 'Thousands of Percent' for Live-Saving Meds, Pocketing Extra Billions: Feds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unitedhealth-price-gouging-cancer-患者-overcharging-thousands-percent-live- saving-meds-472993 <description><![CDATA[The UnitedHealth Group is overcharging patients for necessary life-saving drugs as a result of price gouging that increases the cost of such medication exponentially.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unitedhealth-price-gouging-cancer-患者-overcharging-thousands-percent-live- saving-meds-472993</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:41:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Bans Red Dye No. 3 Citing Cancer Risk: From Candies To Drinks, Here Are Foods That Contain It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-bans-red-dye-no-3-citing-cancer-risk-candies-drinks-here-are-foods-that-c​​ontain-it-472990 <description><![CDATA[The FDA's decision to ban the use of Red Dye No. 3 in foods, beverages, oral drugs, and dietary supplements comes nearly 35 years after it prohibited the use of the same in cosmetics due to cancer risks found in animal studies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-bans-red-dye-no-3-citing-cancer-risk-candies-drinks-here-are-foods-that-c​​ontain-it-472990</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 Jan 2025 03:27:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[That Extra Sausage May Harm Your Brain: Here's How Red And Processed Meats Affect Cognitive Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/that-extra-sausage-may-harm-your-brain-heres-how-red-processed-meats-affect-cognitive-health-472987 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now urge cutting back on red meat, particularly processed ones, to reduce the risk of memory issues and dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/that-extra-sausage-may-harm-your-brain-heres-how-red-processed-meats-affect-cognitive-health-472987</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 Jan 2025 01:32:13 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hospital Mixes Up Patients, Pulls Plug On Wrong Man After Getting Permission from Different Family]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospital-mixes-病人-pulls-plug-wrong-man-after-getting-permission- Different-family-472986 <description><![CDATA[A Washington state hospital faces lawsuits after mistakenly taking the wrong patient off life support when a different family authorized the removal for someone else.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospital-mixes-病人-pulls-plug-wrong-man-after-getting-permission- Different-family-472986</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:21:50 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>