<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Top 5 Baby Milk Formulas: Nutrient-Rich Options to Support Your Little One's Growth and Development]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-baby-milk-formulas- Nutrition-rich-options-support-your-little-ones-growth-development-471612 <description><![CDATA[When it comes to your baby's nutrition, it is best to consider only the best when it comes to formula milk]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-baby-milk-formulas- Nutrition-rich-options-support-your-little-ones-growth-development-471612</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:28:52 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Cold Plunge Tub 2024: Top 5 Picks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cold-plunge-tub-2024-top-5-picks-471610 <description><![CDATA[Here are our top picks for cold plunge tubs that are decently priced and worth the money.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cold-plunge-tub-2024-top-5-picks-471610</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:40:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Shake Up Your Nutrition: The Top 7 Meal Replacement Shakes for Busy Lifestyles]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/shake-your-nutrition-top-7-meal-replacement-shakes-busy-lifestyles-471609 <description><![CDATA[Meal replacement shakes are designed to replace either your breakfast, lunch, or dinner, which are perfect for people on the go or on their wellness journey.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/shake-your-nutrition-top-7-meal-replacement-shakes-busy-lifestyles-471609</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:40:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top Mouthwash Brands for a Fresh and Healthy Smile: Your Ultimate Guide to Oral Care]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-mouthwash-brands-fresh-healthy-smile-your-ultimate-guide-oral-care-471608 <description><![CDATA[Choosing the right mouthwash plays a pivotal role in oral care routine, and the options explored in this guide offer diverse benefits tailored to individual preferences.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-mouthwash-brands-fresh-healthy-smile-your-ultimate-guide-oral-care-471608</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:39:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Hyaluronic Acid Serums For 2024: Unlock Radiant Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hyaluronic-acid-serums-unlock-radiant-skin-471596 <description><![CDATA[Drops of the best hyaluronic acids will be enough to give you that glowing skin that will give you that confidence every single time.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hyaluronic-acid-serums-unlock-radiant-skin-471596</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 08:08:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Botulism-Like Illness In Illinois: Officials Suspect Links To Fake Botox Injections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/botulism-like-illness-illinois-officials-suspect-links-fake-botox-injections-471606 <description><![CDATA[The illnesses were reported in two people who received fake Botox or a similar, possibly counterfeit products in LaSalle County, health officials said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/botulism-like-illness-illinois-officials-suspect-links-fake-botox-injections-471606</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 04:39:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Accelerated Aging Raises Cancer Risk In Young Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/accelerated-aging-raises-cancer-risk-young-adults-study-471604 <description><![CDATA[The researchers suggest that their discoveries open the door for future interventions to slow biological aging that could be a new avenue for cancer prevention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/accelerated-aging-raises-cancer-risk-young-adults-study-471604</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 03:03:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Know Dangerous Pitfalls Of Diet Culture; Expert Explains Benefits Of Intuitive Eating]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-dangerous-pitfalls-diet-culture-expert-explains-benefits-intuitive-eating-471603 <description><![CDATA[Eating healthy and maintaining a balanced lifestyle is essential for overall well-being. But, in our pursuit of wellness, do we inadvertently fall into the trap of diet culture?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-dangerous-pitfalls-diet-culture-expert-explains-benefits-intuitive-eating-471603</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 02:32:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Protein Powders For Weight Loss In 2024: Shedding Pounds The Healthy Way]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-powders-weight-loss-shedding-pounds-healthy-way-471595 <description><![CDATA[If you are trying to lose weight, but would like make sure your body derives the optimum nutrition, then taking protein powder for weight loss is the way to go.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-powders-weight-loss-shedding-pounds-healthy-way-471595</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Apr 2024 11:24:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Got 15 Minutes? Study Suggests That's All You Need To Exercise For Immunity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-15-minutes-study-suggests-thats-all-you-need-exercise-immunity-471599 <description><![CDATA[The results of the recent study offer hope to those seeking immunity benefits from exercise but do not have long hours to spend.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-15-minutes-study-suggests-thats-all-you-need-exercise-immunity-471599</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:01:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Viewing Solar Eclipse: Here's How To Protect Eyes From Permanent Damage]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viewing-solar-eclipse-heres-how-protect-eyes-permanent-damage-471597 <description><![CDATA[A brief direct glance at the sun during an eclipse for as short as 100 seconds, can trigger permanent eye damage. Here's how to view solar eclipse safely.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viewing-solar-eclipse-heres-how-protect-eyes-permanent-damage-471597</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:36:05 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>