<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Certain Types Of Cancers Are Rising Among Young Adults In US, Researchers Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/certain-types-cancers-are-rising-among-young-adults-us-researchers-say-470670 <description><![CDATA[There has been a considerable spike in certain types of cancers among young adults, especially women, in the U.S., according to a new study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/certain-types-cancers-are-rising-among-young-adults-us-researchers-say-470670</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Aug 2023 04:06:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Don't Stifle Your Sneeze, Let It Go: Here's Why Holding In Can Be Dangerous]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-stifle-your-sneeze-let-it-go-heres-why-holding-can-dangerous-470667 <description><![CDATA[Although it is instinctive to stifle the sneeze for controlling the spread of germs, holding it in can cause more harm.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-stifle-your-sneeze-let-it-go-heres-why-holding-can-dangerous-470667</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Aug 2023 03:01:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiorespiratory Fitness In Men Reduces Risk Of 9 Types Of Cancers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiorespiratory-fitness-men-reduces-risk-9-types-cancers-study-470666 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that good cardiorespiratory health in men can reduce the risk of developing nine types of cancers, including lung, liver and rectal cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiorespiratory-fitness-men-reduces-risk-9-types-cancers-study-470666</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:27:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Little Bit Of Snapback Goes A Long Way: If We Love Our Bodies, They Will Love Us Back]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/little-bit-snapback-goes-long-way-if-we-love-our-bodies-they-will-love-us-back-470664 <description><![CDATA[Unlike caffeine and energy drinks, Snapback has no negative aftereffects. It complements the liver with antioxidants, amino acids and toxin-fighting natural remedies to break down the effects of alcohol consumption and mitigates migraines and nausea.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/little-bit-snapback-goes-long-way-if-we-love-our-bodies-they-will-love-us-back-470664</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:42:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Organ Earlier Thought To Be Nonfunctional In Adults Actually Prevents Cancer, Autoimmune Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/organ-earlier-thought-nonfunction-adults-actually-prevents-cancer-autoimmune-disease-study-470662 <description><![CDATA[A new study has revealed the unexpected importance of an often-forgotten gland tucked between the breast bone – the thymus gland.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/organ-earlier-thought-nonfunction-adults-actually-prevents-cancer-autoimmune-disease-study-470662</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Aug 2023 01:48:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Handful Of Nuts Could Cut Depression Risk; Know Other Health Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/handful-nuts-could-cut-depression-risk-know-other-health-benefits-470661 <description><![CDATA[A study has found that snacking on a handful of nuts can cut down the risk of depression by 17%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/handful-nuts-could-cut-depression-risk-know-other-health-benefits-470661</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Aug 2023 01:19:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tackle Football Linked To Higher Risk Of Parkinson's Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tackle-football-linked-higher-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-470658 <description><![CDATA[Football players with extended careers and higher competition levels face elevated Parkinson's disease risk, especially in college/professional contexts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tackle-football-linked-higher-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-470658</guid><pubDate> Tue, 15 Aug 2023 06:16:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Harmful 'Forever Chemicals' Detected In Menstrual Products, Raising Health And Environmental Concerns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/harmful-forever-chemicals-Detected-menstrual-products-raise-health-environmental-concerns-470656 <description><![CDATA[A study has highlighted uncertainty about PFAS entering the skin from various period products.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/harmful-forever-chemicals-Detected-menstrual-products-raise-health-environmental-concerns-470656</guid><pubDate> Tue, 15 Aug 2023 05:08:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[From Increased Appetite To Reduced Inflammation, Study Reveals Health Benefits Of Cardamom]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/increased-appetite-reduced-inflammation-study-reveals-health-benefits-cardamom-470654 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that consuming at least eight to 10 cardamom pods every day can bring in the desired health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/increased-appetite-reduced-inflammation-study-reveals-health-benefits-cardamom-470654</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:09:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Blood Sugar Levels Even Without Diabetes Can Raise Risk Of Heart Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-blood-sugar-levels-even-without-diabetes-can-raise-risk-heart-disease-study-470653 <description><![CDATA[Elevated blood sugar levels in prediabetes patients increase the risk of heart diseases such as heart failure by 30% to 47%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-blood-sugar-levels-even-without-diabetes-can-raise-risk-heart-disease-study-470653</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Aug 2023 02:55:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are Girl Dinners Safe? Here's What Experts Have To Say About The Latest Food Trend]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-girl-dinners-safe-heres-what-experts-have-say-about-latest-food-trend-470652 <description><![CDATA[Health experts believe girl dinners, the latest food trend on TikTok, can be healthy if approached with "balance in mind."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-girl-dinners-safe-heres-what-experts-have-say-about-latest-food-trend-470652</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Aug 2023 02:04:36 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>