<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[19 Botched Botox Cases Reported Across 9 States: CDC, FDA Investigate]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/19-botched-botox-cases-reported-across-9-states-cdc-fda-investigate-471648 <description><![CDATA[Officials said that all the incidents involved women who reported sick following the administration of counterfeit Botox injections of AbbVie or those who received injections from unlicensed or untrained individuals in non-healthcare environments.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/19-botched-botox-cases-reported-across-9-states-cdc-fda-investigate-471648</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Apr 2024 05:08:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stress During Adolescence May Up The Risk Of Postpartum Depression In Adulthood: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-during-adolescent-may-risk-postpartum-depression-adulthood-study-471644 <description><![CDATA[Based on the findings of a rat study, researchers suggest that early life stress could contribute to the worsening of postpartum depression from a pathophysiological standpoint.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-during-adolescent-may-risk-postpartum-depression-adulthood-study-471644</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Apr 2024 03:48:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Junk Food Diet In Teens May Lead To Long-Term Memory Damage: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/junk-food-diet-teens-may-lead-long-term-memory-damage-study-471640 <description><![CDATA[A high-fat, high-sugar diet in teenagers may lead to long-term memory damage, according to the results of a rat study conducted by researchers from the University of Southern California.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/junk-food-diet-teens-may-lead-long-term-memory-damage-study-471640</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Apr 2024 01:58:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exercise Lowers Heart Disease Risk By Reducing Stress; Depression Patients At Greater Benefits: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-lowers-heart-disease-risk-reducing-stress-depression-fighters-greater-benefits-study-471639 <description><![CDATA[People with stress-related conditions such as depression reap the most cardiovascular benefits from physical activity, according to the latest study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-lowers-heart-disease-risk-reducing-stress-depression-fighters-greater-benefits-study-471639</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Apr 2024 03:33:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong Reports First Human B Virus Case: Know All About Deadly Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hong-kong-reports-first- human-b-virus-case-know-all-about-deadly-infection-471637 <description><![CDATA[The monkey B virus is an extremely rare infection that could lead to severe brain damage or death in humans.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hong-kong-reports-first- human-b-virus-case-know-all-about-deadly-infection-471637</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Apr 2024 02:29:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pressure To Lose Weight In Teens Linked To 'Internalized' Weight Stigma Later: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-Pressure-teens-tied-internalized-weight-stigma-later-study-471635 <description><![CDATA[People who were bullied, teased, and pressured to lose weight during their teenage years by family and media may develop internalized weight stigma by the age of 31, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-Pressure-teens-tied-internalized-weight-stigma-later-study-471635</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:48:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Peter Rentrop Shares Medical Technology That Is Revolutionizing The Future Of Heart Health In Cardiology]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/dr-peter-rentrop-shares-medical-technology-that-revolutionizing-future-heart-health-cardiology-471633 <description><![CDATA[The world of cardiology is witnessing a remarkable transformation driven by cutting-edge medical technologies, says Dr. Peter Rentrop.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/dr-peter-rentrop-shares-medical-technology-that-revolutionizing-future-heart-health-cardiology-471633</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 19:10:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nathan Guerette: A Pioneer in Pelvic Reconstructive Surgery and Academic Excellence]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/nathan-guerette-pioneer-pelvic-reconstructive-surgery-academic-excellence-471631 <description><![CDATA[From individualized care to ongoing efforts to integrate innovative techniques, those seeking the best care can expect unparalleled care from Nathan Guerette, MD.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/nathan-guerette-pioneer-pelvic-reconstructive-surgery-academic-excellence-471631</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 19:04:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Empowering Moms: Navigating the Choices in Wearable Breast Pump - Efficiently]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/empowering-moms-navigating-choices-wearable-breast-pump-efficiently-471619 <description><![CDATA[Breastfeeding mothers now have a reliable ally in technology with wearable breast pumps]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/empowering-moms-navigating-choices-wearable-breast-pump-efficiently-471619</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 15:05:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Seafood Diet Raises Exposure To 'Forever Chemicals': Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-seafood-diet-raises-exposure-forever-chemicals-study-471629 <description><![CDATA[The results showed that shrimp and lobster had the highest concentrations of certain PFAS compounds, with averages ranging as high as 1.74 and 3.30 nanograms per gram of flesh, respectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-seafood-diet-raises-exposure-forever-chemicals-study-471629</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 03:50:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Single Low-Dose Esketamine Injection May Reduce Postpartum Depression In New Mothers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/single-low-dose-esketamine-injection-may-reduce-postpartum-depression-new-mothers-study-471627 <description><![CDATA[The study found that a single low-dose injection of esketamine given just after childbirth could reduce the risk of postpartum depression in new mothers who experienced prenatal depression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/single-low-dose-esketamine-injection-may-reduce-postpartum-depression-new-mothers-study-471627</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:15:03 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>