<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Gastroenterologist's Fruit Washing Tip: One Simple Inexpensive Ingredient You Already Have In Your Kitchen]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gastroenterologies-fruit-washing-tip-one-simple-inexpective-ingredient-you-already-have-your-472940 <description><![CDATA[For those seeking the right technique to wash fruits, you don't need expensive fruit-washing liquids. All you need is one simple, inexpensive ingredient already in your kitchen.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gastroenterologies-fruit-washing-tip-one-simple-inexpective-ingredient-you-already-have-your-472940</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 03:01:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Coffee For Heart Health: Timing Matters More Than Quantity-Here's Best Time To Drink]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/coffee-heart-health-timing-matters-more-quantity-heres-best-time-drink-472937 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that people who drink coffee in the morning have a lower risk of death from cardiovascular disease and overall mortality risk compared to all-day coffee drinkers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/coffee-heart-health-timing-matters-more-quantity-heres-best-time-drink-472937</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 01:07:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[VRenity: The Next Step In The Field Of Mental Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vrenity-next-step-field-mental-health-472936 <description><![CDATA[VRenity's ultimate goal with its software is to harness cutting-edge virtual reality technology to boost mental wellness in the workplace, and to build upon the mind and body pillars of their model's design.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vrenity-next-step-field-mental-health-472936</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 12:57:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Erectile Dysfunction Treatment Provider Donates $1 Million to Trump Inauguration]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/erectile-dysfunction-treatment-provider-donates-1-million-trump-inauguration-472935 <description><![CDATA[Hims &amp; Hers is the latest US corporation to donate $1 million to President-elect Donald Trump's ever-growing inauguration fund.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/erectile-dysfunction-treatment-provider-donates-1-million-trump-inauguration-472935</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 12:31:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fluoride In Drinking Water Linked To Lower IQ Scores In Children: Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluide-drinking-water-linked-lower-iq-scores-children-study-reveals-472933 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that even a slight increase in fluoride levels was associated with a 1.63-point decrease in IQ in children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluide-drinking-water-linked-lower-iq-scores-children-study-reveals-472933</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 05:37:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Plant-Based Milk Alternatives Linked To Increased Risk Of Depression: Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/plant-based-milk-alternatives-linked-increased-risk-depression-study-reveals-472932 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that drinking plant-based milk alternatives, such as soy, oat, and almond milk, is linked to an increased risk of depression, while semi-skimmed cow's milk may offer protective benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/plant-based-milk-alternatives-linked-increased-risk-depression-study-reveals-472932</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 04:12:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teen's Breast Grew To Triple G-Cup Size After COVID Vaccinations: Researchers Call It 'Exceedingly Rare']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-breast-grew-triple-g-cup-size-after-covid-vaccinations-researchers-call-it-exceedingly-472931 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have identified the condition as Pseudoangiomatous stromal hyperplasia (PASH)-associated gigantomastia, an "exceedingly rare" condition linked to COVID-19 vaccination.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-breast-grew-triple-g-cup-size-after-covid-vaccinations-researchers-call-it-exceedingly-472931</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:43:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bird Flu Claims First US Victim As Louisiana Man Dies in Hospital]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-claims-first-us-victim-louisiana-man-dies-hospital-472929 <description><![CDATA[A patient that had been hospitalized with avian influenza, otherwise known as bird flu, has died following a stay in the hospital.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-claims-first-us-victim-louisiana-man-dies-hospital-472929</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:45:48 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Governor Blocks Bill Allowing Doctors to Disagree with the Medical Opinions of State Officials]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-governor-blocks-bill-allowing-doctors-disagree-medical-opinions-state-officials-472928 <description><![CDATA[Gov. Mike DeWine blocked a bill seeking to protect medical professionals from disciplinary action for stating opinions that contradict state health officials.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-governor-blocks-bill-allowing-doctors-disagree-medical-opinions-state-officials-472928</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:39:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Revolutionizing Men's Health: A Deep Dive Into Justin Pulliam's Innovative Approach To Sexual Wellness And Hormone Therapy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/revolutionizing-mens-health-deep-dive-justin-pulliams-innovative-approach- Sex-wellness-472926 <description><![CDATA[Nearly 40 percent of men over the age of 40 experience some degree of erectile dysfunction, according to the Cleveland Clinic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/revolutionizing-mens-health-deep-dive-justin-pulliams-innovative-approach- Sex-wellness-472926</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:39:32 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[It Is Now Illegal to Use AI to Deny a Medically Necessary Health Insurance Claim in California]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/it-now-illegal-use-ai-deny-medically-necessary-health-insurance-claim-california-472923 <description><![CDATA[It is now illegal to use artificial intelligence to deny any medically necessary health insurance claims in California now that a new bill has gone into effect.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/it-now-illegal-use-ai-deny-medically-necessary-health-insurance-claim-california-472923</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:06:23 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>