<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Mediterranean Diet Lowers Anxiety And Stress In Elderly Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mediterranean-diet-lowers-anxiety-stress-elderly-adults-study-471752 <description><![CDATA[The study found that in addition to promoting physical health, the Mediterranean diet could also play a significant role in improving mental wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mediterranean-diet-lowers-anxiety-stress-elderly-adults-study-471752</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 May 2024 03:42:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Men At Higher Risk Of Diabetic Complications Than Women: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/men-higher-risk-diabetic-complications-women-study-471751 <description><![CDATA[Men are at higher risk of developing complications from diabetes than women, regardless of the duration for which they have had type 1 or type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/men-higher-risk-diabetic-complications-women-study-471751</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 May 2024 01:54:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Planning To Lose Weight? Here's A Technique Recommended For Men]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-lose-weight-heres-technique-recommished-men-471749 <description><![CDATA[A simple intervention technique that involves receiving text messages with cash incentives could improve men's chances of losing weight by around four times, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-lose-weight-heres-technique-recommished-men-471749</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 May 2024 08:03:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Infertility Treatment Doubles Risk Of Heart Disease Within Year After Delivery: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/infertility-treatment-doubles-risk-heart-disease-within-year-after-delivery-study-471748 <description><![CDATA[The increased risk was most pronounced in the month following the delivery, particularly in those patients who experienced dangerously high blood pressure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/infertility-treatment-doubles-risk-heart-disease-within-year-after-delivery-study-471748</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 May 2024 02:14:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure Drugs More Than Double Risk Of Bone Fractures In Elderly: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-Pressure-drugs-more-double-risk-bone-fractures-elderly-study-471747 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that patients with dementia, those with systolic blood pressure above 139, people with diastolic blood pressure above 79, or those with no recent use of blood pressure medication have at least triple the fracture risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-Pressure-drugs-more-double-risk-bone-fractures-elderly-study-471747</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 May 2024 01:32:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Severe Obesity In Childhood Halves Life Expectancy, Weight Loss Brings Back Decades: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/severe-obesity-childhood-halfs-life-expectancy-weight-loss-brings-back-decades-study-471745 <description><![CDATA[A child with severe obesity at age 4 has only a life expectancy of 39 if the individual does not lose weight. However, losing weight could add decades back to their lives, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/severe-obesity-childhood-halfs-life-expectancy-weight-loss-brings-back-decades-study-471745</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 May 2024 03:50:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[C-Section Doubles Risk Of Measles Vaccine Failure; Study Recommends Taking 2 Doses]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/c-section-doubles-risk-measles-vaccine-failure-study-recommends-take-2-doses-471743 <description><![CDATA[To have robust protection against measles, children born with C-sections should receive two doses of the vaccination, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/c-section-doubles-risk-measles-vaccine-failure-study-recommends-take-2-doses-471743</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 May 2024 03:09:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Skin Cancer Awareness Month: Expert Dispels Misconceptions About Sunscreen Use]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skin-cancer-awareness-month-expert-dispels-misconceptions-about-sunscreen-use-471741 <description><![CDATA[During this Skin Cancer Awareness Month, an expert dermatologist shares with us facts about sunscreen that will encourage more people to start using it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skin-cancer-awareness-month-expert-dispels-misconceptions-about-sunscreen-use-471741</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 May 2024 02:05:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Source Of Sugar Matters More Than Amount For Childhood Obesity: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/source-sugar-matters-more-amount-childhood-obesity-study-471739 <description><![CDATA[Children who get more sugar from sweet snacks, confectioneries, sweetened milk, and yogurt drinks, have a higher risk of gaining weight, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/source-sugar-matters-more-amount-childhood-obesity-study-471739</guid><pubDate> Tue, 14 May 2024 04:05:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Potency Cannabis Use In Teens Doubles Risk Of Psychotic Episodes: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-potency-cannabis-use-teens-doubles-risk-psychotic-episodes-study-471738 <description><![CDATA[The use of high-potency cannabis in teen years almost doubles the risk of developing psychotic episodes in early adulthood compared to the use of those with lower potency, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-potency-cannabis-use-teens-doubles-risk-psychotic-episodes-study-471738</guid><pubDate> Tue, 14 May 2024 03:03:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Low Testosterone In Men Affects Heart Health, Raises Risk Of Death: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-testosterone-men-affects-heart-health-raises-risk-death-study-471736 <description><![CDATA[Men who have testosterone levels below the normal range are at a 40 percent higher risk of death from all causes, and those with extremely low T are at a 60% higher risk of death from heart disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-testosterone-men-affects-heart-health-raises-risk-death-study-471736</guid><pubDate> Tue, 14 May 2024 01:49:02 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>