<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>A </language><item><title><![CDATA[Women Who Get False-Positive Mammograms More Likely To Develop Breast Cancer Later: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-who-get-false-positive-mammograms-more-likely-develop-breast-cancer-later-study-471071 <description><![CDATA[The link between false-positive mammograms and future breast cancer risk is highest among women between 60 and 75 years old and those with low breast density.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-who-get-false-positive-mammograms-more-likely-develop-breast-cancer-later-study-471071</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:14:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Seasonal Affective Disorder: 6 Food Items To Beat Winter Blues]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/seasonal-affective-disorder-6-food-items-beat-winter-blues-471070 <description><![CDATA[SAD is a form of depressive disorder triggered by seasonal changes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/seasonal-affective-disorder-6-food-items-beat-winter-blues-471070</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:33:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Positive Attitude Toward Exercise May Help Ease Aging Anxiety: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/positive-attitude-toward-exercise-may-help-ease-aging-anxiety-study-471067 <description><![CDATA[Age-related anxiety may stem from various factors such as worries over physical changes, discomfort of being around older people and fear of losing independence.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/positive-attitude-toward-exercise-may-help-ease-aging-anxiety-study-471067</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Nov 2023 01:43:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Expands Recall Of Fruit Purees Linked To Lead Poisoning: Here Are The Products]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-expands-recall-fruit-purees-linked-lead-poisoning-here-are-products-471064 <description><![CDATA[Parents and caregivers are cautioned not to buy or serve brands of fruit puree pouches associated with lead contamination as it can lead to "acute toxicity" in children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-expands-recall-fruit-purees-linked-lead-poisoning-here-are-products-471064</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:51:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cut Down On Salt: Study Says High Consumption Increases Risk Of Diabetes]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-down-salt-study-says-high-conspiration-increases-risk-diabetes-471061 <description><![CDATA[The frequent use of added salt increases the risk of developing type 2 diabetes, the study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-down-salt-study-says-high-conspiration-increases-risk-diabetes-471061</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 Nov 2023 04:15:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Several Tuberculosis Cases Linked To California Casino; Officials Urge Visitors To Get Tested]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/several-tuberculosis-cases-linked-california-casino-officials-urge-visitors-get-tested-471060 <description><![CDATA[At least 10 cases of TB have been linked to the casino located in Pacheco, in Contra Costa County. However, the casino has not been identified as a current or ongoing source of transmission.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/several-tuberculosis-cases-linked-california-casino-officials-urge-visitors-get-tested-471060</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 Nov 2023 02:47:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Proposes Ban On Food Additive Found In Soft Drinks, Says It's No Longer Safe To Use]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-proposes-ban-food-additive-found-soft-drinks-says-its-no-longer-safe-use-471058 <description><![CDATA[The proposed ban on brominated vegetable oil was based on several studies that indicated its toxic effects on the thyroid gland.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-proposes-ban-food-additive-found-soft-drinks-says-its-no-longer-safe-use-471058</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 Nov 2023 01:19:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Male Fertility: Study Says Excessive Mobile Use May Affect Semen Quality]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/male-fertility-study-says-excessive-mobile-use-may-affect-semen-quality-471057 <description><![CDATA[Men who use their phones more than 20 times a day are at 21% higher risk of having a low sperm count and a 30% higher risk for a low sperm concentration, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/male-fertility-study-says-excessive-mobile-use-may-affect-semen-quality-471057</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:55:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[American Cancer Society Broadens Age Range For Lung Cancer Screening; Here's When To Get Tested]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/american-cancer-society-broadens-age-range-lung-cancer-screening-heres-when-get-tested-471056 <description><![CDATA[The updated guidelines not only include a wider age group but also suggest smokers who quit the habit undergo screening based on their level of smoking.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/american-cancer-society-broadens-age-range-lung-cancer-screening-heres-when-get-tested-471056</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:49:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Healthy Skin Month: Expert Shares Skincare Tips To Prevent Damage]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-healthy-skin-month-expert-shares-skincare-tips-prevent-damage-471053 <description><![CDATA[November is marked as National Healthy Skin Month to raise awareness about the importance of adopting a healthy skincare regimen for better skin, hair and nails.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-healthy-skin-month-expert-shares-skincare-tips-prevent-damage-471053</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 Nov 2023 01:29:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Lack Of Deep Sleep May Raise Risk Of Dementia In Elderly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lack-deep-sleep-may-raise-risk-dementia-elderly-471049 <description><![CDATA[For people over the age of 60, getting 1% less deep sleep a year could increase the risk of dementia by 27%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lack-deep-sleep-may-raise-risk-dementia-elderly-471049</guid><pubDate> Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:45:58 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>