<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Cut Your Salt Intake: Study Says It Can Worsen Eczema]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-your-salt-intake-study-says-it-can-worsen-eczema-471830 <description><![CDATA[Taking just one extra gram of sodium per day can increase the likelihood of eczema flares by 22%.  ]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-your-salt-intake-study-says-it-can-worsen-eczema-471830</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:54:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man In Mexico Dies From Bird Flu; First Human Case Of H5N2 Virus: WHO]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-mexico-dies-bird-flu-first- human-case-h5n2-virus-who-471829 <description><![CDATA[Although the strain H5N2 had earlier been detected in poultry in Mexico, the source from which the patient contracted the fatal infection is not known, as he did not have any contact with poultry.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-mexico-dies-bird-flu-first- human-case-h5n2-virus-who-471829</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:18:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Highly Contagious Sexually Transmitted Fungal Infection Makes US Debut: First Case In NYC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/highly-contagious- Sexly-transmissed-fungal-infection-makes-us-debut-first-case-nyc-471827 <description><![CDATA[Health experts caution that the infection caused by a sexually transmitted form of ringworm can take months to resolve, even with treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/highly-contagious- Sexly-transmissed-fungal-infection-makes-us-debut-first-case-nyc-471827</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jun 2024 01:10:32 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Susan Heitler: Life and Work]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/susan-heitler-life-work-471825 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Susan Heitler, renowned for her notable contributions to psychotherapy, specializes in treating couples and conducts workshops across the US and abroad, imparting her expertise in couples' therapy to therapy practitioners.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/susan-heitler-life-work-471825</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:57:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Controversy Around ABA Therapy Finally Addressed]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/controversy-around-aba-therapy-finally-addressed-471823 <description><![CDATA[Rethinking autism therapy, a new approach focuses on compassionate, play-based methods that address the emotional and behavioral needs of children with autism, fostering a supportive and inclusive community for families.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/controversy-around-aba-therapy-finally-addressed-471823</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:53:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Embrace Generosity As A Form Of Self-Care During Mental Health Awareness Month]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/embrace-generosity-form-self-care-during-mental-health-awareness-month-471822 <description><![CDATA[Generosity experts Dr. Nicole Roberts and Monte Wood, share more on how the simple act of giving can be a catalyst for better mental health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/embrace-generosity-form-self-care-during-mental-health-awareness-month-471822</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:51:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[More Than Half Of Americans Will Develop Cardiovascular Disease In 30 Years: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-half-americans-will-develop-cardioangio-disease-30-years-report-471821 <description><![CDATA[Around 61% of U.S. adults are expected to have some type of cardiovascular disease within the next 30 years, according to a recent report from the American Heart Association.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-half-americans-will-develop-cardioangio-disease-30-years-report-471821</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jun 2024 03:45:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Internet Addiction In Adolescence Alters Brains: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/internet-addiction-adolescent-alters-brains-study-471819 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that internet addiction in young people could alter their brains, and disrupt the signaling in critical neural networks impacting decision-making, attention, memory, coordination, and mental health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/internet-addiction-adolescent-alters-brains-study-471819</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jun 2024 01:52:09 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Better Sleep May Help People Overcome Feelings Of Loneliness: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/better-sleep-may-help-people-overcome-feelings-loneiness-study-471817 <description><![CDATA[In the study, better sleep health was associated with lower total and emotional loneliness across ages, particularly for younger adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/better-sleep-may-help-people-overcome-feelings-loneiness-study-471817</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:39:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[In-Flight Drinking Linked To Heart Risks Even In Young, Healthy Individuals: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flight-drinking-linked-heart-risks-even-young-healthy-individuals-study-471816 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that the combination of alcohol intake with sleeping under hypobaric conditions poses a considerable strain on the cardiac system even for healthy individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flight-drinking-linked-heart-risks-even-young-healthy-individuals-study-471816</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:19:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Auto-Brewery Syndrome: Rare Condition Causes Intoxication In 50-Year-Old Without Drinking Alcohol]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/auto-brewery-syndrome-rare-condition-causes-intoxation-50-year-old-without-drinking-alcohol-471815 <description><![CDATA[Auto-brewery syndrome is a rare condition where the gut microorganism creates alcohol through fermentation, causing intoxication without drinking.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/auto-brewery-syndrome-rare-condition-causes-intoxation-50-year-old-without-drinking-alcohol-471815</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jun 2024 02:35:09 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>