<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Louisiana Health Department Orders Employees to Stop Promoting Mass Vaccinations As it Accuses CDC of Being 'Woefully Out of Touch']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/louisiana-health-deportment-orders-orporters-employes-stop-promoting-mass-vaccinations-caccuses-caccuses-cdc-473119 <description><![CDATA[Louisiana's Health Department has ordered employees to stop promoting mass vaccinations, which experts say could lead to declining immunization rates.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/louisiana-health-deportment-orders-orporters-employes-stop-promoting-mass-vaccinations-caccuses-caccuses-cdc-473119</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:30:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiac Doctor Realizes He's Having a Heart Attack After Comparing Symptoms to Patient He Had Just Helped]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-doctor-realizes-hes-having-having-having-having heart-attack-ferter-tefter-and-ofterting症状 -  he-just-just-just-just-473118 <description><![CDATA[A cardiac doctor unknowingly suffered a heart attack while treating a patient with identical symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-doctor-realizes-hes-having-having-having-having-ward-sattack-efer-抑制症状患者had-just-just-just-just-just-just-just-473118</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:08:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Real Housewives' Star Teddi Mellencamp Hospitalized After Severe Headaches Lead To Multiple Tumor Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/real-housewives-star-teddi-mellencamp-hospitalized-ifter-sever-sever-sever-headaches-headaches-multiph-multiph-multiple-tumer-473115 <description><![CDATA[Mellencamp was experiencing "severe and debilitating headaches" for the last several weeks before getting hospitalized.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/real-housewives-star-teddi-mellencamp-hospitalized-ifter-sever-sever-sever-headaches-headaches-multiph-multiph-multiple-tumer-473115</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 04:08:47 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are Hormonal Birth Control Methods Safe? Contraceptives That May Increase Risk Of Heart Attack And Stroke]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-hormonal-birth-control-mhods-mhods-safe-contraceptives-that-may-insrease-insrease-riske-heart-heart-attack-stroke-stroke-stroke-stroke-473112 <description><![CDATA[For those considering different contraceptive methods, the results of a recent study may help them make informed choices.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-hormonal-birth-control-mhods-mhods-safe-contraceptives-that-may-insrease-insrease-riske-heart-heart-attack-stroke-stroke-stroke-stroke-473112</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:58:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Common Painkiller Use During Pregnancy Raise ADHD Risk In Kids? Here's What Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-common-painkiller-use-During-Pregnancy-Raise-Adhd-risk--heres-what-study-says-473111 <description><![CDATA[The results showed that children whose mothers had acetaminophen in their blood during the second trimester were over three times more likely to be diagnosed with ADHD.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-common-painkiller-use-During-Pregnancy-Raise-Adhd-risk--heres-what-study-says-473111</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:52:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Hangover? Have This Before Drinks, Says Doctor]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-hangover-have-have-this-before-drinks-says-says-doctor-473108 <description><![CDATA[Here's a simple trick to prevent the unpleasant aftermath of drinking alcohol.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-hangover-have-have-this-before-drinks-says-says-doctor-473108</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:51:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Have This Gut Healthy Snack Twice A Week, It Can Protect You From Aggressive Colorectal Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/have-have-this-gut-healthy-snack-twice-twice-twice-it-can-can-can-pan-partect-you-agegression-colorecrorecorrorecrorectal-cancercer-473107 <description><![CDATA[A new study discovered that a popular gut-healthy snack could offer protection against colorectal cancer, a finding that offers hope as cases rise, particularly among young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/have-have-this-gut-healthy-snack-twice-twice-twice-it-can-can-can-pan-partect-you-agegression-colorecrorecorrorecrorectal-cancercer-473107</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:45:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Warns: Avoid These Foods If You Take Medications, Eating This Fruit Can Even Be Toxic]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-warns-avoid-sosis-foods-you-you-take-medications-eating ---果实can-en-en-en-en-en-en-en-en toxic-473106 <description><![CDATA[A doctor now warns that certain food items can interfere with the absorption of medications, affecting their effectiveness, or in rare cases causing toxicity when combined with pills.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-warns-avoid-sosis-foods-you-you-take-medications-eating ---果实can-en-en-en-en-en-en-en-en toxic-473106</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:40:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Lose Weight? Nutritionist Shares Foods That Naturally Mimic Ozempic]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-lose-weight-nutritionist-shares-foods-dat-naturally-mimic-ozempic-473104 <description><![CDATA[A nutritionist shares 8 high-quality foods that naturally mimic the effects of Ozempic by boosting satiety, balancing blood sugar, reducing cravings, and helping make fat loss easier.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-lose-weight-nutritionist-shares-foods-dat-naturally-mimic-ozempic-473104</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Feb 2025 03:51:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[6-Year-Old's Weight Doubles In A Year, And Mom Thinks It's Lockdown Gain Before Fatal Cancer Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/6岁的weight-doubled-double-double-mom-thinks-thin--thin-lockdown-be-be-be for-fatal-cancer-diarsion-negnosis-473101 <description><![CDATA[The boy's mother now realizes his weight gain and other unusual signs were early warnings of cancer, and now shares his story to raise awareness about brain tumor symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/6岁的weight-doubled-double-double-mom-thinks-thin--thin-lockdown-be-be-be for-fatal-cancer-diarsion-negnosis-473101</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:54:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Indiana Doctors Go To Court To Keep Terminated Pregnancy Reports From Being Released To The Public]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/indiana-doctors--court-keep-终止 - 终止 - 释放释放 - 释放public-473100 <description><![CDATA[Two abortion providers in Indiana advocating against the release of individual terminated pregnancy reports have filed a lawsuit to keep the records private.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/indiana-doctors--court-keep-终止 - 终止 - 释放释放 - 释放public-473100</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:59:36 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>