<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Cycle Of Health: 8 Best Fitness Bikes For Effective Workouts]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cycle-health-8-best-fitness-bikes- effective-workouts-470851 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top 8 fitness bikes for achieving effective workouts to a more healthier lifestyle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cycle-health-8-best-fitness-bikes- effective-workouts-470851</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Sep 2023 11:54:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Migraines Linked To Higher Risk Of Heart Disease In Women: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/migraines-linked-higher-risk-of-heart-disease-women-study-470859 <description><![CDATA[Women with migraine headaches have an elevated risk of having a heart attack or hemorrhagic stroke compared to men.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/migraines-linked-higher-risk-of-heart-disease-women-study-470859</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Sep 2023 07:25:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Happiness Changes With Age? Scientists Say Here's When People Are Happiest After Childhood]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/happiness-changes-as-scientists-say-here-when-people-are-happiest-after-childhood-470856 <description><![CDATA[Although happiness may vary between people based on personal experiences, the researchers found that life satisfaction – one of the factors that determines happiness – decreases after the age of nine and increases between the ages of 70 and 96.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/happiness-changes-as-scientists-say-here-when-people-are-happiest-after-childhood-470856</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Sep 2023 05:29:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Morning Exercise May Be Most Effective For Weight Loss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-morning-exercise-may-most- effective-weight-loss-470854 <description><![CDATA[A new study shows that people who exercised in the morning exhibited the lowest BMI and waist size compared to those who exercised later in the day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-morning-exercise-may-most- effective-weight-loss-470854</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Sep 2023 04:20:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Acne Problems: Scientists Say New Antibiotic Treatment Could Be A Game-Changer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/acne-problems-scientists-say-new-antibiotic-treatment-could-change-the-game-470853 <description><![CDATA[A new study says nanoparticle delivery of narasin, an antibiotic compound, could work effectively against drug-resistant bacteria that cause Acne vulgaris.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/acne-problems-scientists-say-new-antibiotic-treatment-could-change-the-game-470853</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Sep 2023 03:33:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Blood Pressure Medication In Old Age May Lower Risk Of Dementia: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/takeing-blood-Pressure-medication-old-age-may-lower-risk-dementia-study-470852 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that older adults on blood pressure medications have a 26% lower risk of developing dementia than those with untreated hypertension.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/takeing-blood-Pressure-medication-old-age-may-lower-risk-dementia-study-470852</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Sep 2023 01:51:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Have Distressing Thoughts? Suppressing Them Might Help, Suggests New Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/have-suppressing-distressing-thoughts-might-help-suggestes-new-study-470849 <description><![CDATA[The study indicates that training the brain to block out negative thoughts could improve symptoms of anxiety, depression, and PTSD.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/have-suppressing-distressing-thoughts-might-help-suggestes-new-study-470849</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 10:30:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra-Processed Food, Especially Those With Artificial Sweeteners, May Elevate Depression Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-尤其-those-artificial-sweeteners-may-elevate-depression-risk-470847 <description><![CDATA[Participants who consumed nine or more portions of ultra-processed foods daily had a 49% increased risk of depression compared to those who consumed less than four portions a day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-尤其-those-artificial-sweeteners-may-elevate-depression-risk-470847</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 05:16:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Brucella Canis? This Rare Bacteria Causing Incurable Disease In Dogs Is Now Spreading To Humans]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-brucella-canis-this-rare-bacteria-causing-incurable-disease-dogs-now-spreading- humans-470845 <description><![CDATA[Three people in the U.K. have been infected with Brucella Canis, which causes a rare incurable infection in dogs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-brucella-canis-this-rare-bacteria-causing-incurable-disease-dogs-now-spreading- humans-470845</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 03:45:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[PCOS Awareness Month: Experts Debunk Myths About The Common Hormonal Disorder]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pcos-awareness-month-experts-debunk-myths-about-common-hormonal-disorders-470843 <description><![CDATA[As September marks PCOS Awareness Month, experts share their thoughts on the long-term impacts of PCOS and debunk some of the common myths about the condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pcos-awareness-month-experts-debunk-myths-about-common-hormonal-disorders-470843</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 01:39:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Yoga Could Help Improve Symptoms Of Rheumatoid Arthritis: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-yoga-help-improve-symptoms-of-rheumatoid-arthritis-study-470841 <description><![CDATA[Rheumatoid arthritis (RA) is an autoimmune and inflammatory disease that occurs when a person's immune system attacks healthy cells in the body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-yoga-help-improve-symptoms-of-rheumatoid-arthritis-study-470841</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Sep 2023 08:41:33 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>