<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医药日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Snack On 2 Handfuls Of Nuts Daily, Study Says They Can Boost Memory, Brain Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/snack-2-handfuls-nuts-daily-study-says-they-can-boost-memory-brain-health-470088 <description><![CDATA[The latest study has found that eating two handfuls of mixed nuts every day can improve memory and boost brain health in older adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/snack-2-handfuls-nuts-daily-study-says-they-can-boost-memory-brain-health-470088</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 01:30:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[International Men's Health Week: 5 Healthy Habits To Stay Fit]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-mens-health-week-5-healthy-habits-stay-fit-470087 <description><![CDATA[This year, the celebrations focus on the theme "Healthy Habits" to encourage men and boys around the world to make lifestyle changes for their better health and well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-mens-health-week-5-healthy-habits-stay-fit-470087</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:54:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Does Stress Make Us Crave Comfort Food? Tips To Prevent Emotional Eating]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-does-stress-make-us-crave-comfort-food-tips-prevent-emotional-eating-470084 <description><![CDATA[The latest study explains how the brain signals during stress cause over-indulgence in comfort food.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-does-stress-make-us-crave-comfort-food-tips-prevent-emotional-eating-470084</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 02:59:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Older Adults Exhale More Aerosol Particles Into The Air Than Others, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-exhale-more-aerosol-particles-air-others-study-says-470083 <description><![CDATA[Airborne diseases spread through tiny respiratory particles in the air.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-exhale-more-aerosol-particles-air-others-study-says-470083</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 02:43:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alcohol Intake In Any Quantity Is Linked To Over 60 Diseases, Study Shows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-intake-any-quantity-linked-over-60-diseases-study-shows-470082 <description><![CDATA[Alcohol intake increases the risk of 33 diseases that were not previously associated with consumption.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-intake-any-quantity-linked-over-60-diseases-study-shows-470082</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:04:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Pathogen Made By Chinese Scientists, Military In Wuhan Lab: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-pathogen-made-chinese-scientists-military-wuhan-lab-report-470078 <description><![CDATA[A report has claimed Chinese scientists and military could be responsible for the virus that caused the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-pathogen-made-chinese-scientists-military-wuhan-lab-report-470078</guid><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:11:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mpox Vaccination Update: What You Need To Know Amid Resurgence]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-vaccination-update-what-you-need-know-amid-resurgence-470077 <description><![CDATA[Experts recommend completing the two-dose JYNNEOS vaccine against mpox.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-vaccination-update-what-you-need-know-amid-resurgence-470077</guid><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:02:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[BioNTech Heading To Court Over COVID Vaccine Side Effects Suit In Germany]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/biontech-heading-court-over-covid-vaccine-side-effects-suit-germany-470074 <description><![CDATA[The company will defend itself in court against a lawsuit alleging the side effects of its mRNA vaccine with Pfizer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/biontech-heading-court-over-covid-vaccine-side-effects-suit-germany-470074</guid><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:56:36 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Experts Warn Of Ozempic's Serious Side Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experts-warn-ozempics-serious-side-effects-470079 <description><![CDATA[Ozempic and other similar drugs are not free from side effects, according to experts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experts-warn-ozempics-serious-side-effects-470079</guid><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:51:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Chicago Healthcare Law: Compliance and Regulations for Medical Professionals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chicago-healthcare-law-compliance-regulations-medical-professionals-470072 <description><![CDATA[As a medical professional in the vibrant city of Chicago, providing quality healthcare services to patients is undoubtedly your top priority.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chicago-healthcare-law-compliance-regulations-medical-professionals-470072</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 09:35:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Heart-In-A-Box': Innovative Transplant Method Deemed Safe, Could Expand Donor Pool]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-box-innovative-transplant-method-deemed-safe-could-expand-donor-pool-470069 <description><![CDATA[With the help of the device, doctors can revive and evaluate donor hearts that have stopped beating, determining their suitability for transplantation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-box-innovative-transplant-method-deemed-safe-could-expand-donor-pool-470069</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 06:05:28 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>