<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Lumbar Pillows: Top Choices To Support Your Back, Improve Posture]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lumbar-pillows-top-choices-support-your-back-improve-posture-472292 <description><![CDATA[Poor posture can lead to severe lower back pain, especially for those who sit for long periods. Lumbar pillows provide an easy solution by relieving pressure on the lower spine and helping maintain good posture. These orthopedic support pillows fit snugly between the spine and the sitting surface, adapting to the body's natural curve to offer maximum support and evenly distribute weight.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lumbar-pillows-top-choices-support-your-back-improve-posture-472292</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 12:48:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Coccyx Cushions To Alleviate Tailbone Pain And Improve Comfort: Top Picks For Every Need]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-coccyx-cushions-alleviate-tailbone-pain-improve-comfort-top-picks-every-need-472293 <description><![CDATA[Coccyx cushions are a simple yet effective solution for tailbone pain and discomfort. Whether you're looking for cooling relief, portability, or orthopedic support, there's a coccyx cushion to meet your specific needs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-coccyx-cushions-alleviate-tailbone-pain-improve-comfort-top-picks-every-need-472293</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 12:45:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best SAM-e Supplements For Mental And Physical Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-supplements-sam-e-mental-physical-health-472266 <description><![CDATA[SAM-e is a versatile compound with potential benefits for mood support, joint health, liver function, and cognitive health. As a naturally occurring molecule involved in various biochemical processes, SAM-e plays a crucial role in maintaining overall health and well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-supplements-sam-e-mental-physical-health-472266</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 12:41:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unlocking The Full Health Potential Of Probiotics: Beyond Digestive Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unlocking-full-health-potial-probiotics-beyond-digestive-benefits-472302 <description><![CDATA[Incorporating probiotics into your diet can support not only a healthy gut but also improve respiratory function and cardiovascular health, promoting overall well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unlocking-full-health-potial-probiotics-beyond-digestive-benefits-472302</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 12:38:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excessive Exposure To Night Light Linked To Higher Risk Of Alzheimer's: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excessive-exposure-night-light-linked-higher-risk-alzheimers-study-472308 <description><![CDATA[Excessive light pollution increases the risk of Alzheimer's in both older and younger adults. For those under 65, nighttime light exposure poses a greater risk of developing Alzheimer's disease compared to many other known factors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excessive-exposure-night-light-linked-higher-risk-alzheimers-study-472308</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 04:57:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Insulin Resistance Risk Factor For 26 Diseases, Linked To Early Death In Women: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/insulin-resistance-risk-factor-26-diseases-linked-early-death-women-study-472307 <description><![CDATA[The study found that insulin resistance is associated with more than 30 diseases, elevating the risk for 26 of them and potentially leading to early death in women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/insulin-resistance-risk-factor-26-diseases-linked-early-death-women-study-472307</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 03:08:21 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Night Owls At Higher Risk Of Diabetes: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-owls-higher-risk-diabetes-study-472305 <description><![CDATA[Compared with an intermediate chronotype, participants with a late chronotype had a 46% higher risk of type 2 diabetes, even after adjusting for other factors including age and lifestyle factors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-owls-higher-risk-diabetes-study-472305</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 01:42:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eating Fish During Pregnancy May Cut Offspring's Autism Risk, Not Omega-3: Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-fish-during-pregnancy-may-cut-offsprings-autism-risk-not-omega-3-study-says-472298 <description><![CDATA[Including fish in the diet during pregnancy is linked to a 20% reduction in the risk of autism spectrum disorder and a decreased risk of autism-related traits in children, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-fish-during-pregnancy-may-cut-offsprings-autism-risk-not-omega-3-study-says-472298</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Sep 2024 05:05:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Low-Carb, High-Fat Diet May Help Weight Loss, But Study Says It Raises Diabetes Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-carb-high-fat-diet-may-help-weight-loss-study-says-it-raises-diabetes-risk-472296 <description><![CDATA[A low-carb, high-fat diet is linked to a 20% increased risk of developing type 2 diabetes, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-carb-high-fat-diet-may-help-weight-loss-study-says-it-raises-diabetes-risk-472296</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Sep 2024 03:53:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Researchers Say This Simple Technique Could Shorten Colds In Kids By 2 Days]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/researchers-discover-simple-technique-shorten-cold-kids-2-days-472295 <description><![CDATA[A recent study offers a quick fix that not only shortens the duration of common cold but also significantly reduces the risk of transmission.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/researchers-discover-simple-technique-shorten-cold-kids-2-days-472295</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Sep 2024 01:46:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Orthopedic Ergonomic Chairs For Spine Support, Back Pain]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-orthopedic-ergonomic-chairs-spine-support-back-pain-472276 <description><![CDATA[Investing in good-quality ergonomic chairs may save you a lot of pain in the future. These orthopedic chairs can support your lower back, align your spine, and give your neck the comfort it needs while working.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-orthopedic-ergonomic-chairs-spine-support-back-pain-472276</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:10:19 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>