<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh</language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Sunscreens For Face: Guard Your Glow]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-sunscreens-face-guard-your-glow-471334 <description><![CDATA[Whether it's summer or winter, finding the best sunscreen for the face is a must. Here is our list of the most popular sunscreens to protect your skin.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-sunscreens-face-guard-your-glow-471334</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jan 2024 04:28:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Good Nutrition Before And During Pregnancy Could Prevent Childhood Obesity, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/good-nutrition-before-during-pregnancy-could-prevent-childhood-obesity-study-says-471340 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that when mothers take supplements with probiotics, myoinositol and vitamins B2, B6, B12 and D before giving birth, their children have less rapid weight gain and obesity by the age of 2.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/good-nutrition-before-during-pregnancy-could-prevent-childhood-obesity-study-says-471340</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jan 2024 01:13:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Drink More Tomato Juice: Study Says It Has Antimicrobial Properties To Eliminate Typhoid-Causing Salmonella]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drink-more-tomato-juice-study-says-it-has-antimicrobial-properties-eliminate-typhoid-causing-471338 <description><![CDATA[The researchers hope their findings will inspire more people, particularly children and teenagers, to eat and drink more tomatoes and other fruits and vegetables rich in antimicrobial properties.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drink-more-tomato-juice-study-says-it-has-antimicrobial-properties-eliminate-typhoid-causing-471338</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 23:53:29 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Piping Rock Empowers Wellness With Quality Supplements]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-piping-rock-empowers-wellness-quality-supplements-471337 <description><![CDATA[With the market flooded with countless options, navigating through the sea of options to find effective products is important.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-piping-rock-empowers-wellness-quality-supplements-471337</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:25:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Hair Growth Products For 2024: Unlock Luscious Tresses]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hair-growth-products-unlock-luscious-tresses-471332 <description><![CDATA[Here, we have curated a list of products designed to address hair loss and promote healthy hair growth.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hair-growth-products-unlock-luscious-tresses-471332</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:27:47 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Protein Bars Of 2024: Healthy Goodness To Fuel Your Day]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-bars-healthy-goodness-fuel-your-day-471327 <description><![CDATA[Protein bars are among the quickest ways for you to have the energy that you need. Take a look at some of the best protein bars that we have listed for you.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-bars-healthy-goodness-fuel-your-day-471327</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 08:17:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Shampoo For Thinning Hair In 2024: Nourish Your Strands]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shampoo-thinning-hair-nourish-your-strands-471333 <description><![CDATA[Say goodbye to worries about thinning hair and hello to confidence and vitality with our top picks for the best shampoo to combat thinning hair.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shampoo-thinning-hair-nourish-your-strands-471333</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 07:43:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Tinted Moisturizers For 2024: Unveiling Natural Radiance And Glow]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tinted-moisturizers-unveiling-natural-radiance-glow-471329 <description><![CDATA[Tinted moisturizers offer lightweight coverage while hydrating the skin, making them perfect for achieving a natural, dewy look.  Here, we have compiled some of the best products that will provide an effortless way to enhance your complexion.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tinted-moisturizers-unveiling-natural-radiance-glow-471329</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 06:49:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Cycling Consequences: Researchers Say People Should Avoid Dieting Unless Medically Necessary]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-cycling-consequences-researchers-say-people-should-avoid-dieting-unless-medically-necessary-471331 <description><![CDATA[A recent study shed light on how toxic yo-yo dieting can be and how difficult it can be for people to get out of the cycle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-cycling-consequences-researchers-say-people-should-avoid-dieting-unless-medically-necessary-471331</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 03:26:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Music For Brain Health: Researchers Say Singing, Playing Instruments Linked To Better Memory In Old Age]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/music-brain-health-researchers-say-singing-playing-instruments-linked-better-memory-old-age-471328 <description><![CDATA[The findings of a recent large-scale study suggest that lifelong exposure to music could help improve a person's memory and brain health in old age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/music-brain-health-researchers-say-singing-playing-instruments-linked-better-memory-old-age-471328</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:54:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exploring Non-Surgical Solutions For Neuromas And Chronic Plantar Fasciitis: Dr. Alan Shih's Approach]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exploring-non-surgical-solutions-neuromas-chronic-plantar-fasciitis-dr-alan-shihs-approach-471325 <description><![CDATA[While surgical interventions are often the go-to option for recalcitrant neuromas and plantar fasciitis, Dr. Shih introduces Radiofrequency Ablation (RFA) as a viable alternative.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exploring-non-surgical-solutions-neuromas-chronic-plantar-fasciitis-dr-alan-shihs-approach-471325</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Jan 2024 12:08:25 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>