<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Stay Up To Date With COVID-19 Shots: CDC Says Vaccinating Expectant Mothers Helps Protect Newborns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-date-covid-19-shots-cdc-says-vaccinating-expectant-mothers-offers-protection-newborns-470912 <description><![CDATA[When mothers received COVID-19 vaccination during pregnancy, the vaccine effectiveness against COVID-related hospitalization was 35% among infants less than six months and 54% in the initial three months of their life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-date-covid-19-shots-cdc-says-vaccinating-expectant-mothers-offers-protection-newborns-470912</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:47:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Premenstrual Food Cravings Are Common: Scientists Might Have Found Out Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/premenstrual-food-cravings-are-common-scientists-might-have-found-out-why-470910 <description><![CDATA[Researchers assessed insulin sensitivity in women to find out the reason behind increased food cravings right before a period.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/premenstrual-food-cravings-are-common-scientists-might-have-found-out-why-470910</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Sep 2023 16:10:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Power Of Magnesium: 10 Supplements For Optimal Health And Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/power-magnesium-10-supplements-optimal-health-wellness-470864 <description><![CDATA[Explore the transformative benefits of magnesium supplements for achieving optimal health and wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/power-magnesium-10-supplements-optimal-health-wellness-470864</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Sep 2023 10:59:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pain Reprocessing Therapy For Chronic Back Pain? Scientists Say The Treatment May Work]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pain-reprocessing-therapy-chronic-back-pain-scientists-say-treatment-may-work-470907 <description><![CDATA[People experience pain for various reasons, but there are instances wherein some experience physical pain without any definite cause. In such cases, managing one's perspective about the brain's role in chronic pain could give them more control.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pain-reprocessing-therapy-chronic-back-pain-scientists-say-treatment-may-work-470907</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:31:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Not Just Smoking, Use Of Unclean Cooking Fuel Also Linked To Developmental Delays In Children: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-just-smoking-use-unclean-cooking-fuel-also-linked-developmental-delays-children-study-470904 <description><![CDATA[A new study has revealed a link between indoor air pollution, stemming from both passive smoking and the use of unclean cooking fuels, and development delays in children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-just-smoking-use-unclean-cooking-fuel-also-linked-developmental-delays-children-study-470904</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Sep 2023 04:31:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch Out For Menopausal Signs: Study Says Hot Flashes During Sleep May Be Linked To Alzheimer's]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watch-out-menopausal-signs-study-says-hot-flashes-during-sleep-may-linked-alzheimers-470902 <description><![CDATA[The study has found that women who experience hot flashes during sleep are at a higher risk of Alzheimer's.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watch-out-menopausal-signs-study-says-hot-flashes-during-sleep-may-linked-alzheimers-470902</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:22:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Heart Day: Experts Discuss Risk Factors, Share Tips To Prevent Cardiac Issues In Young Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-heart-day-experts-discuss-risk-factors-share-tips-prevent-cardiac-issues-young-adults-470899 <description><![CDATA[On this World Heart Day, let's understand the risk factors associated with cardiac issues in young adults and listen to expert opinions for prevention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-heart-day-experts-discuss-risk-factors-share-tips-prevent-cardiac-issues-young-adults-470899</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Sep 2023 01:39:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even Short-Term Exposure To Air Pollution Can Increase Risk Of Strokes, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-short-term-exposure-to-air-pollution-can-increase-risk-of-中风-says-study-470896 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that higher concentrations of nitrogen dioxide showed a notable 28% increase in stroke risk, while high ozone levels indicated a 5% increase. Carbon monoxide was linked to a 26% increase, and sulfur dioxide, 15%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-short-term-exposure-to-air-pollution-can-increase-risk-of-中风-says-study-470896</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 09:31:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Eosinophilic Meningitis? Here's Everything About The Rare Infection That Spreads From Rodents]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-eosinophilic-meningitis-here-is-everything-about-rare-infection-that-spreads-rodents-470894 <description><![CDATA[Angiostrongylus cantonensis or rat lungworm worm causes a rare form of infection known as eosinophilic meningitis, which can cause paralysis and even death in severe cases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-eosinophilic-meningitis-here-is-everything-about-rare-infection-that-spreads-rodents-470894</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 08:17:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Almost 10% Of Adults In US Live With Chronic Conditions Like Diabetes, Heart Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/almost-10-adults-us-living-chronic-conditions-like-diabetic-heart-disease-study-470893 <description><![CDATA[Approximately one in 10 adults in the U.S. suffer from multiple cardiac, renal or metabolic conditions. The risk also increases with age as one in three adults aged 65 or older had a CRM condition, whereas one in four had overlapping conditions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/almost-10-adults-us-living-chronic-conditions-like-diabetic-heart-disease-study-470893</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:56:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nail Abnormalities: Here's What Your Nails Say About Your Health]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/nail-abnormalities-here-what-your-nails-say-about-your-health-470890 <description><![CDATA[Changes in your fingernails can be worrisome and may be a result of more serious underlying health issues.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nail-abnormalities-here-what-your-nails-say-about-your-health-470890</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:11:01 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>