<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh</language><item><title><![CDATA[9 Ways To Boost Society's Mental Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-ways-boost-societys-mental-wellness-470524 <description><![CDATA[In a world where war, economic woes, crime, and other negative forces seem to be on the upswing]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-ways-boost-societys-mental-wellness-470524</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 11:14:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bipolar Patients 6 Times More At Risk Of Early Death From External Causes: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bipolar-病人-6-times-more-risk-early-death-external-causes-study-470523 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that people with bipolar disorders are six times more likely to die before their time from external causes, such as accidents, violence and suicide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bipolar-病人-6-times-more-risk-early-death-external-causes-study-470523</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 04:03:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Prosthetic Breakthrough Allows Man With Amputated Arm Move Every Finger Of His Bionic Hand]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prosthetic-breakthrough-allows-man-amputated-arm-move-every-finger-his-bionic-hand-470522 <description><![CDATA[A man who lost an arm above the elbow has become the world's first amputee to freely control all five fingers of his bionic hand thanks to new surgical and engineering innovations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prosthetic-breakthrough-allows-man-amputated-arm-move-every-finger-his-bionic-hand-470522</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 02:50:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 10 Air Purifiers of 2023 for Improved Indoor Air Quality]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-air-purifiers-2023-improved-indoor-air-quality-470483 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top 10 air purifiers of 2023 that are revolutionizing indoor air quality, providing cleaner and healthier environments for you and your loved ones.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-air-purifiers-2023-improved-indoor-air-quality-470483</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 22:42:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Step Closer To An Anti-Aging Pill? Harvard Researchers Find Age-Reversing Chemical Cocktails]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/step-closer-anti-aging-pill-harvard-researchers-find-age-reversing-chemical-cocktails-470521 <description><![CDATA[In what could be a groundbreaking discovery, researchers from Harvard have identified six chemical cocktails that they say can reverse the aging process in both human and mouse skin cells.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/step-closer-anti-aging-pill-harvard-researchers-find-age-reversing-chemical-cocktails-470521</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 03:56:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Thought Diabetes Caused Excessive Thirst Until He Tested His Eyes; Know Signs Of Pituitary Tumors]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-thought-diabetes-caused-excessive-thirst-until-he-tested-his-eyes-know-signs-pituitary-tumors-470520 <description><![CDATA[The man was diagnosed with a type of brain tumor – a germ cell tumor on his pituitary gland that interfered with water retention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-thought-diabetes-caused-excessive-thirst-until-he-tested-his-eyes-know-signs-pituitary-tumors-470520</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 02:51:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Failing Eyesight Signal Dementia? Study Says Vision Loss Is A Modifiable Risk Factor]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-failing-eyesight-signal-dementia-study-says-vision-loss-modulated-risk-factor-470518 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that vision loss has a significant association with dementia in the elderly.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-failing-eyesight-signal-dementia-study-says-vision-loss-modulated-risk-factor-470518</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:58:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10-Year-Old Diagnosed With 'Most Painful' Condition; Learn More About Complex Regional Pain Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/10-year-old-diagnosed-most-painful-condition-learn-more-about-complex-regional-pain-syndrome-470517 <description><![CDATA[Complex Regional Pain Syndrome (CRPS) is a relatively rare disorder, often dubbed the most painful condition known to mankind.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/10-year-old-diagnosed-most-painful-condition-learn-more-about-complex-regional-pain-syndrome-470517</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:21:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gut Microbe And Heart Health: Study Says Intestinal Bacteria Can Cause Fatty Deposits In Arteries]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-microbe-heart-health-study-says-intestinal-bacteria-can-cause-fatty-deposits-arteries-470516 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that an increase in the number of a particular type of bacteria in the gut increases the risk of coronary atherosclerotic plaques or fatty deposits in arteries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-microbe-heart-health-study-says-intestinal-bacteria-can-cause-fatty-deposits-arteries-470516</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:55:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Hyperlactation Syndrome? Woman With Rare Condition Sets Guinness Record By Donating Breast Milk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-hyperlactation-syndrome-woman-rare-condition-sets-guinness-record-donating-breast-milk-470515 <description><![CDATA[Elisabeth Anderson-Sierra, a mother of two from Aloha, has saved the lives of thousands of premature babies by donating around 1,600 liters of her breastmilk over the past nine years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-hyperlactation-syndrome-woman-rare-condition-sets-guinness-record-donating-breast-milk-470515</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 01:40:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Could Carpal Tunnel Syndrome Signal Heart Failure? Study Finds Potential Link Between The Two]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-carpal-tunnel-syndrome-signal-heart-failure-study-finds-pottial-link- Between-two-470505 <description><![CDATA[Elderly patients with carpal tunnel syndrome are 39% more likely to develop heart failure compared with those without the condition, a recent study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-carpal-tunnel-syndrome-signal-heart-failure-study-finds-pottial-link- Between-two-470505</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jul 2023 05:17:36 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>