<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一个</language><item><title><![CDATA[Childhood BMI Linked To Lung Function Later; Low And High Values Harmful: Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childhood-bmi-linked-lung-function-later-low-high-values-harmful-says-study-472649 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that both high and low BMI values during the critical years of lung development can have lasting harmful effects.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childhood-bmi-linked-lung-function-later-low-high-values-harmful-says-study-472649</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Nov 2024 03:00:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Milk Intake May Increase Heart Disease Risk In Women; Yogurt Healthier Alternative: Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/milk-intake-may-increase-heart-disease-risk-women-yogurt-healthier-alternative-says-study-472647 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that non-fermented milk intake could raise heart disease risk in women while switching to a fermented alternative like yogurt might reduce the risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/milk-intake-may-increase-heart-disease-risk-women-yogurt-healthier-alternative-says-study-472647</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:01:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excessive Daytime Sleepiness In Elderly Might Be Linked To Pre-Dementia Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excessive-daytime-sleepiness-elderly-might-linked-pre-dementia-syndrome-472644 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that elderly adults who have excessive daytime sleepiness are at risk of developing motoric cognitive risk syndrome that can lead to dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excessive-daytime-sleepiness-elderly-might-linked-pre-dementia-syndrome-472644</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Nov 2024 04:40:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Proposes To Ban Popular Decongestant In Cold Medicines Citing 'Not Effective']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-proposes-ban-popular-decongestant-cold-medicines-citing-not- effective-472643 <description><![CDATA[Officials clarified that the proposed ban is not related to the safety of oral phenylephrine and companies may continue selling products containing the ingredient until the order is finalized.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-proposes-ban-popular-decongestant-cold-medicines-citing-not- effective-472643</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Nov 2024 02:56:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Just 80 Minutes Of Weekly Exercise Reduces Baby Blues, Postpartum Depression Symptoms: Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/just-80-minutes-weekly-exercise-reduces-baby-blues-postpartum-depression-symptoms-says-study-472640 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that mothers who engage in exercise programs with at least 80 minutes of moderate activity each week experience significant reductions in the severity of baby blues and postpartum depression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/just-80-minutes-weekly-exercise-reduces-baby-blues-postpartum-depression-symptoms-says-study-472640</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Nov 2024 01:18:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitamin D During Pregnancy Linked To Better Bone Health In Children At Age 7: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-during-pregnancy-linked-better-bone-health-children-age-7-study-472638 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that children have greater bone mineral density at age 7 when expectant mothers take vitamin D supplements during pregnancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-during-pregnancy-linked-better-bone-health-children-age-7-study-472638</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Nov 2024 04:42:13 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Time To Exercise? Study Finds Two Key Times To Lower Colorectal Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-time-exercise-study-finds-two-key-times-lower-colorectal-cancer-risk-472637 <description><![CDATA[According to new research, getting active at two specific times of day may significantly lower the risk of colorectal cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-time-exercise-study-finds-two-key-times-lower-colorectal-cancer-risk-472637</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Nov 2024 01:01:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleep An Extra 46 Minutes: Study Links It to Improved Well-Being, Positive Behavioral Traits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-extra-46-minutes-study-links-it-improved-well-being-positive-behavioral-traits-472635 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that sleeping an additional 46 minutes is linked to improved well-being and positive traits such as gratitude, flourishing, resilience, and prosocial behaviors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-extra-46-minutes-study-links-it-improved-well-being-positive-behavioral-traits-472635</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Nov 2024 04:32:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pregnant Mothers With Obesity And PCOS At Higher Risk Of Having Smaller Babies: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnant-mothers-obesity-pcos-higher-risk-having-smaller-babies-study-472633 <description><![CDATA[On average, babies born to mothers with PCOS faced a higher risk of growth restriction, and the effects were more pronounced in mothers who were obese.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnant-mothers-obesity-pcos-higher-risk-having-smaller-babies-study-472633</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Nov 2024 02:35:52 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Suggests A Medication-Free Treatment For Depression, Finds Symptom Relief In 40% Cases]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-suggests-medication-free-treatment-depression-finds-symptom-relief-40-cases-472630 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have identified a drug-free therapy that could offer a safe, effective adjunctive treatment for non-seasonal depressive disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-suggests-medication-free-treatment-depression-finds-symptom-relief-40-cases-472630</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Nov 2024 01:10:13 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Reveals Breakfast Item That May Boost Focus And Keep You Full]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-breakfast-item-that-may-boost-focus-keep-you-full-472627 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that a dairy-based high-protein diet is most effective for promoting fullness and boosting concentration compared to a carb-rich meal or skipping breakfast entirely.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-breakfast-item-that-may-boost-focus-keep-you-full-472627</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Nov 2024 04:30:02 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>