<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Soups And Shakes Diet Safe For Nash, May Improve Advanced Fatty Liver Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/soups-shakes-diet-safe-nash-may-improve-advanced-fatty-liver-disease-study-470397 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that a soups and shakes diet can benefit people with non-alcoholic steatohepatitis (NASH).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/soups-shakes-diet-safe-nash-may-improve-advanced-fatty-liver-disease-study-470397</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 01:02:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Reveals How Many Americans Still Haven't Caught COVID-19]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-reveals-how-many-americans-still-havent-caught-covid-19-470395 <description><![CDATA[CDC estimates suggested a vast majority of Americans had developed antibodies against COVID-19.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-reveals-how-many-americans-still-havent-caught-covid-19-470395</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 20:28:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Study Links COVID-19 Severity To Autoantibodies Against Blood Clotting]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-study-links-covid-19-severity-autoantibodies-against-blood-clotting-470394 <description><![CDATA[The study explored how a blood clotting regulator gene performed during COVID-19 infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-study-links-covid-19-severity-autoantibodies-against-blood-clotting-470394</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 20:24:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Auria: Pioneering Tear-Based Cancer Screening for Breast Abnormalities]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/auria-pioneering-tear-based-cancer-screening-breast-abnormalities-470388 <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer is one of the leading causes of cancer-related deaths among women worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/auria-pioneering-tear-based-cancer-screening-breast-abnormalities-470388</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 10:46:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Signs Of Depression May Linger Even After Joint Pain Subsides In Orthopedic Patients, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/signs-depression-may-linger-even-after-joint-pain-subsides-orthopedic-病人-study-says-470385 <description><![CDATA[A new study suggests that even when the physical pain subsides, it doesn't mean the mental health issues will improve.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/signs-depression-may-linger-even-after-joint-pain-subsides-orthopedic-病人-study-says-470385</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 05:46:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Older Adults in Warmer Regions Have Higher Risk of Severe Vision Impairment: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-warmer-regions-have-higher-risk-severe-vision-impairment-study-470384 <description><![CDATA[Living in counties with temperatures ranging from 50-54.99°F increases the likelihood of severe vision impairment by 14%, the recent study said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-warmer-regions-have-higher-risk-severe-vision-impairment-study-470384</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 05:19:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitamin D For Heart Health? Study Says Supplements Can Cut Cardiovascular Risk In Elderly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-heart-health-study-says-supplements-can-cut-cardioangiography-risk-elderly-470381 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found vitamin D supplementation could help prevent major cardiovascular events such as heart attacks in people above the age of 60.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-heart-health-study-says-supplements-can-cut-cardioangiography-risk-elderly-470381</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:58:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Opioids May Not Be Effective In Treating Low Back And Neck Pain, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/opioids-may-not- effective-treating-low-back-neck-pain-study-finds-470378 <description><![CDATA[The study's findings indicate that opioids have minimal or negligible impact in addressing acute lower back pain. Researchers also express concerns about the potential risks associated with these medications.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/opioids-may-not- effective-treating-low-back-neck-pain-study-finds-470378</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:06:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experimental Probiotic Could Help Reduce Mercury Absorption In Gut]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-probiotic-could-help-reduce-mercury-absorbation-gut-470380 <description><![CDATA[In the latest study, researchers developed a new probiotic bacteria that can express an enzyme to convert more absorbable forms of mercury into less absorbable forms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-probiotic-could-help-reduce-mercury-absorbation-gut-470380</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 02:29:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[40% Of Young Women In US Have Iron Deficiency, Study Says; Know The Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/40-young-women-us-have-iron-deficiency-study-says-know-symptoms-470376 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests a blood test to measure the body's iron reserves should be included in routine health checkups as 40% of American teenage girls and young women have low levels of iron.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/40-young-women-us-have-iron-deficiency-study-says-know-symptoms-470376</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:38:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Giving Birth Between Ages 23 And 32 Reduces Baby's Risk Of 'Non-Chromosomal Anomalies': Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/giving-birth- Between-ages-23-32-reduces-babys-risk-non-chromosomal-abnormalities-study-470374 <description><![CDATA[Women older than 32 had a 15% higher chance of such births, while younger mothers had a 20% higher chance.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/giving-birth- Between-ages-23-32-reduces-babys-risk-non-chromosomal-abnormalities-study-470374</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 06:03:40 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>