<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Antiviral Drugs To Prevent Type 1 Diabetes? Study Says Treatment May Slow Disease Progression]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antiviral-drugs-prevent-type-1-diabetes-study-says-treatment-may-slow-disease-progression-470926 <description><![CDATA[The team earlier observed an association between diabetes and viral infection. In the latest study, they tried to address this connection using a combination therapy of antiviral drugs pleconaril and ribavirin.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antiviral-drugs-prevent-type-1-diabetes-study-says-treatment-may-slow-disease-progression-470926</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 01:27:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Diabetes And Longevity: Study Explains How Age Of Diagnosis Affects Life Expectancy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-longevity-study-explains-how-age-diagnosis-affects-life-expectancy-470924 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say getting diagnosed with type 2 diabetes before the age of 30 could potentially reduce life expectancy by around 14 years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-longevity-study-explains-how-age-diagnosis-affects-life-expectancy-470924</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:30:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Issues Warning Against Use Of Probiotics After Preterm Baby Dies In Hospital]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-issues-warning-against-use-probiotics-after-preterm-baby-dies-hospital-470921 <description><![CDATA[The premature baby, who weighed less than 2.2 pounds, died at an unidentified hospital due to sepsis caused by the same species of bacteria found in the probiotics that were administered to them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-issues-warning-against-use-probiotics-after-preterm-baby-dies-hospital-470921</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 03:26:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Depression Awareness Month: Expert Insights On How To Support A Loved One With Mental Illness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-awareness-month-expert-insights-how-support-loved-one-mental-illness-470920 <description><![CDATA[On this Depression Awareness Month, here are some insights on how to support your loved ones through their mental health journey.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-awareness-month-expert-insights-how-support-loved-one-mental-illness-470920</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 02:03:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People With Chronic Stress, Depression More Likely To Be Diagnosed With Alzheimer's: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-chronic-stress-depression-more-likely-diagnosed-alzheimers-study-470919 <description><![CDATA[Researchers tried to understand if chronic stress and depression – both known factors for mild cognitive impairment and Alzheimer's – had additive effects.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-chronic-stress-depression-more-likely-diagnosed-alzheimers-study-470919</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Oct 2023 05:16:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Drinking Dark Tea Daily May Help Reduce Diabetes Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking-dark-tea-daily-may-help-reduce-diabetes-risk-study-470918 <description><![CDATA[People who consume dark tea every day are at a 53% lower risk of developing prediabetes and 47% reduced risk for type 2 diabetes compared to those who never drink tea.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking-dark-tea-daily-may-help-reduce-diabetes-risk-study-470918</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Oct 2023 03:51:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High School Student Diagnosed With Tuberculosis In Kansas; Know Types, Risk Factors Of The Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-school-student-diagnosed-tuberculosis-kansas-know-types-risk-factors-infection-470917 <description><![CDATA[Health officials are working with the school district to identify people who had close contact with the infected student and have set up tuberculosis testing clinics.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-school-student-diagnosed-tuberculosis-kansas-know-types-risk-factors-infection-470917</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Oct 2023 01:36:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Climbing More Than 5 Flights Of Stairs Daily Can Reduce Heart Disease Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/climbing-more-5-flights-stairs-daily-can-reduce-heart-disease-risk-study-470916 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that climbing more than five flights of stairs daily could slash the risk of atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease by 20%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/climbing-more-5-flights-stairs-daily-can-reduce-heart-disease-risk-study-470916</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Oct 2023 04:53:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Migraines Linked To Breast Cancer? Researchers Identify A Possible Genetic Connection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/migraines-linked-breast-cancer-researchers-identify-possible-genic-connection-470914 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that women with any type of migraine are at an increased risk of developing overall breast cancer, especially estrogen-receptor breast cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/migraines-linked-breast-cancer-researchers-identify-possible-genic-connection-470914</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Oct 2023 03:40:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stay Up To Date With COVID-19 Shots: CDC Says Vaccinating Expectant Mothers Helps Protect Newborns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-date-covid-19-shots-cdc-says-vaccinating-expectant-mothers-offers-protection-newborns-470912 <description><![CDATA[When mothers received COVID-19 vaccination during pregnancy, the vaccine effectiveness against COVID-related hospitalization was 35% among infants less than six months and 54% in the initial three months of their life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-date-covid-19-shots-cdc-says-vaccinating-expectant-mothers-offers-protection-newborns-470912</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:47:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Premenstrual Food Cravings Are Common: Scientists Might Have Found Out Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/premenstrual-food-cravings-are-common-scientists-might-have-found-out-why-470910 <description><![CDATA[Researchers assessed insulin sensitivity in women to find out the reason behind increased food cravings right before a period.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/premenstrual-food-cravings-are-common-scientists-might-have-found-out-why-470910</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Sep 2023 16:10:01 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>