<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Intranasal Insulin Might Boost Cognition In Alzheimer's Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intranasal-insulin-might-boost-cognition-in-alzheimers-患者-study-470371 <description><![CDATA[The researchers conducted a meta-analysis of 29 studies involving 1,726 participants to examine the effect of intranasal insulin on cognitive function.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intranasal-insulin-might-boost-cognition-in-alzheimers-患者-study-470371</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 04:13:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Water Fasting For Weight Loss: Study Reveals Limited Long-Term Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/water-fasting-weight-loss-study-reveals-limited-long-term-effects-470365 <description><![CDATA[A recent study from the University of Illinois Chicago reveals that although water fasting may lead to initial weight loss, the weight is quickly regained.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/water-fasting-weight-loss-study-reveals-limited-long-term-effects-470365</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 02:56:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Aspartame Cause Cancer? Know Which Products Contain The Artificial Sweetener As WHO Raises Concerns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-aspartame-cause-cancer-know-which-products-contain-artificial-sweetener-who-raises-concerns-470369 <description><![CDATA[After the safety review conducted by the World Health Organization's cancer research arm, the International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC), aspartame is likely to be classified as possibly carcinogenic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-aspartame-cause-cancer-know-which-products-contain-artificial-sweetener-who-raises-concerns-470369</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 02:25:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Loneliness More Dangerous Than Smoking In Diabetes Patients, Could Increase Heart Disease Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-more-dangerous-smoking-diabetes-病人-could-increase-heart-disease-risk-study-470364 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that loneliness, which refers to the quality of social interaction, has a significant impact on heart health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-more-dangerous-smoking-diabetes-病人-could-increase-heart-disease-risk-study-470364</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 01:01:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Canine Influenza Outbreak: Minnesota Cases Surge As Vaccines Run Low]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/canine-influenza-outbreak-minnesota-cases-surge-vaccines-run-low-470361 <description><![CDATA[Nearly 300 dogs are suspected to have been infected with canine influenza.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/canine-influenza-outbreak-minnesota-cases-surge-vaccines-run-low-470361</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:51:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Here's Why Humans Can Fend Off Most Bird Flu Viruses]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heres-why- humans-can-fend-off-most-bird-flu-viruses-470358 <description><![CDATA[Researchers said a human gene plays a crucial role in protecting against most bird flu viruses.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heres-why- humans-can-fend-off-most-bird-flu-viruses-470358</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:41:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[West Nile Virus Detected In Mosquito Pools: Austin, Indianapolis On Alert]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-virus-Detected-mosquito-pools-austin-indianapolis-alert-470357 <description><![CDATA[The discovery raised concerns about potential human infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-virus-Detected-mosquito-pools-austin-indianapolis-alert-470357</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:34:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Older Adults Encouraged To Get RSV Vaccines To Combat Severe Illness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-encouraging-to-get-rsv-vaccines-fighting-severe-illness-470355 <description><![CDATA[The CDC recommends older adults get vaccinated against RSV come fall season.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-encouraging-to-get-rsv-vaccines-fighting-severe-illness-470355</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:18:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Ketamine For Depression Safe And Effective? Elon Musk Says It's A 'Better Option']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ketamine-depression-safe- effective-elon-musk-says-its-better-option-470349 <description><![CDATA[Elon Musk has told people he is taking small doses of ketamine to treat depression, a report claims.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ketamine-depression-safe- effective-elon-musk-says-its-better-option-470349</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 05:41:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[NHS Doctor Reveals The Correct Way Of Pooping For A 'Truly Wonderful Dump']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nhs-doctor-reveals- Correct-way-pooping-truly-wonderful-dump-470346 <description><![CDATA[A doctor in the United Kingdom shared with his over 5.1 million TikTok followers the proper and comfortable method of bowel movement.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nhs-doctor-reveals- Correct-way-pooping-truly-wonderful-dump-470346</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 05:36:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mpox Resurgence Expected As More People Step Out With Less Clothing On This Summer: Expert]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-resurgence-expected-more-people-stepping-out-less-clothing-this-summer-expert-470338 <description><![CDATA[Experts brace for the resurgence of mpox infections this summer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-resurgence-expected-more-people-stepping-out-less-clothing-this-summer-expert-470338</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:04:49 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>