<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Body Dysmorphia 6 Times More Common In Girls: Know About Condition That Affects Many Teens]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/body-dysmorphia-6-times-more-common-girls-know-about-condition-that-affects-many-teens-471539 <description><![CDATA[Body dysmorphic disorder (BDD) affects 1.8% of girls compared to 0.3% of boys, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/body-dysmorphia-6-times-more-common-girls-know-about-condition-that-affects-many-teens-471539</guid><pubDate> Mon, 25 Mar 2024 02:00:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Imagine Seeing Faces Like Demons? Know Rare Condition Behind Distorted Visual Perception]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/imagine-seeing-faces-like-demons-know-rare-condition-behind- Distorted-Visual-perception-471537 <description><![CDATA[Prosopometamorphopsia (PMO) is an extremely rare neurological disorder that alters visual perception, causing individuals to see distorted facial appearances, including shape, size, texture, or color.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/imagine-seeing-faces-like-demons-know-rare-condition-behind- Distorted-Visual-perception-471537</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Mar 2024 04:18:09 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flu Raises Risk Of Neurological Disorders More Than COVID-19: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-raises-risk-neurological-disorders-more-covid-19-study-471535 <description><![CDATA[People infected with the flu were more likely to need hospital care in the following year for common neurologic conditions than people who had the SARS-CoV2 infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-raises-risk-neurological-disorders-more-covid-19-study-471535</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Mar 2024 02:58:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pregnancy Complications Affect Women's Heart Health, Following Healthy Lifestyle Can Cut Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-complications-affect-womens-heart-health-following-healthy-lifestyle-can-cut-risk-study-471533 <description><![CDATA[Among women with a history of pregnancy complications, those who achieved or maintained high heart health after pregnancy were at a similar risk for heart disease as women without adverse pregnancy outcomes and good cardiovascular health, the study stated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-complications-affect-womens-heart-health-following-healthy-lifestyle-can-cut-risk-study-471533</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Mar 2024 02:28:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cannabis Vaping Liquids May Have Toxic Metal Particles Even Before First Use: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cannabis-vaping-liquids-may-have-有毒-金属-粒子-even-before-first-use-study-471531 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found metal contamination in cannabis vaping liquids even before the vaping device was first used or heated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cannabis-vaping-liquids-may-have-有毒-金属-粒子-even-before-first-use-study-471531</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:55:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Prenatal Tobacco Exposure, Smoking In Childhood Raise Risk Of Diabetes In Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prenatal-tobacco-exposure-smoking-childhood-raise-risk-diabetes-adults-study-471530 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that being exposed to tobacco before birth, as well as starting smoking during childhood or adolescence, significantly increases the risk of developing Type 2 diabetes later in life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prenatal-tobacco-exposure-smoking-childhood-raise-risk-diabetes-adults-study-471530</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Mar 2024 02:01:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Jason Shumard Revolutionizes Holistic Healing And Transformative Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-jason-shumad-revolutionizes-holistic-healing-transformative-wellness-471528 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Shumard's nearly 20-year career is dedicated to exploring complex health conditions and advocating for holistic healing methods.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-jason-shumad-revolutionizes-holistic-healing-transformative-wellness-471528</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:50:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Says 'Double Jointed' People At Higher Risk Of Long COVID]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-double-jointed-people-higher-risk-long-covid-471527 <description><![CDATA[The study published in the journal BMJ indicated that individuals with hypermobile joints had a 30% higher chance of not fully recovering from COVID-19 and experiencing persistent fatigue associated with long COVID.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-double-jointed-people-higher-risk-long-covid-471527</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Mar 2024 03:36:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sugary Drinks, Fruit Juices Linked To Elevated Risk Of Type 2 Diabetes In Boys: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sugary-drinks-fruit-juices-linked-elevated-risk-type-2-diabetes-boys-study-471525 <description><![CDATA[The study found that boys who regularly use sugary drinks and fruit juices during childhood and adolescence are at a heightened risk of Type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sugary-drinks-fruit-juices-linked-elevated-risk-type-2-diabetes-boys-study-471525</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Mar 2024 01:47:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[8-Hour Time-Restricted Eating Associated With Higher Risk Of Death From Heart Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-hour-time-restricted-eating-linked-higher-risk-death-heart-disease-study-471523 <description><![CDATA[The study found that people who followed an 8-hour time-restricted eating schedule had a 91% higher risk of cardiovascular death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-hour-time-restricted-eating-linked-higher-risk-death-heart-disease-study-471523</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Mar 2024 04:15:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Says 129,000 Kids In Chicago Under 6 Exposed To Lead-Contaminated Water]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-129000-kids-chicago-under-6-expose-lead-contamerated-water-471522 <description><![CDATA[The study also identified disparities in exposure levels and testing rates among different racial groups, highlighting racial inequities in the context of lead exposure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-129000-kids-chicago-under-6-expose-lead-contamerated-water-471522</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Mar 2024 02:51:45 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>