<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Exposure To BPA Linked To Gut Microbiome, Childhood Obesity: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-bpa-linked-gut-microbiome-childhood-obesity-study-471477 <description><![CDATA[The researchers identified that normal-weight children had more unique bacteria taxa, which may help degrade BPA.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-bpa-linked-gut-microbiome-childhood-obesity-study-471477</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Mar 2024 03:25:49 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Obesity Day: Here's How To Promote Healthy Lifestyle In Overweight Children]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-obesity-day-heres-how-promote-healthy-lifestyle-overweight-children-471476 <description><![CDATA[On this World Obesity Day, know ways to promote a healthy lifestyle to tackle obesity in children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-obesity-day-heres-how-promote-healthy-lifestyle-overweight-children-471476</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:08:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tandem Cycling Boosts Well-Being For Parkinson's Patients And Their Care Partners: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tandem-cycling-could-benefit-both-parkinsons-患者-care-partners-health-study-471475 <description><![CDATA[In a small-scale study, researchers examined how engaging in a simple exercise together such as tandem cycling could benefit a patient who suffers from Parkinson's disease and their respective caretakers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tandem-cycling-could-benefit-both-parkinsons-患者-care-partners-health-study-471475</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Mar 2024 01:13:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Quick And Effective Ways To Lower Cortisol Levels: Harnessing Supplements, Acupressure And Acupuncture]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quick- effective-ways-lower-cortisol-levels-harnessing-supplements-acuPressure-acupuncture-471473 <description><![CDATA[Discover quick and effective ways to lower your cortisol levels naturally. Explore supplements, acupressure, and acupuncture techniques to reduce stress hormone levels.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quick- effective-ways-lower-cortisol-levels-harnessing-supplements-acuPressure-acupuncture-471473</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Mar 2024 17:28:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Understand And Manage Binge Eating: Insights From Experts During Eating Disorders Awareness Week]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/understand-manage-binge-eating-insights-experts-during-eating-disorders-awareness-week-471471 <description><![CDATA[As we observe Eating Disorders Awareness Week, we at Medical Daily engaged experts to bring a better understanding of binge eating, one of the most common eating disorders, shedding light on its signs and offering effective management strategies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/understand-manage-binge-eating-insights-experts-during-eating-disorders-awareness-week-471471</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:03:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Timing Of COVID-19 Shot Can Affect Menstrual Cycle Length: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/timing-covid-19-shot-can-affect-menstrual-cycle-length-study-471470 <description><![CDATA[Those individuals who receive a COVID-19 vaccine during the first half of their menstrual cycle are more likely to experience cycle length changes than those receiving a vaccine in the latter half.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/timing-covid-19-shot-can-affect-menstrual-cycle-length-study-471470</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:57:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Red Light Therapy Devices For Hair Growth: Experience Glowing Strands]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/red-light-therapy-devices-hair-growth-experience-glowing-strands-471465 <description><![CDATA[Discover how harnessing the benefits of red light therapy can revitalize your hair and boost your confidence.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/red-light-therapy-devices-hair-growth-experience-glowing-strands-471465</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Feb 2024 07:13:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Older Adults Should Get COVID Booster Shot This Spring, CDC Says]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-should-get-covid-booster-shot-this-spring-cdc-says-471468 <description><![CDATA[The current booster dose is meant for older adults at least four months after a previous dose, or at least three months after a COVID-19 infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-should-get-covid-booster-shot-this-spring-cdc-says-471468</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Feb 2024 02:45:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra-Processed Food Linked To 32 Health Issues: Early Death, Heart Disease, And Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-linked-32-health-issues-early-death-heart-disease-cancer-471467 <description><![CDATA[Ultra-processed food has a connection to 32 health issues, including diabetes, heart disease, poor mental health, cancer, and premature death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-linked-32-health-issues-early-death-heart-disease-cancer-471467</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Feb 2024 01:56:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Better Air Quality Reduces Suicide Rates: Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/better-air-quality-reduces-suicide-rates-study-finds-471463 <description><![CDATA[The suicide rates increase substantially when air pollution rises, and the effect was particularly strong in the elderly, with older women 2.5 times more at risk than other groups.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/better-air-quality-reduces-suicide-rates-study-finds-471463</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Feb 2024 01:11:44 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Daylight Saving Time Affect Heart Health? Mayo Clinic Study Says Effect Is Minimal]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-daylight- saving-time-affect-heart-health-mayo-clinic-study-says-effect-minimal-471461 <description><![CDATA[The researchers note that there is no compelling reason to alter the daylight saving time system based on concerns related to heart health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-daylight- saving-time-affect-heart-health-mayo-clinic-study-says-effect-minimal-471461</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Feb 2024 03:02:09 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>