<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA[CDC To Investigate Swine Flu Case That Killed 42-Year-Old Woman In Brazil]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-investigate-fatal-swine-flu-case-brazil-470236 <description><![CDATA[The fatality resulted from an H1N1 variant spreading among pigs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-investigate-fatal-swine-flu-case-brazil-470236</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:34:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mpox Cases Surge Globally, Sparking Vaccine Access Concerns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-cases-surge-globally-sparking-vaccine-access-concerns-470234<description><![CDATA[Experts expressed concerns over the spread of mpox worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-cases-surge-globally-sparking-vaccine-access-concerns-470234</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:30:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[California Student Sues University For Class Ban After Refusing COVID-19 Vaccine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-student-sues-university-class-ban-after-refusing-covid-19-vaccine-470232 <description><![CDATA[The student got barred from attending in-person classes after refusing the vaccine and other COVID-19 regulations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-student-sues-university-class-ban-after-refusing-covid-19-vaccine-470232</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:24:09 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctors Worry As Ozempic Causes Spike In ER Visits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctors-worry-ozempic-causes-spike-er-visits-470230 <description><![CDATA[The famous diabetes drug for weight loss reportedly comes with serious side effects.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctors-worry-ozempic-causes-spike-er-visits-470230</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:13:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[20% Of Women Who Need Fertility Treatment Can Get Pregnant Naturally Later: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20-women-who-need-fertility-treatment-can-get-pregnant-naturally-later-study-470228 <description><![CDATA[One in five women who had IVF treatment conceived naturally during their subsequent pregnancy, according to a study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20-women-who-need-fertility-treatment-can-get-pregnant-naturally-later-study-470228</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 05:32:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exercise Can Increase Stroke Risk In People With Blocked Arteries, Study Shows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-can-increase-中风-risk-people-blocked-arteries-study-shows-470225 <description><![CDATA["It substantially increases the shear stress at the stenosis zone, which may cause the stenosis to rupture. This ruptured plaque may then flow to the brain and its blood supply, causing ischemic stroke," the study's lead author says.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-can-increase-中风-risk-people-blocked-arteries-study-shows-470225</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:26:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[International Yoga Day: 5 Poses To Treat Sleep Disorders]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-yoga-day-5-poses-treat-sleep-disorders-470222 <description><![CDATA[On this International Yoga Day, learn more about the poses that can help you treat sleep disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-yoga-day-5-poses-treat-sleep-disorders-470222</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:02:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Scientists Identify Key Process Driving The Progression Of Huntington's Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-identify-key-process-driven-progression-huntingtons-disease-470220 <description><![CDATA[The researchers said the toxic clumps of protein that trigger Huntington's Disease spread like a destructive forest fire.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-identify-key-process-driven-progression-huntingtons-disease-470220</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 03:27:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Some Medications Can Make You More Prone To Sunburns; Tips To Protect Your Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/some-medications-can-make-you-more-prone-sunburns-tips-protect-your-skin-470219 <description><![CDATA[Take more care to apply sunscreen and minimize direct exposure to sunlight if you are on a medication that causes photosensitivity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/some-medications-can-make-you-more-prone-sunburns-tips-protect-your-skin-470219</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 01:58:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mental Health Patients On Antidepressants Less Likely To Test Positive For COVID-19: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mental-health-患者-antidepressants-less-likely-test-positive-covid-19-study-470218 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that patients who had antidepressants prescribed on their medical records were approximately 40% less likely to test positive for COVID-19 compared to those who were not taking the medication.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mental-health-患者-antidepressants-less-likely-test-positive-covid-19-study-470218</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:19:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Missouri Man Dies After Eating Raw Oysters From Seafood Stand]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/missouri-man-dies-after-eating-raw-oysters-seafood-stand-470210 <description><![CDATA[The man died shortly after contracting a flesh-eating infection from eating raw oysters.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/missouri-man-dies-after-eating-raw-oysters-seafood-stand-470210</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:28:40 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>