<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Everything About Eye Twitching: Causes Of The Condition And Precautions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/everything-about-eye-twitching-causes-condition-precautions-470264 <description><![CDATA[The underlying cause of eye twitching is the accidental misfiring of neurons responsible for stimulating the eyelid muscles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/everything-about-eye-twitching-causes-condition-precautions-470264</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 06:23:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Health Benefits Of Fermented Food; Ways To Include Them In Diet]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-benefits-of-fermented-food-ways-to-include-them-diet-470263 <description><![CDATA[Fermented foods are gaining popularity in recent years, not just for their flavor and aroma but for their nutritional value and health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-benefits-of-fermented-food-ways-to-include-them-diet-470263</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 04:14:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even 'Safe' Levels Of Air Pollution Can Negatively Impact Brain Development: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-safe-levels-of-air-pollution-can-negatively-impact-brain-development-study-470258 <description><![CDATA[The study emphasizes the need for regulators to consider brain health, along with respiratory and cardiometabolic health, while setting air quality standards.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-safe-levels-of-air-pollution-can-negatively-impact-brain-development-study-470258</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 03:04:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Poo Transplant' May Benefit People With Advanced Liver Disease; Clinical Trial Begins]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poo-transplant-may-benefit-people-with-advanced-liver-disease-clinical-trial-begins-470261 <description><![CDATA[The relatively unconventional way of treatment involves patients consuming capsules containing freeze-dried feces from a healthy donor. They contain microorganisms needed for a healthy digestive system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poo-transplant-may-benefit-people-with-advanced-liver-disease-clinical-trial-begins-470261</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 02:14:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cure For Baldness In Skin Moles? Scientists Discover New Mechanism For Stimulating Hair Growth]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cure-baldness-skin-moles-scientists-discover-new-mechanism-stimulate-hair-growth-470257 <description><![CDATA[According to the researchers, the mechanism by which aged or senescent cells in the skin moles make significant hair growth offers a road map for developing new molecular therapies to treat baldness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cure-baldness-skin-moles-scientists-discover-new-mechanism-stimulate-hair-growth-470257</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:15:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[E-Cigarette Sales Surge As Study Raises Concerns Regarding Youth Appeal]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-香烟-sales-surge-study-reports-concern-regarding-youth-appeal-470256 <description><![CDATA[There's been a significant increase in monthly e-cigarette sales in the U.S.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-香烟-sales-surge-study-reports-concern-regarding-youth-appeal-470256</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:54:06 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Spike Prompts CDC To Issue Warning For Summer Travel Season]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-spike-prompts-cdc-issue-warning-summer-travel-season-470255 <description><![CDATA[The public health agency emphasized the importance of receiving two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella (MMR) vaccine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-spike-prompts-cdc-issue-warning-summer-travel-season-470255</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:47:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Moderna's Updated COVID Vaccine Seeks FDA Authorization Ahead Of Fall Rollout]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/modern-updated-covid-vaccine-seeks-fda-authorization-ahead-fall-rollout-470253 <description><![CDATA[Moderna's new vaccine is specifically designed to target the current dominant strain, XBB.1.5.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/modern-updated-covid-vaccine-seeks-fda-authorization-ahead-fall-rollout-470253</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:43:57 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is The Mpox Vaccine Safe For Children?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pox-vaccine-safe-children-470250 <description><![CDATA[A study examined the safety of the JYNNEOS vaccine for mpox in children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pox-vaccine-safe-children-470250</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:39:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Human Brain Replays Past Events To Make Sense Of Present Experiences: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ human-brain-replays-past-events-make-sense-present-experiences-study-470248 <description><![CDATA[Researchers find that the human brain replays past events, even in non-spatial contexts, in a more complex manner than rodents.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ human-brain-replays-past-events-make-sense-present-experiences-study-470248</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 06:18:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[First Saliva-Based Pregnancy Tests: Everything To Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-saliva-based-pregnancy-tests-know-everything-470246 <description><![CDATA[Salistick detects pregnancy by identifying a hormone called human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG), which is present in the body of a pregnant person.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-saliva-based-pregnancy-tests-know-everything-470246</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:37:33 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>