<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Extreme Heat Straining Health Systems: WHO]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/extreme-heat-straining-health-systems-who-470548 <description><![CDATA[Experts have blamed the heatwaves on climate change, driven by the burning of fossil fuels releasing the greenhouse gas carbon dioxide into the atmosphere. The UN's WMO weather agency has said repeated high overnight temperatures are a particular health risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/extreme-heat-straining-health-systems-who-470548</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 06:53:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sydney's Former HIV Epicentre Close To Ending Transmission: Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sydneys-former-hiv-epicentre-close-ending-transmission-research-470547 <description><![CDATA[A study announced at the AIDS conference said people on antiretrovirals who have low but detectible levels of HIV have almost zero risk of sexually transmitting the virus to others.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sydneys-former-hiv-epicentre-close-ending-transmission-research-470547</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 06:51:23 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hiccup Hacks: 7 Quick Tips To Get Rid Of The Spasms]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/hiccup-hacks-7-quick-tips-get-rid-spasms-470544 <description><![CDATA[In case you are having a bad case of hiccups, try these simple remedies for an instant cure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hiccup-hacks-7-quick-tips-get-rid-spasms-470544</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 05:30:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Finding It Hard To Stop Nail Biting? Simple Habit Replacement Techniques Could Be Helpful]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/finding-it-hard-stop-nail-biting-simple-habit-replacement-techniques-could-helpful-470539 <description><![CDATA[A new study suggests simple habit-replacement techniques to help people with hard-to-curb repetitive behaviors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/finding-it-hard-stop-nail-biting-simple-habit-replacement-techniques-could-helpful-470539</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 03:52:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Not Just Mother's, But Father's Mental Illness Also Increases Chances Of Preterm Birth: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-just-mothers-fathers-mental-illness-also-increases-chances-preterm-birth-study-470536 <description><![CDATA[The chance of preterm births was highest in cases where both parents had mental health conditions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-just-mothers-fathers-mental-illness-also-increases-chances-preterm-birth-study-470536</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 02:07:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dahlia Flower For Fighting Diabetes? Study Says Petal Extract Helps In Blood Sugar Control]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dahlia-flower-fighting-diabetes-study-says-petal-extract-helps-blood-sugar-control-470533 <description><![CDATA[According to researchers, the petal extract from the dahlia flower showed considerable improvement in blood sugar regulation in people with prediabetes and type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dahlia-flower-fighting-diabetes-study-says-petal-extract-helps-blood-sugar-control-470533</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:47:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Espresso Is More Than A Kickstarter; Study Says It Can Reduce Alzheimer's Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/espresso-more-kickstarter-study-says-it-can-reduce-alzheimers-risk-470532 <description><![CDATA[Researchers from the University of Verona in Italy found that a complete extract of espresso can inhibit tau protein aggregation associated with Alzheimer's.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/espresso-more-kickstarter-study-says-it-can-reduce-alzheimers-risk-470532</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:14:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breast Cancer Treatment May Speed Up Aging; Radiation Therapy Has Strongest Association: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-treatment-may-speed-aging-radiation-therapy-has-strongest-association-study-470531 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say women who have been treated for breast cancer may experience faster aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-treatment-may-speed-aging-radiation-therapy-has-strongest-association-study-470531</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 03:00:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Do Some People Never Get COVID Symptoms? Study Says Gene Mutation Makes Them Super Dodgers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-do-some-people-never-get-covid-symptoms-study-says-gene-mutation-makes-them-super-dodgers-470530 <description><![CDATA[Researchers from the University of California-San Francisco have found the first evidence for a genetic basis for asymptomatic SARS-CoV-2.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-do-some-people-never-get-covid-symptoms-study-says-gene-mutation-makes-them-super-dodgers-470530</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 01:12:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthcare Without Borders: How Dr. Germaine Spencer is Pioneering the Future of Medical Tourism]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthcare-without-borders-how-dr-germaine-spencer-pioneering-future-medical-tourism-470528 <description><![CDATA[In a world that's getting smaller and more connected than ever, healthcare too is crossing borders, fuelled by the rising trend of medical tourism.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthcare-without-borders-how-dr-germaine-spencer-pioneering-future-medical-tourism-470528</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 12:38:17 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tips To Stay Moving While Working From Home]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tips-stay-moving-while-working-home-470526 <description><![CDATA[Working from home is great, but the lack of movement can leave you feeling sluggish and unmotivated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tips-stay-moving-while-working-home-470526</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 12:35:35 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>