<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh</language><item><title><![CDATA[Got A Test Tomorrow? Take A Brisk Walk Now To Boost Your Memory]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-test-tomorrow-take-brisk-walk-now-boost-your-memory-472803 <description><![CDATA[A new study reveals that moderate to vigorous physical activity on one day can improve your performance on memory tests the following day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-test-tomorrow-take-brisk-walk-now-boost-your-memory-472803</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Dec 2024 04:08:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[From Night Sweats To Changes In Bowel Habits: Colorectal Cancer Survivor Reflects On Red Flags He Overlooked]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-sweats-changes-bowel-habits-colorectal-cancer-survivor-reflects-red-flags-he-overlooked-472802 <description><![CDATA["Don't risk your life by waiting to see a doc. Early screening could save you and your family," Joe Faratzis, a colorectal cancer survivor said sharing his story on TikTok.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-sweats-changes-bowel-habits-colorectal-cancer-survivor-reflects-red-flags-he-overlooked-472802</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Dec 2024 02:22:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Reverse The Clock: This Simple Exercise Thrice A Week Can Make You 8 Years Younger]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reverse-clock-this-simple-exercise-thrice-week-can-make-you-8-years-younger-472799 <description><![CDATA[The weights you lift at the gym might be lifting years off your biological age too, suggests a recent study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reverse-clock-this-simple-exercise-thrice-week-can-make-you-8-years-younger-472799</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:25:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Understanding Different Types Of Coughs: Remedies And When To Seek Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/understanding- Different-types-coughs-remedies-when-seek-treatment-472795 <description><![CDATA[It's important to know when to manage a cough at home and when to seek professional care.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/understanding- Different-types-coughs-remedies-when-seek-treatment-472795</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Dec 2024 04:33:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Not All Sweets Do Harm: Here's How Different Sugar Sources Affect Cardiovascular Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-all-sweets-do-harm-heres-how- Different-sugar-sources-affect-cardioangio-health-472792 <description><![CDATA[A recent study found that while fizzy drinks significantly raise your risk of stroke, heart failure, and atrial fibrillation, occasional sweet treats may not do much harm.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-all-sweets-do-harm-heres-how- Different-sugar-sources-affect-cardioangio-health-472792</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Dec 2024 02:29:30 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Somebody Has To Find Out': Trump Says RFK Jr. Will Reexamine Disproved Link Between Childhood Vaccines And Autism]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/somebody-has-find-out-trump-says-rfk-jr-will-reexamine-disproved-link- Between-childhood-472789 <description><![CDATA[President-elect Donald Trump also stated that he is "open to anything," hinting at the possibility of eliminating vaccines to address the rising autism cases in the United States over recent decades.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/somebody-has-find-out-trump-says-rfk-jr-will-reexamine-disproved-link- Between-childhood-472789</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Dec 2024 01:06:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Americans Share Devastating Healthcare Horror Stories in Wake of UnitedHealthcare CEO Assassination]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-share-devastating-healthcare-horror-stories-wake-unitedhealthcare-ceo-assassination-472787 <description><![CDATA[Social media users have been sharing their negative experiences with healthcare following the death of UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson in New York earlier this week.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-share-devastating-healthcare-horror-stories-wake-unitedhealthcare-ceo-assassination-472787</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:44:42 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Keep Kids Safe From 'Granny's Purse Syndrome': Pediatrician's Tips To Avoid Accidental Poisoning]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keep-kids-safe-grannys-purse-syndrome-pediatricians-tips-avoid-accidental-poisoning-472785 <description><![CDATA[A Florida-based pediatric emergency physician took to TikTok to warn parents about an unexpected holiday hazard she calls "Granny's purse syndrome", responsible for 20% of accidental poisoning in kids.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keep-kids-safe-grannys-purse-syndrome-pediatricians-tips-avoid-accidental-poisoning-472785</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Dec 2024 05:22:42 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Larger Waistline May Not Be Always Bad: Know Ideal Waist Size If You've Diabetes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/larger-waistline-may-not-always-bad-know-ideal-waist-size-if-youve-diabetes-472784 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that, in some cases, a larger waist circumference might actually help reduce mortality risk for people with diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/larger-waistline-may-not-always-bad-know-ideal-waist-size-if-youve-diabetes-472784</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:47:42 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can't Say No To Sugary Treats? 10 Ways To Curb Your Sugar Cravings]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cant-say-no-sugary-treats-10-ways-curb-your-sugar-cravings-472782 <description><![CDATA[Craving for sugar is perfectly normal. But it's important to know that your sugar craving is not always because the body needs food or you are hungry.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cant-say-no-sugary-treats-10-ways-curb-your-sugar-cravings-472782</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:48:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthem Blue Cross Cancels Controversial Plan to Limit Anesthesia Coverage After Overwhelming Public Outcry]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anthem-blue-cross-cancels-controversial-plan-limit-anesthesia-coverage-after-overwhelming-public-472779 <description><![CDATA[Anthem Blue Cross Blue Shield will not follow through with its proposed policy that would have limited coverage for anesthesia during surgeries and procedures.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anthem-blue-cross-cancels-controversial-plan-limit-anesthesia-coverage-after-overwhelming-public-472779</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:28:35 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>