<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Screen Use In 9- And 10-Year-Olds Elevates Risk Of Depression, Anxiety, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/screen-use-9-10-year-olds-elevates-risk-depression-anxiety-study-says-472514 <description><![CDATA[The study found that each additional hour of screen time correlated with a 10% increase in depressive symptoms, a 7% increase in conduct symptoms, and a 6% increase in somatic symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/screen-use-9-10-year-olds-elevates-risk-depression-anxiety-study-says-472514</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Oct 2024 04:13:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Warns: These Incorrect Arm Positions Often Lead To Overestimated Blood Pressure Readings]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-warns-these-in Correct-arm-positions-often-lead-overestimated-blood-Pressure-readings-472511 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that incorrect positioning often leads to inflated blood pressure readings, potentially misdiagnosing millions of Americans with hypertension.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-warns-these-in Correct-arm-positions-often-lead-overestimated-blood-Pressure-readings-472511</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Oct 2024 02:43:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eggs Or Toast? Breakfast For Weight Loss Depends On Your Gender]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eggs-toast-breakfast-weight-loss-depends-your-gender-472510 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered that when it comes to breaking down meals after fasting for hours, men respond better to carbs, while women manage fat more effectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eggs-toast-breakfast-weight-loss-depends-your-gender-472510</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Oct 2024 01:16:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fall-Proof Your Health: Essential Household Items For A Wellness Boost]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fall-proof-your-health-essential-household-items-wellness-boost-472503 <description><![CDATA[Simple practices such as dressing for the weather, using a humidifier, and taking time to de-stress will enhance your body's resilience during the fall season]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fall-proof-your-health-essential-household-items-wellness-boost-472503</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:03:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Eggs Prevent Dementia? Here's How Many To Eat For Beneficial Effects]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-eggs-prevent-dementia-heres-how-many-eat-beneficial-effects-472507 <description><![CDATA[Eating more than two eggs per day, or not consuming eggs at all, will not help with dementia risk, the study suggests]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-eggs-prevent-dementia-heres-how-many-eat-beneficial-effects-472507</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Oct 2024 05:12:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling With Sleep? Study Says Forever Chemicals Could Be Factor Among Young Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-sleep-study-says-forever-chemicals-could-factor-among-young-adults-472506 <description><![CDATA[The study found that higher levels of four specific types of PFAs  namely PFDA, PFHxS, PFOA, and PFOS could be linked to worsened sleep in young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-sleep-study-says-forever-chemicals-could-factor-among-young-adults-472506</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Oct 2024 03:25:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Flu Shots Less Effective In South: Why CDC Urges Vaccination Despite Similar U.S. Forecast]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-shots-less- effective-south-why-cdc-urges-vaccination-despite-similar-us-forecast-472504 <description><![CDATA[The flu shot reduced the risk of hospitalization among high-risk groups by 35% in five South American countries, Argentina, Brazil, Chile, Paraguay, and Uruguay, according to the interim vaccine effectiveness report by the CDC.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-shots-less- effective-south-why-cdc-urges-vaccination-despite-similar-us-forecast-472504</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Oct 2024 01:51:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Being Overweight Raises Pregnancy Complications Regardless Of Women's Country Of Birth: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-overweight-raises-pregnancy-complications-regardless-womens-country-birth-study-472501 <description><![CDATA[The findings suggest that promoting a healthy weight has the potential to prevent pregnancy complications for all women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-overweight-raises-pregnancy-complications-regardless-womens-country-birth-study-472501</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:54:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Promising Alzheimer's Drug May Prevent Tau Build-Up, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-promising-alzheimers-drug-may-prevent-tau-build-study-finds-472500 <description><![CDATA[The latest drug, RI-AG03, is a peptide inhibitor that blocks tau-build-up, acting at two regions of the protein, preventing it from sticking together.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-promising-alzheimers-drug-may-prevent-tau-build-study-finds-472500</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Oct 2024 03:56:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Warns Of Dangerous Counterfeit Drugs From Online Pharmacies, Highlighting Overdose Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-dangerous-counterfeit-drugs-online-pharmacies-highlighting-overdose-risk-472497 <description><![CDATA[The warning follows last week's U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) indictment of illegal online pharmacies selling counterfeit prescription pills laced with fentanyl and methamphetamine to tens of thousands of people in the U.S., leading to at least nine deaths.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-dangerous-counterfeit-drugs-online-pharmacies-highlighting-overdose-risk-472497</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Oct 2024 01:58:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Over Half Of Americans Follow Pro-Inflammatory Diets, Study Says: Here's What To Eat Instead]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-half-americans-follow-pro-炎症-diets-study-says-heres-what-eat-instead-472496 <description><![CDATA[According to the study, 57% of participants followed pro-inflammatory diets, while only 34% maintained anti-inflammatory diets.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-half-americans-follow-pro-炎症-diets-study-says-heres-what-eat-instead-472496</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Oct 2024 05:12:31 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>