<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Exercise For Treating Depression? Researchers Identify Activities That May Be As Effective As Therapy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-treating-depression-researchers-identify-activities-that-may- effective-therapy-471405 <description><![CDATA[Researchers noted that the intensity of the activity was directly linked to the extent of improvement in depression symptoms. However, certain low-intensity activities also had significant benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-treating-depression-researchers-identify-activities-that-may- effective-therapy-471405</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:16:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Childhood Bullying Can Increase Mental Health Risk By Three Times: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-thirdfold-increase-mental-health-risk-linked-childhood-bullying-471403 <description><![CDATA[Children who get bullied by the age of 11 develop strong interpersonal distrust as they grow, and are at threefold risk of developing mental health issues by their late teens, a study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-thirdfold-increase-mental-health-risk-linked-childhood-bullying-471403</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:59:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alaskapox: Know All About The Rare Virus That Claimed A Life In US]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alaskapox-know-all-about-rare-virus-officials-report-first-fatality-it-471401 <description><![CDATA[An elderly man has succumbed to a severe case of Alaskapox, marking the first human fatality linked to this recently identified virus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alaskapox-know-all-about-rare-virus-officials-report-first-fatality-it-471401</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Feb 2024 04:08:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Reduced Risk Of COVID-19, Hospitalization In Older Adults Who Exercised Before Pandemic: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reduced-risk-covid-19-hospitalization-older-adults-who-exercising-before-pandemic-study-471399 <description><![CDATA[Senior adults who followed recommended exercise guidelines before the pandemic had significantly lower odds of being infected or getting hospitalized from COVID-19 compared to those who did not follow guidelines, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reduced-risk-covid-19-hospitalization-older-adults-who-exercising-before-pandemic-study-471399</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Feb 2024 02:58:21 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smelling Familiar Scents May Help Depressed Individuals In Their Recovery: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smelling-familiar-scents-may-help-depressed-individuals-their-recovery-study-471398 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that familiar scents could be more powerful than words in bringing depressed people out of negative thoughts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smelling-familiar-scents-may-help-depressed-individuals-their-recovery-study-471398</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:53:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exercise Helps, But Cannot Eliminate Cardiovascular Risk Linked To Sugary Sodas: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-helps-cannot-eliminate-cardioangio-risk-linked-sugary-sodas-study-471397 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that even if a person meets the recommended 150 minutes of weekly physical activity, it may not be sufficient to guard them against the cardiovascular risk associated with sugary drinks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-helps-cannot-eliminate-cardioangio-risk-linked-sugary-sodas-study-471397</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:16:26 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Simple Blood Test Can Predict Risk Of Heart Attack In Next 6 Months]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-blood-test-can-predict-risk-heart-attack-next-6-months-471396 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found that a simple blood test, when coupled with an online tool, can predict a person's risk of a heart attack within the next six months.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-blood-test-can-predict-risk-heart-attack-next-6-months-471396</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:15:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salt Substitute For Hypertension: Study Says It Reduces Low, High Blood Pressure Episodes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salt-substitute-hypertension-study-says-it-reduces-low-high-blood-Pressure-episodes-471395 <description><![CDATA[Replacing regular salt with a potassium-enriched alternative reduces the chances of high and low blood pressure episodes in people with hypertension, according to findings of a recent study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salt-substitute-hypertension-study-says-it-reduces-low-high-blood-Pressure-episodes-471395</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 01:09:52 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unlock Excellence In Fitness: A Dive Into Huge Supplements' Premium Formulas]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/unlock-excellence-fitness-dive-huge-supplements-premium-formulas-471252 <description><![CDATA[Explore the world of Huge Supplements and elevate your fitness to new heights.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/unlock-excellence-fitness-dive-huge-supplements-premium-formulas-471252</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Feb 2024 13:02:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smokers Who Quit Before 40 Have Similar Life-Expectancy Of Non-smokers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smokers-who-quit-before-age-40-have-similar-life-expectancy-non-smokers-study-471393 <description><![CDATA[The study also revealed that individuals who quit smoking, regardless of age, can achieve a life expectancy similar to non-smokers within approximately 10 years after quitting, and nearly half of this benefit can be noticed within just three years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smokers-who-quit-before-age-40-have-similar-life-expectancy-non-smokers-study-471393</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Feb 2024 03:11:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Oregon Reports Human Plague Linked To Pet Cat: Learn All About The Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/oregon-reports- human-plague-linked-pet-cat-learn-all-about-disease-471394 <description><![CDATA[The officials noted that plague occurrence is rare in Oregon, with the last case reported in 2015.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/oregon-reports- human-plague-linked-pet-cat-learn-all-about-disease-471394</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:29:08 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>