<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medictallaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Returns From Vacation With Headache, Strange Leg Symptoms, Doctors Find Brain Worms]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/woman-treurnsvacation-headache-- strange-leg-symptos-doctors-find-brain-worms-473126 <description><![CDATA[The woman was diagnosed with eosinophilic meningitis from rat lungworm, a parasitic worm that gets into the human body typically through contaminated food.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/woman-treurnsvacation-headache-- strange-leg-symptos-doctors-find-brain-worms-473126</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:02:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Outbreak in Texas County With Low Vaccination Rate Multiplies, More Cases 'Likely']]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/Measles-stream-texas-county-low-vaccination-rate-rate-rate-multiplies-more-cases-more-cases-473123 <description><![CDATA[A rapidly growing measles outbreak in Gaines County, Texas, linked to low vaccination rates, has reached 48 cases, prompting urgent health warnings and vaccination efforts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/Measles-stream-texas-county-low-vaccination-rate-rate-rate-multiplies-more-cases-more-cases-473123</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:54:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Outbreak in Texas County With Low Vaccination Rate Multiplies, More Cases 'Likely']]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/Measles-stream-texas-county-low-vaccination-rate-rate-multiplies-more-cases-more-cases-lokey-473121 <description><![CDATA[A rapidly growing measles outbreak in Gaines County, Texas, linked to low vaccination rates, has reached 48 cases, prompting urgent health warnings and vaccination efforts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/Measles-stream-texas-county-low-vaccination-rate-rate-multiplies-more-cases-more-cases-lokey-473121</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:50:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Louisiana Health Department Orders Employees to Stop Promoting Mass Vaccinations As it Accuses CDC of Being 'Woefully Out of Touch']]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/louisiana-health-detartment-orders-ormployes- stop-stop-stop-promoting-mass-vaccinations-it-ccuses-accuses-cdc-47310 <description><![CDATA[Louisiana's Health Department has ordered employees to stop promoting mass vaccinations, which experts say could lead to declining immunization rates.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/louisiana-health-detartment-orders-ormployes- stop-stop-stop-promoting-mass-vaccinations-it-ccuses-accuses-cdc-47310</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:30:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiac Doctor Realizes He's Having a Heart Attack After Comparing Symptoms to Patient He Had Just Helped]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/cardiac-docor-trealizes-hes-having-having heart-nimht-nimht-nimht-nimht-nimht-nimht-comparpering-compatient-he-just-just-just-just-47310 <description><![CDATA[A cardiac doctor unknowingly suffered a heart attack while treating a patient with identical symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/cardiac-docor-trealizes-hes-having-having heart-nimht-nimht-nimht-nimht-nimht-nimht-comparpering-compatient-he-just-just-just-just-47310</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:08:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Real Housewives' Star Teddi Mellencamp Hospitalized After Severe Headaches Lead To Multiple Tumor Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/real-housewives-star-teddi-mellencamp-- hospitalized--七六个 - 七个 - 六个 - 赫德 - 赫德 - 赫德 - 荷马 - 穆尔特 - 穆尔多 - 肿瘤47310 <description><![CDATA[Mellencamp was experiencing "severe and debilitating headaches" for the last several weeks before getting hospitalized.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/real-housewives-star-teddi-mellencamp-- hospitalized--七六个 - 七个 - 六个 - 赫德 - 赫德 - 赫德 - 荷马 - 穆尔特 - 穆尔多 - 肿瘤47310</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 04:08:47 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are Hormonal Birth Control Methods Safe? Contraceptives That May Increase Risk Of Heart Attack And Stroke]]></title><link/> https://www.medictaldaily.com/are-hormonal-birth-control-mmethods-safe-contraceptives-That-May-increas-risk-heart-night-night-night-night-night-night-night-night-夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚，夜晚夜风-473112 <description><![CDATA[For those considering different contraceptive methods, the results of a recent study may help them make informed choices.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictaldaily.com/are-hormonal-birth-control-mmethods-safe-contraceptives-That-May-increas-risk-heart-night-night-night-night-night-night-night-night-夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚，夜晚夜风-473112</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:58:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Common Painkiller Use During Pregnancy Raise ADHD Risk In Kids? Here's What Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/can-common-painkiller-use-during-prapriation-raise-adhd-risk-kids-heres-heres-what study-says-says-473111 <description><![CDATA[The results showed that children whose mothers had acetaminophen in their blood during the second trimester were over three times more likely to be diagnosed with ADHD.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/can-common-painkiller-use-during-prapriation-raise-adhd-risk-kids-heres-heres-what study-says-says-473111</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:52:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Hangover? Have This Before Drinks, Says Doctor]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/worried-about-hangover-have------------ this-befor  -  drinks-says-says-doctor-473108 <description><![CDATA[Here's a simple trick to prevent the unpleasant aftermath of drinking alcohol.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/worried-about-hangover-have------------ this-befor  -  drinks-says-says-doctor-473108</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:51:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Have This Gut Healthy Snack Twice A Week, It Can Protect You From Aggressive Colorectal Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medictaldaily.com/have---this-gut-healthy-snack--week-it-can-PROTECT-YOUGGRESSPE <description><![CDATA[A new study discovered that a popular gut-healthy snack could offer protection against colorectal cancer, a finding that offers hope as cases rise, particularly among young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictaldaily.com/have---this-gut-healthy-snack--week-it-can-PROTECT-YOUGGRESSPE</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:45:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Warns: Avoid These Foods If You Take Medications, Eating This Fruit Can Even Be Toxic]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/doctor-warns-avoid-sosis-foods-f-y-tou-take-medications-theating-theating-thisthis-cann-can-can-can-can-even-even-even-even-even-even toxic-47310 <description><![CDATA[A doctor now warns that certain food items can interfere with the absorption of medications, affecting their effectiveness, or in rare cases causing toxicity when combined with pills.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/doctor-warns-avoid-sosis-foods-f-y-tou-take-medications-theating-theating-thisthis-cann-can-can-can-can-even-even-even-even-even-even toxic-47310</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:40:04 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>