<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[HPV Infection Affects Male Fertility, High-Risk Strains Linked To Sperm Death, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hpv-infection-affects-male-fertility-high-risk-strains-linked-sperm-death-says-study-472191 <description><![CDATA[The study analyzed the impact of both high-risk and low-risk HPV strains on male fertility and found that high-risk strains are more prevalent and pose a greater threat to sperm quality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hpv-infection-affects-male-fertility-high-risk-strains-linked-sperm-death-says-study-472191</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Aug 2024 03:32:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[EEE In Massachusetts: Rare Deadly Mosquito-Borne Illness Puts Towns Under Vigilance]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eee-massachusetts-rare-deadly-mosquito-borne-illness-puts-towns-under-vigilance-472190 <description><![CDATA[Eastern equine encephalitis (EEE) typically spreads through mosquito bites and has no vaccines or drugs for prevention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eee-massachusetts-rare-deadly-mosquito-borne-illness-puts-towns-under-vigilance-472190</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Aug 2024 01:33:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Milk Thistle Supplements: Discover the Top Choices For Liver Health And Detoxification]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-milk-thistle-supplements-discover-top-choices-liver-health-detoxification-472175 <description><![CDATA[Milk thistle, renowned for liver support, detoxification, and skin health, is backed by scientific research. Studies highlight its protective and regenerative effects on the liver, enhance detoxification, and provide antioxidant benefits for skin health. Choosing a high-quality supplement can support overall wellness effectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-milk-thistle-supplements-discover-top-choices-liver-health-detoxification-472175</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:33:39 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Biotin Supplements For Healthier Hair, Skin And Nails]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-biotin-supplements-healthier-hair-skin-nails-472173 <description><![CDATA[Biotin, or Vitamin B7, is essential for healthy hair, skin, and nails, aiding in the metabolism of fats and proteins. A deficiency can cause thinning hair and brittle nails. Supplements can enhance these benefits, and incorporating biotin into your routine, along with a balanced diet, supports overall beauty and health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-biotin-supplements-healthier-hair-skin-nails-472173</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:15:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Tyrosine Supplements: Improve Focus, Relieve Stress With These Top Picks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tyrosine-supplements-improve-focus-relieve-stress-these-top-picks-472170 <description><![CDATA[Tyrosine, also known as L-tyrosine, is an amino acid that serves as a building block for all proteins in the body. It is synthesized when the body obtains sufficient amounts of another essential amino acid, phenylalanine. Tyrosine is crucial for various bodily functions, including neurotransmission and hormone regulation, and is commonly used as a supplement to boost mood-enhancing dopamine, reduce stress, and improve focus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tyrosine-supplements-improve-focus-relieve-stress-these-top-picks-472170</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:12:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Updated COVID mRNA Vaccines Get FDA Approval: Here's What To Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/updated-covid-mrna-vaccines-get-fda-approval-heres-what-know-472180 <description><![CDATA[The updated COVID shots from Pfizer-BioNTech and Moderna target the current KP.2 strain of SARS-CoV-2, a descendant of the highly contagious Omicron subvariant JN.1.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/updated-covid-mrna-vaccines-get-fda-approval-heres-what-know-472180</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 03:13:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hot Flashes And Night Sweats? Experimental Non-Hormonal Pill Offers Hope For Menopause Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hot-flashes-night-sweats-experimental-non-hormonal-pill-offers-hope-menopause-relief-472177 <description><![CDATA[In a phase 3 clinical trial, researchers have found that the new non-hormonal drug, Elinzanetant, could reduce the frequency and severity of vasomotor symptoms in menopausal women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hot-flashes-night-sweats-experimental-non-hormonal-pill-offers-hope-menopause-relief-472177</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 01:18:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Importance of Early Detection in Preventive Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/importance-early-detection-preventive-health-472172 <description><![CDATA[Catching potential health issues early can make a world of difference in overall well-being and quality of life down the road.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/importance-early-detection-preventive-health-472172</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 10:42:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Selenium Supplements And Why You Must Include Them In Your Diet]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-selenium-supplements-why-you-must-include-them-your-diet-472153 <description><![CDATA[Selenium is a trace mineral which essentially implies that our body needs it only in small amounts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-selenium-supplements-why-you-must-include-them-your-diet-472153</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 09:17:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Melatonin Supplements: The Top Picks for Better Sleep and Overall Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-melatonin-supplements-top-picks-better-sleep-overall-health-472155 <description><![CDATA[Melatonin supplements are natural aids that help regulate sleep cycles, improve sleep quality, and support overall well-being. Ideal for those struggling with insomnia, jet lag, or irregular sleep patterns, these supplements are a powerful tool for achieving restful sleep and waking up refreshed. Choose wisely to enhance your sleep health effectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-melatonin-supplements-top-picks-better-sleep-overall-health-472155</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 09:16:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Higher Incidence Of Mental Illness After Severe COVID In Unvaccinated Adults, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-incidence-mental-illness-after-severe-covid-unvaccinated-adults-says-study-472168 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that elevated incidence of mental illnesses after COVID-19 infection was mainly observed among cases where there were hospitalizations. The risk remained high for up to a year following severe COVID-19 in unvaccinated individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-incidence-mental-illness-after-severe-covid-unvaccinated-adults-says-study-472168</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 04:14:25 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>