<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>看</language><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Eosinophilic Meningitis? Here's Everything About The Rare Infection That Spreads From Rodents]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-eosinophilic-meningitis-here-is-everything-about-rare-infection-that-spreads-rodents-470894 <description><![CDATA[Angiostrongylus cantonensis or rat lungworm worm causes a rare form of infection known as eosinophilic meningitis, which can cause paralysis and even death in severe cases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-eosinophilic-meningitis-here-is-everything-about-rare-infection-that-spreads-rodents-470894</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 08:17:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Almost 10% Of Adults In US Live With Chronic Conditions Like Diabetes, Heart Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/almost-10-adults-us-living-chronic-conditions-like-diabetic-heart-disease-study-470893 <description><![CDATA[Approximately one in 10 adults in the U.S. suffer from multiple cardiac, renal or metabolic conditions. The risk also increases with age as one in three adults aged 65 or older had a CRM condition, whereas one in four had overlapping conditions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/almost-10-adults-us-living-chronic-conditions-like-diabetic-heart-disease-study-470893</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:56:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nail Abnormalities: Here's What Your Nails Say About Your Health]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/nail-abnormalities-here-what-your-nails-say-about-your-health-470890 <description><![CDATA[Changes in your fingernails can be worrisome and may be a result of more serious underlying health issues.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nail-abnormalities-here-what-your-nails-say-about-your-health-470890</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:11:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Creatine Supplementation Alleviate Long COVID Symptoms? New Research Says Yes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-creatine-supplementation-alleviate-long-covid-symptoms-new-research-says-yes-4 <description><![CDATA[It was observed that individuals who took dietary creatine for three months experienced significant improvement in their long COVID symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-creatine-supplementation-alleviate-long-covid-symptoms-new-research-says-yes-4</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:27:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Yoga As Complementary Therapy Improves Quality Of Life, Cardiovascular Function In Heart Failure Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yoga-complementary-therapy-improves-quality-of-life-cardioangio-function-heart-failure-470887 <description><![CDATA[Researchers saw improvements in endurance, strength, balance, symptom stability, quality of life and cardiovascular function in the group that used yoga as a complementary therapy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yoga-complementary-therapy-improves-quality-of-life-cardioangio-function-heart-failure-470887</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Sep 2023 04:01:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is HMPV? Here's All About The Lesser-Known Respiratory Illness Spreading In Australia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-hmpv-here-is-all-about-lesser-known-respiratory-illness-spreading-australia-470886 <description><![CDATA[Australia's southeastern state of New South Wales has reported thousands of cases of HMPV infections since the beginning of the month.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-hmpv-here-is-all-about-lesser-known-respiratory-illness-spreading-australia-470886</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Sep 2023 02:26:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Rabies Day: How Infection Gets Transmitted, What Symptoms And Preventive Measures Are]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-rabies-day-how-infection-gets-transmission-what-symptoms-preventive-measures-are-470883 <description><![CDATA[Rabies is nearly fatal once the symptoms appear, but it is 100% preventable through medical care.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-rabies-day-how-infection-gets-transmission-what-symptoms-preventive-measures-are-470883</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:47:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Physically Demanding Jobs Could Increase Risk Of Cognitive Impairment, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/physically-demanding-jobs-could-increase-risk-of-cognitive-impairment-study-finds-470882 <description><![CDATA[Individuals in occupations with an intermediate level of physical activity are at an elevated risk of experiencing mild cognitive impairment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/physically-demanding-jobs-could-increase-risk-of-cognitive-impairment-study-finds-470882</guid><pubDate> Tue, 26 Sep 2023 11:34:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[US Households To Receive Free At-Home COVID-19 Tests As Cases Spike: Here's How To Order Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/us-households-receive-free-home-covid-19-tests-cases-spike-here-how-to-order-them-470879 <description><![CDATA[Every household in the United States will be able place an order of four free COVID-⁠19 rapid antigen tests, the Department of Health and Human Services announced.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/us-households-receive-free-home-covid-19-tests-cases-spike-here-how-to-order-them-470879</guid><pubDate> Tue, 26 Sep 2023 08:53:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exposure To Blue Light From Smartphones, Tablets May Trigger Early Onset Of Puberty]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-blue-light-smartphones-tablets-may-trigger-early-onset-puberty-470876 <description><![CDATA[The findings of a mice study suggest that exposure to blue light from smartphones and tablets may alter hormone levels and lead to early puberty.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-blue-light-smartphones-tablets-may-trigger-early-onset-puberty-470876</guid><pubDate> Tue, 26 Sep 2023 05:57:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dengue Outbreak In Jamaica: Know Symptoms, Steps To Prevent The Mosquito-Borne Illness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dengue-outbreak-jamaica-know-symptoms-steps-prevent-mosquito-borne-illness-470875 <description><![CDATA[Jamaica has reported 565 cases of dengue. Although there are no confirmed dengue-related deaths in the country so far, six deaths are being investigated, health officials said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dengue-outbreak-jamaica-know-symptoms-steps-prevent-mosquito-borne-illness-470875</guid><pubDate> Tue, 26 Sep 2023 03:52:37 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>