<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA[Chinese Drugmakers Scramble To Address Skyrocketing Demand For Ozempic]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chinese-drugmakers-scramble-address-skyrocketing-demand-ozempic-470045 <description><![CDATA[Ozempic is in shortage in China due to the frenzy over its rapid weight loss effects.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chinese-drugmakers-scramble-address-skyrocketing-demand-ozempic-470045</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:57:51 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Strep A Cases On The Rise, UMMC Experts Warn]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strep-cases-rise-ummc-experts-warn-470044 <description><![CDATA[Cases of Strep A have been increasing across the U.S. and worldwide.]]></description><guid>https://www.medicaldaily.com/strep-cases-rise-ummc-experts-warn-470044</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:47:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Warns Of Higher Risk Of Mpox Outbreak In Tampa Bay]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-higher-risk-mpox-outbreak-tampa-bay-470043<description><![CDATA[There's a 50% chance of an uptick in cases this year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-higher-risk-mpox-outbreak-tampa-bay-470043</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:35:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Studies Discover Potential Treatment Pathways For Long COVID]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-studies-discover-potential-treatment-pathways-long-covid-470041 <description><![CDATA[Researchers may have mapped out new treatment pathways for chronic COVID-19.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-studies-discover-potential-treatment-pathways-long-covid-470041</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:27:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 10 Must-Have Skincare Products for Youthful and Radiant Skin]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-must-have-skincare-products-youthful-radiant-skin-470036 <description><![CDATA[Discover the ultimate collection of essential skincare products to achieve and maintain youthful, radiant skin with our expert-curated list of the top 10 must-haves.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-must-have-skincare-products-youthful-radiant-skin-470036</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 10:24:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 11 Must-Try Food and Drink Trends for a Healthier Lifestyle]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-11-must-try-food-drink-trends-healthier-lifestyle-470039 <description><![CDATA[Embrace a healthier lifestyle and indulge in the latest food and drink trends with our handpicked selection of the top 11 must-try options that will tantalize your taste buds and nourish your body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-11-must-try-food-drink-trends-healthier-lifestyle-470039</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 10:23:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Benefits Of Chia Seeds, And Why It Is Important To Soak Them Before Consumption]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-chia-seeds-why-it-important-soak-them-before-consumption-470033 <description><![CDATA[Soaking chia seeds aids digestion and nutrient absorption while consuming them dry can cause esophageal blockages.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-chia-seeds-why-it-important-soak-them-before-consumption-470033</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:14:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Personalized Bi-Sensory Stimulation Shows Promise In Treating Tinnitus, Study Shows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/personalized-bi-sensory-stimulation-shows-promise-treating-tinnitus-study-shows-470030 <description><![CDATA[Tinnitus is described as a ringing in the ears or sensing a constant hissing sound in the ear.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/personalized-bi-sensory-stimulation-shows-promise-treating-tinnitus-study-shows-470030</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:30:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Food Safety Day: Tips To Prevent Contamination]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-food-safety-day-tips-prevent-contamination-470029 <description><![CDATA[The theme of this year's World Food Safety Day is "Food standards save lives."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-food-safety-day-tips-prevent-contamination-470029</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:44:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Brisk Walking, Yoga Can Cut Risk Of Cancer Relapse, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brisk-walking-yoga-can-cut-risk-cancer-relapse-study-finds-470026 <description><![CDATA[Being physically active lowers the mortality risk in cancer patients, with regular walks significantly improving the chances of survival.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brisk-walking-yoga-can-cut-risk-cancer-relapse-study-finds-470026</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:27:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Glass Of Beetroot Juice A Day May Reduce Heart Attack Risk In Angina Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/glass-beetroot-juice-day-may-reduce-heart-attack-risk-angina-patients-470028 <description><![CDATA[Trials showed that when angina patients drank beetroot juice daily, the risk of heart attack or the need to repeat the stent procedure was reduced to 7.5%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/glass-beetroot-juice-day-may-reduce-heart-attack-risk-angina-patients-470028</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 02:20:04 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>