<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Step Into The Ring: Patella Knee Brace Vs Other Alternatives In the Arthritis Showdown]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/step-ring-patella-knee-brace-vs-other-alternatives-arthritis-showdown-470310 <description><![CDATA[Explore the showdown between the patella knee brace and alternative options in the realm of arthritis management, helping you make an informed decision on stepping into the ring for optimal knee support.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/step-ring-patella-knee-brace-vs-other-alternatives-arthritis-showdown-470310</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 23:55:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How To Relieve Knee Pain And Boost Performance With A Patellar Support Strap: A Step-By-Step Guide]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-relieve-knee-pain-boost-performance-patellar-support-strap-step-step-guide-470306 <description><![CDATA[Discover effective strategies to alleviate knee pain and enhance performance using a step-by-step guide featuring the utilization of a patellar support strap.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-relieve-knee-pain-boost-performance-patellar-support-strap-step-step-guide-470306</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 23:53:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Maximize Stability And Recovery: A Comprehensive Guide On Using A Knee Brace For Optimal Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maximize-stability-recovery-compressive-guide-using-knee-brace-optimal-support-470352 <description><![CDATA[Unlock the potential for enhanced stability and accelerated recovery with a comprehensive guide that explores the optimal utilization of a knee brace.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maximize-stability-recovery-compressive-guide-using-knee-brace-optimal-support-470352</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:48:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fit Geno Back Brace Posture Corrector Review: For Improved Posture And Pain Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fit-geno-back-brace-posture- Corrector-review-improved-posture-pain-relief-470386 <description><![CDATA[This product review explores the features and benefits of the Fit Geno Back Brace Posture Corrector, highlighting its potential effectiveness as a posture correction tool.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fit-geno-back-brace-posture- Corrector-review-improved-posture-pain-relief-470386</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:33:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide To Electrical Muscle Stimulators In 2023: Top 8 Picks]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultimate-guide-electrical-muscle-stimulators-2023-top-8-picks-470509 <description><![CDATA[A guide to the top-rated Electrical Muscle Stimulators (EMS) in 2023, offering insights, expert recommendations and innovative devices that revolutionize fitness and muscle stimulation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultimate-guide-electrical-muscle-stimulators-2023-top-8-picks-470509</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:10:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Guard Your Home Against Germs: Discover The Top-Rated Home Disinfectant System And Air Purifiers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/guard-your-home-against-germs-discover-top-erated-home-disinfectant-system-air-purifiers-470457 <description><![CDATA[Introducing a groundbreaking home disinfectant system that transforms cleanliness and enhances protection against harmful microbes for germ-conscious homeowners.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/guard-your-home-against-germs-discover-top-erated-home-disinfectant-system-air-purifiers-470457</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 14:37:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best High-Quality Digital Stethoscope To Unlock The Pulse Of Perfection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-high-quality-digital-stethscope-unlock-pulse-perfection-470463 <description><![CDATA[The revolutionary EKO Digital Stethoscope combines cutting-edge technology with the trusted quality of the Littmann brand.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-high-quality-digital-stethscope-unlock-pulse-perfection-470463</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:47:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unveiling The 5 Perfect Gifts For Medical Professionals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unveiling-5-perfect-gifts-medical-professionals-470461 <description><![CDATA[Discover the ideal gift for medical professionals with this carefully curated selection of thoughtful and practical presents that express gratitude and appreciation for their dedicated service.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unveiling-5-perfect-gifts-medical-professionals-470461</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:57:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Gregory Crichlow on Life with Purpose and Fulfilling the Barbadian Dream Through His Work at AvantBlue]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-gregory-crichlow-life- Purpose-fulfilling-barbadian-dream-through-his-work-avantblue-470599 <description><![CDATA[In 2021, the average life expectancy decreased from 79 years in 2019 to only 77, registering the largest decrease over a two-year span since the 1920s.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-gregory-crichlow-life- Purpose-fulfilling-barbadian-dream-through-his-work-avantblue-470599</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:32:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rev Up Your Productivity: Stay Active At Work With These Top 5 Desk Pedal Devices]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rev-your-productivity-stay-active-work-这些-top-5-desk-pedal-devices-470392 <description><![CDATA[These 5 nifty devices offer a convenient solution to engage your body and mind, all from the comfort of your desk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rev-your-productivity-stay-active-work-这些-top-5-desk-pedal-devices-470392</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:16:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Lead Exposure Instills Criminal Instincts? Study Says People Exposed In Womb, Childhood Are At Higher Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lead-exposure-instils-criminal-instincts-study-says-people-expose-womb-childhood-are-higher-470596 <description><![CDATA[The latest study has found that lead exposure in the womb or in childhood increases the risk of criminal behavior in adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lead-exposure-instils-criminal-instincts-study-says-people-expose-womb-childhood-are-higher-470596</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 03:38:57 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>