<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Common Drug Could Cut Colorectal Cancer Risk In People With Unhealthy Lifestyle: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-drug-could-cut-colorectal-cancer-risk-people-unhealthy-lifestyle-study-472047 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that regular use of aspirin could slash colorectal cancer risk in people already at risk from unhealthy lifestyles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-drug-could-cut-colorectal-cancer-risk-people-unhealthy-lifestyle-study-472047</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:13:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[One Step Closer To Hair Rejuvenation: The Best Ways To Deal With Hairloss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/one-step-closer-hair-rejuvenation-best-ways-deal-hairloss-472028 <description><![CDATA[For men, FDA-approved medications like Minoxidil, the generic for Rogaine®, offer a safe and effective solution for hair loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/one-step-closer-hair-rejuvenation-best-ways-deal-hairloss-472028</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Aug 2024 08:50:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cut Down On Processed Meat, Swap It With Nuts To Reduce Dementia Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-down-processed-meat-swap-it-nuts-reduce-dementia-risk-study-472045 <description><![CDATA[Recent research uncovers a concerning link between processed meat and an increased risk of dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-down-processed-meat-swap-it-nuts-reduce-dementia-risk-study-472045</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:51:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Many Cocoa Products Contain Toxic Heavy Metals, Higher Levels In Organic Chocolates: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/many-cocoa-products-contain-有毒-heavy-metals-higher-levels-organic-chocolates-study-472042 <description><![CDATA[Researchers cautioned that their findings do not mean consumers should completely avoid chocolates but enjoy them in moderation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/many-cocoa-products-contain-有毒-heavy-metals-higher-levels-organic-chocolates-study-472042</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:48:04 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gen X, Millennials At Higher Risk Of Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gen-x-millennials-higher-risk-cancer-study-472041 <description><![CDATA[The study found that 17 types of cancers, including breast, pancreatic, and gastric cancers, are rising in younger generations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gen-x-millennials-higher-risk-cancer-study-472041</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:50:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Loss Drugs With Semaglutide May Help Quit Smoking: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-semaglutide-may-help-quit-smoking-study-472038 <description><![CDATA[Semaglutide drugs such as Ozempic and Wegovy could help tobacco smokers quit smoking, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-semaglutide-may-help-quit-smoking-study-472038</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:16:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Chronic Cough Be Inherited? Here's What Studies Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-chronic-cough-inherited-heres-what-studies-say-472037 <description><![CDATA[Two separate studies have found that chronic cough may have a genetic component, and the condition particularly impacts middle-aged women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-chronic-cough-inherited-heres-what-studies-say-472037</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:38:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Don't Skip Breakfast: Study Reveals Children Who Miss It Regularly Are Less Happy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-skip-breakfast-study-reveals-children-who-miss-it-regularly-are-less-happy-472035 <description><![CDATA[Can the regularity of the morning meal affect happiness? The researchers discovered "a nearly linear relationship" between a higher frequency of eating breakfast and greater life satisfaction.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-skip-breakfast-study-reveals-children-who-miss-it-regularly-are-less-happy-472035</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:20:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cutting Out This Item From Your Diet Could Reverse Aging, New Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cutting-out-this-item-your-diet-could-reverse-aging-new-study-finds-472032 <description><![CDATA[Can an item in your diet turn back the biological clock? Researchers have now identified a specific item, which, when reduced, could potentially reverse the signs of aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cutting-out-this-item-your-diet-could-reverse-aging-new-study-finds-472032</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:32:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Expert Reveals Dangers Of UV Index Tanning Trend, Shares Tips To Protect Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-reveals-dangers-uv-index-tanning-trend-shares-tips-protect-skin-472029 <description><![CDATA[Chasing that perfect tan could be more harmful than you think. Know from an expert how tanning accelerates skin aging and increases the risk of skin cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-reveals-dangers-uv-index-tanning-trend-shares-tips-protect-skin-472029</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:03:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[First Ever Deaths From Oropouche Virus: Know About Rare Illness, Life-Threatening Complications]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-ever-deaths-oropouche-virus-know-about-rare-illness-life-throne-complications-472027 <description><![CDATA[The world's first-ever deaths from the Oropouche virus have been reported in Brazil. The relatively unknown infection has no specific vaccines or medications for prevention and treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-ever-deaths-oropouche-virus-know-about-rare-illness-life-throne-complications-472027</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:46:36 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>