<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA['Not Worth Your Life': 21-Year-Old Warns After Throwing Up Blood, Falling In Coma From Continuous Vaping]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-worth-your-life-21-year-old-warns-after-throwing-blood-falling-coma-continuous-vaping-472997 <description><![CDATA[The young man, who now lives with one functioning lung after surviving two weeks in a coma and bilateral pneumonia, is now raising awareness about the dangers of vaping.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-worth-your-life-21-year-old-warns-after-throwing-blood-falling-coma-continuous-vaping-472997</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 Jan 2025 01:15:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide to 17 Energy-Boosting Supplements You Need in 2025]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/ultimate-guide-17-energy-boosting-supplements-you-need-2025-472996 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top 17 natural energy boosters for 2025! Perfect for athletes, professionals, and anyone seeking all-day vitality. Unlock your full potential today!]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/ultimate-guide-17-energy-boosting-supplements-you-need-2025-472996</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:51:32 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth Is Price Gouging Cancer Patients by Overcharging 'Thousands of Percent' for Live-Saving Meds, Pocketing Extra Billions: Feds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unitedhealth-price-gouging-cancer-患者-overcharging-thousands-percent-live- saving-meds-472993 <description><![CDATA[The UnitedHealth Group is overcharging patients for necessary life-saving drugs as a result of price gouging that increases the cost of such medication exponentially.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unitedhealth-price-gouging-cancer-患者-overcharging-thousands-percent-live- saving-meds-472993</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:41:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Bans Red Dye No. 3 Citing Cancer Risk: From Candies To Drinks, Here Are Foods That Contain It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-bans-red-dye-no-3-citing-cancer-risk-candies-drinks-here-are-foods-that-c​​ontain-it-472990 <description><![CDATA[The FDA's decision to ban the use of Red Dye No. 3 in foods, beverages, oral drugs, and dietary supplements comes nearly 35 years after it prohibited the use of the same in cosmetics due to cancer risks found in animal studies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-bans-red-dye-no-3-citing-cancer-risk-candies-drinks-here-are-foods-that-c​​ontain-it-472990</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 Jan 2025 03:27:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[That Extra Sausage May Harm Your Brain: Here's How Red And Processed Meats Affect Cognitive Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/that-extra-sausage-may-harm-your-brain-heres-how-red-processed-meats-affect-cognitive-health-472987 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now urge cutting back on red meat, particularly processed ones, to reduce the risk of memory issues and dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/that-extra-sausage-may-harm-your-brain-heres-how-red-processed-meats-affect-cognitive-health-472987</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 Jan 2025 01:32:13 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hospital Mixes Up Patients, Pulls Plug On Wrong Man After Getting Permission from Different Family]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospital-mixes-病人-pulls-plug-wrong-man-after-getting-permission- Different-family-472986 <description><![CDATA[A Washington state hospital faces lawsuits after mistakenly taking the wrong patient off life support when a different family authorized the removal for someone else.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospital-mixes-病人-pulls-plug-wrong-man-after-getting-permission- Different-family-472986</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:21:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Hospital Called Cops on Woman Who Suffered Horrific Miscarriage in Bathroom: Lawsuit]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-hospital- Called-cops-woman-who-suffered-horrific-miscarriage-bathroom-lawsuit-472984 <description><![CDATA[An Ohio woman is suing her hometown, her healthcare providers and law enforcement after she was arrested for having a miscarriage about a year ago.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-hospital- Called-cops-woman-who-suffered-horrific-miscarriage-bathroom-lawsuit-472984</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:22:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Green Tea Protect Brain? Here's How Much To Drink Daily For Beneficial Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-green-tea-protect-brain-heres-how-much-drink-daily-beneficial-effects-472981 <description><![CDATA[New research suggests that drinking green tea every day may help reduce white matter lesions in the brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-green-tea-protect-brain-heres-how-much-drink-daily-beneficial-effects-472981</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 03:55:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Died After Pharmacy Ran Out Of Epilepsy Drug, Left Him With An 'IOU' Note]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-died-after-pharmacy-ran-out-epilepsy-drug-left-him-iou-note-472978 <description><![CDATA[A recent coroner's report concluded that epilepsy was a contributory factor in the man's death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-died-after-pharmacy-ran-out-epilepsy-drug-left-him-iou-note-472978</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 02:48:21 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Suffered Severe Injuries After Going Through MRI Scan With Inserted Sex Toy, Butt Plug 'Dragged' Through Body: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-suffered-severe-injuries-after-going-through-mri-scan-inserted-sex-toy-butt-plug-dragged-472975 <description><![CDATA[The young woman reportedly went into the scan without realizing the silicone sex toy she was using had metal in its core.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-suffered-severe-injuries-after-going-through-mri-scan-inserted-sex-toy-butt-plug-dragged-472975</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 01:02:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Supplements Increase Cancer Risk? Here's What Cancer Dietitian Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-supplements-increase-cancer-risk-heres-what-c​​ancer-dietitian-says-472973 <description><![CDATA[A seemingly harmless wellness trend is now being questioned by a cancer dietitian, who advises you to evaluate whether you really need to take supplements or if whole foods might be a better choice.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-supplements-increase-cancer-risk-heres-what-c​​ancer-dietitian-says-472973</guid><pubDate> Tue, 14 Jan 2025 02:55:47 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>