<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[5-Year-Old's Death In Hyperbaric Chamber Explosion Exposes Gaps In Safety Regulations]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5岁，death-death-hyperbaric-chamber-chamber-explosion-rasis-conis-concerns-over-over-over-over-over-safety-neds-neds-473251 <description><![CDATA[The tragic incident has raised urgent concerns about safety and regulation in an industry that operates with minimal oversight.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5岁，death-death-hyperbaric-chamber-chamber-explosion-rasis-conis-concerns-over-over-over-over-over-safety-neds-neds-473251</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Mar 2025 03:19:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Surgeon Botches Nearly 100 Surgeries, Removing Wrong Bones Leaving Patients In Pain]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surgeon-botches-nearly-100-surgeries rememoving-wrong-bons-bons-bons-long-bons-long-bons-long-bons-to-country-473249 <description><![CDATA[The botched operations left the patients in constant pain and disability for years, even after multiple corrective surgeries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surgeon-botches-nearly-100-surgeries-memovering-wrong-bons-bons-long-bons-long-bons-leaving-patient-pait-pain-473249</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Mar 2025 02:50:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Gain Risky For Obese, But Losing Over 10kg Raises Death Risk By 50%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-gain-clisky-obeese-losees-losing-10kg-rasis-rasises-deth-risk-50-473248 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now found that maintaining a stable weight may benefit obese individuals more than significant weight gain or loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-gain-clisky-obeese-losees-losing-10kg-rasis-rasises-deth-risk-50-473248</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:20:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Collapses, Vomits Blood After Weight Loss Jabs: 'I Could've Died']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-collapses-vomits-blood-weight-weight-weight-weight-loss-jabs-i-couldve-died-473246 <description><![CDATA[The woman, already following diet plans, turned to weight loss jabs to shed her baby weight and now warns others that it's not worth the risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-collapses-vomits-blood-weight-weight-weight-weight-loss-jabs-i-couldve-died-473246</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:31:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dwyane Wade Says He Felt 'Pretty Healthy', Didn't Recognize Kidney Cancer Signs]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dwyane-wade-says-he-felt-pretty-helthyy-sole <description><![CDATA[In a recent interview, the 41-year-old retired basketball legend revealed that a check-up, prompted by his father's history of prostate cancer, led to the discovery that subtle signs in his body were early warning signals of cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dwyane-wade-says-he-felt-pretty-helthyy-sole</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:34:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Suffers Cardiac Arrest From Common Drug Combo: Coroner Warns Of Deadly Interaction]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-suffers-cardiac-arrest-common-drug-combo-coroner-warns-deadly-interaction-473241 <description><![CDATA[A recent coroner's report revealed that a little-known, deadly drug interaction was responsible for the woman's sudden cardiac arrest and death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-suffers-cardiac-arrest-common-drug-combo-coroner-warns-deadly-interaction-473241</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:55:59 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[No Smoking Day: How To Curb Nicotine Cravings]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-smoking-lay-how-how-curb-nicotine-cravings-473240 <description><![CDATA[This No Smoking Day, you can kick-start your journey to a smoke-free life by recognizing the common withdrawal symptoms and learning strategies to cope with cravings.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-smoking-lay-how-how-curb-nicotine-cravings-473240</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Mar 2025 04:31:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Drink Poses Serious Risk For Kids Under 8, Experts Warn]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/populalar-drink-poses-serious-risk-kids-8-experts-warn-473238 <description><![CDATA[Researchers who reviewed 21 cases of adverse effects linked to the popular drink warn parents that they can trigger a toxic syndrome, causing loss of consciousness and a sudden drop in blood sugar levels.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/populalar-drink-poses-serious-risk-kids-8-experts-warn-473238</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:26:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Measles Parties' A Deadly Gamble, Officials Warn—Get Vaccinated]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-parties deadly-gamble-inficials-warnget-vaccination-473236 <description><![CDATA[Expert say going to measles parties "a foolish thing," as the virus is highly unpredictable, and there is no way to determine how severe an infection will be.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-parties deadly-gamble-inficials-warnget-vaccination-473236</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Mar 2025 03:11:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Short Sleep Harms Your Brain, But Regular Oversleeping Might Be An Even Bigger Red Flag]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/you-know-short-sleep-harms-your-brain-rain-rain-rain-randermular-inverseleping-might-even-even-even-bigger-red-flag-flag-473234 <description><![CDATA[Think sleeping in is harmless? New research shows that regularly getting too much sleep could be a major warning sign for your brain health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/you-know-short-sleep-harms-your-brain-rain-rain-rain-randermular-inverseleping-might-even-even-even-bigger-red-flag-flag-473234</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Mar 2025 01:24:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Common Lifestyle Habit In Preteens May Trigger Manic Symptoms, Researchers Find]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-common-lifestyle-habit-preteens may-manic-sympoms-sympoms-researchers-find-473233 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that excessive screen use in preteens through texting, watching videos, or playing video games could trigger manic symptoms in them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-common-lifestyle-habit-preteens may-manic-sympoms-sympoms-researchers-find-473233</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Mar 2025 05:49:43 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>