<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Freshly Made Pizza A Good Choice For People With Rheumatoid Arthritis, Researchers Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/freshly-made-pizza-good-choice-people-rheumatoid-arthritis-researchers-say-470636 <description><![CDATA[If prepared with fresh ingredients and in a perfect balance of carbs, protein and fats, pizza can be a nutritious choice for people with rheumatoid arthritis, a study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/freshly-made-pizza-good-choice-people-rheumatoid-arthritis-researchers-say-470636</guid><pubDate> Wed, 09 Aug 2023 04:20:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily Intake Of Sugary Drinks Raises Liver Cancer Risk In Women By 85%: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-intake-sugary-drinks-raises-liver-cancer-risk-women-85-study-470633 <description><![CDATA[A study conducted among post-menopausal women showed that those who consumed one or more sugar-sweetened beverages daily were at an 85% higher risk of developing liver cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-intake-sugary-drinks-raises-liver-cancer-risk-women-85-study-470633</guid><pubDate> Wed, 09 Aug 2023 02:56:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Walking Just 4,000 Steps A Day Could Help Reduce Risk Of Early Death]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/walking-just-4000-steps-day-could-help-reduce-risk-early-death-470632 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that all-cause mortality reduces by 15% with each additional 1,000 steps taken daily.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/walking-just-4000-steps-day-could-help-reduce-risk-early-death-470632</guid><pubDate> Wed, 09 Aug 2023 01:20:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Lyme Disease? Know More About The Condition Supermodel Bella Hadid Suffers From]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-lyme-disease-know-more-about-condition-supermodel-bella-hadid-suffers-470631 <description><![CDATA[When left untreated, Lyme disease can lead to complications as the infection spreads to joints, heart and the nervous system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-lyme-disease-know-more-about-condition-supermodel-bella-hadid-suffers-470631</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:02:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Sleep Quality Depends On How You Feel It, Not What Your Smartwatch Says: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-sleep-quality-depends-how-you-feel-it-not-what-your-smartwatch-says-study-470628 <description><![CDATA[The study found that the way a person feels about sleep quality affects their mood more than what is measured through sleep trackers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-sleep-quality-depends-how-you-feel-it-not-what-your-smartwatch-says-study-470628</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:32:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Added Sugars In Diet May Elevate Risk Of Kidney Stones; Know Ways To Prevent Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/added-sugars-diet-may-elevate-risk-developing-kidney-stone-know-ways-prevent-condition-470626 <description><![CDATA[People who get more than 25% of their total energy from added sugars are at an 88% higher risk of developing kidney stones, a new study says.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/added-sugars-diet-may-elevate-risk-developing-kidney-stone-know-ways-prevent-condition-470626</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:13:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Golfers More Vulnerable To Skin Cancer Than Others, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/golfers-more-vulnerable-skin-cancer-others-study-says-470624 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say golfers face a nearly 250% higher risk of developing skin cancer than non-players.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/golfers-more-vulnerable-skin-cancer-others-study-says-470624</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 05:27:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Aroma To Boost Memory? Study Says Exposure To Fragrances During Sleep Can Improve Brain Function]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aroma-boost-memory-study-says-exposure-fragrances-during-sleep-can-improve-brain-function-470621 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found infusing aroma in the bedrooms of older adults for two hours each night resulted in significant improvements in their memory.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aroma-boost-memory-study-says-exposure-fragrances-during-sleep-can-improve-brain-function-470621</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:07:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleeping Late, Oversleeping During Weekends Could Be Harmful For Your Gut Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleeping-late-oversleeping-during-weekends-could-harmful-your-gut-health-470619 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found a link between "social jet lag" and gut health. It shows irregular sleep patterns can harm gut health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleeping-late-oversleeping-during-weekends-could-harmful-your-gut-health-470619</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 02:50:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Beer Tanning: Expert Warns Viral Trend Could Lead To Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beer-tanning-expert-warns-viral-trend-could-lead-cancer-470617 <description><![CDATA[As beer tanning is gaining popularity on social media, a health expert cautions people about the skin damage it can bring along.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beer-tanning-expert-warns-viral-trend-could-lead-cancer-470617</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 01:13:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Success Stories: Inspiring Testimonials of Med Students Who Achieved Residency Dreams with Dr. Michael Everest]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/success-stories-inspiring-testimonials-med-students-who-achieved-residency-dreams-dr-michael-470612 <description><![CDATA[Securing a medical residency position is a dream countless aspiring doctors cherish.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/success-stories-inspiring-testimonials-med-students-who-achieved-residency-dreams-dr-michael-470612</guid><pubDate> Sun, 06 Aug 2023 22:16:14 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>