<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best-Selling Toilet Seats For Seniors In 2024: Elevate Your Comfort]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best- sell-toilet-seats-seniors-2024-elevate-your-comfort-471239 <description><![CDATA[Discover top-rated toilet seats for seniors, with adjustable heights, handles, and essential safety features for a secure and accessible bathroom experience.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best- sell-toilet-seats-seniors-2024-elevate-your-comfort-471239</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:42:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Dark Spot Removers 2024:  The Ultimate Guide To Flawless Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-dark-spot-removers-2024-ultimate-guide-flawless-skin-471237 <description><![CDATA[Here, we explore the five best dark spot removers for 2024, examining their ingredients, possible benefits, and feedback from users.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-dark-spot-removers-2024-ultimate-guide-flawless-skin-471237</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jan 2024 04:37:47 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is There A Link Between Early Rising And Anorexia? Researchers Say 'Yes']]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/there-link- Between-early-rising-anorexia-researchers-say-yes-471238 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found a bidirectional association between anorexia nervosa and morning chronotype - the natural inclination of the body to wake up and sleep early.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/there-link- Between-early-rising-anorexia-researchers-say-yes-471238</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jan 2024 04:34:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bipolar Disorder: Study Says People With The Condition At Higher Risk Of Early Death Than Smokers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bipolar-disorder-study-says-people-condition-higher-risk-early-death-smokers-471236 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say bipolar disorder is associated with a four to six-fold risk of premature death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bipolar-disorder-study-says-people-condition-higher-risk-early-death-smokers-471236</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jan 2024 02:16:48 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Glaucoma Awareness Month: Experts Share Insights On Signs, Risk Factors And Importance Of Screening]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-glaucoma-awareness-month-experts-share-insights-signs-risk-factors-importance-471235 <description><![CDATA[Glaucoma currently has no cure. Nevertheless, early detection and treatment can halt the progression of the disease, potentially preventing blindness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-glaucoma-awareness-month-experts-share-insights-signs-risk-factors-importance-471235</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:35:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Going Dry In January? Study Says It Could Cut Risk Of Certain Cancers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/going-dry-january-study-says-it-could-cut-risk-certain-cancers-471233 <description><![CDATA[The study shows that abstaining from or cutting down on the amount of alcohol you consume could reduce the risk of developing oral or esophageal cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/going-dry-january-study-says-it-could-cut-risk-certain-cancers-471233</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Jan 2024 06:06:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Teeth Whitening Kits For 2024: Helping You Unveil Brighter Smiles]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-teeth-whitening-kits-2024-helping-you-unveil-brighter-smiles-471234 <description><![CDATA[In this article, we've curated a detailed analysis of the five best teeth whitening kits for 2024.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-teeth-whitening-kits-2024-helping-you-unveil-brighter-smiles-471234</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Jan 2024 05:55:48 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Disrupted Sleep In 30s And 40s Linked To Memory, Thinking Problems In Future: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/disrupted-sleep-30s-40s-linked-memory-thinking-problems-future-study-471232 <description><![CDATA[Scientists have discovered a connection between disrupted sleep during middle age and cognitive decline in the future.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/disrupted-sleep-30s-40s-linked-memory-thinking-problems-future-study-471232</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Jan 2024 01:40:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hearing Aids May Help Prevent Early Death; Study Finds 25% Reduction In Mortality Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hearing-aids-may-help-prevent-early-death-study-finds-25-reduction-mortality-risk-471231 <description><![CDATA[The regular use of hearing aids in people with hearing loss could reduce the risk of early death by 25%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hearing-aids-may-help-prevent-early-death-study-finds-25-reduction-mortality-risk-471231</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Jan 2024 00:22:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Looking Forward To A Healthier, Happier 2024? Combining Mindfulness With Exercise May Help]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/looking-forward-healthier-happier-2024-combining-mindativity-exercise-may-help-471230 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found life changes that combine physical activity and mindfulness can help enhance mood and improve mental health and well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/looking-forward-healthier-happier-2024-combining-mindativity-exercise-may-help-471230</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:03:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Surge In Scabies Cases In UK Amid Acute Treatment Shortage; Know Signs, Steps To Prevent Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surge-scabies-cases-uk-amid-acute-treatment-shortage-know-signs-steps-prevent-infection-471229 <description><![CDATA[The shortage of treatment drugs can lead to rapid spread of infection, causing a public health crisis, health officials warn.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surge-scabies-cases-uk-amid-acute-treatment-shortage-know-signs-steps-prevent-infection-471229</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jan 2024 02:50:44 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>