<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Survey Says 25% Of Adults In U.S Suspect They Have Undiagnosed ADHD]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/survey-says-25-adults-us-suspect-they-have-undiagnosed-adhd-472528 <description><![CDATA[The survey revealed that a striking 25% of U.S. adults suspect they may have undiagnosed ADHD. Even more concerning is that only 13% of respondents have taken the crucial step of discussing their symptoms with a healthcare professional.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/survey-says-25-adults-us-suspect-they-have-undiagnosed-adhd-472528</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Oct 2024 04:09:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Child's Bedtime Affects Their Gut Health: Here's How Early Sleep Benefits Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-childs-bedtime-affects-their-gut-health-heres-how-early-sleep-benefits-them-472527 <description><![CDATA[The findings indicate that an early bedtime, particularly before 9:30 p.m., is a valuable habit to cultivate, as children who went to bed earlier had a higher abundance of beneficial gut bacteria and a lower presence of various harmful gut microbes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-childs-bedtime-affects-their-gut-health-heres-how-early-sleep-benefits-them-472527</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Oct 2024 03:14:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Quality, Not Quantity Of Good Cholesterol Linked To Alzheimer's Risk: Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quality-not-quantity-good-cholesterol-linked-alzheimers-risk-study-says-472525 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that the number of larger HDL particles in women's bodies increases during menopause, and these larger particles are less effective in supporting cognitive health compared to their smaller counterparts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quality-not-quantity-good-cholesterol-linked-alzheimers-risk-study-says-472525</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Oct 2024 01:40:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Oil Cleansers: Top Solutions For Deep Cleansing, Nourishing Skin, And Hydration]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-oil-cleansers-top-solutions-deep-cleansing-nourishing-skin-Hydration-472458 <description><![CDATA[Oil cleansers are a vital part of any skincare routine, especially for those looking to effectively remove makeup, sunscreen, and impurities from the skin. These products work by attracting and dissolving oil-based substances, making them ideal for deep cleansing without stripping the skin of its natural moisture.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-oil-cleansers-top-solutions-deep-cleansing-nourishing-skin-Hydration-472458</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Oct 2024 15:20:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mindfulness For Anxiety Disorders: Study Says It's Comparable To Antidepressant]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mindativity-anxiety-disorders-study-says-its-comparable-antidepressant-472524 <description><![CDATA[The study found that Mindfulness-Based Stress Reduction could be as effective as the antidepressant escitalopram in alleviating symptoms of several anxiety disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mindativity-anxiety-disorders-study-says-its-comparable-antidepressant-472524</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Oct 2024 04:13:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[It's Never Too Late: Quitting Smoking Can Improve Longevity Even At 75]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/its-never-too-late-quitting-smoking-can-improve-longevity-even-75-472523 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that while the benefits of quitting smoking may decrease with age, older individuals can still achieve significant gains in life expectancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/its-never-too-late-quitting-smoking-can-improve-longevity-even-75-472523</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Oct 2024 03:07:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Cells Inherit Energy From Mother; Study Offers Insights On Mitochondrial Disorders]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-cells-inherit-energy-mother-study-offers-insights-mitochondrial-disorders-472522 <description><![CDATA[The researchers discovered that humans inherit the DNA inside their mitochondria from their mothers alone, with all traces of their father's mitochondrial genome destroyed the moment sperm joins the egg.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-cells-inherit-energy-mother-study-offers-insights-mitochondrial-disorders-472522</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Oct 2024 01:26:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Residency Success: Key Tools and Strategies Residents Medical Provides for Aspiring Doctors Facing OSCE and Beyond]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/residency-success-key-tools-strategies-residents-medical-provides-aspiring-doctors-faceing-osce-472521 <description><![CDATA[Residents Medical gives international doctors that fair chance by offering personalized guidance, test preparation help, educational resources, and even real-world clinical placements to help maximize medical graduates' chances of securing a residency.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/residency-success-key-tools-strategies-residents-medical-provides-aspiring-doctors-faceing-osce-472521</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:38:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI-Powered Automation: The Lifeline Reviving Physicians' Shrinking Revenues]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-powered-automation-lifeline-reviving-physicals-shrinking-revenues-472519 <description><![CDATA[Unlike traditional manual processes, AI-powered solutions can drastically improve efficiency in the medical billing cycle. AI can identify patterns in denied claims, correct common errors, and even predict the likelihood of claim approval.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-powered-automation-lifeline-reviving-physicals-shrinking-revenues-472519</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:34:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Doubles Risk Of Heart Attacks, Strokes For Up To Three Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-doubles-risk-heart-attacks-中风-三年-study-472517 <description><![CDATA[The cardiovascular risk is significantly higher for those hospitalized with severe COVID and individuals with a preexisting history of heart disease, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-doubles-risk-heart-attacks-中风-三年-study-472517</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Oct 2024 03:04:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eating Less Extends Lifespan, But Those With Least Weight Loss Have Maximum Benefits: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-less-extends-lifespan-those-least-weight-loss-have-maximum-benefits-study-472516 <description><![CDATA[Researchers explored how eating less could extend lifespan and discovered that those who experienced the least weight loss while eating less had the greatest longevity benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-less-extends-lifespan-those-least-weight-loss-have-maximum-benefits-study-472516</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Oct 2024 01:35:39 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>