<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Ayurveda For Stress Relief: Here's What Experts Have To Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ayurveda-stress-relief-heres-what-experts-have-say-470696 <description><![CDATA[Ayurveda, a traditional system of medicine that originated in India thousands of years ago, is based on the idea that wellness depends on the balance between the mind, body and spirit.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ayurveda-stress-relief-heres-what-experts-have-say-470696</guid><pubDate> Tue, 22 Aug 2023 01:34:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experience The Blissful Realm Of Rejuvenating Slumber With These 5 Innovative Sleep Products]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experience-blissful-realm-rejuvenating-slumber-these-5-innovative-sleep-products-470508 <description><![CDATA[Discover the transformative power of restful sleep through an exploration of five cutting-edge sleep products that promise to immerse you in a realm of revitalizing tranquility.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experience-blissful-realm-rejuvenating-slumber-these-5-innovative-sleep-products-470508</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:43:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[8 Signs That Suggest You May Have A Weak Immune System; Tips To Stay Healthy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-signs-that-suggest-you-may-have-weak-immune-system-tips-stay-healthy-470694 <description><![CDATA[Certain red flags such as frequent infections and fatigue should not be overlooked as they are warning signs of a weak immune system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-signs-that-suggest-you-may-have-weak-immune-system-tips-stay-healthy-470694</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:15:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A 30-Second Oral Rinse Could Detect Heart Disease Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/30-second-oral-rinse-could-detect-heart-disease-risk-470691 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now claim they can predict heart disease using a 30-second oral saline rinse in young, otherwise healthy people.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/30-second-oral-rinse-could-detect-heart-disease-risk-470691</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:56:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Maryland Reports First Case Of Locally Acquired Malaria After 40 Years; Know All About The Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maryland-reports-first-case-locally-acquired-malaria-after-40-years-know-all-about-disease-470689 <description><![CDATA[The unidentified patient from Maryland's National Capital Region is recovering after being hospitalized with the infection, health officials said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maryland-reports-first-case-locally-acquired-malaria-after-40-years-know-all-about-disease-470689</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 01:02:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Vibrio Vulnificus? Rare Bacterial Infection Claims 3 Lives In New York, Connecticut]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-vibrio-vulnificus-rare-bacterial-infection-claims-3-lives-new-york-connecticut-470679 <description><![CDATA[Health authorities said two patients died in Connecticut and one in New York's Suffolk County this summer after contracting Vibrio vulnificus infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-vibrio-vulnificus-rare-bacterial-infection-claims-3-lives-new-york-connecticut-470679</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 04:43:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Drug Prescribed For Weight Loss Could Help Improve Associative Learning In People With Obesity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-prescribed-weight-loss-could-help-improve-associative-learning-people-obesity-470681 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that reduced insulin sensitivity from obesity impairs associative learning and the effect can be reversed with the use of weight loss drug liraglutide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-prescribed-weight-loss-could-help-improve-associative-learning-people-obesity-470681</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 03:54:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Scientists Decode Song From Listeners' Brain Activity; Tech Could Help Speech-Impaired Users Communicate]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-decode-song-listeners-brain-activity-tech-could-help-speech-impaired-users-communicate-470675 <description><![CDATA[Someone's brain activity patterns may influence how they process musical notes, according to a new study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-decode-song-listeners-brain-activity-tech-could-help-speech-impaired-users-communicate-470675</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 03:21:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 And Menstruation: Study Says Infections And Vaccinations Lengthen The Cycle]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-menstruation-study-says-infections-vaccinations-lengthen-cycle-470678 <description><![CDATA[Unvaccinated participants showed a 1.45-day increase in their menstrual cycle after experiencing a COVID-19 infection, while participants who received the COVID shot had a 1.14-day increase in the cycle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-menstruation-study-says-infections-vaccinations-lengthen-cycle-470678</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 02:23:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Heart Attack Survivors With Chronic Pain More Likely To Die Within 8 Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-attack-survivors-chronic-pain-more-likely-die-within-8-years-study-470672 <description><![CDATA[Heart attack survivors with any kind of moderate to severe pain during the first year – even if the pain is not directly related to the heart attack – are still at a high risk of mortality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-attack-survivors-chronic-pain-more-likely-die-within-8-years-study-470672</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:48:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Too High? Say Hello To The Product That Will Fix Your Problem]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/too-high-say-hello-product-that-will-fix-your-problem-470663 <description><![CDATA[HIBEGONE, a 2 oz. drink, can remove the effects of cannabis in as little as 15 minutes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/too-high-say-hello-product-that-will-fix-your-problem-470663</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:48:54 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>