<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Maryland Reports First Case Of Locally Acquired Malaria After 40 Years; Know All About The Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maryland-reports-first-case-locally-acquired-malaria-after-40-years-know-all-about-disease-470689 <description><![CDATA[The unidentified patient from Maryland's National Capital Region is recovering after being hospitalized with the infection, health officials said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maryland-reports-first-case-locally-acquired-malaria-after-40-years-know-all-about-disease-470689</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 01:02:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Vibrio Vulnificus? Rare Bacterial Infection Claims 3 Lives In New York, Connecticut]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-vibrio-vulnificus-rare-bacterial-infection-claims-3-lives-new-york-connecticut-470679 <description><![CDATA[Health authorities said two patients died in Connecticut and one in New York's Suffolk County this summer after contracting Vibrio vulnificus infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-vibrio-vulnificus-rare-bacterial-infection-claims-3-lives-new-york-connecticut-470679</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 04:43:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Drug Prescribed For Weight Loss Could Help Improve Associative Learning In People With Obesity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-prescribed-weight-loss-could-help-improve-associative-learning-people-obesity-470681 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that reduced insulin sensitivity from obesity impairs associative learning and the effect can be reversed with the use of weight loss drug liraglutide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-prescribed-weight-loss-could-help-improve-associative-learning-people-obesity-470681</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 03:54:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Scientists Decode Song From Listeners' Brain Activity; Tech Could Help Speech-Impaired Users Communicate]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-decode-song-listeners-brain-activity-tech-could-help-speech-impaired-users-communicate-470675 <description><![CDATA[Someone's brain activity patterns may influence how they process musical notes, according to a new study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-decode-song-listeners-brain-activity-tech-could-help-speech-impaired-users-communicate-470675</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 03:21:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 And Menstruation: Study Says Infections And Vaccinations Lengthen The Cycle]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-menstruation-study-says-infections-vaccinations-lengthen-cycle-470678 <description><![CDATA[Unvaccinated participants showed a 1.45-day increase in their menstrual cycle after experiencing a COVID-19 infection, while participants who received the COVID shot had a 1.14-day increase in the cycle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-menstruation-study-says-infections-vaccinations-lengthen-cycle-470678</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 02:23:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Heart Attack Survivors With Chronic Pain More Likely To Die Within 8 Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-attack-survivors-chronic-pain-more-likely-die-within-8-years-study-470672 <description><![CDATA[Heart attack survivors with any kind of moderate to severe pain during the first year – even if the pain is not directly related to the heart attack – are still at a high risk of mortality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-attack-survivors-chronic-pain-more-likely-die-within-8-years-study-470672</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:48:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Too High? Say Hello To The Product That Will Fix Your Problem]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/too-high-say-hello-product-that-will-fix-your-problem-470663 <description><![CDATA[HIBEGONE, a 2 oz. drink, can remove the effects of cannabis in as little as 15 minutes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/too-high-say-hello-product-that-will-fix-your-problem-470663</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:48:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Certain Types Of Cancers Are Rising Among Young Adults In US, Researchers Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/certain-types-cancers-are-rising-among-young-adults-us-researchers-say-470670 <description><![CDATA[There has been a considerable spike in certain types of cancers among young adults, especially women, in the U.S., according to a new study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/certain-types-cancers-are-rising-among-young-adults-us-researchers-say-470670</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Aug 2023 04:06:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Don't Stifle Your Sneeze, Let It Go: Here's Why Holding In Can Be Dangerous]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-stifle-your-sneeze-let-it-go-heres-why-holding-can-dangerous-470667 <description><![CDATA[Although it is instinctive to stifle the sneeze for controlling the spread of germs, holding it in can cause more harm.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-stifle-your-sneeze-let-it-go-heres-why-holding-can-dangerous-470667</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Aug 2023 03:01:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiorespiratory Fitness In Men Reduces Risk Of 9 Types Of Cancers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiorespiratory-fitness-men-reduces-risk-9-types-cancers-study-470666 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that good cardiorespiratory health in men can reduce the risk of developing nine types of cancers, including lung, liver and rectal cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiorespiratory-fitness-men-reduces-risk-9-types-cancers-study-470666</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:27:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Little Bit Of Snapback Goes A Long Way: If We Love Our Bodies, They Will Love Us Back]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/little-bit-snapback-goes-long-way-if-we-love-our-bodies-they-will-love-us-back-470664 <description><![CDATA[Unlike caffeine and energy drinks, Snapback has no negative aftereffects. It complements the liver with antioxidants, amino acids and toxin-fighting natural remedies to break down the effects of alcohol consumption and mitigates migraines and nausea.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/little-bit-snapback-goes-long-way-if-we-love-our-bodies-they-will-love-us-back-470664</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:42:18 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>