<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Active Lifestyle With Moderate Exercise May Reduce Risk Of ALS In Men: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/active-lifestyle-moderate-exercise-may-reduce-risk-als-men-study-471891 <description><![CDATA[Maintaining an active lifestyle with moderate physical activity and fitness may reduce the risk of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) in men, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/active-lifestyle-moderate-exercise-may-reduce-risk-als-men-study-471891</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jun 2024 04:01:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Warns Of Increased Risk Of Dengue Infections: Know Symptoms, Steps For Prevention]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-increased-risk-dengue-infections-know-symptoms-steps-prevention-471890 <description><![CDATA[Healthcare providers are advised to remain highly vigilant for dengue in patients presenting with fever and a recent travel history to regions with frequent or continuous dengue transmission.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-increased-risk-dengue-infections-know-symptoms-steps-prevention-471890</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:55:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Oral Health Month: Dental Expert Shares Teeth Brushing Techniques For Radiant Smile]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-oral-health-month-dental-expert-shares-teeth-brushing-techniques-radiant-smile-471889 <description><![CDATA[During this National Oral Health Month, a leading dental expert shares the secrets to improved oral hygiene through effective teeth-brushing techniques.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-oral-health-month-dental-expert-shares-teeth-brushing-techniques-radiant-smile-471889</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:50:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People With Anxiety At Double Risk Of Parkinson's Disease: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-anxiety-double-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-471888 <description><![CDATA[There is a two-fold increased risk of Parkinson's disease in the anxiety group compared to the control group, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-anxiety-double-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-471888</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:45 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Loneliness May Raise Risk Of Stroke In Older Adults]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-may-raise-risk-中风-older-adults-471887 <description><![CDATA[A study discovered that elderly adults who experienced chronic loneliness had a 56% higher risk of stroke compared to those who consistently reported not being lonely.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-may-raise-risk-中风-older-adults-471887</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:57:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Underweight Babies At Higher Risk Of Complications If They Develop Obesity: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/underweight-babies-higher-risk-complications-if-they-develop-obesity-study-471886 <description><![CDATA[According to the study results published in the journal eBiomedicine, children born underweight face greater health risks if they develop obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/underweight-babies-higher-risk-complications-if-they-develop-obesity-study-471886</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:45:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Intermittent Dieting Plan To Improve Glycemic Control In Diabetic Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-intermittent-dieting-plan-improve-glycemic-control-diabetic-病人-471884 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that following a specific intermittent fasting plan, such as the 5:2 intermittent fasting technique and a meal replacement diet, might help improve glycemic control among those with type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-intermittent-dieting-plan-improve-glycemic-control-diabetic-病人-471884</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:51:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Penis Cancer Cases On The Rise Worldwide: Know Signs For Early Detection]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/penis-cancer-cases-rise-worldwide-know-signs-early-detection-471883 <description><![CDATA[The relatively rare malignancy affecting genitals is predicted to increase at an alarming rate of 77% in the next three decades.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/penis-cancer-cases-rise-worldwide-know-signs-early-detection-471883</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:52:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cannabis Use Nearly Doubles Risk Of Severe COVID Infection, Hospitalization: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cannabis-use-nearly-doubles-risk-severe-covid-infection-hospitalization-study-471881 <description><![CDATA[The study results showed that cannabis users had an 80% increased risk of hospitalization and a 27% increased risk of ICU admission.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cannabis-use-nearly-doubles-risk-severe-covid-infection-hospitalization-study-471881</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jun 2024 01:52:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Early Removal Of Ovaries May Affect Women's Brain Health: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-removal-ovaries-may-affect-womens-brain-health-study-471880 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered that women who undergo oophorectomy before menopause may face a higher risk of experiencing reduced white matter integrity in their brains as they age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-removal-ovaries-may-affect-womens-brain-health-study-471880</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jun 2024 03:59:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nuts For Weight Loss: Study Says Including Them In Reduced-Calorie Diet Helps]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nuts-weight-loss-study-says-include-them-reduced-calorie-diet-helps-471878 <description><![CDATA[The researchers also noted that none of the trials showed an adverse effect on weight loss when nuts were included as part of the diet.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nuts-weight-loss-study-says-include-them-reduced-calorie-diet-helps-471878</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jun 2024 03:26:45 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>