<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Long-Term Daily Use Of Aspirin Helps In Prevention, Progression Of Colorectal Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-term-daily-use-aspirin-helps-prevention-progression-colorectal-cancer-study-471675 <description><![CDATA[Regular aspirin use may have an active role in enhancing immunosurveillance against colorectal cancer, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-term-daily-use-aspirin-helps-prevention-progression-colorectal-cancer-study-471675</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Apr 2024 03:41:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[When Does Old Age Begin? Survey Suggests An Upward Shift In Perception Among Elderly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-shows-people-their-mid-60s-perceive-old-age-begin-75-471674 <description><![CDATA[The survey results indicate an upward shift in people's perception of age as respondents in their mid-60s perceive old age to begin at 75.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-shows-people-their-mid-60s-perceive-old-age-begin-75-471674</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Apr 2024 02:24:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Common Antibiotic Could Prevent, Treat Respiratory Illnesses Including COVID-19: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-antibiotic-could-prevent-treat-respiratory-illnesses-include-covid-19-study-471672 <description><![CDATA[Antibiotic neomycin through the nasal passage triggers a robust interferon-stimulated genes (ISG) line of defense against both SARS-CoV-2 and a highly virulent strain of influenza A virus, the results of an animal study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-antibiotic-could-prevent-treat-respiratory-illnesses-include-covid-19-study-471672</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Apr 2024 01:29:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Quick and Safe: Top 5 Bottle Warmers for Modern Parents]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quick-safe-top-5-bottle-warmers-modern-parents-471646 <description><![CDATA[Explore our top picks for bottle warmers, designed to provide quick and safe milk or formula heating solutions for modern parents.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quick-safe-top-5-bottle-warmers-modern-parents-471646</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:59:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Bluetooth Hearing Aids For 2024: Amplify Your Listening]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-bluetooth-hearing-aids-amplify-your-listening-471652 <description><![CDATA[Whether you're a longtime hearing aid user looking for a more convenient option, or someone experiencing the first signs of hearing loss, Bluetooth hearing aids offer a powerful solution to stay connected and engaged with the world around you.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-bluetooth-hearing-aids-amplify-your-listening-471652</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:31:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mediterranean Diet Linked To Reduced Risk Of Hypertension: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/mediterranean-diet-linked-reduced-risk-hypertension-study-471669 <description><![CDATA[Those who consistently follow a Mediterranean diet are at a reduced risk of hypertension, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mediterranean-diet-linked-reduced-risk-hypertension-study-471669</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:37:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Calorie Counting Trumps Meal Timing For Weight Loss, Study Finds]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/calorie-counting-trumps-meal-timing-weight-loss-study-finds-471667 <description><![CDATA[The study discovered that the total number of calories consumed throughout the day matters more than when those calories are consumed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/calorie-counting-trumps-meal-timing-weight-loss-study-finds-471667</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:11:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Evolution of Psychedelic Therapy in Mental Health and Spirituality]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/evolution-psychedelic-therapy-mental-health-spirituality-471665 <description><![CDATA[Matt Zemon's work contributes to the broader discussion on mental health treatment, the use of psychedelics in ceremonial contexts, and the acceptance of alternative therapies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/evolution-psychedelic-therapy-mental-health-spirituality-471665</guid><pubDate> Sat, 20 Apr 2024 04:48:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Thatch.ai's Game-Changing Healthcare Solutions Empower Workforce Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/thatchais-game-changing-healthcare-solutions-empower-workforce-wellness-471663 <description><![CDATA[Rooted in the fundamental belief of equalizing access to quality healthcare, Thatch is on a mission to simplify and personalize the healthcare journey for employees across diverse industries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/thatchais-game-changing-healthcare-solutions-empower-workforce-wellness-471663</guid><pubDate> Sat, 20 Apr 2024 04:44:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Korean Sunscreens For 2024: Build Your Dream Skincare Regimen]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-korean-sunscreens-build-your-dream-skincare-regimen-471624 <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of Korean sunscreen, where skincare meets innovation! Let's explore why the best Korean sunscreens are taking the beauty world by storm, offering a powerful shield against harmful UV rays while keeping your skin feeling pampered.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-korean-sunscreens-build-your-dream-skincare-regimen-471624</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:52:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salmonella Infections Linked To Contaminated Basil Sold At Trader Joe's, CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-infections-linked-contaminate-basil-sold-trader-joes-cdc-warns-471659 <description><![CDATA[The CDC has received reports of 12 Salmonella infections in seven states.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-infections-linked-contaminate-basil-sold-trader-joes-cdc-warns-471659</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:05:29 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>