<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一个</language><item><title><![CDATA[Pregnant Mothers With Obesity And PCOS At Higher Risk Of Having Smaller Babies: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnant-mothers-obesity-pcos-higher-risk-having-smaller-babies-study-472633 <description><![CDATA[On average, babies born to mothers with PCOS faced a higher risk of growth restriction, and the effects were more pronounced in mothers who were obese.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnant-mothers-obesity-pcos-higher-risk-having-smaller-babies-study-472633</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Nov 2024 02:35:52 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Suggests A Medication-Free Treatment For Depression, Finds Symptom Relief In 40% Cases]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-suggests-medication-free-treatment-depression-finds-symptom-relief-40-cases-472630 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have identified a drug-free therapy that could offer a safe, effective adjunctive treatment for non-seasonal depressive disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-suggests-medication-free-treatment-depression-finds-symptom-relief-40-cases-472630</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Nov 2024 01:10:13 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Reveals Breakfast Item That May Boost Focus And Keep You Full]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-breakfast-item-that-may-boost-focus-keep-you-full-472627 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that a dairy-based high-protein diet is most effective for promoting fullness and boosting concentration compared to a carb-rich meal or skipping breakfast entirely.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-breakfast-item-that-may-boost-focus-keep-you-full-472627</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Nov 2024 04:30:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Diabetes Awareness Month: Expert Dietitian Dispels Common Misconceptions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-diabetes-awareness-month-expert-dietitian-dispels-common-misconceptions-472624 <description><![CDATA[Learn about the crucial role that a nutritious diet plays in preventing and managing diabetes, while Laurel Deinininger-Kimmerly, a Registered Dietitian and Certified Diabetes Educator from Florida debunks common myths that could affect effective management.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-diabetes-awareness-month-expert-dietitian-dispels-common-misconceptions-472624</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Nov 2024 02:28:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Prolonged Sitting Accelerates Aging: Walk After Work May Not Fix It, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prolonged-sitting-accelerates-aging-walk-after-work-may-not-fix-it-says-study-472622 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that even the recommended 20 minutes of daily moderate exercise may not be sufficient to reduce the heart disease risk and signs of aging linked to prolonged sedentary time.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prolonged-sitting-accelerates-aging-walk-after-work-may-not-fix-it-says-study-472622</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Scheduling Surgery After A Heart Attack? Here's How Long You Might Have To Wait]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scheduling-surgery-after-heart-attack-heres-how-long-you-might-have-wait-472619 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now identified a "sweet spot" for safely scheduling surgeries in those who had a heart attack.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scheduling-surgery-after-heart-attack-heres-how-long-you-might-have-wait-472619</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Nov 2024 04:52:21 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Loss Drugs Could Be A Treatment Option For Osteoarthritis: Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-could-treatment-option-osteoarthritis-says-study-472617 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that semaglutide injections, a drug commonly used for weight loss, could dramatically reduce osteoarthritis symptoms, cutting pain levels by nearly 50%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-could-treatment-option-osteoarthritis-says-study-472617</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:30:42 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Links A Common Sleep Disorder To Dementia; Higher Risk In Women]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-links-common-sleep-disorder-dementia-higher-risk-women-472616 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed a concerning sex-specific link between obstructive sleep apnea and the risk of dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-links-common-sleep-disorder-dementia-higher-risk-women-472616</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:11:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Behavioral Therapy For Insomnia May Lower Risk Of Postpartum Depression: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/behavioral-therapy-insomnia-may-lower-risk-postpartum-depression-study-472614 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that getting cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBTi) may serve as a protective factor against postpartum depression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/behavioral-therapy-insomnia-may-lower-risk-postpartum-depression-study-472614</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:32:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Less Sugar In First 1000 Days Of Life Slashes Diabetes, Hypertension Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-sugar-first-1000-days-life-slashes-diabetes-hypertension-risk-study-472612 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that limiting sugar intake during early life could cut the diabetes risk by 35% and the risk of hypertension by 20%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-sugar-first-1000-days-life-slashes-diabetes-hypertension-risk-study-472612</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:07:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Red and Infrared Light Therapy Devices for Enhanced Health and Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-red-infrared-light-therapy-devices-enhanced-health-wellness-472547 <description><![CDATA[Red and infrared light therapy devices offer a plethora of benefits for those seeking to enhance their health and well-being. From promoting wound healing to improving skin health and alleviating pain, these innovative tools are paving the way for a holistic approach to health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-red-infrared-light-therapy-devices-enhanced-health-wellness-472547</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:35:07 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>