<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Poor Sleep In 40s May Add Years To Your Brain Age: Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poor-sleep-40s-may-add-years-your-brain-age-study-finds-472579 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found that poor sleep in the middle ages is linked to accelerated brain aging in the next ten years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poor-sleep-40s-may-add-years-your-brain-age-study-finds-472579</guid><pubDate> Fri, 25 Oct 2024 04:05:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Diabetes Onset Before 40 Raises Risk Of Death To Four Times: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-onset-before-40-raises-risk-death-four-times-study-472578 <description><![CDATA[Diagnosing diabetes before 40 quadrupled the risk of early death and later onset was linked to a one-and-a-half times higher risk of death compared with the general population without the condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-onset-before-40-raises-risk-death-four-times-study-472578</guid><pubDate> Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:23:40 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Curious About Your Aging? Here's A Simple Test To Find Out]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/curious-about-your-aging-heres-simple-test-find-out-472576 <description><![CDATA[Balance is a better measure of biological aging than muscle strength or gait, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/curious-about-your-aging-heres-simple-test-find-out-472576</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:46:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleep Loss In Babies Linked To Risk Of Autism Spectrum Disorder: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-loss-babies-linked-risk-autism-spectrum-disorder-study-472573 <description><![CDATA[Researchers investigated how sleep loss during early life impacts key parts of brain development and discovered it can  increase the risk of developing autism spectrum disorder.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-loss-babies-linked-risk-autism-spectrum-disorder-study-472573</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 02:48:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even Single Jog Reduces Diabetes Risk, Benefits Notable By Next Day: Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-single-jog-reduces-diabetes-risk-benefits-notable-next-day-says-study-472570 <description><![CDATA[The study reveals that even a single bout of exercise could help reduce type 2 diabetes risk factors, with benefits notable by the next day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-single-jog-reduces-diabetes-risk-benefits-notable-next-day-says-study-472570</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 01:59:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[History Of Eating Disorders, Pre-Pregnancy Obesity Raises Offspring's Risk Of Mental Health Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/history-eating-disorders-pre-pregnancy-obesity-raises-offsprings-risk-mental-health-diagnosis-472567 <description><![CDATA[The study found associations between a mother's history of eating disorders and pre-pregnancy body mass index (BMI) higher than the normal weight range to most of the nine psychiatric diagnoses examined in the offspring.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/history-eating-disorders-pre-pregnancy-obesity-raises-offsprings-risk-mental-health-diagnosis-472567</guid><pubDate> Wed, 23 Oct 2024 07:18:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Scurvy Returns: Study Says Cost Of Living Crisis And Weight-Loss Surgeries Drive Resurgence]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scurvy-returns-study-says-cost-living-crisis-weight-loss-surgeries-drive-resurgence-472566 <description><![CDATA[Scurvy, a dietary deficiency disease, once considered a thing of the past is making a surprising comeback.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scurvy-returns-study-says-cost-living-crisis-weight-loss-surgeries-drive-resurgence-472566</guid><pubDate> Wed, 23 Oct 2024 03:57:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[1 Dead, Dozens Hospitalized From E-Coli Outbreak Linked To McDonald's Quarter Pounders]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/1-dead-dozens-hospitalized-e-coli-outbreak-linked-mcdonalds-quarter-pounders-472565 <description><![CDATA[Officials are urging the public to contact their healthcare provider if they experience E. coli symptoms after eating a McDonald's Quarter Pounder hamburger.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/1-dead-dozens-hospitalized-e-coli-outbreak-linked-mcdonalds-quarter-pounders-472565</guid><pubDate> Wed, 23 Oct 2024 01:21:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitamin D Deficiency In Kids Raises Risk Of Auto-Immune Disorders: Study Explains How]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-deficiency-kids-raises-risk-auto-immune-disorders-study-explains-how-472563 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed how a deficiency of vitamin D in young children can raise the risk of developing autoimmune disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-deficiency-kids-raises-risk-auto-immune-disorders-study-explains-how-472563</guid><pubDate> Tue, 22 Oct 2024 05:22:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Warns Of Unusual Rise In Walking Pneumonia Cases Among Young Children]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-unusual-rise-walking-pneumonia-cases-among-young-children-472561 <description><![CDATA[According to the latest CDC report, this year has seen a spike in cases since late spring, particularly among young children, a shift from previous years when most cases were reported in school-aged children and adolescents.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-unusual-rise-walking-pneumonia-cases-among-young-children-472561</guid><pubDate> Tue, 22 Oct 2024 03:48:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Strokes Can Be Deadly But Preventable: Guidelines To Reduce Your Risk Of First Stroke]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/中风-can-deadly-preventable-guidelines-reduce-your-risk-first-中风-472559 <description><![CDATA[The current stroke prevention guidelines issued by the American Stroke Association replace the 2014 guidelines and target the prevention of the first stroke.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/中风-can-deadly-preventable-guidelines-reduce-your-risk-first-中风-472559</guid><pubDate> Tue, 22 Oct 2024 02:11:47 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>