<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealthcare Interrupted Cancer Patient's Surgery to Demand Justification for Overnight Hospital Stay: 'Insurance Is Out of Control']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unitedhealthcare-interrupted-cancer-患者-surgery-demand-justification-overnight-hospital-472945 <description><![CDATA[A surgeon shared her frustration after her patient's operation was interrupted by UnitedHealthcare's demand to justify the patient's overnight hospital stay.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unitedhealthcare-interrupted-cancer-患者-surgery-demand-justification-overnight-hospital-472945</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 16:31:18 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Kansas Set a New State Record for Abortions in 2023. Most of the Patients Were from Texas]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kansas-set-new-state-record-abortions-2023-most-患者-were-texas-472944 <description><![CDATA[The largest group of patients to receive an abortion in Kansas were Texas residents, according to a report released by the Kansas Department of Health and Environment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kansas-set-new-state-record-abortions-2023-most-患者-were-texas-472944</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 15:19:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New FDA Guidelines On Lead In Baby Food 'Insufficient', Say Health Advocates, Calling For Stricter Limits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-fda-guidelines-lead-baby-food-insufficient-say-health-advocates-calling-stricter-limits-472942 <description><![CDATA[As part of its "Closer to Zero" initiative to reduce toxic elements like lead in foods, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration unveiled new guidelines for lead in baby food this week.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-fda-guidelines-lead-baby-food-insufficient-say-health-advocates-calling-stricter-limits-472942</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 04:38:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gastroenterologist's Fruit Washing Tip: One Simple Inexpensive Ingredient You Already Have In Your Kitchen]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gastroenterologies-fruit-washing-tip-one-simple-inexpective-ingredient-you-already-have-your-472940 <description><![CDATA[For those seeking the right technique to wash fruits, you don't need expensive fruit-washing liquids. All you need is one simple, inexpensive ingredient already in your kitchen.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gastroenterologies-fruit-washing-tip-one-simple-inexpective-ingredient-you-already-have-your-472940</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 03:01:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Coffee For Heart Health: Timing Matters More Than Quantity-Here's Best Time To Drink]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/coffee-heart-health-timing-matters-more-quantity-heres-best-time-drink-472937 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that people who drink coffee in the morning have a lower risk of death from cardiovascular disease and overall mortality risk compared to all-day coffee drinkers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/coffee-heart-health-timing-matters-more-quantity-heres-best-time-drink-472937</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 01:07:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[VRenity: The Next Step In The Field Of Mental Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vrenity-next-step-field-mental-health-472936 <description><![CDATA[VRenity's ultimate goal with its software is to harness cutting-edge virtual reality technology to boost mental wellness in the workplace, and to build upon the mind and body pillars of their model's design.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vrenity-next-step-field-mental-health-472936</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 12:57:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Erectile Dysfunction Treatment Provider Donates $1 Million to Trump Inauguration]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/erectile-dysfunction-treatment-provider-donates-1-million-trump-inauguration-472935 <description><![CDATA[Hims &amp; Hers is the latest US corporation to donate $1 million to President-elect Donald Trump's ever-growing inauguration fund.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/erectile-dysfunction-treatment-provider-donates-1-million-trump-inauguration-472935</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 12:31:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fluoride In Drinking Water Linked To Lower IQ Scores In Children: Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluide-drinking-water-linked-lower-iq-scores-children-study-reveals-472933 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that even a slight increase in fluoride levels was associated with a 1.63-point decrease in IQ in children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluide-drinking-water-linked-lower-iq-scores-children-study-reveals-472933</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 05:37:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Plant-Based Milk Alternatives Linked To Increased Risk Of Depression: Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/plant-based-milk-alternatives-linked-increased-risk-depression-study-reveals-472932 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that drinking plant-based milk alternatives, such as soy, oat, and almond milk, is linked to an increased risk of depression, while semi-skimmed cow's milk may offer protective benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/plant-based-milk-alternatives-linked-increased-risk-depression-study-reveals-472932</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 04:12:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teen's Breast Grew To Triple G-Cup Size After COVID Vaccinations: Researchers Call It 'Exceedingly Rare']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-breast-grew-triple-g-cup-size-after-covid-vaccinations-researchers-call-it-exceedingly-472931 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have identified the condition as Pseudoangiomatous stromal hyperplasia (PASH)-associated gigantomastia, an "exceedingly rare" condition linked to COVID-19 vaccination.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-breast-grew-triple-g-cup-size-after-covid-vaccinations-researchers-call-it-exceedingly-472931</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:43:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bird Flu Claims First US Victim As Louisiana Man Dies in Hospital]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-claims-first-us-victim-louisiana-man-dies-hospital-472929 <description><![CDATA[A patient that had been hospitalized with avian influenza, otherwise known as bird flu, has died following a stay in the hospital.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-claims-first-us-victim-louisiana-man-dies-hospital-472929</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:45:48 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>