<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Reveals 5 Signs Of Fatty Liver You Can Check At Home]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-reveals-5-signs-fatty-liver-you-can-check-home-473020 <description><![CDATA[The symptoms of liver damage may be subtle and are easy to miss in the early stages. A gastroenterologist from California, reveals five key symptoms of fatty liver disease that everyone should watch for.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-reveals-5-signs-fatty-liver-you-can-check-home-473020</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 Jan 2025 02:10:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Dismisses Eye Twitching And Headaches As Stress—Discovers Rare Tumor That Left Her Face Paralyzed]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-dismisses-eye-twitching-headaches-stressdiscovers-rare-tumor-that-left-her-face-paralyzed-473018 <description><![CDATA[What seemed as a harmless eye twitching and stress-induced headaches turned into a devastating diagnosis for a young mother from the U.K.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-dismisses-eye-twitching-headaches-stressdiscovers-rare-tumor-that-left-her-face-paralyzed-473018</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 Jan 2025 01:01:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Promising New Therapy Emerges For Children With Acute Flaccid Myelitis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/promising-new-therapy-emerges-children-acute-flaccid-myelitis-473006 <description><![CDATA[Treating conditions like AFM requires a high level of pediatric neurology and rehabilitation expertise.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/promising-new-therapy-emerges-children-acute-flaccid-myelitis-473006</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 Jan 2025 18:06:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Sleep Due To Stress? Doc Shares Tips To Calm Your Mind Before Bed]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-sleep-due-stress-doc-shares-tips-calm-your-mind-before-bed-473017 <description><![CDATA[According to a sleep specialist the secret to calming your mind before sleep is not avoiding these thoughts, but addressing them during a scheduled "worry time"]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-sleep-due-stress-doc-shares-tips-calm-your-mind-before-bed-473017</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 Jan 2025 04:42:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Weight In This Body Area May Raise Cancer Risk Even If You Exercise Regularly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-weight-this-body-area-may-raise-cancer-risk-even-if-you-exercise-regularly-473014 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that it may not just be a higher Body Mass Index (BMI), but excess weight in a specific area of the body, that could increase cancer risk, even for those who exercise regularly.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-weight-this-body-area-may-raise-cancer-risk-even-if-you-exercise-regularly-473014</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 Jan 2025 03:03:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man's Speech Struggle Initially Dismissed As Laryngitis Was Stage 4 Cancer, Given 6 Months To Live]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mans-speech-struggle-initially-dismissed-laryngitis-was-stage-4-cancer-given-6-months-live-473012 <description><![CDATA[The man, who had been told for months that there was nothing to worry about regarding his speech struggles, was diagnosed with stage 4 throat cancer nearly a year after the symptoms first appeared.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mans-speech-struggle-initially-dismissed-laryngitis-was-stage-4-cancer-given-6-months-live-473012</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 Jan 2025 01:05:45 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Got Prediabetes? Nutritionist Recommends Simple Hacks To Reverse It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-prediabetes-nutritionist-recommends-simple-hacks-reverse-it-473010 <description><![CDATA[Prediabetes could be the beginning of all your chronic woes. But what if you could reverse the condition without medications or complicated treatments?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-prediabetes-nutritionist-recommends-simple-hacks-reverse-it-473010</guid><pubDate> Tue, 21 Jan 2025 03:11:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hospice Nurse Shares One Thing That Most People Regret On Deathbeds—And It's Not Often Discussed]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospice-nurse-shares-one-thing-that-most-people-regret-deathbeds-its-not-often-discussed-473009 <description><![CDATA[While spending too much time working is a common regret, a hospice nurse who has witnessed thousands on deathbed reveals an issue shared by many but often overlooked.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospice-nurse-shares-one-thing-that-most-people-regret-deathbeds-its-not-often-discussed-473009</guid><pubDate> Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:26:52 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[BMI, Waist Size Aren't Only Risk Factors Of Heart Disease, This Hidden Fat May Matter More]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bmi-waist-size-arent-only-risk-factors-heart-disease-this-hidden-fat-may-matter-more-473007 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that "intermuscular fat", not BMI or waist measurement, may be a more accurate predictor of heart disease risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bmi-waist-size-arent-only-risk-factors-heart-disease-this-hidden-fat-may-matter-more-473007</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 Jan 2025 04:40:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Kids Not Sleeping Well? Not Just Caffeine And Chocolate; Doc Shares Sneaky Culprits That Steal Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kids-not-sleeping-well-not-just-caffeine-chocolate-doc-shares-sneaky-culprits-that-steal-sleep-473004 <description><![CDATA[For parents with light sleepers at home, a sleep doctor suggests paying close attention to what they eat, especially before bedtime.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kids-not-sleeping-well-not-just-caffeine-chocolate-doc-shares-sneaky-culprits-that-steal-sleep-473004</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:25:13 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiac Surgeon's Tips: Detect Heart Blockages At Home Without Tests, Stay Safe If Home Alone During Attack]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-surgeons-tips-detect-heart-blocks-home-without-tests-stay-safe-if-home-alone-during-473002 <description><![CDATA[What if you could spot the body's red flags of a heart attack and act in time? It could save lives.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-surgeons-tips-detect-heart-blocks-home-without-tests-stay-safe-if-home-alone-during-473002</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 Jan 2025 01:22:37 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>