<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Tummy Fat Linked To Widespread Chronic Pain, Particularly For Women: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-tummy-fat-linked-widespread-chronic-pain-pspecially-women-study-472323 <description><![CDATA[The study explored how excess fat tissue around the abdomen affects the risk of chronic musculoskeletal pain at multiple body sites.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-tummy-fat-linked-widespread-chronic-pain-pspecially-women-study-472323</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 02:01:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Blood Glucose Test Strips: Top Choices For Accurate Diabetes Management]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-blood-glucose-test-strips-top-choices-accurate-diabetes-management-472313 <description><![CDATA[Blood glucose test strips are essential for managing diabetes, providing crucial data on blood sugar levels. This comprehensive guide explores what blood glucose test strips are, their uses, and the benefits of regular testing.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-blood-glucose-test-strips-top-choices-accurate-diabetes-management-472313</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:16:54 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Cervical Pillows To Help You Sleep Better And Reduce Neck Pain]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cervical-pillows-help-you-sleep-better-reduce-neck-pain-472287 <description><![CDATA[A cervical pillow, also commonly known as an orthopedic pillow, is especially designed to cure cervical problems, correct the positioning of the body, and prevent neck pain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cervical-pillows-help-you-sleep-better-reduce-neck-pain-472287</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:55:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Anti-Snoring Devices: Effective Solutions For A Restful Night]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-anti-snoring-devices- effective-solutions-restful-night-472301 <description><![CDATA[Snoring affects many people, disrupting sleep and causing discomfort for both the snorer and their partner. Anti-snoring devices are designed to mitigate this issue by addressing the underlying causes of snoring.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-anti-snoring-devices- effective-solutions-restful-night-472301</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:00:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smoking Before 18 Linked To Respiratory Symptoms In 20's: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smoking-before-18-linked-respiratory-symptoms-20s-study-472317 <description><![CDATA[The latest study investigated how starting smoking before the age of 18 affects respiratory health in early adulthood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smoking-before-18-linked-respiratory-symptoms-20s-study-472317</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 03:51:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salmonella Outbreak Linked To Eggs Leaves Dozens Hospitalized Across 9 States]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-eggs-leaves-dozens-hospitalized-across-9-states-472316 <description><![CDATA[In the recent outbreak linked to contaminated chicken eggs, 63 people fell ill, 24 were hospitalized, and no deaths have been reported.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-eggs-leaves-dozens-hospitalized-across-9-states-472316</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 02:35:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Type 2 Diabetes And Asthma: Study Identifies Two-Way Relationship Between The Conditions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/type-2-diabetes-asthma-study-identizes-two-way-relationship- Between-conditions-472314 <description><![CDATA[Diabetes patients are at an increased risk of developing asthma and the relationship between the two conditions is reciprocal, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/type-2-diabetes-asthma-study-identizes-two-way-relationship- Between-conditions-472314</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 01:15:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Lumbar Pillows: Top Choices To Support Your Back, Improve Posture]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lumbar-pillows-top-choices-support-your-back-improve-posture-472292 <description><![CDATA[Poor posture can lead to severe lower back pain, especially for those who sit for long periods. Lumbar pillows provide an easy solution by relieving pressure on the lower spine and helping maintain good posture. These orthopedic support pillows fit snugly between the spine and the sitting surface, adapting to the body's natural curve to offer maximum support and evenly distribute weight.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lumbar-pillows-top-choices-support-your-back-improve-posture-472292</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 12:48:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Coccyx Cushions To Alleviate Tailbone Pain And Improve Comfort: Top Picks For Every Need]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-coccyx-cushions-alleviate-tailbone-pain-improve-comfort-top-picks-every-need-472293 <description><![CDATA[Coccyx cushions are a simple yet effective solution for tailbone pain and discomfort. Whether you're looking for cooling relief, portability, or orthopedic support, there's a coccyx cushion to meet your specific needs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-coccyx-cushions-alleviate-tailbone-pain-improve-comfort-top-picks-every-need-472293</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 12:45:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best SAM-e Supplements For Mental And Physical Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-supplements-sam-e-mental-physical-health-472266 <description><![CDATA[SAM-e is a versatile compound with potential benefits for mood support, joint health, liver function, and cognitive health. As a naturally occurring molecule involved in various biochemical processes, SAM-e plays a crucial role in maintaining overall health and well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-supplements-sam-e-mental-physical-health-472266</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 12:41:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unlocking The Full Health Potential Of Probiotics: Beyond Digestive Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unlocking-full-health-potial-probiotics-beyond-digestive-benefits-472302 <description><![CDATA[Incorporating probiotics into your diet can support not only a healthy gut but also improve respiratory function and cardiovascular health, promoting overall well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unlocking-full-health-potial-probiotics-beyond-digestive-benefits-472302</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Sep 2024 12:38:45 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>