<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Benefits Of Atlantic Diet: Researchers Say It Reduces Risk Of Metabolic Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-atlantic-diet-researchers-say-it-reduces-risk-metabolic-syndrome-471381 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found that the Atlantic Diet, a traditional diet pattern in Portugal and Galicia, a region in northwest Spain could help reduce the risk of metabolic syndrome.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-atlantic-diet-researchers-say-it-reduces-risk-metabolic-syndrome-471381</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:55:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Green Juice Products For Nutrient-Rich Refreshment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-green-juice-products- Nutrition-rich-refreshment-471212 <description><![CDATA[Each of these offerings presents a unique and flavorful approach to nutrient-rich refreshment]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-green-juice-products- Nutrition-rich-refreshment-471212</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:14:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gentle Relief: Navigating Interstitial Cystitis With CYSTASOLV IC/PBS Dietary Supplement]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/gentle-relief-navigating-interstitial-cystitis-cystasolv-ic-pbs-dietary-supplement-471211 <description><![CDATA[CYSTASOLV is altering the story for individuals seeking relief from the agony of Interstitial Cystitis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/gentle-relief-navigating-interstitial-cystitis-cystasolv-ic-pbs-dietary-supplement-471211</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:01:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exploring The Power Of Oral Probiotics For Immune And Oral Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-power-oral-probiotics-immune-oral-health-471251 <description><![CDATA[Explore how oral probiotics can boost your immune and oral health. Learn about the best oral probiotics out there.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-power-oral-probiotics-immune-oral-health-471251</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:45:10 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Swift Strep: Accelerating Diagnoses With Rapid Strep Tests]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/swift-strep-acceleating-diagnoses-rapid-strep-tests-471250 <description><![CDATA[Strep throat is common but understanding how to diagnose it through strep tests and adopting preventive measures can help safeguard against its impact.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/swift-strep-acceleating-diagnoses-rapid-strep-tests-471250</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:24:49 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stay Energized: A Comprehensive Review Of The Best Electrolyte Product For Optimal Hydration And Performance]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/stay-energized-compressive-review-best- electrolyte-product-optimal-Hydration-performance-471259 <description><![CDATA[Explore the best electrolyte product and learn why it's the optimal choice for hydration.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/stay-energized-compressive-review-best- electrolyte-product-optimal-Hydration-performance-471259</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:10:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Shining Bright: GLO24K GLO24K Recognized Among Top 10 Innovative Skincare Companies]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/shining-bright-glo24k-glo24k-recognized-among-top-10-innovative-skincare-companies-471311 <description><![CDATA[Experience luxury for all with GLO24K's affordable "Unleash the Power of Gold'' skincare line, recognized among the top 10 innovative skincare companies of 2023.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/shining-bright-glo24k-glo24k-recognized-among-top-10-innovative-skincare-companies-471311</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 14:54:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Menstrual Cups Unveiled: Unlocking Benefits, Tips And Essential Information]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/menstrual-cups-unveiled-unlocking-benefits-tips-essential-information-471317 <description><![CDATA[Explore the realm of menstrual cups: embrace sustainability, comfort and empowerment with the Pixie Combo Kit.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/menstrual-cups-unveiled-unlocking-benefits-tips-essential-information-471317</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 14:36:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salt Soothe: Enhancing Wellness With Top 5 Epsom Salts]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salt-soothe-enhancing-wellness-top-5-epsom-salts-471378 <description><![CDATA[Are you seeking an affordable and natural way to relieve muscle soreness? Here are the top 5 Epsom salts with premium ingredients to help soothe your aches.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salt-soothe-enhancing-wellness-top-5-epsom-salts-471378</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:49:34 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[PopShine: Unveiling Your Signature Smile With Confidence And Sensitivity-Free Whitening Solutions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/popshine-unveiling-your-signature-smile-confidence-sensitivity-free-whitening-solutions-471316 <description><![CDATA[Reveal your signature smile with PopShine's teeth-whitening solutions. Say goodbye to sensitivity and embrace a brighter, more confident you.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/popshine-unveiling-your-signature-smile-confidence-sensitivity-free-whitening-solutions-471316</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:38:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Savoring Wellness: Apple Cider's Benefits in Delicious Gummies]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/savoring-wellness-apple-ciders-benefits-delicious-gummies-471318 <description><![CDATA[Transform your health with the goodness of apple cider, now in gummy form. Embrace a flavorful journey to good health and vitality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/savoring-wellness-apple-ciders-benefits-delicious-gummies-471318</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:26:59 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>