<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[New Highly Mutated COVID-19 Variant Is Less Immune-Evasive, Lab Tests Suggest]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-highly-mutated-covid-19-variant-less-immune-evasive-lab-tests-suggest-470746 <description><![CDATA[Based on two separate lab test results in the U.S. experts now believe the new variant is less contagious and immune evasive than feared.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-highly-mutated-covid-19-variant-less-immune-evasive-lab-tests-suggest-470746</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Sep 2023 04:09:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Floatation Therapy For Treating Anorexia? Study Says Novel Technique Reduces Body Image Dissatisfaction]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/floatation-therapy-treating-anorexia-study-says-novel-technique-reduces-body-image-dissatisfaction-470744 <description><![CDATA[Researchers noticed significant reductions in body image dissatisfaction in patients who took a one-hour floatation therapy two times a week for four weeks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/floatation-therapy-treating-anorexia-study-says-novel-technique-reduces-body-image-dissatisfaction-470744</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Sep 2023 02:55:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Merkel Cell Carcinoma: Know All About The Rare Skin Cancer That Killed Jimmy Buffett]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/merkel-cell-carcinoma-know-all-about-rare-skin-cancer-that-killed-jimmy-buffett-470743 <description><![CDATA[Merkel Cell Carcinoma is an aggressive form of skin cancer that develops on Merkel cells found on the skin's outermost layer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/merkel-cell-carcinoma-know-all-about-rare-skin-cancer-that-killed-jimmy-buffett-470743</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:57:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smoking Doubles The Risk Of Depression, Bipolar Disorder, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smoking-doubles-risk-depression-bipolar-disorder-study-says-470741 <description><![CDATA[Researchers believe the mental health issues from smoking might be due to the brain damage caused by nicotine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smoking-doubles-risk-depression-bipolar-disorder-study-says-470741</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Sep 2023 04:05:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Meningococcal Outbreak In Virginia Kills 5; Know Symptoms, Ways To Prevent Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meningococcal-outbreak-virginia-kills-5-know-symptoms-ways-prevent-disease-470739 <description><![CDATA[The Virginia health department has announced a statewide outbreak of meningococcal disease after 27 cases were reported.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meningococcal-outbreak-virginia-kills-5-know-symptoms-ways-prevent-disease-470739</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Sep 2023 02:39:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women Who Take Infertility Treatment At Higher Risk Of Stroke In The Year Following Delivery: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-who-take-infertility-treatment-higher-risk-中风-year-following-delivery-study-470738 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that participants who took infertility treatment were at 66% higher risk of getting hospitalized for a stroke within 12 months of delivery when compared to others who spontaneously conceived.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-who-take-infertility-treatment-higher-risk-中风-year-following-delivery-study-470738</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Sep 2023 01:04:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Blood Cancer Medication May Unlock HIV Cure, Researchers Find]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-cancer-medication-may-unlock-hiv-cure-researchers-find-470736 <description><![CDATA[The drug in question is called venetoclax, and it can be repurposed and used to address HIV infection, as per the researchers behind the study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-cancer-medication-may-unlock-hiv-cure-researchers-find-470736</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Sep 2023 06:07:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Higher Levels Of Metal Seen In Blood And Urine Of Marijuana Users: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-levels-metal-seen-blood-urine-marijuana-users-study-470734 <description><![CDATA[Cadmium and lead remain in the body for quite a long time, according to study lead author Tiffany Sanchez.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-levels-metal-seen-blood-urine-marijuana-users-study-470734</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Sep 2023 04:23:40 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Breathe Easy, Feel Better: The Best Air Humidifier Of 2023]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/breathe-easy-feel-better-best-air-humidifier-2023-470733 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top air humidifier of 2023 that promises to enhance your well-being by promoting optimal air moisture levels.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breathe-easy-feel-better-best-air-humidifier-2023-470733</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:27:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teen Boys Who Smoke Pass On Damaged Genes To Future Offsprings: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen-boys-who-smoke-pass-damaging-genes-future-offsprings-study-470731 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that smoking in the teenage years causes DNA changes in the sperm, which lead to alterations in the DNA of their future babies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen-boys-who-smoke-pass-damaging-genes-future-offsprings-study-470731</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 04:13:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Strive For A Balanced Diet: Study Says Extreme Dietary Habits Involving Carbs And Fats Affect Longevity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strive-balanced-diet-study-says-extreme-dietary-habits-involving-carbs-fats-affect-longevity-470729 <description><![CDATA[The key to longevity is following a balanced diet rather than putting the body through extreme dietary habits involving carbs and fats, according to a new study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strive-balanced-diet-study-says-extreme-dietary-habits-involving-carbs-fats-affect-longevity-470729</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:58:18 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>