<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>看</language><item><title><![CDATA[Sitting For More Than 10 Hours Daily May Raise Dementia Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sitting-more-10-hours-daily-may-raise-dementia-risk-470796 <description><![CDATA[A new study suggests that total sedentary time, irrespective of the pattern in which they are accumulated daily, elevates the risk of dementia in people aged above 60.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sitting-more-10-hours-daily-may-raise-dementia-risk-470796</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Sep 2023 03:03:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Using Tobacco And Cannabis Increases Risk Of Anxiety, Depression, Researchers Warn]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/using-tobacco-cannabis-increases-risk-of-anxiety-depression-researchers-warn-470793 <description><![CDATA[People who used both tobacco and cannabis were approximately 1.8 times more likely to have mental health disorders compared to non-users.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/using-tobacco-cannabis-increases-risk-of-anxiety-depression-researchers-warn-470793</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Sep 2023 02:47:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smoking Speeds Up Aging, Quitting The Habit May Reduce The Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smoking-speeds-aging-quitting-habit-may-reduce-risk-study-470792 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that smoking causes chromosomal damage and speeds up aging. The risk of damage can be reduced by quitting the habit.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smoking-speeds-aging-quitting-habit-may-reduce-risk-study-470792</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Sep 2023 01:16:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Covid's Back: Here's What To Know This Fall And Winter]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covids-back-here-what-know-this-fall-winter-4 <description><![CDATA[Covid is less seasonal than the flu, more contagious, and over the last three U.S. winters peaked from December to January, while flu peaks later.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covids-back-here-what-know-this-fall-winter-4</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:24:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Dies From Rare Infection After Eating Raw Oysters; Know Signs, Ways To Prevent It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-man-dies-rare-infection-after-eating-raw-oysters-know-signs-ways-to-prevent-it-470787 <description><![CDATA[A man in his 30s, who had underlying health conditions, died after contracting Vibrio vulnificus infection, which is transmitted through consumption of raw or undercooked oysters or other shellfish.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-man-dies-rare-infection-after-eating-raw-oysters-know-signs-ways-to-prevent-it-470787</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Sep 2023 03:51:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Turmeric Help Treat Indigestion? Scientists Say It's As Effective As Antacids]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-turmeric-help-treat-indigestion-scientists-say-its- effective-antacids-470786 <description><![CDATA[Although turmeric is used in various parts of the world for treating indigestion, its benefits in comparison to conventional drugs remain understudied.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-turmeric-help-treat-indigestion-scientists-say-its- effective-antacids-470786</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Sep 2023 03:13:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Yoga Awareness Month: Experts Share Tips To Boost Memory And Concentration]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-yoga-awareness-month-experts-share-tips-boost-memory-concentration-470784 <description><![CDATA[In this National Yoga Awareness Month, experts share their thoughts on how yoga benefits the body, especially in boosting memory and concentration.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-yoga-awareness-month-experts-share-tips-boost-memory-concentration-470784</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Sep 2023 02:30:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Approves Updated COVID Vaccines; Here's What You Need To Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-approves-updated-covid-vaccines-here-what-you-need-to-know-470781 <description><![CDATA[Health authorities hope the updated vaccines will provide better protection against serious consequences of COVID-19, including hospitalization and death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-approves-updated-covid-vaccines-here-what-you-need-to-know-470781</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 05:00:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[7 Healthy Lifestyle Habits To Prevent Depression; Researchers Say Sleep Is The Most Important Factor]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/7-healthy-lifestyle-habits-prevent-depression-researchers-say-sleep-most-important-factor-470778 <description><![CDATA[Getting a good night's sleep has a significant impact, as it can reduce the risk of depression by 22%, a team from the University of Cambridge and Fudan University has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/7-healthy-lifestyle-habits-prevent-depression-researchers-say-sleep-most-important-factor-470778</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 02:44:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Keto Diet May Lead To Weight Loss, Improve Fertility In Women With PCOS: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keto-diet-may-improve-weight-loss-fertility-women-pcos-study-470777 <description><![CDATA[Researchers evaluated data from seven clinical trials and found significant improvements in weight loss, fertility and testosterone levels in women who followed the ketogenic diet for at least 45 days.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keto-diet-may-improve-weight-loss-fertility-women-pcos-study-470777</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 01:24:26 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Key Ingredient That's NOT In Your Toothpaste]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-ingredient-that-is-not-your-toothpaste-470769 <description><![CDATA[Discover the essential missing component in your toothpaste, unraveling the mystery of its absence.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-ingredient-that-is-not-your-toothpaste-470769</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:44:38 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>