<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Strange 'Werewolf Syndrome' In Spain, Infants Resembling 'Wookiees' After Parents Use Hair Loss Remedy: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strange-werewolf-syndrome-spain-infants-resembling-wookies-after-parents-use-hair-loss-472776 <description><![CDATA[A strange condition known as "Werewolf Syndrome" has left nearly a dozen babies in Spain covered in hair, with extreme cases even resembling the iconic Wookiees from Star Wars.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strange-werewolf-syndrome-spain-infants-resembling-wookies-after-parents-use-hair-loss-472776</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Dec 2024 04:42:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Thigh Fat? Your Favorite Breakfast Choice Might Be To Blame]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-thigh-fat-your-favorite-breakfast-choice-might-blame-472775 <description><![CDATA[Did you know that cereals, a popular breakfast choice for many, could be contributing to fat accumulation in your thighs?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-thigh-fat-your-favorite-breakfast-choice-might-blame-472775</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Dec 2024 02:24:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mystery Illness Claims Nearly 150 Lives In Africa, Sparking Pandemic Fears]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mystery-illness-claims-nearly-150-lives-africa-sparking-pandemic-fears-472772 <description><![CDATA[. Health officials, including those from the WHO, are investing the mysterious illness with flu-like symptoms that killed dozens of people in southwest Congo.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mystery-illness-claims-nearly-150-lives-africa-sparking-pandemic-fears-472772</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:47:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthem Blue Cross Plans Won't Cover Anesthesia for Entire Length of Surgeries That Exceed Time Limit: 'It's a Cynical Money Grab']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anthem-blue-cross-plans-wont-cover-anesthesia-entire-length-surgeries-that-exceed-time-limit-472769 <description><![CDATA[Anthem Blue Cross Blue Shield has a new policy to limit anesthesia coverage based on arbitrary time caps.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anthem-blue-cross-plans-wont-cover-anesthesia-entire-length-surgeries-that-exceed-time-limit-472769</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Dec 2024 19:21:54 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Spritz Of Hairspray, Splash Of Perfume: Watch Out, These Daily Cosmetics Could Harm Your Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spritz-hairspra​​y-splash-perfume-watch-out-these-daily-cosmetics-could-harm-your-health-472766 <description><![CDATA[Read the label of your cosmetics. Phthalates, commonly found in several everyday makeup products, could be gradually entering your body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spritz-hairspra​​y-splash-perfume-watch-out-these-daily-cosmetics-could-harm-your-health-472766</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Dec 2024 04:49:18 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Algae Oil? This Michelin-Starred Chef Vouched Cooking Oil May Be Healthier And Tastier Alternative]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-algae-oil-this-michelin-starred-chef-vouched-cooking-oil-may-healthier-tastier-alternative-472764 <description><![CDATA[For food enthusiasts and home cooks looking for a healthy cooking oil without compromising on flavor, algae oil could be an alternative.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-algae-oil-this-michelin-starred-chef-vouched-cooking-oil-may-healthier-tastier-alternative-472764</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:02:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Disorder Makes Patients Scream In Pain While Vomiting, Causes Teeth Loss: Cannabis-Linked Syndrome On Rise]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-disorder-makes-病人-scream-pain-while-vomiting-causes-teeth-loss-cannabis-linked-472761 <description><![CDATA[Cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome (CHS) is a relatively new term for the acute reaction to cannabis use, characterized by severe bouts of nausea, abdominal pain, and vomiting. Patients often scream and vomit due to the pain, a phenomenon referred to as 'scromiting.']]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-disorder-makes-病人-scream-pain-while-vomiting-causes-teeth-loss-cannabis-linked-472761</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:51:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Your Drinking Water Safe? This Metal In Your Supply May Pose Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-drinking-water-safe-this-metal-your-supply-may-pose-cancer-risk-472760 <description><![CDATA[A recent study conducted in Texas found that even low levels of arsenic in water, below the regulatory threshold of 10 parts per billion, could pose health risks, including an increased risk of kidney cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-drinking-water-safe-this-metal-your-supply-may-pose-cancer-risk-472760</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Dec 2024 04:21:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Treating Appendicitis In Children: Which Is Better, Antibiotics Or Surgery?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/treating-appendicitis-children-which-better-antibiotics-surgery-472757 <description><![CDATA[Treatment with antibiotics is a safe, cost-effective alternative to laparoscopic appendectomy for pediatric uncomplicated appendicitis, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/treating-appendicitis-children-which-better-antibiotics-surgery-472757</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Dec 2024 02:56:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Testosterone Really Fuel Sex Drive? It May Improve Courtship, Not Desire, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-testosterone-really-fuel-sex-drive-it-may-improve-courtship-not-desire-says-study-472754 <description><![CDATA[The fluctuations in testosterone may not influence sexual desire as much as previously thought, suggest a recent study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-testosterone-really-fuel-sex-drive-it-may-improve-courtship-not-desire-says-study-472754</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Dec 2024 00:49:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Depression May Trigger Severe Period Pain, Sleep Disturbances May Aggravate It: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-may-trigger-severe-period-pain-sleep-disturbances-may-aggravate-it-study-472753 <description><![CDATA[A recent study found that depression may actually trigger severe period pain, with sleep deprivation worsening its severity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-may-trigger-severe-period-pain-sleep-disturbances-may-aggravate-it-study-472753</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:48:55 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>