<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Protein Powders For Weight Loss In 2024: Shedding Pounds The Healthy Way]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-powders-weight-loss-shedding-pounds-healthy-way-471595 <description><![CDATA[If you are trying to lose weight, but would like make sure your body derives the optimum nutrition, then taking protein powder for weight loss is the way to go.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-powders-weight-loss-shedding-pounds-healthy-way-471595</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Apr 2024 11:24:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Got 15 Minutes? Study Suggests That's All You Need To Exercise For Immunity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-15-minutes-study-suggests-thats-all-you-need-exercise-immunity-471599 <description><![CDATA[The results of the recent study offer hope to those seeking immunity benefits from exercise but do not have long hours to spend.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-15-minutes-study-suggests-thats-all-you-need-exercise-immunity-471599</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:01:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Viewing Solar Eclipse: Here's How To Protect Eyes From Permanent Damage]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viewing-solar-eclipse-heres-how-protect-eyes-permanent-damage-471597 <description><![CDATA[A brief direct glance at the sun during an eclipse for as short as 100 seconds, can trigger permanent eye damage. Here's how to view solar eclipse safely.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viewing-solar-eclipse-heres-how-protect-eyes-permanent-damage-471597</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:36:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Hearing Aids For 2024: Enhance Your Hearing And Quality Of Life]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hearing-aids-enhance-your-hearing-quality-life-471591 <description><![CDATA[Several people who suffer from hearing loss can benefit from a hearing aid. Explore top hearing aids and rediscover clear sound.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hearing-aids-enhance-your-hearing-quality-life-471591</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:56:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily Contact With Young Children Increases Pneumonia Risk In Elderly Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-contact-young-children-increases-pneumonia-risk-elderly-adults-study-471594 <description><![CDATA[Adults over the age of 60 who have daily contact with children have six times more risk of being colonized with pneumonia-causing bacteria than those without any contact with children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-contact-young-children-increases-pneumonia-risk-elderly-adults-study-471594</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Apr 2024 04:02:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tuberculosis Cases Confirmed In Chicago Migrant Shelters: Know Symptoms Of Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tuberculosis-cases-confirmed-chicago-migrant-shelters-know-symptoms-infection-471593 <description><![CDATA[The Chicago Department of Public Health has not disclosed the exact number of tuberculosis cases detected, but no reports exist of city residents contracting the infection from exposed migrants who tested positive.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tuberculosis-cases-confirmed-chicago-migrant-shelters-know-symptoms-infection-471593</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Apr 2024 03:14:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Shampoos For Oily Hair In 2024: How To Beat The Grease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shampoos-oily-hair-how-beat-grease-471587 <description><![CDATA[With a myriad of options available in the market, finding the best shampoo for oily hair requires careful consideration of various factors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shampoos-oily-hair-how-beat-grease-471587</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:16:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Electrolyte Powders Of 2024: Enhance Hydration With These Super Picks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- electrolyte-powders-enhance-Hydration-these-super-picks-471580 <description><![CDATA[Keeping yourself hydrated throughout the day is no longer a problem, thanks to some of the best electrolyte powders available today.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- electrolyte-powders-enhance-Hydration-these-super-picks-471580</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Apr 2024 10:30:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Mouthwashes For 2024: Achieve Fresh Breath And Optimal Oral Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-mouthwashes-achieve-fresh-breath-optimal-oral-health-471576 <description><![CDATA[Here, we are exploring the realm of potent mouthwashes that fight the underlying cause of halitosis, while leaving your mouth feeling clean and cool for hours.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-mouthwashes-achieve-fresh-breath-optimal-oral-health-471576</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:53:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Volatile Work Schedule In Early Adulthood Linked To Poor Health Decades Later: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/volatile-work-schedule-early-adulthood-linked-poor-health-decades-later-study-471585 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that working outside the typical 9–5 schedule in early adulthood can worsen a person's health by the age of 50.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/volatile-work-schedule-early-adulthood-linked-poor-health-decades-later-study-471585</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Apr 2024 04:26:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Food Choices Affect Brain? Study Says Balanced Diet Linked To Better Cognition, Mental Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-food-choices-affect-brain-study-says-balanced-diet-linked-better-cognition-mental-health-471584 <description><![CDATA[A balanced diet is associated with better cognitive function and mental health, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-food-choices-affect-brain-study-says-balanced-diet-linked-better-cognition-mental-health-471584</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Apr 2024 03:27:02 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>