<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一个</language><item><title><![CDATA[Cut Back On Makeup During Pregnancy, Lactation: Study Links Increased Use To Harmful PFAS]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-back-makeup-during-pregnancy-lactation-study-links-increased-use-harmful-pfas-472662 <description><![CDATA[The study warns that increased use of personal care products during pregnancy and nursing is linked to higher levels of harmful chemicals such as per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS) in the blood plasma and breast milk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-back-makeup-during-pregnancy-lactation-study-links-increased-use-harmful-pfas-472662</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Nov 2024 04:33:12 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitamin D Supplements May Help Lower Blood Pressure In Older Adults With Obesity; Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-supplements-may-help-lower-blood-Pressure-older-adults-obesity-study-finds-472660 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now suggest that vitamin D supplementation may be an effective, simple way to lower blood pressure levels in elderly adults with obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-supplements-may-help-lower-blood-Pressure-older-adults-obesity-study-finds-472660</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Nov 2024 02:58:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Metformin Use In Pregnancy Linked To Fetal Growth Issues, Obesity And Diabetes Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-use-pregnancy-linked-fetal-growth-issues-obesity-diabetes-risk-study-472659 <description><![CDATA[Although metformin is prescribed during pregnancy to lower the risk of diabetes-related complications, such as obesity and diabetes in children, the study suggests that the drug itself may contribute to these same risks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-use-pregnancy-linked-fetal-growth-issues-obesity-diabetes-risk-study-472659</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Nov 2024 01:05:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Best Time To Get RSV Vaccine During Pregnancy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-time-get-rsv-vaccine-during-pregnancy-472658 <description><![CDATA[Researchers of a recent study found that getting vaccinated earlier in the recommended timeframe, closer to 32 weeks, may offer the best protection for newborns against RSV.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-time-get-rsv-vaccine-during-pregnancy-472658</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Nov 2024 04:34:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Regular Bedtime More Important Than Sleep Quality, Duration For Kid's Behavior: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/regular-bedtime-more-important-sleep-quality-duration-kids-behavior-study-472657 <description><![CDATA[Children with consistent sleep schedules have better control of their emotions and behavior when they work with others or while they are under situations of stress, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/regular-bedtime-more-important-sleep-quality-duration-kids-behavior-study-472657</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Nov 2024 23:21:46 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Loss Drugs May Lower Risk Of Subsequent Heart Attacks, Strokes In Stroke Survivors: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-may-lower-risk-subsequent-heart-attacks-中风-中风-幸存者-study-472656 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found that certain classes of weight loss and diabetes medications could be lifesavers for stroke survivors, slashing their risk of future heart attacks, strokes, and even death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-may-lower-risk-subsequent-heart-attacks-中风-中风-幸存者-study-472656</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Nov 2024 23:00:30 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nearly 23% Of Adults Face Long COVID Symptoms: AI-Based Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nearly-23-adults-face-long-covid-symptoms-ai-based-study-reveals-472651 <description><![CDATA[Long COVID, a complex condition with lingering symptoms like fatigue, chronic cough, and brain fog may be affecting far more people than once believed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nearly-23-adults-face-long-covid-symptoms-ai-based-study-reveals-472651</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Nov 2024 05:09:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Childhood BMI Linked To Lung Function Later; Low And High Values Harmful: Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childhood-bmi-linked-lung-function-later-low-high-values-harmful-says-study-472649 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that both high and low BMI values during the critical years of lung development can have lasting harmful effects.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childhood-bmi-linked-lung-function-later-low-high-values-harmful-says-study-472649</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Nov 2024 03:00:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Milk Intake May Increase Heart Disease Risk In Women; Yogurt Healthier Alternative: Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/milk-intake-may-increase-heart-disease-risk-women-yogurt-healthier-alternative-says-study-472647 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that non-fermented milk intake could raise heart disease risk in women while switching to a fermented alternative like yogurt might reduce the risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/milk-intake-may-increase-heart-disease-risk-women-yogurt-healthier-alternative-says-study-472647</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:01:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excessive Daytime Sleepiness In Elderly Might Be Linked To Pre-Dementia Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excessive-daytime-sleepiness-elderly-might-linked-pre-dementia-syndrome-472644 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that elderly adults who have excessive daytime sleepiness are at risk of developing motoric cognitive risk syndrome that can lead to dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excessive-daytime-sleepiness-elderly-might-linked-pre-dementia-syndrome-472644</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Nov 2024 04:40:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Proposes To Ban Popular Decongestant In Cold Medicines Citing 'Not Effective']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-proposes-ban-popular-decongestant-cold-medicines-citing-not- effective-472643 <description><![CDATA[Officials clarified that the proposed ban is not related to the safety of oral phenylephrine and companies may continue selling products containing the ingredient until the order is finalized.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-proposes-ban-popular-decongestant-cold-medicines-citing-not- effective-472643</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Nov 2024 02:56:20 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>