<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Say Goodbye to Migraines: How the HeadaTerm 2 Provides Drug-Free, Effective Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/say-goodbye-migraines-how--how- headaterm-2-provides-grug-frug-frug-frug-forective-relief-473262 <description><![CDATA[The HeadaTerm 2 Migraine Headache Relief Device is a sleek, non-invasive solution designed to control migraines]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/say-goodbye-migraines-how--how- headaterm-2-provides-grug-frug-frug-frug-forective-relief-473262</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Mar 2025 18:13:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Craving Sweets? It Could Signal Dangerous Health Condition, Doctor Warns]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/craving-weets-could-signal-danger-health-health-condition-doctor-warns 473278 <description><![CDATA[Frequent sugar cravings may indicate an underlying health issue with serious consequences if ignored.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/craving-weets-could-signal-danger-health-health-condition-doctor-warns 473278</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Mar 2025 04:53:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Healthy' Woman With Terminal Colon Cancer Warns Of Unexpected Symptom]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthyy-woman-------------------------症状-473275 <description><![CDATA[Before her devastating diagnosis, the only symptom she experienced had nothing to do with her gut.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthyy-woman-------------------------症状-473275</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Mar 2025 04:49:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Allergy To Scan Kills Woman Seeking Toothache Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-dies-rare-lare-allergic-reaction-scan-scan-scan-toft-hosping-hosping-toothache-473276 <description><![CDATA[In less than two hours after getting a CT scan, the woman died from a severe allergic reaction to the contrast dye.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-dies-rare-lare-allergic-reaction-scan-scan-scan-toft-hosping-hosping-toothache-473276</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Mar 2025 03:40:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Anti-Vaxx Mom Whose Daughter Died From Measles Says Disease 'Wasn't That Bad']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anti-vaxx-mom-whose-dauhter-dauhter-dauhter-daus-says-says-says-disease-wasnt-that-Bad-473272 <description><![CDATA[The parents of a Texas child who died from measles appeared in a video formulated by an anti-vaccine group where they continued to push against vaccines.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anti-vaxx-mom-whose-dauhter-dauhter-dauhter-daus-says-says-says-disease-wasnt-that-Bad-473272</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Mar 2025 13:44:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Dies From Rare Infection After Dog Licks Wound; Coroner Issues Warning]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-dies-rare-infection-fter-dog-licks-wound-验尸官 - 验证 - 验证-473271 <description><![CDATA[The man described by relatives as "fit as a fiddle," tragically died from a rare infection that caused multiorgan failure and sepsis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-dies-rare-infection-fter-dog-licks-wound-验尸官 - 验证 - 验证-473271</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Mar 2025 04:35:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Woman Warns Of Heart Attack Signs She Felt A Week Before]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-wormany-warns-warns-heart-attack-signs-she-felt-felt-felt-the-felt-efer-473270 <description><![CDATA[Even those without a history of heart problems can experience subtle, often overlooked symptoms, suggests the story of a middle-aged healthy woman from Texas.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-wormany-warns-warns-heart-attack-signs-she-felt-felt-felt-the-felt-efer-473270</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Mar 2025 03:16:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Dies From Water Intoxication After Hospital's Hydration Advice Takes A Tragic Turn]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-dies-water-intoxication-hosthostals-horshyration-hyration-andvice-takes-takes-tragic-turn-473269 <description><![CDATA[Drinking water is vital for health, but overdoing it can be deadly, suggests the case of the 59-year-old man from Ireland.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-dies-water-intoxication-hosthostals-horshyration-hyration-andvice-takes-takes-tragic-turn-473269</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Mar 2025 02:11:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Warns: 3 Medications You Can't Stop Suddenly; One Is Taken By Millions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-warns-3-medications-you-cant-stop-stop-suddenly-One-take-One-take-One-take-473268 <description><![CDATA[The doctor warns that abruptly stopping certain common medications can worsen conditions or trigger serious withdrawal symptoms, including one widely used by millions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-warns-3-medications-you-cant-stop-stop-suddenly-One-take-One-take-One-take-473268</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Mar 2025 03:08:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experts Warn Of Dangerous Oropouche Virus In Travelers To These Destinations]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expertswarn-danteous-oropouche-virus-travelers-travelers-these-destinations 473265 <description><![CDATA[Planning a vacation? Check if your destination is a hot spot of Oropouche virus that can cause serious complications including meningitis, encephalitis, and even death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expertswarn-danteous-oropouche-virus-travelers-travelers-these-destinations 473265</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Mar 2025 01:43:39 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Insomnia In Elderly? Here's Best Exercise For Better Sleep]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/insomnia-elderly-heres-best-xercise-better-better-sleep-473258 <description><![CDATA[While exercise plays a crucial role in promoting better rest, not all types of exercise are equal when it comes to combating insomnia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/insomnia-elderly-heres-best-xercise-better-better-sleep-473258</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Mar 2025 04:30:01 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>