<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[28-Year-Old, 'Epitome Of Health,' Dies Of Heart Attack; Mom Blames One Habit]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/28岁 -  pepitome-health-dies-health-dies-attack-mom-blames-blames-one-habit-473295 <description><![CDATA[Her grieving mother is speaking out, blaming one surprising habit for her daughter's unexpected death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/28岁 -  pepitome-health-dies-health-dies-attack-mom-blames-blames-one-habit-473295</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 01:48:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Body Measurement Could Predict Cancer Risk In Men]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-body-measurement-could-Perdict-cancer-cancer-cancer-men-473294 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that waist circumference in men may be a stronger predictor of cancer risk than Body Mass Index (BMI).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-body-measurement-could-Perdict-cancer-cancer-cancer-men-473294</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:18:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Daily Drink Could Extend Your Life—Longevity Expert Reveals Best Time To Consume]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-daily-drink-could-extend-your-lifelongevity-expert-expert-reveals-best-time-time-comsume-473291 <description><![CDATA[A beverage that millions of people consume daily can add years to life if consumed at the right time.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-daily-drink-could-extend-your-lifelongevity-expert-expert-reveals-best-time-time-comsume-473291</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:03:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Meat Allergy Spreads As More Tick Species Linked To Alpha-Gal Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-meat-allergy-spreads-more-tick-pecies-link--alpha-alpha-gal-syndrome-473290 <description><![CDATA[Although alpha-gal syndrome has long been linked to the lone star tick, recent cases suggest other tick species in the U.S. may also be responsible, raising concerns about the allergy spreading to new regions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-meat-allergy-spreads-more-tick-pecies-link--alpha-alpha-gal-syndrome-473290</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:31:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Foreigners in Vietnam Prioritise Doctor Expertise When Choosing Healthcare, Survey Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/foreigners-foreigners-prioritise-doctor-expertise-expertise-when-choosing-healthcare-healthcare-survey-survey-finds-473288 <description><![CDATA[A survey by Indochina Research Vietnam shows that foreign residents prioritise doctor expertise, advanced medical equipment, and patient care when selecting healthcare services in Vietnam.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/foreigners-foreigners-prioritise-doctor-expertise-expertise-when-choosing-healthcare-healthcare-survey-survey-finds-473288</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:58:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Hope for Stage IV Cancer Patients: Immunotherapy and Targeted Therapies]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-hope-stage-iv-cancer-patients-mmunotherapy-targeted-therapies-473280 <description><![CDATA[Medical advancements have introduced new stage IV cancer treatment options, providing hope for those facing this difficult diagnosis]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-hope-stage-iv-cancer-patients-mmunotherapy-targeted-therapies-473280</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:58:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Happens When You Quit Carbs? Nutritionist Shares His Results After 7 Days]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-happens-when-you-quit-carbs-nutritionist-shares-shares-his-results-results-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-473286 <description><![CDATA[If you're wondering whether going keto and completely cutting out carbs is a good idea for weight loss, consider the results of a fascinating experiment conducted by an expert nutrition coach.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-happens-when-you-quit-carbs-nutritionist-shares-shares-his-results-results-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-fer-473286</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Mar 2025 05:51:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pairing Two Drugs May Prevent Over 330,000 Annual Deaths]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pairing-two-drugs-may-prevent-330000- and-nulual-dephs-473284 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests a simple two-pill combination for cholesterol management that's not only effective but could save over 330,000 lives each year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pairing-two-drugs-may-prevent-330000- and-nulual-dephs-473284</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Mar 2025 03:02:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Foods That Stay In Your Gut For Days And Harm Health — One A Protein-Packed Favorite]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/foods-that-your-gut-days-harm-harm-harm-harm-harm-health-one-one-pake-take-takeage-takeage-favorite-473283 <description><![CDATA[A gut health nutritionist cautions about four common foods that can linger longer in the digestive system potentially causing long-term health issues.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/foods-that-your-gut-days-harm-harm-harm-harm-harm-health-one-one-pake-take-takeage-takeage-favorite-473283</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Mar 2025 02:43:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Say Goodbye to Migraines: How the HeadaTerm 2 Provides Drug-Free, Effective Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/say-goodbye-migraines-how-head-headaterm-2-provides-grug-frug-frug-frug-forective-relief-473262 <description><![CDATA[The HeadaTerm 2 Migraine Headache Relief Device is a sleek, non-invasive solution designed to control migraines]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/say-goodbye-migraines-how-head-headaterm-2-provides-grug-frug-frug-frug-forective-relief-473262</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Mar 2025 18:13:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Craving Sweets? It Could Signal Dangerous Health Condition, Doctor Warns]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/craving-sweets-it-could-signal-danger-danger-health-tealter-timent-doctor-warns-473278 <description><![CDATA[Frequent sugar cravings may indicate an underlying health issue with serious consequences if ignored.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/craving-sweets-it-could-signal-danger-danger-health-tealter-timent-doctor-warns-473278</guid><pubDate> Fri, 21 Mar 2025 04:53:12 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>