<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Avoid These Combos: Food-Additives That May Raise Your Diabetes Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-these-combos-food-additives-tht-may-raise-your-diabetes-risk-473359 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now identified the exact combination of food additives that could raise the risk of diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-these-combos-food-additives-tht-may-raise-your-diabetes-risk-473359</guid><pubDate> Wed, 09 Apr 2025 03:45:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Miracle' Baby Born To Woman Without Uterus After Receiving Womb Transplant]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/miracle-baby-born-born-without-without-uterus-ferter-efter-efter-efter-ter-efter-ter-ter-ter-efter-womd-womb-transplant-transplant-473358 <description><![CDATA[In a historic first for the U.K., a woman born without a uterus gave birth to a "miracle" baby girl after receiving a life-changing womb transplant from her sister.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/miracle-baby-born-born-without-without-uterus-ferter-efter-efter-efter-ter-efter-ter-ter-ter-efter-womd-womb-transplant-transplant-473358</guid><pubDate> Wed, 09 Apr 2025 02:20:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Seven Dead After Man Impersonating Doctor Performed Surgeries With Fake Medical Degrees: Police]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/seven-dead-after-man-impersonating-doctor-performed-surged-surgeed-fake-fake-Medical-Medical-Degrees-Police-Police-473355 <description><![CDATA[Authorities in India have arrested a man accused of impersonating a British cardiologist and performing dozens of surgeries, resulting in at least seven deaths.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/seven-dead-after-man-impersonating-doctor-performed-surged-surgeed-fake-fake-Medical-Medical-Degrees-Police-Police-473355</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:01:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Forced to Remove Brazilian Butt Lift After 'Stink' From Procedure Caused Her to Lose Her Boyfriend: 'It Was an Embarrassment']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-forced-remove-brazilian-butt-lift-after-stink-procedure-caused-her-lose-her-boyfriend-473346 <description><![CDATA[Details of the complications one woman experienced following a BBL procedure have raised a stink—literally—on social media after her story went viral.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-forced-remove-brazilian-butt-lift-after-stink-procedure-caused-her-lose-her-boyfriend-473346</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:00:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is PAD? Silent Killer With No Cure Affects Over 10 Million Americans]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-pad-silent-killer-no-cure-cure-aftects-offects-over 1000亿美国人473353 <description><![CDATA[The serious condition that can lead to limb loss and 50% chances of death is often underdiagnosed and undertreated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-pad-silent-killer-no-cure-cure-aftects-offects-over 1000亿美国人473353</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Apr 2025 06:44:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Common Symptom Lasting More Than 3 Weeks May Signal Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-common-symptom-lasting-more-3-weeks-may-signal-cancercer-crisk-473352 <description><![CDATA[An oncologist is raising an alarm about a common symptom experienced by many, often dismissed as harmless.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-common-symptom-lasting-more-3-weeks-may-signal-cancercer-crisk-473352</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:48:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Burn Fat? Your Conception Month Could Be A Reason]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-burn-fat-your-conception-month-month-could-rould-rash-473349 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now say the month you were conceived could play a surprising role in shaping your body's fat-burning potential.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-burn-fat-your-conception-month-month-could-rould-rash-473349</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:34:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Often Could You Swallow In 30 Seconds? It May Reveal A Hidden Health Issue]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-often-should-should-you-swallow-30-conds-it-could-could-reveal-hidden-hidden-hidden-hidden-hidden-hidde-473343 <description><![CDATA[The number of times you swallow in just 30 seconds could serve as an early warning sign for serious conditions such as dementia, cancer, or stroke.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-often-should-should-you-swallow-30-conds-it-could-could-reveal-hidden-hidden-hidden-hidden-hidden-hidde-473343</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Apr 2025 06:24:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Left Paralyzed Neck Down From Rare Deficiency After Weight Loss Surgery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-left-paralyzed-neck-down-rare-deficition-weight-weight-weight-weight-surergery-473340 <description><![CDATA[The woman suffered severe nerve damage from nutritional neuropathy, a rare but serious side effect of gastric sleeve surgery.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-left-paralyzed-neck-down-rare-deficition-weight-weight-weight-weight-surergery-473340</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:09:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Second Child Dies Of Measles In Texas;Victim Was Unvaccinated]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/second-child-dies-measles-texas-victim-was-was-unvaccind-prod-phaccin--phaccin-phacsine-healthy-473338 <description><![CDATA[The unvaccinated school-aged child, who had no underlying health conditions, tragically died from lung failure while receiving treatment for measles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/second-child-dies-measles-texas-victim-was-was-unvaccind-prod-phaccin--phaccin-phacsine-healthy-473338</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:04:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Too Young For Alzheimer's? Easy To Dismiss Symptoms 41-Year-Old Had Before Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/too-young-alzheimers-easy-dismiss-symbstoms-41岁的had-had-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be defor-be defor-be defor-be defor-defor-defor-defor-defor-be defor-defor-defor-be defor-defor-defor-be-be 4733335 <description><![CDATA[After being diagnosed at 41, an Australian dad is raising awareness that Alzheimer's isn't just a disease of old age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/too-young-alzheimers-easy-dismiss-symbstoms-41岁的had-had-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be defor-be defor-be defor-be defor-defor-defor-defor-defor-be defor-defor-defor-be defor-defor-defor-be-be 4733335</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:35:41 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>