<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Nurse Influencer Dies During Childbirth 'After Years of Fertility Struggles': 'Her Spirit Will Live On Through Our Son']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-nurse-inurse-influencer-dies-during-child-childbirth-年份-fertility-truggles-truggles-her-spirit-473328 <description><![CDATA[Nursing and social media communities are mourning the tragic loss of Hailey Okula, an influencer and educator, who passed away due to childbirth complications.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-nurse-inurse-influencer-dies-during-child-childbirth-年份-fertility-truggles-truggles-her-spirit-473328</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:50:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tiny Ears, Big Protection: The Ultimate Guide to Safeguarding Your Baby's Hearing]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tiny-ears-big-protection-ratimate-guide-safeguarding-your-babys-herning-473279 <description><![CDATA[Protect your baby's delicate hearing with Decibel Defense earmuffs, offering comfort, style, and top-tier noise protection for little ears in any environment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tiny-ears-big-protection-ratimate-guide-safeguarding-your-babys-herning-473279</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:14:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Probiotic Supplements Help With Autism Symptoms?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-probiotic-supplements-help-autism-symptoms-473326 <description><![CDATA[A recent trial revealed that probiotic supplements may help ease both behavioral and digestive symptoms of children with autism, offering new hope for millions of children struggling with the condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-probiotic-supplements-help-autism-symptoms-473326</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Apr 2025 05:00:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experimental Drug Shows Promise In Eliminating Hard-To-Treat Deadly Cholesterol]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experiment-drug-shows-promise-eliminating-hard-treat-deadly-cholesterol-473323 <description><![CDATA[A single dose of lepodisiran dramatically lowered dangerous lipoprotein(a) levels for up to a year, offering new hope for heart disease treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experiment-drug-shows-promise-eliminating-hard-treat-deadly-cholesterol-473323</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Apr 2025 04:44:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Yerba Mate Nature's Ozempic? Weighing In Risk Vs. Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yerba-mate-natures-natures-ozempic-weighing-risk-vs-benefits-473320 <description><![CDATA[Hailed as "Nature's Ozempic," yerba mate may aid weight loss and metabolism, but is it a true alternative—or a risky trend?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yerba-mate-natures-natures-ozempic-weighing-risk-vs-benefits-473320</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Apr 2025 02:09:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Simple Supplement May Boost Brain Function And Memory In Elderly]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-supplement-may-boost-brain-finction-memory-elderly-473318 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that a daily prebiotic supplement could sharpen memory and boost cognitive performance in adults over 60.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-supplement-may-boost-brain-finction-memory-elderly-473318</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:07:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Michigan Transplant Patient Dies After Contracting Rabies From Donor]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/michigan-transplant-patient-dies- ferter-carterting-rabies-donor-473315 <description><![CDATA[The donor, exposed to a wild animal weeks before their death, passed away without showing typical rabies symptoms and did not seek medical attention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/michigan-transplant-patient-dies- ferter-carterting-rabies-donor-473315</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:12:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Screens To Bed? Here's How It Affects Your Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/taking-screens-bed-heres-how-it-fects-your-sleep-473313 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now reveal that when it comes to screen use before bed, the total time spent matters more than the specific type of activity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/taking-screens-bed-heres-how-it-fects-your-sleep-473313</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:12:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Spring Into Motion: Why Rollator Walkers Are A Game-Changer For Seniors]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spring-motion-why-why-rollat​​or-walkers-walkers-are-game-changer-seniors-473310 <description><![CDATA[A rollator walker isn't just some medical device with tennis balls slapped on the feet, it's a movement machine. Unlike the clunky walkers of the past, these have wheels, hand brakes, and even a built-in seat, so you're never stuck wondering if the next bench is too far away.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spring-motion-why-why-rollat​​or-walkers-walkers-are-game-changer-seniors-473310</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:25:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Managing Pregnancy Discomfort: Smart Strategies for a Healthier Journey]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/managing-pregnancy-discomfort-smart-smart-strategies-healthier-journey-473307 <description><![CDATA[Practical support and movement strategies can help ease common pregnancy discomforts and promote maternal well-being]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/managing-pregnancy-discomfort-smart-smart-strategies-healthier-journey-473307</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:17:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alternative Healthy Eating Index: Your Diet For Healthy, Disease-Free 70's]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alternative-healthy-eating-index-your-diet-healthy-disease-free-70s-473305 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now identified a specific dietary approach that promotes longevity and disease-free aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alternative-healthy-eating-index-your-diet-healthy-disease-free-70s-473305</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:36:21 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>