<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Heated Yoga For Depression? Study Says Symptoms Reduced In 2 Months With Around 10 Sessions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heated-yoga-depression-study-says-symptoms-reduced-2-months-around-10-sessions-471019 <description><![CDATA[The study indicates the possibility of using heated yoga as a viable treatment option for depression, as 44% of the participants who took up the sessions indicated signs of remission.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heated-yoga-depression-study-says-symptoms-reduced-2-months-around-10-sessions-471019</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:04:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Gut Fungi Linked To Severe COVID-19 Infection: Study Says They Cause Lasting Immune Changes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-gut-fungi-linked-severe-covid-19-infection-study-says-they-cause-having-immune-changes-471017 <description><![CDATA[Researchers identified that an abundance of fungi in the gut, particularly strains of Candida albicans yeast, could trigger an increase in immune cells, which could worsen lung damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-gut-fungi-linked-severe-covid-19-infection-study-says-they-cause-having-immune-changes-471017</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 02:43:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleeping Less Than 5 Hours Daily Raises Depression Risk, While Reverse Chance Is Low: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleeping-less-5-hours-daily-raises-depression-risk-while-reverse-chance-low-study-471016 <description><![CDATA[Sleeping less than five hours daily raises the risk of developing depression by 2.5 times, while the chance of developing poor sleep out of depression is only one-third, the study found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleeping-less-5-hours-daily-raises-depression-risk-while-reverse-chance-low-study-471016</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:53:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Preparing For Surgery? Study Suggests Walking Over 7,500 Steps Daily To Reduce Complications]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/preparing-surgery-study-suggests-walking-over-7500-steps-daily-reduce-complications-471013 <description><![CDATA[The study says walking more than 7500 steps daily during the preoperative period could cut the risk of complications by around half.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/preparing-surgery-study-suggests-walking-over-7500-steps-daily-reduce-complications-471013</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Oct 2023 05:14:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is A Cold Shower Good For You? Here's What Studies Say About Potential Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cold-shower-right-you-heres-what-studies-say-about-pottial-benefits-471011 <description><![CDATA[Cold showers are not approved treatments for any disorders but may be beneficial as supportive strategies to relieve certain symptoms such as itchy skin, stress, and dry scalp.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cold-shower-right-you-heres-what-studies-say-about-pottial-benefits-471011</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:47:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Osteoporosis Day: What To Eat And Avoid For Better Bone Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-osteoporosis-day-what-eat-avoid-better-bone-health-471010 <description><![CDATA[What you eat can directly affect the health of your bones. On this World Osteoporosis Day (Oct. 20), know the things that you need to include and avoid in your diet for better bone health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-osteoporosis-day-what-eat-avoid-better-bone-health-471010</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:24:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Avoid Fast Food In Teen Years, Study Says Eating Them May Raise Breast Cancer Risk Later]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-fast-foods-teen-years-study-says-eating-them-may-raise-breast-cancer-risk-later-471008 <description><![CDATA[Processed foods that are high in sugar, protein and fat must be avoided by teens to prevent the risk of future breast cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-fast-foods-teen-years-study-says-eating-them-may-raise-breast-cancer-risk-later-471008</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Oct 2023 03:42:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Leishmaniasis? CDC Says Flesh-Eating Parasite Is Now Endemic In Some States]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-leishmaniasis-cdc-says-flesh-eating-parasite-now-endemic-some-states-471005 <description><![CDATA[An analysis from the CDC revealed the infection that was earlier seen in people who traveled to tropical regions is now endemic in some southern border states.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-leishmaniasis-cdc-says-flesh-eating-parasite-now-endemic-some-states-471005</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:02:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Proposes Ban On Formaldehyde In Hair Relaxers; Here's How The Chemical Affects Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-proposes-ban-formogenic-hair-relaxers-heres-how-chemical-affects-health-471002 <description><![CDATA[Taking into account the "long-term adverse health effects" of formaldehyde, including the risk of cancers, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration proposes a ban on hair straightening products containing the chemical.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-proposes-ban-formogenic-hair-relaxers-heres-how-chemical-affects-health-471002</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:09:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Cases In Wisconsin, Illinois: Know All About The Disease That Was Once Eliminated From US]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-cases-wisconsin-illinois-know-all-about-disease-that-was-once-eliminate-us-471001 <description><![CDATA[Health officials urge people to stay up to date on immunizations after a case of measles has been confirmed in each state.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-cases-wisconsin-illinois-know-all-about-disease-that-was-once-eliminate-us-471001</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 03:25:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Liver Awareness Month: Experts Offer Dietary, Lifestyle Tips To Keep The Vital Organ Healthy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-liver-awareness-month-experts-offer-dietary-lifestyle-tips-keep-vital-organ-healthy-471000 <description><![CDATA[Many liver conditions, including fatty liver, can be reversed if they are diagnosed and treated at an early stage. A healthy diet and lifestyle modifications are equally essential.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-liver-awareness-month-experts-offer-dietary-lifestyle-tips-keep-vital-organ-healthy-471000</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 01:38:23 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>