<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>A </language><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Your Medical Conditions While Planning A Vacation? Here's How You Can Travel Safe]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-your-medical-conditions-while-planning-vacation-heres-how-you-can-travel-safe-471144 <description><![CDATA[With some thoughtful planning and necessary precautions, traveling could be definitely on the cards for people with health conditions such as heart disease and diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-your-medical-conditions-while-planning-vacation-heres-how-you-can-travel-safe-471144</guid><pubDate> Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:45:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Booster Shot: Study Says Half Dose Of Pfizer Vaccine Produces Strong Immune Response]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-booster-shot-study-says-half-dose-pfizer-vaccine-products-strong-immune-response-471143 <description><![CDATA[The team discovered that people who previously received AstraZeneca or Sinopharm COVID-19 vaccines had a "non-inferior" immune response when given a half dose of a Pfizer COVID-19 booster vaccine, comparable to those who received a full dose.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-booster-shot-study-says-half-dose-pfizer-vaccine-products-strong-immune-response-471143</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Nov 2023 05:00:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eye Syphilis Outbreak In Michigan Linked To Common Sex Partner; Know All About The Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eye-syphilis-outbreak-michigan-linked-common-sex-partner-know-all-about-disease-471142 <description><![CDATA[In a first-of-its-kind report of an outbreak linked to a common male sex partner, officials have identified five women with eye syphilis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eye-syphilis-outbreak-michigan-linked-common-sex-partner-know-all-about-disease-471142</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:03:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Gas Station Heroin' Supplement Causes Seizures, Loss Of Consciousness, FDA Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gas-station-heroin-supplement-causes-seizures-loss-thoughtness-fda-warns-471140 <description><![CDATA[Neptune's Fix, a product sold illegally with claims to improve brain function and treat conditions such as anxiety, depression, pain and opioid use disorder, contains a potentially dangerous substance called tianeptine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gas-station-heroin-supplement-causes-seizures-loss-thoughtness-fda-warns-471140</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:19:30 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Include 3 Servings Of Whole Grains In Diet Daily To Slow Cognitive Decline, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/include-3-servings-whole-grains-diet-daily-slow-cognitive-decline-study-says-471139 <description><![CDATA[People who consumed more food containing whole grains had a slower rate of memory decline, equivalent to being 8.5 years younger, compared to those who ate less whole grains, according to the study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/include-3-servings-whole-grains-diet-daily-slow-cognitive-decline-study-says-471139</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 Nov 2023 03:26:49 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Screen Time Impact Shape Of Children's Brains? Researchers Find Negative And Positive Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-screen-time-affect-shape-childrens-brains-researchers-find-negative-positive-effects-471137 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found that the time spent in front of digital devices can affect the shape of children's brains.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-screen-time-affect-shape-childrens-brains-researchers-find-negative-positive-effects-471137</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 Nov 2023 02:05:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Had A Sleepless Night? Exercising For 20 Minutes May Improve Your Brain Power]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/had-sleepless-night-exercising-20-分钟-may-improve-your-brain-power-471136 <description><![CDATA[Moderate exercise for 20 minutes after a sleepless night can improve brain power, a new study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/had-sleepless-night-exercising-20-分钟-may-improve-your-brain-power-471136</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:29:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Red Meat And Dairy Products Help Fight Cancer? Study Says They Can Improve Immune Response]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-red-meat-dairy-products-help-fight-cancer-study-says-they-can-improve-immune-response-471135 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests the possibility of using trans-vaccenic acid found in red meat and dairy products as a nutritional supplement to complement treatments for cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-red-meat-dairy-products-help-fight-cancer-study-says-they-can-improve-immune-response-471135</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:31:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Minimally Invasive, 10-Minute Procedure Could Restore Sense Of Smell In Long COVID Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/minimally-having-10-minute-procedure-could-restore-sense-smell-long-covid-病人-471133 <description><![CDATA[Using an image-guided minimally invasive procedure that takes less than 10 minutes, patients could alleviate symptoms of parosmia, a condition characterized by a distorted sense of smell.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/minimally-having-10-minute-procedure-could-restore-sense-smell-long-covid-病人-471133</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 Nov 2023 02:38:56 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mysterious Pneumonia Outbreak Among Children In China: Here's What We Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mysterious-pneumonia-outbreak-among-children-china-heres-what-we-know-471131 <description><![CDATA[Hospitals in northern China have reportedly been "overwhelmed" with sick children due to a mysterious pneumonia outbreak.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mysterious-pneumonia-outbreak-among-children-china-heres-what-we-know-471131</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:31:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Treatment For Neurodegenerative Disorders? Study Says Coffee Grounds Could Prevent Brain Cell Damage]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-treatment-neurodogenic-disorders-study-says-coffee-grounds-could-prevent-brain-cell-471129 <description><![CDATA[The study found the possibility of developing a treatment using coffee grounds that could prevent brain cell damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-treatment-neurodogenic-disorders-study-says-coffee-grounds-could-prevent-brain-cell-471129</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 Nov 2023 03:32:32 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>