<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>A </language><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Reports 'Large Uptick' In Child Pneumonia Cases; Officials Say Outbreak Not Linked To China]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-reports-large-uptick-child-pneumonia-cases-officials-say-outbreak-not-linked-china-471159 <description><![CDATA[A total of 142 cases of pediatric pneumonia have been reported in Warren County, surpassing the county average, the Ohio Department of Health revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-reports-large-uptick-child-pneumonia-cases-officials-say-outbreak-not-linked-china-471159</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Dec 2023 01:25:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New 'Prescription Tool' For Postpartum Depression? Study Says Moderate Aerobic Exercise Helps In Prevention, Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-prescription-tool-postpartum-depression-study-says-moderate-aerobic-exercise-helps-471155 <description><![CDATA[Engaging in aerobic exercise sessions 3-4 times per week, each lasting approximately 35-45 minutes, showed significant efficacy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-prescription-tool-postpartum-depression-study-says-moderate-aerobic-exercise-helps-471155</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Nov 2023 03:57:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[7 Healthy Lifestyle Recommendations To Cut Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/7-healthy-lifestyle-recommendations-cut-cancer-risk-471153 <description><![CDATA[A study found that greater adherence to lifestyle recommendations made by the World Cancer Research Fund/American Institute for Cancer Research (WCRF/AICR) was associated with reduced overall cancer risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/7-healthy-lifestyle-recommendations-cut-cancer-risk-471153</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:52:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Warns Of Potentially Life-Threatening Reaction To Seizure Medications; Know Signs Of Severe Side-Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-warns-潜在-生命威胁-反应-seizure-medications-know-signs-severe-471152 <description><![CDATA[Antiseizure drugs levetiracetam and clobazam can cause a serious hypersensitivity reaction called drug reactions with eosinophilia and systemic symptoms (DRESS), the FDA said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-warns-潜在-生命威胁-反应-seizure-medications-know-signs-severe-471152</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:03:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Brisk Walking Reduces Risk Of Type 2 Diabetes: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brisk-walking-reduces-risk-type-2-diabetes-study-471150 <description><![CDATA[With every one km increase in the speed of walking, the researchers found a 9% reduction in diabetes risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brisk-walking-reduces-risk-type-2-diabetes-study-471150</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:37:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fall Asleep In 2 Minutes: Know All About Military Sleep Technique]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fall-asleep-2-minutes-know-all-about-military-sleep-technique-471149 <description><![CDATA[Around 10% of adults in the world suffer from insomnia, a common sleep disorder that causes difficulty in falling asleep and getting a good quality of sleep.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fall-asleep-2-minutes-know-all-about-military-sleep-technique-471149</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Nov 2023 02:26:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hair Styling Products Emit Harmful Chemicals When Used With Heating Tools: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hair-styling-products-emit-harmful-chemicals-when-used-heating-tools-study-471148 <description><![CDATA[A single hair styling session inside a closed room could result in inhalation of 1-17 milligrams of potentially harmful chemicals, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hair-styling-products-emit-harmful-chemicals-when-used-heating-tools-study-471148</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:55:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breathing In Polluted Air During Heavy Traffic Could Raise Blood Pressure Of Passengers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breathing-polluted-air-during-heavy-traffic-could-raise-blood-Pressure-passengers-471146 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that pollution from heavy traffic resulted in an increase in blood pressure equivalent to the effect of a high-sodium diet.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breathing-polluted-air-during-heavy-traffic-could-raise-blood-Pressure-passengers-471146</guid><pubDate> Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:55:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Switch To Healthier Diet In Your 40s; Study Says It Can Add 10 Years To Life]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/switch-healthier-diet-your-40s-study-says-it-can-add-10-years-life-471145 <description><![CDATA[Middle-aged people who shifted from an unhealthy diet to a healthy diet and maintained the pattern could add a decade more to their lives, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/switch-healthier-diet-your-40s-study-says-it-can-add-10-years-life-471145</guid><pubDate> Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:35:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Your Medical Conditions While Planning A Vacation? Here's How You Can Travel Safe]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-your-medical-conditions-while-planning-vacation-heres-how-you-can-travel-safe-471144 <description><![CDATA[With some thoughtful planning and necessary precautions, traveling could be definitely on the cards for people with health conditions such as heart disease and diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-your-medical-conditions-while-planning-vacation-heres-how-you-can-travel-safe-471144</guid><pubDate> Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:45:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Booster Shot: Study Says Half Dose Of Pfizer Vaccine Produces Strong Immune Response]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-booster-shot-study-says-half-dose-pfizer-vaccine-products-strong-immune-response-471143 <description><![CDATA[The team discovered that people who previously received AstraZeneca or Sinopharm COVID-19 vaccines had a "non-inferior" immune response when given a half dose of a Pfizer COVID-19 booster vaccine, comparable to those who received a full dose.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-booster-shot-study-says-half-dose-pfizer-vaccine-products-strong-immune-response-471143</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Nov 2023 05:00:27 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>