<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra-Processed Food, Especially Those With Artificial Sweeteners, May Elevate Depression Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-尤其-those-artificial-sweeteners-may-elevate-depression-risk-470847 <description><![CDATA[Participants who consumed nine or more portions of ultra-processed foods daily had a 49% increased risk of depression compared to those who consumed less than four portions a day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-尤其-those-artificial-sweeteners-may-elevate-depression-risk-470847</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 05:16:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Brucella Canis? This Rare Bacteria Causing Incurable Disease In Dogs Is Now Spreading To Humans]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-brucella-canis-this-rare-bacteria-causing-incurable-disease-dogs-now-spreading- humans-470845 <description><![CDATA[Three people in the U.K. have been infected with Brucella Canis, which causes a rare incurable infection in dogs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-brucella-canis-this-rare-bacteria-causing-incurable-disease-dogs-now-spreading- humans-470845</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 03:45:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[PCOS Awareness Month: Experts Debunk Myths About The Common Hormonal Disorder]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pcos-awareness-month-experts-debunk-myths-about-common-hormonal-disorder-470843 <description><![CDATA[As September marks PCOS Awareness Month, experts share their thoughts on the long-term impacts of PCOS and debunk some of the common myths about the condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pcos-awareness-month-experts-debunk-myths-about-common-hormonal-disorder-470843</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 01:39:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Yoga Could Help Improve Symptoms Of Rheumatoid Arthritis: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yoga-could-help-improve-symptoms-rheumatoid-arthritis-study-470841 <description><![CDATA[Rheumatoid arthritis (RA) is an autoimmune and inflammatory disease that occurs when a person's immune system attacks healthy cells in the body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yoga-could-help-improve-symptoms-rheumatoid-arthritis-study-470841</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Sep 2023 08:41:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Everything You Need To Know About Depression, One Of The Most Common Mental Illnesses]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/everything-you-need-know-about-depression-one-most-common-mental-illnesses-470838 <description><![CDATA[About 280 million people worldwide suffer from depression, as per the WHO's estimate.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/everything-you-need-know-about-depression-one-most-common-mental-illnesses-470838</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Sep 2023 06:39:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Job Stress And Heart Disease: Men Under-Appreciated At Work Twice As Likely To Develop Cardiac Issues]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/job-stress-heart-disease-men-under-appreciated-work-twice-likely-develop-cardiac-issues-470836 <description><![CDATA[High-stress work can double the risk of men developing heart attacks and other complications. The study showed inconclusive results when researchers examined the impact of stress on women's heart health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/job-stress-heart-disease-men-under-appreciated-work-twice-likely-develop-cardiac-issues-470836</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Sep 2023 05:05:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Snacking Isn't Always Harmful. Study Identifies Worst Time To Snack, Types Of Food To Avoid]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/snacking-isnt-always-harmful-study-identizes-worst-time-snack-types-food-avoid-470835 <description><![CDATA[Unhealthy snacking can counteract the benefits of a healthy meal, and snacking after 9 p.m. can lead to poor health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/snacking-isnt-always-harmful-study-identizes-worst-time-snack-types-food-avoid-470835</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:57:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Having All Natural Teeth May Boost Survival Chances In Neck, Head Cancer Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/having-all-natural-teeth-may-boost-survival-chances-neck-head-cancer-患者-470834 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that people with better oral health – those having natural teeth and more frequent dental visits –  had better chances of surviving head and neck cancers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/having-all-natural-teeth-may-boost-survival-chances-neck-head-cancer-患者-470834</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Sep 2023 01:10:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Diabetic, Prediabetic Children Should Steer Clear Of Low-Carb Diets, Warn Pediatricians]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetic-prediabetic-children-should-steer-clear-low-carb-diets-warn-pediatricians-470832 <description><![CDATA[Carb restrictions could lead to "growth deceleration, nutritional deficiencies, poor bone health, nutritional ketosis that cannot be distinguished from ketosis resulting from insulin deficiency, and disordered eating behaviors" among children, the researchers warned.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetic-prediabetic-children-should-steer-clear-low-carb-diets-warn-pediatricians-470832</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:29:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[MDMA-Assisted Therapy Could Significantly Help Reduce PTSD Symptoms: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mdma-treatment-could-significantly-help-reduce-ptsd-symptoms-study-470829 <description><![CDATA[The study was conducted across thirteen sites, with eleven of them located in the United States and two in Israel.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mdma-treatment-could-significantly-help-reduce-ptsd-symptoms-study-470829</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Sep 2023 07:09:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Childhood Obesity: Researchers Say Starting Treatment Early Brings Lasting Effect]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childhood-obesity-researchers-say-starting-treatment-early-brings- permanent-effect-470828 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that kids diagnosed with obesity should kick-start treatment early, even at pre-school age, with intensive parent support for lasting results.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childhood-obesity-researchers-say-starting-treatment-early-brings- permanent-effect-470828</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Sep 2023 03:38:16 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>