<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA[Top 3 Personalized Supplements You Must Take for Better Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-3-personalized-supplements-you-must-take-for-better-health-469992 <description><![CDATA[When it comes to taking care of our health, there are a lot of things we can do. Eating healthy, exercising regularly, and getting enough sleep are just a few examples. However, even these aren't enough to supply your body with all the nutrients it needs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-3-personalized-supplements-you-must-take-for-better-health-469992</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:07:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Servings Of Grapes A Day Increase Gut Bacteria, Boost Metabolic Function, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/3-servings-of-grapes-day-increases-gut-bacteria-boosts-metabolic-function-study-finds-469989 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that grapes can have a positive impact on gut health by increasing the abundance of beneficial gut bacteria, giving yet another reason to incorporate grapes into our dietary routine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/3-servings-of-grapes-day-increases-gut-bacteria-boosts-metabolic-function-study-finds-469989</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 06:04:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Finalizes Stricter Guidance On Inorganic Arsenic Levels in Apple Juice]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-finalizes-stricter-guidance-for-inorganic-arsenic-levels-apple-juice-469987 <description><![CDATA[The heavy presence of arsenic and lead in fruit juices is sometimes beyond the control of the manufacturers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-finalizes-stricter-guidance-for-inorganic-arsenic-levels-apple-juice-469987</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 05:01:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Awareness Month: 7 Ways To Keep Your Brain Healthy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alzheimers-awareness-month-7-ways-to-keep-your-brain-healthy-469984 <description><![CDATA[Every year, June is marked to increase awareness about the degenerative brain disorder that affects the lives of millions of people worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alzheimers-awareness-month-7-ways-to-keep-your-brain-healthy-469984</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:39:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[PCOS Diets: Debunking Popular Myths Surrounding Nutritional Requirements]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/pcos-diets-debunking-popular-myths-surrounding-nutritional-requirements-469983 <description><![CDATA[Alongside advocating the need for early diagnosis, experts recommend following a PCOS-specific diet to address the risks associated with the condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pcos-diets-debunking-popular-myths-surrounding-nutritional-requirements-469983</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:18:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alcohol Dependency In Teens Raises Risk Of Depression Later In Life: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-dependency-teens-raises-risk-of-depression-later-life-study-469982 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that alcohol dependency in adolescence raises the chances of developing depression in young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-dependency-teens-raises-risk-of-depression-later-life-study-469982</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 02:21:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Junk Food Can Disturb Deep Sleep, Study Says; Foods To Have Before Bed]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/junk-food-can-disturb-deep-sleep-study-says-foods-have-before-bed-469981 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that fat and sugar in junk food can reduce sleep quality by disrupting the brain's electrical activity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/junk-food-can-disturb-deep-sleep-study-says-foods-have-before-bed-469981</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 01:17:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New York Hospitals Want To Rehire Employees Fired Over Vaccine Mandate]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-york-hospitals-want-to-rehire-employees-fired-over-vaccine-mandate-469978 <description><![CDATA[At least two hospitals have confirmed they would rehire workers who got fired due to the COVID-19 vaccine mandate.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-york-hospitals-want-to-rehire-employees-fired-over-vaccine-mandate-469978</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:26:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[NYC Wastewater Suggests COVID-19 Rebound: Could This Signify A New Wave?]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/nyc-wastewater-suggests-covid-19-rebound-could-this-signify-new-wave-469977 <description><![CDATA[The virus could be thriving in many places based on wastewater surveillance data.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nyc-wastewater-suggests-covid-19-rebound-could-this-signify-new-wave-469977</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:15:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is A Low-Carb Morning Meal Ideal For Diabetes Patients? Here's How It Works]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-carb-morning-meal-ideal-diabetes-patients-here-how-it-works-469974 <description><![CDATA[Switching to a protein and fat-rich low-carbohydrate meal can help type 2 diabetes patients control blood sugars, a new study shows.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-carb-morning-meal-ideal-diabetes-patients-here-how-it-works-469974</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 06:16:31 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stomach Ulcer Symptoms: 6 Red Flags To Keep An Eye Out For]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/stomach-ulcer-symptoms-6-red-flags-keep-eye-out-469970 <description><![CDATA[These symptoms suggest you might have a stomach ulcer and seek immediate medical help.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stomach-ulcer-symptoms-6-red-flags-keep-eye-out-469970</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:20:24 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>