<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Climate Change Worsening Heatwaves, Air Quality: UN]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/climate-change-worsening-heatwaves-air-quality-un-470762 <description><![CDATA[Climate change is driving more intense and more frequent heatwaves, which in turn generate a "witch's brew" of pollutants, threatening the health of humans and all living things, the UN warned Wednesday.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/climate-change-worsening-heatwaves-air-quality-un-470762</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 04:43:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breast Cancer And Pregnancy: Study Explains Why Older First-Time Moms Are At Higher Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-pregnancy-study-explains-why-older-first-time-moms-are-higher-risk-470760 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say pregnancy could provide a "double whammy" for breast cancer as it induces a rapid expansion of breast cells for breastfeeding.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-pregnancy-study-explains-why-older-first-time-moms-are-higher-risk-470760</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 03:17:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Substance Abuse Causes Intellectual Disability Even If Only One Parent Has The Issue, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/substance-abuse-causes-intellectual-disability-even-if-only-one-parent-has-issue-study-says-470759 <description><![CDATA[The risk of intellectual disability in children was more than two times higher when the father or mother was diagnosed with abuse disorder before or during pregnancy, irrespective of which parent had the diagnosis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/substance-abuse-causes-intellectual-disability-even-if-only-one-parent-has-issue-study-says-470759</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 02:57:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Childhood Obesity Awareness Month: Tips To Promote Healthy Weight In Your Kids]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-childhood-obesity-awareness-month-tips-promote-healthy-weight-your-kids-470757 <description><![CDATA[Families can do a lot to help children tackle obesity, especially by inculcating healthy lifestyle habits in them from a young age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-childhood-obesity-awareness-month-tips-promote-healthy-weight-your-kids-470757</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 01:15:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cancer Surging Among People Under 50; Scientists Say Obesity, Alcohol And Poor Lifestyle Could Be Reasons]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cancer-surging-among-people-under-50-scientists-say-obesity-alcohol-poor-lifestyle-could-be-reasons-470755 <description><![CDATA[The research team found a 79% surge in cancer diagnoses in people under the age of 50 in the past three decades.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cancer-surging-among-people-under-50-scientists-say-obesity-alcohol-poor-lifestyle-could-be-reasons-470755</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 04:18:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Certain Food Additives Used In Chocolates And Cakes May Raise Your Risk Of Heart Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/certain-food-additives-used-chocolates-cakes-may-raise-your-risk-of-heart-disease-470754 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that certain types of emulsifier E, the food additives commonly used in pastries, cakes, desserts, chocolate, bread, margarine and ready meals, can elevate the risk of cardiovascular disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/certain-food-additives-used-chocolates-cakes-may-raise-your-risk-of-heart-disease-470754</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 02:53:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is EDS? Woman Dies From 'Invisible Disease' After Being Accused Of Faking Illness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-eds-woman-die-invisible-disease-after-being-accused-of-faking-illness-470752 <description><![CDATA[EDS is considered an "invisible disease" as patients most often appear healthy, despite suffering from excruciating fatigue and pain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-eds-woman-die-invisible-disease-after-being-accused-of-faking-illness-470752</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 01:19:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Resistant Starch May Help Treat Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease, Study Says; Know Other Health Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pressive-starch-may-help-treat-non-酒精-fatty-liver-disease-study-says-know-other-health-470751 <description><![CDATA[The liver triglyceride levels of the group that received resistant starch treatment were around 40% lower than those in the control group.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pressive-starch-may-help-treat-non-酒精-fatty-liver-disease-study-says-know-other-health-470751</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 03:22:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vaping Reduces Sex Drive? Study Says It May Shrink Testicles, Lower Sperm Counts]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaping-reduces-sex-drive-study-says-it-may-shrink-testicles-lower-sperm-counts-470750 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that vaping can affect male fertility by causing testicles to shrink, reducing sperm count and sex drive.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaping-reduces-sex-drive-study-says-it-may-shrink-testicles-lower-sperm-counts-470750</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:24:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exposure To Chemicals Used In Plastic May Cause Developmental Issues In Toddler Boys]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-chemicals-used- Plastic-may-cause-developmental-issues-toddler-boys-470747 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that exposure to phthalates in the womb affects the emotional and behavioral development of young boys.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-chemicals-used- Plastic-may-cause-developmental-issues-toddler-boys-470747</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:49:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Highly Mutated COVID-19 Variant Is Less Immune-Evasive, Lab Tests Suggest]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-highly-mutated-covid-19-variant-less-immune-evasive-lab-tests-suggest-470746 <description><![CDATA[Based on two separate lab test results in the U.S. experts now believe the new variant is less contagious and immune evasive than feared.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-highly-mutated-covid-19-variant-less-immune-evasive-lab-tests-suggest-470746</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Sep 2023 04:09:44 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>