<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Common Hormonal IUD For Contraception Raises Breast Cancer Risk: Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-hormonal-iud-contraception-raises-breast-cancer-risk-study-finds-472539 <description><![CDATA[The study found that Levonorgestrel-Releasing Intrauterine Systems (LNG-IUS) was linked to 14 extra cases of breast cancer per 10,000 women compared to those not using contraceptive medication.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-hormonal-iud-contraception-raises-breast-cancer-risk-study-finds-472539</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Oct 2024 01:57:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Keep Kids Active: Childhood Fitness Linked To Lower Stress And Depression In Teen Years]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keep-kids-active-childhood-fitness-linked-lower-stress-depression-teen-years-472538 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that maintaining good physical fitness from childhood to adolescence is associated with reduced stress and depression during the teenage years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keep-kids-active-childhood-fitness-linked-lower-stress-depression-teen-years-472538</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:42:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Seizures In Kids From Prescription Medications, Illegal Substances Doubled In 15 Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/seizures-kids-prescription-medications-illegal-substances-doubled-15-years-study-472537 <description><![CDATA[The researchers stressed the need for better awareness among parents and elders about the safe handling of over-the-counter medications.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/seizures-kids-prescription-medications-illegal-substances-doubled-15-years-study-472537</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Oct 2024 03:14:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Breast Cancer Type Linked To Excess Body Fat: Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-breast-cancer-type-linked-excess-body-fat-study-reveals-472534 <description><![CDATA[Excess body fat may be responsible for 40% of postmenopausal hormone-positive breast cancer cases. The new study findings suggest the need to rethink the effectiveness of BMI in assessing cancer risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-breast-cancer-type-linked-excess-body-fat-study-reveals-472534</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Oct 2024 01:48:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Or Too Little Folate During Pregnancy May Raise the Risk of Congenital Heart Defects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-too-little-folate-during-pregnancy-may-raise-risk-congenital-heart-defects-472532 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted a U-shaped association between maternal serum folate levels and congenital heart defect risk in offspring, meaning both low and high maternal folate were linked to a higher risk of heart defect.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-too-little-folate-during-pregnancy-may-raise-risk-congenital-heart-defects-472532</guid><pubDate> Tue, 15 Oct 2024 04:08:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Loss Without Diet Or Exercise? New Fat-Absorbing Nanotherapy Could Be A Game Changer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-without-diet-exercise-new-fat-bearing-nanotherapy-could-game-changer-472531 <description><![CDATA[The breakthrough oral nanotherapy interacts directly with the small intestine to decrease its capacity to absorb fat from the food consumed, making it a game-changer for those looking to manage their weight with minimal lifestyle changes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-without-diet-exercise-new-fat-bearing-nanotherapy-could-game-changer-472531</guid><pubDate> Tue, 15 Oct 2024 02:45:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Children Who Had COVID-19 At Higher Risk Of Type 2 Diabetes: Study Finds]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-who-had-covid-19-higher-risk-type-2-diabetes-study-finds-472529 <description><![CDATA[The study noted an increased risk of type 2 diabetes in pediatric patients after a bout of COVID-19 infection compared to other respiratory infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-who-had-covid-19-higher-risk-type-2-diabetes-study-finds-472529</guid><pubDate> Tue, 15 Oct 2024 01:34:43 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Survey Says 25% Of Adults In U.S Suspect They Have Undiagnosed ADHD]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/survey-says-25-adults-us-suspect-they-have-undiagnosed-adhd-472528 <description><![CDATA[The survey revealed that a striking 25% of U.S. adults suspect they may have undiagnosed ADHD. Even more concerning is that only 13% of respondents have taken the crucial step of discussing their symptoms with a healthcare professional.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/survey-says-25-adults-us-suspect-they-have-undiagnosed-adhd-472528</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Oct 2024 04:09:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Child's Bedtime Affects Their Gut Health: Here's How Early Sleep Benefits Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-childs-bedtime-affects-their-gut-health-heres-how-early-sleep-benefits-them-472527 <description><![CDATA[The findings indicate that an early bedtime, particularly before 9:30 p.m., is a valuable habit to cultivate, as children who went to bed earlier had a higher abundance of beneficial gut bacteria and a lower presence of various harmful gut microbes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-childs-bedtime-affects-their-gut-health-heres-how-early-sleep-benefits-them-472527</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Oct 2024 03:14:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Quality, Not Quantity Of Good Cholesterol Linked To Alzheimer's Risk: Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quality-not-quantity-good-cholesterol-linked-alzheimers-risk-study-says-472525 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that the number of larger HDL particles in women's bodies increases during menopause, and these larger particles are less effective in supporting cognitive health compared to their smaller counterparts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quality-not-quantity-good-cholesterol-linked-alzheimers-risk-study-says-472525</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Oct 2024 01:40:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Oil Cleansers: Top Solutions For Deep Cleansing, Nourishing Skin, And Hydration]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-oil-cleansers-top-solutions-deep-cleansing-nourishing-skin-Hydration-472458 <description><![CDATA[Oil cleansers are a vital part of any skincare routine, especially for those looking to effectively remove makeup, sunscreen, and impurities from the skin. These products work by attracting and dissolving oil-based substances, making them ideal for deep cleansing without stripping the skin of its natural moisture.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-oil-cleansers-top-solutions-deep-cleansing-nourishing-skin-Hydration-472458</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Oct 2024 15:20:20 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>