<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[60% of US Baby Food Lacks Nutrients; Many Exceed Sugar And Salt Limits: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/60-us-baby-food-lacks-nutritions-many-exceed-sugar-salt-limits-study-472164 <description><![CDATA[The study examined 651 products sold across the top 10 U.S. grocery chains and found that none of these products met promotional requirements set by the WHO guidelines.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/60-us-baby-food-lacks-nutritions-many-exceed-sugar-salt-limits-study-472164</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 02:21:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['No Safe Levels': Study Says Even Light Smoking During Pregnancy Affects Newborn's Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-safe-levels-study-says-even-light-smoking-during-pregnancy-affects-newborns-health-472161 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests "that there is no safe period and no safe level of cigarette smoking shortly before or during pregnancy."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-safe-levels-study-says-even-light-smoking-during-pregnancy-affects-newborns-health-472161</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Aug 2024 05:21:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Lose Weight? New Diet Suggests Eating More Protein, Fiber While Limiting Calories]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-lose-weight-new-diet-suggests-eating-more- Protein-Fiber-while-limiting-calories-472158 <description><![CDATA[The study tested a new weight loss program called the Individualized Diet Improvement Program (iDip) which involves increasing protein and fiber intake while consuming 1,500 calories or less daily for one year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-lose-weight-new-diet-suggests-eating-more- Protein-Fiber-while-limiting-calories-472158</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Aug 2024 04:08:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tirzepatide Cuts Diabetes Risk By 94% In Prediabetic, Obese Individuals: Trial Results]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tirzepatide-cuts-diabetes-risk-94-prediabetic-obese-individuals-Trial-results-472156 <description><![CDATA[The three-year trial results revealed that a once-a-week tirzepatide injection for adults who are prediabetic, obese, or overweight reduced their risk of progressing to type 2 diabetes by 94%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tirzepatide-cuts-diabetes-risk-94-prediabetic-obese-individuals-Trial-results-472156</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Aug 2024 01:44:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Fish Oil Supplements For Better Heart Health And Active Lifestyle]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-fish-oil-supplements-better-heart-health-active-lifestyle-472144 <description><![CDATA[Fish oil supplements are known to have positive effects on cardiovascular health. They may slow disease progression and lower the risk of death in people.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-fish-oil-supplements-better-heart-health-active-lifestyle-472144</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:40:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Psyllium Supplements: Discover Digestive, Heart Health And Weight Loss Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-psyllium-supplements-discover-digestive-heart-health-weight-loss-benefits-472142 <description><![CDATA[Psyllium is a soluble, bulk-forming laxative most commonly used to relieve constipation. It is a husk made from Plantago ovata, a plant native to Asia and the Mediterranean region of Europe and North Africa. Available in various forms like powder, granules, capsules, liquid, and wafers, psyllium offers a range of health benefits beyond digestive support, including diabetes control, weight loss, and heart health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-psyllium-supplements-discover-digestive-heart-health-weight-loss-benefits-472142</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:39:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best St. John's Wort Supplements For Mood and Anxiety: Benefits, Studies And Dosage]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-st-johns-wort-supplements-mood-anxiety-benefits-studies-dosage-472148 <description><![CDATA[St. John's Wort is a popular herbal supplement known for its benefits in managing mild to moderate depression, anxiety, and menopausal symptoms. Studies suggest it may be as effective as some antidepressants, with additional benefits like improving sleep and alleviating Seasonal Affective Disorder (SAD).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-st-johns-wort-supplements-mood-anxiety-benefits-studies-dosage-472148</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:36:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Constipation Affect Heart Disease Risk? Know What A New Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-constipation-affect-heart-disease-risk-know-what-new-study-says-472151 <description><![CDATA[People who have constipation face more than twice the risk of a major cardiac event when compared to those without the condition, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-constipation-affect-heart-disease-risk-know-what-new-study-says-472151</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Aug 2024 05:40:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Aging Isn't Linear, Study Says Here's When You Age Dramatically]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aging-isnt-linear-study-says-heres-when-you-age-dramatically-472146 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that the human body ages dramatically at ages 44 and 60.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aging-isnt-linear-study-says-heres-when-you-age-dramatically-472146</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Aug 2024 04:02:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Skipping Through Online Videos Can Boost Boredom, Try Watching Them Fully: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skipping-through-online-videos-can-boost-boredom-try-watching-them-filled-study-472145 <description><![CDATA[The researchers analyzed the impact of digital switching on boredom and found that the habit of watching only short snippets of videos or frequently fast-forwarding through them can actually increase feelings of boredom.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skipping-through-online-videos-can-boost-boredom-try-watching-them-filled-study-472145</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:32:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Resveratrol Supplements to Unlock the Secret to Longevity and Vitality]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-resveratrol-supplements-unlock-secret-longevity-vitality-472137 <description><![CDATA[Resveratrol supplements, sourced from grapes and berries, are renowned for their antioxidant benefits, supporting heart health, cognitive function, and longevity. Ideal for adults interested in anti-aging and overall wellness, these supplements offer a convenient way to harness the natural power of Resveratrol for a healthier, more vibrant life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-resveratrol-supplements-unlock-secret-longevity-vitality-472137</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Aug 2024 12:22:25 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>