<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Can Mental Disorders Spread? Study Says They Can Among Adolescent Social Groups]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-mental-disorders-spread-study-says-they-can-among-teenager-social-groups-471781 <description><![CDATA[The greater the number of classmates diagnosed with a mental disorder, the higher the risk of an individual receiving a mental disorder diagnosis later in life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-mental-disorders-spread-study-says-they-can-among-teenager-social-groups-471781</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 May 2024 04:22:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Exposure In Womb Or As Newborn May Elevate Children's Social, Breathing Issues]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-exposure-womb-newborn-may-elevate-children-social-breathing-issues-4 <description><![CDATA[The study investigated if exposure to COVID-19 during pregnancy or right after birth has a long-term impact on the development and breathing of babies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-exposure-womb-newborn-may-elevate-children-social-breathing-issues-4</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 May 2024 01:23:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Conquer Leg Cramps with These Proven Relief Solutions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/conquer-leg-cramps-these-proven-relief-solutions-471776 <description><![CDATA[Athletes and normal people alike have discovered effective relief solutions for leg cramps, ranging from creams to supplements that provide immediate relief.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/conquer-leg-cramps-these-proven-relief-solutions-471776</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 15:16:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want Better Digestive Health This Year? Try These Fiber Supplements ASAP]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-better-digestive-health-this-year-try-these-fibre-supplements-asap-471770 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top fiber supplements of 2024 that simplify daily nutrition and promote digestive health for a vibrant lifestyle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-better-digestive-health-this-year-try-these-fibre-supplements-asap-471770</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 12:55:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vulnerability To Stress In Adolescence Raises Men's Risk Of Psoriasis Later: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vulnerability-stress-adolescent-raises-while-risk-psoriasis-later-study-471777 <description><![CDATA[Adolescent men with greater vulnerability to stress experience a 31% higher risk of developing psoriasis compared to those with high-stress resilience, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vulnerability-stress-adolescent-raises-while-risk-psoriasis-later-study-471777</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 04:34:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Epidural Use Linked To Reduced Risk Of Complications In Mothers After Childbirth]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/epidural-use-linked-reduced-risk-complications-mothers-after-childbirth-471774 <description><![CDATA[The benefit was particularly seen in those women who had a "medical indication" for epidural analgesia during labor and those who had a premature delivery.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/epidural-use-linked-reduced-risk-complications-mothers-after-childbirth-471774</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 03:22:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Reports Second Human Case Of Bird Flu In Michigan Dairy Worker]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-reports-second- human-case-of-bird-flu-michigan-dairy-worker-471772 <description><![CDATA[The CDC confirmed there is still no evidence of human-to-human transmission, and infection risk to the public remains low.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-reports-second- human-case-of-bird-flu-michigan-dairy-worker-471772</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 02:12:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Metformin Prevent Cancer? Study Links It To Reduced Blood Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-metformin-prevent-cancer-study-links-it-reduced-blood-cancer-risk-471768 <description><![CDATA[The surprising potential of metformin for cancer prevention emerged after researchers found an association between metformin use and a reduced risk of myeloproliferative neoplasms (MPN), a rare type of blood cancer that can progress to acute leukemia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-metformin-prevent-cancer-study-links-it-reduced-blood-cancer-risk-471768</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 May 2024 04:37:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ex-Smokers Who Vape Still At High Risk Of Lung Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ex-smokers-who-vape-still-high-risk-lung-cancer-study-471766 <description><![CDATA[Ex-smokers who vape still face a high risk of lung cancer compared to those who quit nicotine completely.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ex-smokers-who-vape-still-high-risk-lung-cancer-study-471766</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 May 2024 02:45:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fish Oil Supplements May Raise Heart Disease, Stroke Risk In Healthy Individuals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fish-oil-supplements-may-raise-heart-disease-中风-risk-healthy-individuals-471764 <description><![CDATA[While fish oil supplements may slow disease progression and lower the risk of death in people with a history of cardiovascular diseases, they might increase the risk of first-time heart disease and stroke among healthy individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fish-oil-supplements-may-raise-heart-disease-中风-risk-healthy-individuals-471764</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 May 2024 01:29:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Exercise That Could Reduce Knee Pain, Risk Of Osteoarthritis ]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-exercise-that-c​​ould-reduce-knee-pain-risk-of-osteoarthritis-471761 <description><![CDATA[Regular bicycling could reduce the chances of frequent knee pain, radiographic osteoarthritis (ROA), and symptomatic radiographic osteoarthritis (SOA), the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-exercise-that-c​​ould-reduce-knee-pain-risk-of-osteoarthritis-471761</guid><pubDate> Tue, 21 May 2024 05:07:31 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>