<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Daily 3 Servings Of Kimchi Could Reduce Risk Of Obesity In Men: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-3-servings-kimchi-could-reduce-risk-obesity-men-study-471349 <description><![CDATA[The researchers explored if regular consumption of kimchi could cut the risk of overall obesity, and abdominal obesity, which is particularly harmful to health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-3-servings-kimchi-could-reduce-risk-obesity-men-study-471349</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Shampoo For Oily Hair In 2024: Say Goodbye To Grease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shampoo-oily-hair-say-goodbye-grease-471347 <description><![CDATA[Finding the best shampoo for oily hair may not be very easy, especially with the myriads of choices. Fortunately, we have compiled some of the best ones for you.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shampoo-oily-hair-say-goodbye-grease-471347</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:24:36 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Toothpaste For 2024: Ensure Dental Health And Freshness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-toothpaste-ensure-dental-health-freshness-471342 <description><![CDATA[Explore expert-recommended choices and choose the best toothpaste to maintain optimal dental health and a dazzling smile.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-toothpaste-ensure-dental-health-freshness-471342</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:35:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even Moderate Levels Of Radon Linked To Increased Risk Of Stroke, Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-moderate-levels-radon-linked-increased-risk-中风-study-reveals-471345 <description><![CDATA[Radon is a radioactive gas with no smell, taste or color that can make its way into homes. It causes about 21,000 lung cancer deaths in the U.S. every year, according to U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) estimates.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-moderate-levels-radon-linked-increased-risk-中风-study-reveals-471345</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Feb 2024 03:28:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Retinol Serums For 2024: Age-Defying Elixir For Radiant Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-retinol-serums-age-defying-elixir-radiant-skin-471343 <description><![CDATA[Here, we have compiled a list of the best retinol serums to diminish fine lines, wrinkles, and uneven skin tone.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-retinol-serums-age-defying-elixir-radiant-skin-471343</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jan 2024 10:43:37 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Probiotics For Women In 2024: Empower Your Gut Health]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-probiotics-women-empower-your-gut-health-471335 <description><![CDATA[Here is a list of probiotics for women to help them support their digestive health, balance vaginal flora, and boost immunity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-probiotics-women-empower-your-gut-health-471335</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jan 2024 07:57:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Heat Protectant Spray For 2024: The Ultimate Defense For Your Hair]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-heat-protectant-spray-ultimate-defense-your-hair-471341 <description><![CDATA[Here are some of the best heat protectant hair sprays that offer a vital shield against the damaging effects of styling tools like straighteners and curling irons.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-heat-protectant-spray-ultimate-defense-your-hair-471341</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jan 2024 05:58:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Sunscreens For The Face In 2024: Guard Your Glow]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-sunscreens-face-guard-your-glow-471334 <description><![CDATA[Whether it's summer or winter, finding the best sunscreen for the face is a must. Here is our list of the most popular sunscreens to protect your skin.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-sunscreens-face-guard-your-glow-471334</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jan 2024 04:28:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Good Nutrition Before And During Pregnancy Could Prevent Childhood Obesity, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/good-nutrition-before-during-pregnancy-could-prevent-childhood-obesity-study-says-471340 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that when mothers take supplements with probiotics, myoinositol and vitamins B2, B6, B12 and D before giving birth, their children have less rapid weight gain and obesity by the age of 2.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/good-nutrition-before-during-pregnancy-could-prevent-childhood-obesity-study-says-471340</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jan 2024 01:13:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Drink More Tomato Juice: Study Says It Has Antimicrobial Properties To Eliminate Typhoid-Causing Salmonella]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drink-more-tomato-juice-study-says-it-has-antimicrobial-properties-eliminate-typhoid-causing-471338 <description><![CDATA[The researchers hope their findings will inspire more people, particularly children and teenagers, to eat and drink more tomatoes and other fruits and vegetables rich in antimicrobial properties.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drink-more-tomato-juice-study-says-it-has-antimicrobial-properties-eliminate-typhoid-causing-471338</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 23:53:29 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Piping Rock Empowers Wellness With Quality Supplements]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-piping-rock-empowers-wellness-quality-supplements-471337 <description><![CDATA[With the market flooded with countless options, navigating through the sea of options to find effective products is important.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-piping-rock-empowers-wellness-quality-supplements-471337</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:25:43 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>