<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA[Inflammatory Bowel Disease Can Heighten Stroke Risk: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/inflammatory-bowel-disease-can-heighten-stroke-risk-study-470140 <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory Bowel Disease refers to a group of chronic inflammatory disorders, including Crohn's disease and ulcerative colitis, affecting the digestive tract.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/inflammatory-bowel-disease-can-heighten-stroke-risk-study-470140</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 05:28:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Jamestown Canyon Virus Detected In Michigan; How To Protect Yourself Against Bites]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/jamestown-canyon-virus-detected-michigan-how-protect-yourself-against-bites-470136 <description><![CDATA[Those infected with the virus are likely to experience mild-to-moderate symptoms, which can manifest within a few days to two weeks after being bitten by an infected mosquito.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/jamestown-canyon-virus-detected-michigan-how-protect-yourself-against-bites-470136</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:24:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Says Teens May Have Weaker Bones After Bariatric Surgery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-teens-may-have-weaker-bones-after-bariatric-surgery-470139 <description><![CDATA[Although beneficial for reducing weight, bariatric surgeries can affect bone strength in teens and young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-teens-may-have-weaker-bones-after-bariatric-surgery-470139</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:00:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Food Cooked At High Temperatures May Be Cancerous; Here's Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/food-cooked-high-temperatures-may-cancerous-heres-why-470133 <description><![CDATA[Scientists noted that high-heat cooking form small molecules, which interact with the consumer's healthy DNA, making them susceptible to cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/food-cooked-high-temperatures-may-cancerous-heres-why-470133</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:13:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Smart Drugs' May Backfire: Study Says Taking ADHD Pills As Brain Enhancers Reduces Efficiency]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smart-drugs-may-backfire-study-says-taking-adhd-pills-brain-enhancers-reduces-efficiency-470135 <description><![CDATA[Researchers warn against the use of ADHD pills by people without the condition. Taking these "smart drugs" can reduce efficiency and can do more harm than good.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smart-drugs-may-backfire-study-says-taking-adhd-pills-brain-enhancers-reduces-efficiency-470135</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:02:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Probiotics With Antidepressants Reduces Symptoms Of Depression: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/taking-probiotics-antidepressants-reduces-symptoms-depression-study-470131 <description><![CDATA[The latest study suggests that patients on antidepressants may have reduced symptoms of the mental disorder when their gut health is improved with probiotics.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/taking-probiotics-antidepressants-reduces-symptoms-depression-study-470131</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 01:13:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Implants, Liposuction Patients Dead Amid Meningitis Outbreak At Mexico Clinics]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/4-implants-liposuction-patients-dead-amid-meningitis-outbreak-mexico-clinics-470129 <description><![CDATA[Around 200 people from the U.S. might have gotten exposed to fungal meningitis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/4-implants-liposuction-patients-dead-amid-meningitis-outbreak-mexico-clinics-470129</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 23:53:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Wuhan Lab Scientists Studying Coronavirus Contracted COVID-19 First: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/wuhan-lab-scientists-studying-coronavirus-contracted-covid-19-first-report-470127 <description><![CDATA[A report exposed what happened inside the Wuhan lab that's believed to be the origin of COVID-19.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/wuhan-lab-scientists-studying-coronavirus-contracted-covid-19-first-report-470127</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 23:47:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Experts Continue To Track New COVID-19 Variants At Airports]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-experts-continue-track-new-covid-19-variants-airports-470124 <description><![CDATA[CDC experts are monitoring samples from international passengers arriving in the U.S.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-experts-continue-track-new-covid-19-variants-airports-470124</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 23:35:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Could Bird Flu Cause The Next Pandemic After COVID-19?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-bird-flu-cause-next-pandemic-after-covid-19-470121 <description><![CDATA[The re-emergence of avian influenza has raised concerns about a possible global pandemic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-bird-flu-cause-next-pandemic-after-covid-19-470121</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 23:33:12 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TERMS SERVICE]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/terms-service<description><![CDATA[Terms and Conditions of Service]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/terms-service</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:22:46 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>