<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[STSS: Rare Flesh-Eating Bacteria That Kills Within 48 Hours Spreads In Japan]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stss-rare-flesh-eating-bacteria-that-kills-within-48-hours-spreads-japan-471859 <description><![CDATA[Streptococcal Toxic Shock Syndrome (STSS), caused by Group A Streptococcus, can result in severe complications including low blood pressure, irregular heart rate, rapid breathing, necrotizing fasciitis potentially leading to limb loss, organ failure, and toxic shock.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stss-rare-flesh-eating-bacteria-that-kills-within-48-hours-spreads-japan-471859</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jun 2024 01:49:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Small Fish Intake Reduces Risk Of All-Cause Mortality, Death From Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/small-fish-intake-reduces-risk-all-cause-mortality-death-cancer-study-471857 <description><![CDATA[A group of researchers from Japan discovered potential life-extending benefits of habitually eating small fish eaten whole, particularly among women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/small-fish-intake-reduces-risk-all-cause-mortality-death-cancer-study-471857</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:59:06 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Turning To Junk Food During Stress? Study Says It Increases Anxiety]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/turning-junk-food-during-stress-study-says-it-increases-anxiety-471856 <description><![CDATA[The study investigated the underlying factors behind the connection between a high-fat diet and anxiety.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/turning-junk-food-during-stress-study-says-it-increases-anxiety-471856</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jun 2024 01:50:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Kickstart Your Health Journey? Get Your Cholesterol Checked At Home Today!]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-kickstart-your-health-journey-get-your-cholesterol-checked-home-today-471845 <description><![CDATA[To proactively combat abnormal cholesterol, it's essential to have a test. This allows you to detect early signs that may affect your overall health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-kickstart-your-health-journey-get-your-cholesterol-checked-home-today-471845</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:29:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Delivering Low Birth Weight Babies May Heighten Women's Risk Of Dementia]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/delivering-low-birth-weight-babies-may-heighten-womens-risk-dementia-471855 <description><![CDATA[Individuals who give birth to infants weighing less than 5.5 pounds are at a higher risk of experiencing memory and cognitive problems later in life, in contrast to those who deliver infants without low birth weight, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/delivering-low-birth-weight-babies-may-heighten-womens-risk-dementia-471855</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 04:39:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[9/11 First Responders At Elevated Risk Of Early Onset Dementia, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-11-first-responders-elevated-risk-early-onset-dementia-study-says-471853 <description><![CDATA[There is a higher likelihood of developing dementia before reaching the age of 65 in the first responders to the 9/11 site who experienced severe exposure to toxic debris in contrast to minimally exposed responders or those who utilized personal protective equipment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-11-first-responders-elevated-risk-early-onset-dementia-study-says-471853</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 03:24:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Reduce TV Watching And Get Off The Couch: Study Reveals Secret To Healthy Aging]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reduce-tv-watching-get-off-couch-study-reveals-secret-healthy-aging-471852 <description><![CDATA[Swapping just one hour of daily TV watching for light physical activity at home can improve the odds of reaching a healthy age of 70 or beyond by 8%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reduce-tv-watching-get-off-couch-study-reveals-secret-healthy-aging-471852</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:56:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Levels Of Toxic Cancer-Causing Ethylene Oxide Detected In Louisiana: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-有毒-癌症-导致-乙烯-氧化物-检测到-路易斯安那-报告-471850 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that the air in the industrialized stretch of southeast Louisiana dubbed "cancer alley" has 20 times higher concentrations of carcinogenic ethylene oxide than previously expected.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-有毒-癌症-导致-乙烯-氧化物-检测到-路易斯安那-报告-471850</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jun 2024 03:47:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra-Processed Plant Food Raises Risk Of Heart Diseases, Related Deaths: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-plant-food-raises-risk-heart-diseases-lated-deaths-study-471848 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that ultra-processed plant-based foods do not offer health benefits and are actually linked to an increased risk of heart disease and heart-related mortality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-plant-food-raises-risk-heart-diseases-lated-deaths-study-471848</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jun 2024 02:34:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder Awareness Month: Eliminate Stigma As Expert Unveils Facts And Myths]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/post-traumatic-stress-disorder-awareness-month-eliminate-stigma-expert-unveils-facts-myths-471846 <description><![CDATA[Post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) is a frequently misunderstood mental health condition, often unfairly seen as a sign of weakness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/post-traumatic-stress-disorder-awareness-month-eliminate-stigma-expert-unveils-facts-myths-471846</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jun 2024 01:30:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Planetary Health Diet? Study Says It May Reduce Premature Death By 30%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-planetary-health-diet-study-says-it-may-reduce-premature-death-30-471844 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered that adhering to a healthy, sustainable diet, termed the planetary health diet, can help preserve the environment and lower the risk of premature death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-planetary-health-diet-study-says-it-may-reduce-premature-death-30-471844</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jun 2024 03:58:52 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>