<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Heme Iron And Diabetes: Study Says Reducing Red Meat Could Lower Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heme-iron-diabetes-study-says-reducing-red-meat-could-lower-risk-472122 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that heme iron, which is present in red meat and other animal products, could increase the risk of type 2 diabetes. In contrast, non-heme iron in plant-based food does not pose a similar risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heme-iron-diabetes-study-says-reducing-red-meat-could-lower-risk-472122</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Aug 2024 05:08:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cancer Risk 'From The First Drop': Study Warns Even Light Drinking Risky To Elderly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cancer-risk-first-drop-study-warns-even-light-drinking-risky-elderly-472119 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that no amount of alcohol could help heart health, and even light drinking could increase cancer deaths among elderly adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cancer-risk-first-drop-study-warns-even-light-drinking-risky-elderly-472119</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:29:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Human Parvovirus B19 Cases Surge, Certain Groups At High Risk, CDC Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ human-parvovirus-b19-cases-surge-certain-groups-high-risk-cdc-says-472116 <description><![CDATA[The CDC reports a surge in highly contagious human parvovirus B19 infections in the U.S., particularly among children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ human-parvovirus-b19-cases-surge-certain-groups-high-risk-cdc-says-472116</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:10:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Guide to Ginseng's Benefits, Uses and Varieties]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/compressive-guide-ginsengs-benefits-uses-varieties-472112 <description><![CDATA[Ginseng, a potent herb in traditional medicine, is prized for boosting energy, enhancing immunity, and improving mental clarity. The main types—Asian, American, and Siberian—each offer unique benefits. Ginseng supports energy, cognitive function, immune health, and cardiovascular wellness while reducing inflammation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/compressive-guide-ginsengs-benefits-uses-varieties-472112</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:42:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Glucosamine Sulfate Supplements Of 2024 And Its Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-glucosamine-sulfate-supplements-2024-its-benefits-472101 <description><![CDATA[As you age, your body loses the ability to make sufficient levels of glucosamine needed to maintain cartilage health. Glucosamine sulfate supplements may help improve joint health and mobility.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-glucosamine-sulfate-supplements-2024-its-benefits-472101</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:32:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tablet To Control Tantrums? Study Says It Reduces Child's Ability To Manage Anger]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tablet-control-tantrums-study-says-it-reduces-childs-ability-manage-anger-472108 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now warn that tablet use in early years may create a vicious cycle as it could impair a child's ability to manage anger and increase outbursts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tablet-control-tantrums-study-says-it-reduces-childs-ability-manage-anger-472108</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:58:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Parents' Eating Habits Influence Children To Develop Similar Behaviors, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/parents-eating-habits-influence-children-develop-similar-behaviors-study-finds-472107 <description><![CDATA[A study suggests that when parents stick to their commitment to a balanced diet, they are more likely to eat and feed healthily, which will foster healthy eating habits in children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/parents-eating-habits-influence-children-develop-similar-behaviors-study-finds-472107</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:45:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Global Cancer Crisis: Cases, Deaths Among Men Expected To Surge By 2050]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/global-cancer-crisis-cases-deaths-among-men-expected-surge-2050-472105 <description><![CDATA[The researchers analyzed 30 types of cancers in men across 185 countries and territories in 2022 to make projections for 2050.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/global-cancer-crisis-cases-deaths-among-men-expected-surge-2050-472105</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Aug 2024 01:38:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Diabetic Remission Possible Through Soups And Shakes Diet, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetic-remission-possible-through-soups-shakes-diet-says-study-472099 <description><![CDATA[A recent study gives hope to millions of people struggling with diabetes, as researchers say diabetic remission is possible through a simple dietary intervention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetic-remission-possible-through-soups-shakes-diet-says-study-472099</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Aug 2024 04:37:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Washing May Not Reduce Pesticides On Fruits, But Peeling Helps: Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/washing-may-not-reduce-pesticides-fruits-peeling-helps-says-study-472096 <description><![CDATA[Using a new imaging technique—surface-enhanced Raman spectroscopy (SERS)—researchers found that pesticides can penetrate beyond the peel and into the pulp layer of fruits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/washing-may-not-reduce-pesticides-fruits-peeling-helps-says-study-472096</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:21:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Neffy: Know All About First FDA Approved Nasal Spray To Treat Severe Allergic Reactions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neffy-know-all-about-first-fda-approved-nasal-spray-treat-severe-allergic-reactions-472095 <description><![CDATA[The new treatment, a needle-free alternative, could be used for managing severe allergic responses in children and adults, weighing at least 66 pounds, the FDA said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neffy-know-all-about-first-fda-approved-nasal-spray-treat-severe-allergic-reactions-472095</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Aug 2024 01:58:36 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>