<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Can Constipation Affect Heart Disease Risk? Know What A New Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-constipation-affect-heart-disease-risk-know-what-new-study-says-472151 <description><![CDATA[People who have constipation face more than twice the risk of a major cardiac event when compared to those without the condition, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-constipation-affect-heart-disease-risk-know-what-new-study-says-472151</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Aug 2024 05:40:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Aging Isn't Linear, Study Says Here's When You Age Dramatically]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aging-isnt-linear-study-says-heres-when-you-age-dramatically-472146 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that the human body ages dramatically at ages 44 and 60.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aging-isnt-linear-study-says-heres-when-you-age-dramatically-472146</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Aug 2024 04:02:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Skipping Through Online Videos Can Boost Boredom, Try Watching Them Fully: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skipping-through-online-videos-can-boost-boredom-try-watching-them-filled-study-472145 <description><![CDATA[The researchers analyzed the impact of digital switching on boredom and found that the habit of watching only short snippets of videos or frequently fast-forwarding through them can actually increase feelings of boredom.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skipping-through-online-videos-can-boost-boredom-try-watching-them-filled-study-472145</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:32:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Resveratrol Supplements to Unlock the Secret to Longevity and Vitality]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-resveratrol-supplements-unlock-secret-longevity-vitality-472137 <description><![CDATA[Resveratrol supplements, sourced from grapes and berries, are renowned for their antioxidant benefits, supporting heart health, cognitive function, and longevity. Ideal for adults interested in anti-aging and overall wellness, these supplements offer a convenient way to harness the natural power of Resveratrol for a healthier, more vibrant life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-resveratrol-supplements-unlock-secret-longevity-vitality-472137</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Aug 2024 12:22:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Lutien Supplements: Benefits, Side Effects, Dosage And More]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lutien-supplements-benefits-side-effects-dosage-more-472126 <description><![CDATA[Lutein provides a protective layer for the eye's natural defense and ensures your eyes stay sharp and healthy even during old age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lutien-supplements-benefits-side-effects-dosage-more-472126</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Aug 2024 08:54:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Curcumin Supplements And Their Impact On Health: Benefits You Should Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-curcumin-supplements-their-impact-health-472113 <description><![CDATA[In recent years, turmeric and its active ingredient -- curcumin -- have become a subject of much research due to their potential health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-curcumin-supplements-their-impact-health-472113</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:43:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best NAC Supplements Uncovered: How N-Acetyl L-Cysteine Supports Health and Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-nac-supplements-uncovered-how-n-乙酰-l-半胱氨酸-supports-health-wellness-472128 <description><![CDATA[N-Acetyl L-Cysteine (NAC) is a powerful supplement that enhances overall health by supporting respiratory function, liver detoxification, and antioxidant protection through increased glutathione levels. Known for its potential benefits in mental well-being and immune system support, NAC is a versatile addition to any wellness routine. Available in convenient forms like capsules and powders, NAC is valued for its wide-ranging health benefits and effectiveness in promoting long-term vitality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-nac-supplements-uncovered-how-n-乙酰-l-半胱氨酸-supports-health-wellness-472128</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:39:39 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Wants To Further Reduce Salt Levels In Packaged, Processed Food]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-wants-further-reduce-salt-levels-packaged-processed-food-472135 <description><![CDATA[After the successful execution of the Phase I target, the FDA plans to further reduce sodium levels by 20%, to bring the average intake to about 2,750 milligrams per day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-wants-further-reduce-salt-levels-packaged-processed-food-472135</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Aug 2024 05:19:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Untreated Hypertension Linked To 42% Higher Risk Of Alzheimer's Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/untreatment-hypertension-linked-42-higher-risk-alzheimers-disease-study-472134 <description><![CDATA[Untreated hypertension is linked to a 42% higher risk of Alzheimer's disease in adults aged 60 or older, a study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/untreatment-hypertension-linked-42-higher-risk-alzheimers-disease-study-472134</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:17:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Chronic High Coffee Consumption Raises Heart Disease Risk, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-high-coffee-conspiration-raises-heart-disease-risk-says-study-472132 <description><![CDATA[The study found that drinking more than 400 mg of caffeine most days raises the risk of heart disease in otherwise healthy individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-high-coffee-conspiration-raises-heart-disease-risk-says-study-472132</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Aug 2024 02:19:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Dandelion Extract Supplements: A Natural Medicine Staple]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-dandelion-extract-supplements-natural-medicine-staple-472117 <description><![CDATA[Dandelion supplements offer numerous health benefits, including liver support, digestive aid, and anti-inflammatory effects. Rich in vitamins and antioxidants, they help detoxify the body and regulate blood sugar levels. Available in forms like capsules, teas, and extracts, dandelion supplements are versatile and easy to incorporate into wellness routines.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-dandelion-extract-supplements-natural-medicine-staple-472117</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:58:06 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>