<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh</language><item><title><![CDATA[Top 5 Back Braces Of 2024: Discover The Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-back-braces-discover-relief-471274 <description><![CDATA[Say goodbye to slouching and welcome a more confident, pain-free you as we explore the key features of the top five back braces]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-back-braces-discover-relief-471274</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 05:05:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Eyelash Growth Serums For 2024: Transform Your Lashes And Elevate Your Gaze]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-eyelash-growth-serums-transform-your-lashes-elevate-your-gaze-471272 <description><![CDATA[Having long lashes can enhance your confidence. Here are some eyelash serums to help you achieve the perfect look.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-eyelash-growth-serums-transform-your-lashes-elevate-your-gaze-471272</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 04:05:36 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Diabetes Treatment? Study Suggests Cold Water Swimming, Cinnamon Supplements Could Lower Blood Sugar Levels]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-diabetes-treatment-study-suggests-cold-water-swimming-cinnamon-supplements-could-lower-blood-471277 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that the new approach helped lower the blood sugar levels of rats with diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-diabetes-treatment-study-suggests-cold-water-swimming-cinnamon-supplements-could-lower-blood-471277</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 03:07:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Finds Surprising Link Between Childhood Stress And Heart Disease Risk In The Future]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-surprising-link- Between-childhood-stress-heart-disease-risk-future-471275 <description><![CDATA[Individuals who endure consistently high perceived stress are more prone to high blood pressure, obesity and other cardiometabolic risk factors, according to the new study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-surprising-link- Between-childhood-stress-heart-disease-risk-future-471275</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:36:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 5 Belly Tightening Creams Of 2024: For A Boost Of Confidence]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-belly-tightening-creams-boost-confidence-471271 <description><![CDATA[Enriched with powerful natural ingredients, each cream offers a unique blend that tightens, tones, and rejuvenates the delicate skin around the abdomen.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-belly-tightening-creams-boost-confidence-471271</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Jan 2024 10:19:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Silicone Gels For Scar Treatment: Journey Toward Flawless Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-silicone-gels-scar-treatment-journey-toward-flawless-skin-471268 <description><![CDATA[Using silicone gels can aid in minimizing the visibility of scars. Here are some of the best silicone gels for scar treatment in the market today.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-silicone-gels-scar-treatment-journey-toward-flawless-skin-471268</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:29:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Skip Juice, Take Whole Fruits: 100% Fruit Juice Associated With Weight Gain In Children, Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skip-juice-take-whole-fruits-100-fruit-juice- Associated-weight-gain-children-adults-471267 <description><![CDATA[The American Academy of Pediatrics recommends avoiding juices for babies younger than 1 year and limiting intake to four ounces a day for children from 1 to 3 years old and to six ounces a day for children between 4 and 6 years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skip-juice-take-whole-fruits-100-fruit-juice- Associated-weight-gain-children-adults-471267</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Jan 2024 02:59:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cannabis Use In Pregnancy Linked To Certain Childhood Cancers, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cannabis-use-pregnancy-linked-certain-childhood-cancers-study-finds-471265 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that children born to mothers exposed to illicit drugs, particularly cannabis, are at an increased risk of tumors of the central nervous system such as medulloblastomas and supratentorial primitive neuroectodermal tumors (PNETS), and retinoblastoma.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cannabis-use-pregnancy-linked-certain-childhood-cancers-study-finds-471265</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Jan 2024 23:53:18 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Hospital Beds For Home Care In 2024: Combining Comfort And Healing]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-hospital-beds-home-care-2024-combining-comfort-healing-471264 <description><![CDATA[A hospital bed is crucial due to its specialized features designed to meet the unique needs of patients with health issues.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-hospital-beds-home-care-2024-combining-comfort-healing-471264</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Jan 2024 11:35:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Erectile Dysfunction Drugs With Common Chest Pain Medication May Lead To Early Death]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-erectile-dysfunction-drugs-common-chest-pain-medication-may-lead-early-death-471263 <description><![CDATA[People who take the drug phosphodiesterase-5 inhibitors (PDE5i) – a common medication for erectile dysfunction – are at higher risk of early death when they use it along with nitrates, a medication for chest pain, a new study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-erectile-dysfunction-drugs-common-chest-pain-medication-may-lead-early-death-471263</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Jan 2024 04:36:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Temperature, Humidity During Pregnancy May Affect Child's Blood Pressure: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-temporal-humidity-during-pregnancy-may-affect-childs-blood-Pressure-study-471261 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that prenatal exposure to higher humidity was associated with a faster increase in systolic and diastolic blood pressure, and a higher temperature was linked to a slower increase in systolic blood pressure in childhood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-temporal-humidity-during-pregnancy-may-affect-childs-blood-Pressure-study-471261</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:14:14 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>