<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh</language><item><title><![CDATA[Internet Addiction In Adolescence Alters Brains: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/internet-addiction-adolescent-alters-brains-study-471819 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that internet addiction in young people could alter their brains, and disrupt the signaling in critical neural networks impacting decision-making, attention, memory, coordination, and mental health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/internet-addiction-adolescent-alters-brains-study-471819</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jun 2024 01:52:09 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Better Sleep May Help People Overcome Feelings Of Loneliness: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/better-sleep-may-help-people-overcome-feelings-loneiness-study-471817 <description><![CDATA[In the study, better sleep health was associated with lower total and emotional loneliness across ages, particularly for younger adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/better-sleep-may-help-people-overcome-feelings-loneiness-study-471817</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:39:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[In-Flight Drinking Linked To Heart Risks Even In Young, Healthy Individuals: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flight-drinking-linked-heart-risks-even-young-healthy-individuals-study-471816 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that the combination of alcohol intake with sleeping under hypobaric conditions poses a considerable strain on the cardiac system even for healthy individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flight-drinking-linked-heart-risks-even-young-healthy-individuals-study-471816</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:19:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Auto-Brewery Syndrome: Rare Condition Causes Intoxication In 50-Year-Old Without Drinking Alcohol]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/auto-brewery-syndrome-rare-condition-causes-intoxation-50-year-old-without-drinking-alcohol-471815 <description><![CDATA[Auto-brewery syndrome is a rare condition where the gut microorganism creates alcohol through fermentation, causing intoxication without drinking.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/auto-brewery-syndrome-rare-condition-causes-intoxation-50-year-old-without-drinking-alcohol-471815</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jun 2024 02:35:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Northern Light Polaris Tub Promises The Benefits Of Both Hot and Cold Baths]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/northern-light-polaris-tub-promises-benefits-both-hot-cold-baths-471801 <description><![CDATA[This innovative product combines the best of both worlds, merging the company's expertise in hot and cold tubs into one convenient package.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/northern-light-polaris-tub-promises-benefits-both-hot-cold-baths-471801</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:30:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Having Obesity For 10 Years Or More Increases Risk Of Heart Attacks, Stroke: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/having-obesity-10-years-more-increases-risk-heart-attacks-中风-study-471814 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that being obese for 10 or more years significantly increases the risk for individuals under the age of 50.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/having-obesity-10-years-more-increases-risk-heart-attacks-中风-study-471814</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jun 2024 03:30:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women With Premenstrual Disorders At Double Risk Of Suicide: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-premenstrual-disorders-double-risk-suicide-study-471813 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that women with premenstrual dysphoric disorders (PMD) are more likely to die from non-natural causes, and average twice the risk of death from suicide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-premenstrual-disorders-double-risk-suicide-study-471813</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:28:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Diet That Could Lower Risk Of Death In US Women To 23%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-diet-that-c​​ould-lower-risk-death-us-women-23-471812 <description><![CDATA[Greater adherence to the Mediterranean diet had up to 23% reduced risk of all-cause mortality in U.S. women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-diet-that-c​​ould-lower-risk-death-us-women-23-471812</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jun 2024 01:33:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Scaling Success: BiomeBank's Product Offerings Unlock the Potential of Microbiome Therapy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scaling-success-biomebanks-product-offerings-unlock-pottial-microbiome-therapy-471811 <description><![CDATA[BiomeBank's donor-derived microbiome therapy, provides an alternative way of treating conditions like C. difficile infection than traditional treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scaling-success-biomebanks-product-offerings-unlock-pottial-microbiome-therapy-471811</guid><pubDate> Fri, 31 May 2024 16:43:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Augmented Assistant Robots (AAR) Unveils A New Era In Robotic Surgery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/augmented-assistant-robots-aar-unveils-new-era-robotic-surgery-471809 <description><![CDATA[From the onset of research and development, the team at AAR focused on minimizing operational costs to ensure that the cost of the surgical procedure could be fully covered by insurance.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/augmented-assistant-robots-aar-unveils-new-era-robotic-surgery-471809</guid><pubDate> Fri, 31 May 2024 16:40:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[One In Three People Experience Insomnia Linked To Ultra-Processed Food: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/one- Three-people-experience-insomnia-linked-ultra-processed-food-study-471807 <description><![CDATA[The consumption of ultra-processed food has a significant association with chronic insomnia, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/one- Three-people-experience-insomnia-linked-ultra-processed-food-study-471807</guid><pubDate> Fri, 31 May 2024 04:54:02 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>