<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Partner's Adult ADHD Raises Risk Of Depression In Women: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partners-adult-adhd-raises-risk-depression-women-study-472435 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that about 59% of women with partners who have ADHD showed depression, with symptoms ranging from mild to severe.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partners-adult-adhd-raises-risk-depression-women-study-472435</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Sep 2024 05:20:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Enterovirus D68 Rising In U.S: Know About Virus Linked To Paralysis In Kids]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/enterovirus-d68-rising-us-know-about-virus-linked-parathesis-kids-472432 <description><![CDATA[Although symptoms of Enterovirus D68 are usually mild in most adults, children are at risk for complications, including severe breathing problems and a nervous system disorder called acute flaccid myelitis, which can cause sudden muscle weakness and paralysis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/enterovirus-d68-rising-us-know-about-virus-linked-parathesis-kids-472432</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Sep 2024 03:43:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pregnancy And Postpartum Complications High In Surrogates: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-postpartum-complications-high-surrogates-study-472429 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that surrogates are at a higher risk of severe postpartum hemorrhage, hypertension, and preeclampsia. Compared to those who conceive naturally or with IVF, they are also at a higher risk of preterm birth.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-postpartum-complications-high-surrogates-study-472429</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Sep 2024 01:50:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Heating Pads To Ease Back Pain And Period Cramps]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-heating-pads-ease-back-pain-period-cramps-472397 <description><![CDATA[There are several ways to give your sore muscles some heat therapy; however, one such extreme and convenient method is heating pads. They are portable and immensely easy to use. They work by improving the elasticity of connective tissues and improving blood flow to the sore muscles. They are also effective in menstrual cramps.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-heating-pads-ease-back-pain-period-cramps-472397</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:54:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Migraine Hats and Wraps For Instant Pain Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-migraine-hats-wraps-instant-pain-relief-472410 <description><![CDATA[According to the American Migraine Foundation, It is the third most common disease in the world and affects 1 in 4 households in the United States alone. Globally, more than 1 billion people have this condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-migraine-hats-wraps-instant-pain-relief-472410</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:41:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best EKG Monitors For Home: Essential Tools For Heart Health Monitoring]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-ekg-monitors-home-essential-tools-heart-health-monitoring-472413 <description><![CDATA[This article explores the top EKG monitors available for home use, highlighting their importance in monitoring heart health. These devices are designed to track heart rhythm and detect irregularities, making them essential for individuals with existing heart conditions or those seeking to maintain their cardiovascular health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-ekg-monitors-home-essential-tools-heart-health-monitoring-472413</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:38:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alcohol-Dependency Treatment Should Be Different For Men And Women: Study Explains Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-dependency-treatment-should- Different-men-women-study-explains-why-472420 <description><![CDATA[The latest study suggests that hormonal and biochemical factors play a crucial role in shaping patterns of alcohol use and dependence in men and women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-dependency-treatment-should- Different-men-women-study-explains-why-472420</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Sep 2024 04:18:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Anti-Depressants May Improve Brain Function, Verbal Memory: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anti-depressants-may-improve-brain-function-verbal-memory-study-472418 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found that the use of antidepressant medications SSRI (Selective Serotonin Reuptake Inhibitors) can help improve brain function, particularly verbal memory.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anti-depressants-may-improve-brain-function-verbal-memory-study-472418</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Sep 2024 02:51:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[First Self-Administered Flu Vaccine For Home Use Gets FDA Approval]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-self-administered-flu-vaccine-home-use-gets-fda-approval-472417 <description><![CDATA[FluMist nasal spray manufactured by AstraZeneca is now approved for home use against influenza infection caused by subtypes A and B from ages 2 through 49.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-self-administered-flu-vaccine-home-use-gets-fda-approval-472417</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:37:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Face Masks For Skincare: Hydration, Cleansing, And Anti-Aging]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-face-masks-skincare-Hydration-cleansing-anti-aging-472369 <description><![CDATA[Face masks are popular skincare treatments designed to hydrate, cleanse, and rejuvenate the skin. They come in various forms like sheet masks, clay masks, and gel-based options, each serving specific skincare needs. Whether you're looking to address dryness, acne, or signs of aging, the right mask can enhance your routine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-face-masks-skincare-Hydration-cleansing-anti-aging-472369</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:21:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Facial Hair Removing Tools For Women: Elevate Your Beauty Routine And Skin Texture]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-facial-hair-removing-tools-women-elevate-your-beauty-routine-skin-texture-472386 <description><![CDATA[If you are someone who is looking for a way to get rid of that unwanted peach fuzz, unruly brows, and chin hairs, you have to invest your money in good facial hair removing products that are available in different forms and cater to various skin types.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-facial-hair-removing-tools-women-elevate-your-beauty-routine-skin-texture-472386</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:20:33 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>