<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Fetal Alcohol Syndrome: Researchers Say Men Should Abstain From Drinking At Least 3 Months Before Conceiving]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fetal-alcohol-syndrome-researchers-say-men-should-abstain-drinking-least-3-months-before-471191 <description><![CDATA[The effect of paternal drinking on the sperm lasts much longer than expected, a new study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fetal-alcohol-syndrome-researchers-say-men-should-abstain-drinking-least-3-months-before-471191</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:52:59 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Holiday Heart Syndrome? Know Symptoms, Steps For Prevention]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-holiday-heart-syndrome-know-symptoms-steps-prevention-471190 <description><![CDATA[Holiday heart syndrome is a heart condition that causes atrial fibrillation or irregular heartbeat after excessive alcohol consumption or binge drinking.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-holiday-heart-syndrome-know-symptoms-steps-prevention-471190</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:42:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Respiratory Illnesses Surging In US; 15 States See 'High' Or 'Very High' Levels, CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/respiratory-illnesses-surge-us-15-states-see-high-very-high-levels-cdc-warns-471189 <description><![CDATA[The U.S Centers for Disease Control and Prevention warns of a surge in respiratory illnesses across the country, with 15 states facing "high" or "very high" levels of infections, including flu, COVID-19, RSV and common cold.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/respiratory-illnesses-surge-us-15-states-see-high-very-high-levels-cdc-warns-471189</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Dec 2023 02:42:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Siblings Of Dementia Patients May Face Risk Of Shortened Lifespan, Even If They Are Not Diagnosed]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/siblings-dementia-病人-may-face-risk-shortened-lifespan-even-if-they-are-not-diagnosed-471188 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that a combination of genetics and environmental factors reduces longevity in dementia patients. The same combination may shorten the lives of their siblings even without dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/siblings-dementia-病人-may-face-risk-shortened-lifespan-even-if-they-are-not-diagnosed-471188</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:53:18 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Wasabi For Cognitive Health? Researchers Say It Could Improve Memory]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/wasabi-cognitive-health-researchers-say-it-could-improve-memory-471187 <description><![CDATA[In a trial conducted in a small group of healthy participants above the age of 60, researchers found a "significant improvement" in short-term and long-term memory with the use of a supplement containing 6-MSITC, the main bioactive compound found in wasabi.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/wasabi-cognitive-health-researchers-say-it-could-improve-memory-471187</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 06:06:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[WHO Warns Of Anthrax Outbreaks In 5 African Countries; Know Symptoms, Risk Factors Of Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/who-warns-anthrax-outbreaks-5-african-countries-know-symptoms-risk-factors-infection-471186 <description><![CDATA[Five countries in east and southern Africa are witnessing anthrax outbreaks, with more than 1,100 suspected cases and 20 related deaths reported this year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/who-warns-anthrax-outbreaks-5-african-countries-know-symptoms-risk-factors-infection-471186</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 02:34:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Chronic Fatigue Syndrome Affects 3.3 Million Adults In US, CDC Says; Know Symptoms, Treatment Options]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-fatigue-syndrome-affects-33-million-adults-us-cdc-says-know-symptoms-treatment-options-471185 <description><![CDATA[Myalgic encephalomyelitis, or chronic fatigue syndrome, is a serious, long-term multisystem illness that limits a person's activity due to fatigue.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-fatigue-syndrome-affects-33-million-adults-us-cdc-says-know-symptoms-treatment-options-471185</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 01:02:48 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Owning A Cat Raises Risk Of Schizophrenia? Study Reveals A Mysterious Association Between The Two]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/owning-cat-raises-risk-schizophrenia-study-reveals-mysterious-association- Between-two-471184 <description><![CDATA[A research team from the University of Queensland in Australia reviewed 17 studies on the topic and found a 2.35 times higher likelihood of Schizophrenia in cat owners. However, the study did not take into account other potential contributing factors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/owning-cat-raises-risk-schizophrenia-study-reveals-mysterious-association- Between-two-471184</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:32:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever: Know Symptoms, Prevention Steps As CDC Warns Travelers To Mexico]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rocky-mountain-spotted-fever-know-symptoms-prevention-steps-cdc-warns-travelers-mexico-471182 <description><![CDATA[The CDC has issued a health alert warning travelers to Baja California, Mexico, about Rocky Mountain spotted fever, after five people from Southern California have been hospitalized with the infection since July.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rocky-mountain-spotted-fever-know-symptoms-prevention-steps-cdc-warns-travelers-mexico-471182</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:44:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Constipation Awareness Month: Expert Shares Tips To Ease Bowel Movement]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/constipation-awareness-month-expert-shares-tips-ease-bowel-movement-471181 <description><![CDATA[While occasional constipation is not a cause of concern and may be resolved with diet and lifestyle adjustments, some people might need additional support from over-the-counter fiber supplements, laxatives or prescription medication.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/constipation-awareness-month-expert-shares-tips-ease-bowel-movement-471181</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:49:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Flaxseeds For Breast Cancer? Study Says Manipulating Gut Microbiota Using Them Could Reduce Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flaxseeds-breast-cancer-study-says-manipulated-gut-microbiota-using-them-could-reduce-risk-471180 <description><![CDATA[In a new study, researchers manipulated gut microbiota using flaxseeds and found it could be beneficial in the prevention of breast cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flaxseeds-breast-cancer-study-says-manipulated-gut-microbiota-using-them-could-reduce-risk-471180</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Dec 2023 03:32:53 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>