<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Mothers' Diet During Pregnancy Can Protect Brain Health Of Her Grandchildren; Researchers Explain How]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mothers-diet-during-pregnancy-can-protect-brain-health-her-grandchildren-researchers-explain-how-470606 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that a woman's diet during early pregnancy, especially the consumption of apples and herbs, can protect the brain health of her children and grandchildren.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mothers-diet-during-pregnancy-can-protect-brain-health-her-grandchildren-researchers-explain-how-470606</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:56:49 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 10 Best Air Purifiers Of 2023]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-air-purifiers-2023-470590 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top-rated air purifiers of 2023, featuring cutting-edge technology and exceptional performance to ensure cleaner and healthier indoor air.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-air-purifiers-2023-470590</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:42:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[8 Best Eye Health Supplements: How These Essential Nutrients Support, Improve Vision]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-best-eye-health-supplements-how-这些-essential- Nutritions-support-improve-vision-470589 <description><![CDATA[Whether you are looking to preserve your vision or address specific eye concerns, these carefully curated supplements are here to enhance and protect your eyesight in the year 2023.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-best-eye-health-supplements-how-这些-essential- Nutritions-support-improve-vision-470589</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:11:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hookworms Can Improve Insulin Resistance In Diabetes Patients, Clinical Trial Shows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hookworms-can-improve-insulin-resistance-diabetes-病人-clinical-tri-shows-470605 <description><![CDATA[A human trial that involves infecting people with live hookworms has proven beneficial for patients at risk of type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hookworms-can-improve-insulin-resistance-diabetes-病人-clinical-tri-shows-470605</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:10:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bone Health And Diet: Researchers Say Vegetarians At 50% Higher Risk Of Hip Fracture]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bone-health-diet-researchers-say-vegetarians-50-higher-risk-hip-fracture-470604 <description><![CDATA[A vegetarian diet, even though considered beneficial for preventing several diseases such as cancer, blood pressure and diabetes, can lead to an increased risk of hip fracture in both men and women, a new study shows.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bone-health-diet-researchers-say-vegetarians-50-higher-risk-hip-fracture-470604</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 02:38:32 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 10 Best Body Detoxes Of 2023]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-body-detoxes-2023-470390 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top 10 body detoxes of 2023 in this comprehensive guide, showcasing the best products and methods to cleanse and rejuvenate your body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-body-detoxes-2023-470390</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 02:26:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hypertension: Study Identifies Best Exercises To Reduce Blood Pressure]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hypertension-study-identizes-best-exercises-reduce-blood-Pressure-470601 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that isometric exercises are the most effective exercises for reducing blood pressure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hypertension-study-identizes-best-exercises-reduce-blood-Pressure-470601</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:38:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[60 Skin Care Tools That Deliver Results And Are Worth Every Penny]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/60-skin-care-tools-that-deliver-results-are-worth-every-penny-470512 <description><![CDATA[Discover a comprehensive guide to 60 top-notch skin care tools that provide remarkable outcomes and are worth every penny.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/60-skin-care-tools-that-deliver-results-are-worth-every-penny-470512</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:19:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Step Into The Ring: Patella Knee Brace Vs Other Alternatives In the Arthritis Showdown]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/step-ring-patella-knee-brace-vs-other-alternatives-arthritis-showdown-470310 <description><![CDATA[Explore the showdown between the patella knee brace and alternative options in the realm of arthritis management, helping you make an informed decision on stepping into the ring for optimal knee support.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/step-ring-patella-knee-brace-vs-other-alternatives-arthritis-showdown-470310</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 23:55:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How To Relieve Knee Pain And Boost Performance With A Patellar Support Strap: A Step-By-Step Guide]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-relieve-knee-pain-boost-performance-patellar-support-strap-step-step-guide-470306 <description><![CDATA[Discover effective strategies to alleviate knee pain and enhance performance using a step-by-step guide featuring the utilization of a patellar support strap.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-relieve-knee-pain-boost-performance-patellar-support-strap-step-step-guide-470306</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 23:53:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Maximize Stability And Recovery: A Comprehensive Guide On Using A Knee Brace For Optimal Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maximize-stability-recovery-compressive-guide-using-knee-brace-optimal-support-470352 <description><![CDATA[Unlock the potential for enhanced stability and accelerated recovery with a comprehensive guide that explores the optimal utilization of a knee brace.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maximize-stability-recovery-compressive-guide-using-knee-brace-optimal-support-470352</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:48:15 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>