<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA[International Yoga Day: 5 Poses To Treat Sleep Disorders]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-yoga-day-5-poses-treat-sleep-disorders-470222 <description><![CDATA[On this International Yoga Day, learn more about the poses that can help you treat sleep disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-yoga-day-5-poses-treat-sleep-disorders-470222</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:02:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Scientists Identify Key Process Driving The Progression Of Huntington's Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-identify-key-process-driving-progression-huntingtons-disease-470220 <description><![CDATA[The researchers said the toxic clumps of protein that trigger Huntington's Disease spread like a destructive forest fire.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-identify-key-process-driving-progression-huntingtons-disease-470220</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 03:27:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Some Medications Can Make You More Prone To Sunburns; Tips To Protect Your Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/some-medications-can-make-you-more-prone-sunburns-tips-protect-your-skin-470219 <description><![CDATA[Take more care to apply sunscreen and minimize direct exposure to sunlight if you are on a medication that causes photosensitivity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/some-medications-can-make-you-more-prone-sunburns-tips-protect-your-skin-470219</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 01:58:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mental Health Patients On Antidepressants Less Likely To Test Positive For COVID-19: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mental-health-patients-antidepressants-less-likely-test-positive-covid-19-study-470218 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that patients who had antidepressants prescribed on their medical records were approximately 40% less likely to test positive for COVID-19 compared to those who were not taking the medication.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mental-health-patients-antidepressants-less-likely-test-positive-covid-19-study-470218</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:19:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Missouri Man Dies After Eating Raw Oysters From Seafood Stand]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/missouri-man-dies-after-eating-raw-oysters-seafood-stand-470210 <description><![CDATA[The man died shortly after contracting a flesh-eating infection from eating raw oysters.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/missouri-man-dies-after-eating-raw-oysters-seafood-stand-470210</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:28:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Virologist Advising WHO Acknowledges Mistake In Dismissing Wuhan Lab Leak Theory]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virologist-advising-who-acknowledges-mistake-dismissing-wuhan-lab-leak-theory-470212 <description><![CDATA[The expert expressed regret over the dismissal of the lab leak theory.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virologist-advising-who-acknowledges-mistake-dismissing-wuhan-lab-leak-theory-470212</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:22:20 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[This Could Explain Why COVID-19 Is Mild For Some, Deadly For Others]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-could-explain-why-covid-19-mild-some-deadly-others-470214 <description><![CDATA[A new study may have identified the regulators of the immune response against COVID-19.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-could-explain-why-covid-19-mild-some-deadly-others-470214</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:16:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vaccine Makers Gear Up For Fall Rollout, Embracing FDA's Strain Selection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaccine-makers-gear-fall-rollout-embracing-fdas-strain-selection-470216 <description><![CDATA[Pfizer, Moderna and Novavax are preparing for the fall rollout of their new COVID-19 vaccines.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaccine-makers-gear-fall-rollout-embracing-fdas-strain-selection-470216</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:13:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ease your Headaches and Migraines with the 5 Best Caps of 2023]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ease-your-headaches-migraines-5-best-caps-2023-470208 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top 5 caps of 2023 that provide relief and ease headaches and migraines in this comprehensive guide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ease-your-headaches-migraines-5-best-caps-2023-470208</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 10:42:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Laser Hair Removal For Men: Key Things To Keep In Mind]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/laser-hair-removal-men-key-things-keep-mind-470206 <description><![CDATA[Choosing laser hair removal over traditional methods like wax patches and razors comes with a host of benefits, such as respite from uncontrolled and continued hair growth.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/laser-hair-removal-men-key-things-keep-mind-470206</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 05:56:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Multivitamins Daily May Improve Nutrition Biomarkers, Cellular Function In Older Men: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/taking-multivitamins-daily-may-improve-nutrition-biomarkers-cellular-function-older-men-study-470205 <description><![CDATA[A study conducted by a team from Oregon State University highlights the potential benefits of multivitamin supplementation in supporting overall health and well-being as people age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/taking-multivitamins-daily-may-improve-nutrition-biomarkers-cellular-function-older-men-study-470205</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 04:51:19 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>