<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[EVL BCAA Energy: The Perfect Pre-Workout Energy Drink To Boost Exercise Productivity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/evl-bcaa-energy-perfect-pre-workout-energy-drink-boost-exercise-productivity-471684 <description><![CDATA[Introducing EVL BCAA Energy: A natural pre-workout drink with green coffee for focus, BCAAs for performance, and essential vitamins.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/evl-bcaa-energy-perfect-pre-workout-energy-drink-boost-exercise-productivity-471684</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 12:45:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[E-Coli Outbreak Linked To Organic Walnuts Sickens 12: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-walnuts-sickens-12-cdc-471699 <description><![CDATA[The outbreak linked to contaminated organic walnuts sold in bulk bins has led to 12 reported cases of illness and seven hospitalizations in California and Washington.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-walnuts-sickens-12-cdc-471699</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 04:08:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[An Omega-6 Fatty Acid Linked To Reduced Risk Of Bipolar Disorder: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-6-fatty-acid-linked-reduced-risk-bipolar-disorder-study-471697 <description><![CDATA[The new study also indicates the possibility of using dietary intervention to prevent or slow down the progression of psychiatric disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-6-fatty-acid-linked-reduced-risk-bipolar-disorder-study-471697</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 03:10:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Guidelines Recommend Mammograms at 40, Biennial Breast Cancer Screening For Women]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-guidelines-recommend-mammograms-40-biennial-breast-cancer-screening-women-471696 <description><![CDATA[The new guidelines by the U.S. Preventive Services Task Force (USPSTF) lower the screening age to include all individuals assigned female at birth who are at an average risk of breast cancer, extending beyond the previous threshold of 50.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-guidelines-recommend-mammograms-40-biennial-breast-cancer-screening-women-471696</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 01:50:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teens At Risk Of Exposure To Toxic Lead And Uranium From Frequent Vaping: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-risk-exposure-token-uranium-frequent-vaping-study-471694 <description><![CDATA[Teenagers who frequently vape may face increased exposure to harmful metals like lead and uranium, which could potentially impact brain and organ development adversely, a study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-risk-exposure-token-uranium-frequent-vaping-study-471694</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Apr 2024 04:20:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Reveals Ideal Duration You May Stand, Sit, Sleep, And Exercise For Optimal Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-ideal-duration-you-may-stand-sit-sleep-exercise-optimal-health-471693 <description><![CDATA[The researchers have identified the ideal number of hours you should spend standing, sitting, sleeping, and engaging in physical activities for optimal heart health and diabetic control.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-ideal-duration-you-may-stand-sit-sleep-exercise-optimal-health-471693</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:38:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Lifestyle At 40 Adds 5 Years To Life, Offsets Genetic Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-lifestyle-40-adds-5-years-life-offsets-genic-risk-study-471691 <description><![CDATA[People with a strong genetic risk of shorter lifespans could add almost 5.5 years to their lives if they adopt a healthy lifestyle at 40, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-lifestyle-40-adds-5-years-life-offsets-genic-risk-study-471691</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Apr 2024 02:15:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Top 8 Tanning Oils: Achieved a Sun-Kissed Skin with these Nourishing and Bronzing Formulas]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-8-tanning-oils-achieved-sun-kissed-skin-these-nourishing-bronzing-formulas-471671 <description><![CDATA[With so many choices out there to achieve a sun-kissed skin, here are our top 8 picks for you to decide on, whichever on this list is your next summer buddy!]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-8-tanning-oils-achieved-sun-kissed-skin-these-nourishing-bronzing-formulas-471671</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:23:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Women Diagnosed With HIV After 'Vampire Facial' At Unlicensed New Mexico Spa: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/3-women-diagnosed-hiv-after-vampire-facial-unlicensed-new-mexico-spa-cdc-471687 <description><![CDATA[Although HIV transmission from contaminated blood through unsterile injection is a well-known risk, the cluster marks the first known case of transmission during a cosmetic injection procedure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/3-women-diagnosed-hiv-after-vampire-facial-unlicensed-new-mexico-spa-cdc-471687</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:04:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Positive Childhood Experiences Linked To Reduced Risk Of Anxiety, Depression In Teens: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/positive-childhood-experiences-linked-reduced-risk-anxiety-depression-teens-study-471689 <description><![CDATA[Adults who experienced four or more adverse childhood experiences are four times more likely to experience depression and low life satisfaction, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/positive-childhood-experiences-linked-reduced-risk-anxiety-depression-teens-study-471689</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:46:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Not Getting Enough Sleep? Expert Offers Tips To Manage Stress For Improved Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-getting-enough-sleep-expert-offers-tips-manage-stress-improved-sleep-471685 <description><![CDATA[Inadequate sleep is not just about feeling tired or sluggish; it can also lead to serious long-term consequences.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-getting-enough-sleep-expert-offers-tips-manage-stress-improved-sleep-471685</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Apr 2024 01:55:22 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>