<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra-Processed Food Can Be Addictive Like Nicotine, Alcohol; Study Says It Affects 14% Of Adults Globally]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-can-addictive-like-nicotine-alcohol-study-says-it-affects-14-adults-470981 <description><![CDATA[After analyzing 281 studies across 36 countries, a team of researchers estimated that 14% of adults and 12% of children have an addiction to ultra-processed food.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-can-addictive-like-nicotine-alcohol-study-says-it-affects-14-adults-470981</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 01:40:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Spine Day: Know How Bad Postures Affect Health, Ways To Improve]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-spine-day-know-how-bad-postures-affect-health-ways-improve-470978 <description><![CDATA[This year's theme, "Move Your Spine," aims to encourage people to stay active for better spine health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-spine-day-know-how-bad-postures-affect-health-ways-improve-470978</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 04:32:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pumpkin Seeds: Here's How The Superfood Can Be Beneficial]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pumpkin-seeds-heres-how-superfood-can-beneficial-470975 <description><![CDATA[Toasted pumpkin seeds can be a nutritious and satisfying snack. They can be easily included in your everyday diet in the form of toppings in cereals, soups or salads.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pumpkin-seeds-heres-how-superfood-can-beneficial-470975</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:57:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Key To Exceptional Longevity: Study Identifies Common Blood Traits Among People Who Live To 100]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-exceptional-longevity-study-identizes-common-blood-traits-among-people-who-live-100-470974 <description><![CDATA[People who live to 100 years have lower measures of creatinine, glucose and uric acid in their blood compared to those with a comparatively shorter lifespan, researchers say.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-exceptional-longevity-study-identizes-common-blood-traits-among-people-who-live-100-470974</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 01:57:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dementia Expert Dr Ashok J Bharucha Releases New Book 'Healing Hearts']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dementia-expert-dr-ashok-j-bharucha-releases-new-book-healing-hearts-470971 <description><![CDATA[With the World Health Organization estimating about 50 million people worldwide living with dementia and 10 million new cases diagnosed annually, the call for grows louder each day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dementia-expert-dr-ashok-j-bharucha-releases-new-book-healing-hearts-470971</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:29:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Grapes For Eye Health: Study Says Regular Consumption Can Improve Macular Degeneration In Older Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/grapes-eye-health-study-says-regular-conspiration-can-improve-macular-degenesis-older-adults-470970 <description><![CDATA[Macular degeneration is a condition that results in blurred central vision, which is the leading cause of vision loss in older adults. It occurs when part of the retina, called the macula, that controls sharp, straight-ahead vision gets damaged with aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/grapes-eye-health-study-says-regular-conspiration-can-improve-macular-degenesis-older-adults-470970</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Oct 2023 05:13:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is CKM Syndrome? American Heart Association Says 1 In 3 Adults Are At Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-c​​km-syndrome-american-heart-association-says-1-3-adults-are-risk-470969 <description><![CDATA[The AHA has identified a new medical condition called cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic (CKM) syndrome, which reflects a strong link between cardiovascular disease, kidney disease, type 2 diabetes and obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-c​​km-syndrome-american-heart-association-says-1-3-adults-are-risk-470969</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Oct 2023 04:01:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Loneliness Raises Risk Of Parkinson's Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-raises-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-470967 <description><![CDATA[Loneliness, defined as a lack of meaningful social relationships or a sense of belonging, can raise the chances of a Parkinson's diagnosis by 37%, researchers say.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-raises-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-470967</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Oct 2023 01:01:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bird Flu Spreads To Seals In Washington; Here's What You Need To Know About H5N1 Avian Influenza]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-spreads-seals-washington-heres-what-you-need-know-about-h5n1-avian-influenza-470965 <description><![CDATA[Several adult harbor seals in the Puget Sound region in Washington have tested positive for the H5N1 strain since September.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-spreads-seals-washington-heres-what-you-need-know-about-h5n1-avian-influenza-470965</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:35:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Rasmussen's Encephalitis? Doctors Disconnect Half Of 6-Year-Old's Brain To Prevent Progression Of Rare Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-rasmussens-encephalitis-doctors-disconnect-half-6-year-olds-brain-prevent-progression-470964 <description><![CDATA[Rasmussen's Encephalitis is a rare neurological disorder that can lead to loss of motor skills and speech, and eventual paralysis on one side of the body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-rasmussens-encephalitis-doctors-disconnect-half-6-year-olds-brain-prevent-progression-470964</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:10:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breast Cancer Awareness Month: Expert Shares Benefits Of Screenings, Self-Examination]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-awareness-month-expert-shares-benefits-screenings-self-examination-470961 <description><![CDATA[Breast self-examinations can help detect cancer signs early. While doing so, it is important to understand what is normal for each person, a breast and gynecologic medical oncologist says.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-awareness-month-expert-shares-benefits-screenings-self-examination-470961</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 02:16:33 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>