<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Suicide Prevention Week: Expert Insights On Ways To Help People Battling Suicidal Thoughts]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/suicide-prevention-week-expert-insights-ways-help-people-battle-suicidal-thoughts-472335 <description><![CDATA[In recognition of Suicide Prevention Week, an expert shares valuable insights on recognizing the warning signs and supporting those struggling with suicidal thoughts, which could potentially save lives.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/suicide-prevention-week-expert-insights-ways-help-people-battle-suicidal-thoughts-472335</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:08:32 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Cooling Towels To Help Your Regulate Body Temperature]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cooling-towels-help-your-regulate-body-Temperature-472310 <description><![CDATA[A cooling towel works by absorbing the heat from the skin surface and dissipating it into the environment. Cooling towels offer refreshing chill that lasts for hours and keeps your body cool. These can be easily folded and tossed into a bag and carried anywhere.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cooling-towels-help-your-regulate-body-Temperature-472310</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:17:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Baby Carriers To Simplify Your Life, Boost Child's Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-baby-riers-simplify-your-life-boost-childs-health-472304 <description><![CDATA[You might see more parents using sling bags and carriers to carry their babies these days, but babywearing is far from just a modern trend. It is an ancient practice ingrained across several cultures, valued for its many benefits, from convenience for parents and caregivers to improved health and mood for children. Beyond the practical advantages of baby carriers, here we explore their safety and health benefits for children and highlight top choices available in the market, to help you find the perfect one for your needs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-baby-riers-simplify-your-life-boost-childs-health-472304</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:07:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Resistance Bands For Every Workout: Top Picks To Boost Your Fitness Routine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-resistance-bands-every-workout-top-picks-boost-your-fitness-routine-472320 <description><![CDATA[Resistance bands help target multiple muscle groups, improve strength, flexibility, and endurance.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-resistance-bands-every-workout-top-picks-boost-your-fitness-routine-472320</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:05:13 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peptides And Dermatological Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/peptides-dermatological-research-472328 <description><![CDATA[Peptides are composed of two or more amino acids linked by peptide bonds. Research indicates that they may play diverse roles within an organism, ranging from signaling molecules to structural components.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/peptides-dermatological-research-472328</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:23:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Asthma Linked To Miscarriage And Fertility Issues In Women: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/asthma-linked-miscarriage-fertility-issues-women-study-472325 <description><![CDATA[As the findings suggest that the severity of asthma can impact fertility, the researchers stress the importance of effective asthma control to improve reproductive outcomes in women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/asthma-linked-miscarriage-fertility-issues-women-study-472325</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 02:47:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Tummy Fat Linked To Widespread Chronic Pain, Particularly For Women: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-tummy-fat-linked-widespread-chronic-pain-pspecially-women-study-472323 <description><![CDATA[The study explored how excess fat tissue around the abdomen affects the risk of chronic musculoskeletal pain at multiple body sites.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-tummy-fat-linked-widespread-chronic-pain-pspecially-women-study-472323</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 02:01:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Blood Glucose Test Strips: Top Choices For Accurate Diabetes Management]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-blood-glucose-test-strips-top-choices-accurate-diabetes-management-472313 <description><![CDATA[Blood glucose test strips are essential for managing diabetes, providing crucial data on blood sugar levels. This comprehensive guide explores what blood glucose test strips are, their uses, and the benefits of regular testing.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-blood-glucose-test-strips-top-choices-accurate-diabetes-management-472313</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:16:54 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Cervical Pillows To Help You Sleep Better And Reduce Neck Pain]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cervical-pillows-help-you-sleep-better-reduce-neck-pain-472287 <description><![CDATA[A cervical pillow, also commonly known as an orthopedic pillow, is especially designed to cure cervical problems, correct the positioning of the body, and prevent neck pain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cervical-pillows-help-you-sleep-better-reduce-neck-pain-472287</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:55:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Anti-Snoring Devices: Effective Solutions For A Restful Night]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-anti-snoring-devices- effective-solutions-restful-night-472301 <description><![CDATA[Snoring affects many people, disrupting sleep and causing discomfort for both the snorer and their partner. Anti-snoring devices are designed to mitigate this issue by addressing the underlying causes of snoring.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-anti-snoring-devices- effective-solutions-restful-night-472301</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:00:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smoking Before 18 Linked To Respiratory Symptoms In 20's: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smoking-before-18-linked-respiratory-symptoms-20s-study-472317 <description><![CDATA[The latest study investigated how starting smoking before the age of 18 affects respiratory health in early adulthood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smoking-before-18-linked-respiratory-symptoms-20s-study-472317</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Sep 2024 03:51:51 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>