<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[The Top 5 Cod Liver Oil Supplements: A Nutrient-Rich Addition To Your Wellness Routine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-cod-liver-oil-supplements- Nutrition-rich-addition-your-wellness-routine-471488 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top 5 cod liver oil supplements to boost your well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-cod-liver-oil-supplements- Nutrition-rich-addition-your-wellness-routine-471488</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:20:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Medications Help Cut Risk Of Premature Death In ADHD Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/medications-help-cut-risk-premature-death-adhd-病人-study-471506 <description><![CDATA[The latest study included 148,000 individuals in Sweden who were diagnosed with ADHD. The researchers noted that starting ADHD medications reduced their overall mortality risk, particularly from unnatural causes such as accidents and drug overdose.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/medications-help-cut-risk-premature-death-adhd-病人-study-471506</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:58:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People With Persisting, Worsening Metabolic Syndrome At Higher Risk Of Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-persisting-worsening-metabolic-syndrome-higher-risk-cancer-study-471505 <description><![CDATA[The findings of the study suggest that managing metabolic syndrome could be an effective strategy to reduce cancer risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-persisting-worsening-metabolic-syndrome-higher-risk-cancer-study-471505</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:00:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Depression Affects Heart Health: Study Says Women At Greater Risk Than Men]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-affects-heart-health-study-says-women-greater-risk-men-471504 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that depression raised the risk for heart disease by 39 percent in men, while the risk was 64 percent in women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-affects-heart-health-study-says-women-greater-risk-men-471504</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Mar 2024 01:47:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Folic Acid Fortified Table Salt Could Prevent Life-Threatening Birth Defects: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/folic-acid-fortified-table-salt-could-prevent-life-throne-birth-defects-study-471503 <description><![CDATA[The researchers hope that the use of folic acid-fortified salt could potentially prevent up to 50 percent of global spina bifida cases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/folic-acid-fortified-table-salt-could-prevent-life-throne-birth-defects-study-471503</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Mar 2024 04:16:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Activity Tracking Wrist-Worn Device Could Detect Alzheimer's Disease Early: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/activity-tracking-wrist-worn-device-could-detect-alzheimers-disease-early-study-471501 <description><![CDATA[With over 6 million Americans impacted by Alzheimer's across all age groups, the researchers hope their innovative approach could help identify the condition promptly, enabling early intervention for timely help and support.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/activity-tracking-wrist-worn-device-could-detect-alzheimers-disease-early-study-471501</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:47:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Dies From Bubonic Plague In New Mexico: Here's What We Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-dies-bubonic-plague-new-mexico-heres-what-we-know-471499 <description><![CDATA[The case marks the first fatality attributed to bubonic plague in the state since 2020 and the first human case of infection since 2021.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-dies-bubonic-plague-new-mexico-heres-what-we-know-471499</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:45:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Take Off Your Make-Up Before Exercise: Here's How Cosmetic Foundation Affects Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-off-your-make-before-exercise-heres-how-cosmetic-foundation-affects-skin-471498 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that wearing a cosmetic foundation before exercise affects skin health as it leads to clogged pores, potentially sparking acne breakouts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-off-your-make-before-exercise-heres-how-cosmetic-foundation-affects-skin-471498</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Mar 2024 04:03:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Children With Lazy Eye At Risk Of Hypertension And Heart Attacks In Adulthood: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-lazy-eye-risk-hypertension-heart-attacks-adulthood-study-471497 <description><![CDATA[The researchers identified a correlation between the lazy eye in childhood and increased health risks later in adulthood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-lazy-eye-risk-hypertension-heart-attacks-adulthood-study-471497</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:46:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Endometriosis Awareness Month: Dispel Myths With Expert Insights On The Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-awareness-month-dispel-myths-expert-insights-condition-471495 <description><![CDATA[During this Endometriosis Awareness Month, understand the condition better from an expert who dispels common myths around it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-awareness-month-dispel-myths-expert-insights-condition-471495</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Mar 2024 01:45:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Levels Of Cancer-Causing Benzene Detected In Some Acne Products: Independent Lab Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-cancer-causing-苯-Detected-some-acne-products-independent-lab-report-471493 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found unacceptably high levels of benzene in numerous prescription and over-the-counter benzoyl peroxide products when they were stored or handled at high temperatures.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-cancer-causing-苯-Detected-some-acne-products-independent-lab-report-471493</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Mar 2024 03:55:03 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>