<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Beyond The Dental Chair: Dr. Montoya's All-in-One Cultural And Dental Experience]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-dental-chair-dr-montoyas-all-one-culture-dental-experience-470941 <description><![CDATA[Globalization has fueled a billion-dollar medical tourism industry, where patients seek top-tier healthcare, turning it into a holistic experience blending wellness, luxury and cultural immersion.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-dental-chair-dr-montoyas-all-one-culture-dental-experience-470941</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 15:49:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Good Cholesterol Completely Healthy? Study Says Extreme Levels Of It May Raise Dementia Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/good-cholesterol-completely-healthy-study-says-extreme-levels-it-may-raise-dementia-risk-470936 <description><![CDATA[Too much or too little high-density lipoprotein can slightly increase the risk of dementia, a new study showed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/good-cholesterol-completely-healthy-study-says-extreme-levels-it-may-raise-dementia-risk-470936</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 06:32:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pregnancy And Cytomegalovirus: Study Says Prior Infection Reduces Risk Of Miscarriage, Birth Defects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-cytomegalovirus-study-says-prior-infection-reduces-risk-miscarriage-birth-defects-470939 <description><![CDATA[Pregnant women infected with cytomegalovirus are less likely to transmit it to their children if they have pre-existing immunity, the study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-cytomegalovirus-study-says-prior-infection-reduces-risk-miscarriage-birth-defects-470939</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:57:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Cerebral Palsy Day: What Causes The Condition, Risk Factors]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-cerebral-palsy-day-what-c​​auses-condition-risk-factors-470933 <description><![CDATA[On this World Cerebral Palsy Day, know the causes and risk factors of the complex disability that affects more than 18 million people worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-cerebral-palsy-day-what-c​​auses-condition-risk-factors-470933</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Oct 2023 03:49:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Syphilis Cases On The Rise In US; Know Signs And Complications Of The Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/syphilis-cases-rise-us-know-signs-complications-disease-470932 <description><![CDATA[Mississippi reports a staggering 1000% increase in infant hospitalizations due to congenital transmission of syphilis since 2016, a CDC study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/syphilis-cases-rise-us-know-signs-complications-disease-470932</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Oct 2023 02:18:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fatty Liver Disease: Study Says Patients Are At 3 Times Higher Risk Of Personality Disorders]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fatty-liver-disease-study-says-病人-are-3-times-higher-risk-personality-disorders-470931 <description><![CDATA[The new study also indicates that people with non-alcoholic fatty liver disease frequently exhibit uncontrolled eating behaviors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fatty-liver-disease-study-says-病人-are-3-times-higher-risk-personality-disorders-470931</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 04:14:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Arkansas Reports 1 Case Of Locally Acquired Malaria: Know Symptoms, Complications]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/arkansas-reports-1-case-locally-acquired-malaria-know-symptoms-complications-470928 <description><![CDATA[Health officials in Arkansas have issued a warning against malaria after a locally transmitted case of the mosquito-borne disease was confirmed in the state.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/arkansas-reports-1-case-locally-acquired-malaria-know-symptoms-complications-470928</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 02:53:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Antiviral Drugs To Prevent Type 1 Diabetes? Study Says Treatment May Slow Disease Progression]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antiviral-drugs-prevent-type-1-diabetes-study-says-treatment-may-slow-disease-progression-470926 <description><![CDATA[The team earlier observed an association between diabetes and viral infection. In the latest study, they tried to address this connection using a combination therapy of antiviral drugs pleconaril and ribavirin.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antiviral-drugs-prevent-type-1-diabetes-study-says-treatment-may-slow-disease-progression-470926</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 01:27:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Diabetes And Longevity: Study Explains How Age Of Diagnosis Affects Life Expectancy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-longevity-study-explains-how-age-diagnosis-affects-life-expectancy-470924 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say getting diagnosed with type 2 diabetes before the age of 30 could potentially reduce life expectancy by around 14 years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-longevity-study-explains-how-age-diagnosis-affects-life-expectancy-470924</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:30:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Issues Warning Against Use Of Probiotics After Preterm Baby Dies In Hospital]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-issues-warning-against-use-probiotics-after-preterm-baby-dies-hospital-470921 <description><![CDATA[The premature baby, who weighed less than 2.2 pounds, died at an unidentified hospital due to sepsis caused by the same species of bacteria found in the probiotics that were administered to them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-issues-warning-against-use-probiotics-after-preterm-baby-dies-hospital-470921</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 03:26:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Depression Awareness Month: Expert Insights On How To Support A Loved One With Mental Illness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-awareness-month-expert-insights-how-support-loved-one-mental-illness-470920 <description><![CDATA[On this Depression Awareness Month, here are some insights on how to support your loved ones through their mental health journey.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-awareness-month-expert-insights-how-support-loved-one-mental-illness-470920</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 02:03:16 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>