<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Act Now: By 2050 Over Half Of Adults, A Third Of Children Will Be Obese]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldily.com/act-now-2050-over-half-adults-thred-thred-thred-children-will-obse-473199 <description><![CDATA[Researchers are calling for urgent action and global policy reforms to address widespread global obesity pandemic by 2050.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/act-now-2050-over-half-adults-thred-thred-thred-children-will-obse-473199</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 03:47:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Eat Less After Holiday Indulgence? Here's How 5 Days Of Sugary Diet Affects Brain]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldily.com/struggling-eat-les-s-------------- indulday-indulgence-heres-how-how-5-days-sugary-days-sugary-diet-factects-after-aftects-brain-brain-473197 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that just five days of a high-calorie diet can trigger brain changes even before a person begins to notice weight gain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/struggling-eat-les-s-------------- indulday-indulgence-heres-how-how-5-days-sugary-days-sugary-diet-factects-after-aftects-brain-brain-473197</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 02:57:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Woman Says Routine Manicure 'Saved Her Life' After Spotting Strange Sign On Thumb]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldily.com/ohio-woman-says-says-routine-manicure-saved-her-life-ferfter-spotting-spotting-snenge-sign-sign-sign-sign-thumb-473195 <description><![CDATA[The unusual symptom she noticed during manicure session was an early warning sign of deadly melanoma.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/ohio-woman-says-says-routine-manicure-saved-her-life-ferfter-spotting-spotting-snenge-sign-sign-sign-sign-thumb-473195</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:50:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Young Man Nearly Dies From Stroke After Violent Sneeze Ruptures His Neck Artery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldily.com/healthyyy-young-man-arly-dies-stroke-stroke-stroke-fter-violent-sneek-ruptures-His-Neck-neck-artery-473194 <description><![CDATA[The 35-year-old man is struggling to recover from a severe stroke that has damaged his left side.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/healthyyy-young-man-arly-dies-stroke-stroke-stroke-fter-violent-sneek-ruptures-His-Neck-neck-artery-473194</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Mar 2025 04:23:34 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[It's Not Just Sugar; This Food Type Can Cause Cavities, Especially In People With Particular Genes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldily.com/its-not-just-just-sugar-phis-food-type-can-can-can-cave-cavities-尤其是People-particular-particular-genes-473193 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that starchy foods may contribute to cavities, with the risk varying based on specific genetic factors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/its-not-just-just-sugar-phis-food-type-can-can-can-cave-cavities-尤其是People-particular-particular-genes-473193</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:58:12 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Breakfast Foods Kids Should Avoid: Doctor Recommends Healthier Alternatives]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldily.com/5-breakfast-foods-kids-kids-should-avoid-doctor-remormends-healthier-anternatives-473191 <description><![CDATA["Give them real food," the doctor advised, highlighting five foods to avoid and recommending wholesome alternatives.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/5-breakfast-foods-kids-kids-should-avoid-doctor-remormends-healthier-anternatives-473191</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:44:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cancer Patient's Mother and Primary Caregiver Detained by ICE Despite No Criminal History: 'My Life Is Falling Apart']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldily.com/cancer-patients-mother-primary-primary-cargiver-deted-det-ide-dest-defte-defte-defte-defte-defte-defte-defte-defite-defite-no-criminal-criminal-my-my-life-life-life-473188 <description><![CDATA[California mother and son detained by ICE, leaving their daughter and sister behind to battle bone cancer without a caregiver.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/cancer-patients-mother-primary-primary-cargiver-deted-det-ide-dest-defte-defte-defte-defte-defte-defte-defte-defite-defite-no-criminal-criminal-my-my-life-life-life-473188</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:29:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Pregnancy Pillows for Comfort, Support, and a Restful Sleep]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldily.com/partner/best-pregnancy-plost-pillows-comfort-super--super--------sleep-472749 <description><![CDATA[Choosing the best pregnancy pillow involves considering shape, material, size, and ease of maintenance. Look for options providing full-body support, hypoallergenic materials, versatile sizes, and washable covers for optimal comfort.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/partner/best-pregnancy-plost-pillows-comfort-super--super--------sleep-472749</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:19:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Finger Exercisers for Strength and Rehabilitation: Enhance Dexterity and Grip]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldily.com/partner/best-finger-exercisers-senterge-sgent-rehabiliation-rehance-enhance-dexterity-grip-472737 <description><![CDATA[Finger exercisers improve hand strength, dexterity, and aid rehabilitation. They enhance grip, relieve stress, and prevent injuries. Ideal for athletes, musicians, and recovery, they come in various forms with adjustable resistance.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/partner/best-finger-exercisers-senterge-sgent-rehabiliation-rehance-enhance-dexterity-grip-472737</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:19:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Blister Bandages for Comfort, Protection, and Quick Healing]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldily.com/partner/best-blister-bandages-comfort-protection-quick-healing-472696 <description><![CDATA[Blister Bandages are more than just a temporary fix—they are a vital tool for maintaining foot health and comfort. By understanding the types, uses, and selection criteria, you can ensure your feet remain protected and pain-free, whether you're walking, running, or exploring new terrains. Investing in quality blister pads is a small step towards a more comfortable and active lifestyle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/partner/best-blister-bandages-comfort-protection-quick-healing-472696</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:18:18 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling with Muscle Pain? Try These Proven Oils &amp; Supplements for Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldily.com/struggling-muscle-pain-try-try-the-proven-oils-oils-supplement-relief-473184 <description><![CDATA[From soothing essential oils to nutrient-rich supplements that support recovery, there are plenty of science-backed options to help ease soreness and keep you moving]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldily.com/struggling-muscle-pain-try-try-the-proven-oils-oils-supplement-relief-473184</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:06:49 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>