<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Use Of Social Media Photo Filters Raises Muscle Dysmorphia In Young Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/use-social-media-photo-filters-raises-muscle-dysmorphia-young-adults-study-471838 <description><![CDATA[The use of social media photo filters has a strong association with increased symptoms of muscle dysmorphia, a mental health condition characterized by excessive obsession with muscularity and leanness, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/use-social-media-photo-filters-raises-muscle-dysmorphia-young-adults-study-471838</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:01:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Planning A Trip Abroad? Here's How To Reduce Risk Of Yellow Fever]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-trip-abroad-heres-how-reduce-risk-yellow-fever-471837 <description><![CDATA[If tropical destinations such as South America or Africa are on your itinerary, know all about yellow fever and learn essential tips to minimize your risk of contracting the infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-trip-abroad-heres-how-reduce-risk-yellow-fever-471837</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:30:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Viagra Improves Brain Blood Flow, Reduces Dementia Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viagra-improves-brain-blood-flow-reduces-dementia-risk-study-471836 <description><![CDATA[A study suggests Viagra could revolutionize the treatment and prevention of vascular dementia, a condition for which specific therapies are currently unavailable.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viagra-improves-brain-blood-flow-reduces-dementia-risk-study-471836</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:20:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Higher Stroke Risk For Women Overweight In Teenage Or Young Adult Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-行程-risk-women-overweight-teenage-young-adult-years-study-471835 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that having excess body weight at age 14 or 31 raises the risk of ischemic stroke in women by the age of 55.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-行程-risk-women-overweight-teenage-young-adult-years-study-471835</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:45:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Xylitol Sweetener Linked To Increased Risk Of Heart Attacks, Stroke: Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/xylitol-sweetener-linked-increased-risk-heart-attacks-中风-study-finds-471833 <description><![CDATA[Xylitol, a natural sugar alcohol found in plants, is a sugar substitute used in candies, gums, baked goods, and toothpaste. ]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/xylitol-sweetener-linked-increased-risk-heart-attacks-中风-study-finds-471833</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jun 2024 03:27:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salmonella Outbreak Linked To Cucumbers Sickens 162 In 25 States, CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-cucumbers-sickens-162-25-states-cdc-warns-471831 <description><![CDATA[Salmonella outbreak linked to cucumbers sickened 162, resulting in 54 hospitalizations across 25 states.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-cucumbers-sickens-162-25-states-cdc-warns-471831</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:06:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cut Your Salt Intake: Study Says It Can Worsen Eczema]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-your-salt-intake-study-says-it-can-worsen-eczema-471830 <description><![CDATA[Taking just one extra gram of sodium per day can increase the likelihood of eczema flares by 22%.  ]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-your-salt-intake-study-says-it-can-worsen-eczema-471830</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:54:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man In Mexico Dies From Bird Flu; First Human Case Of H5N2 Virus: WHO]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-mexico-dies-bird-flu-first- human-case-h5n2-virus-who-471829 <description><![CDATA[Although the strain H5N2 had earlier been detected in poultry in Mexico, the source from which the patient contracted the fatal infection is not known, as he did not have any contact with poultry.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-mexico-dies-bird-flu-first- human-case-h5n2-virus-who-471829</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:18:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Highly Contagious Sexually Transmitted Fungal Infection Makes US Debut: First Case In NYC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/highly-contagious- Sexly-transmissed-fungal-infection-makes-us-debut-first-case-nyc-471827 <description><![CDATA[Health experts caution that the infection caused by a sexually transmitted form of ringworm can take months to resolve, even with treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/highly-contagious- Sexly-transmissed-fungal-infection-makes-us-debut-first-case-nyc-471827</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jun 2024 01:10:32 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Susan Heitler: Life and Work]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/susan-heitler-life-work-471825 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Susan Heitler, renowned for her notable contributions to psychotherapy, specializes in treating couples and conducts workshops across the US and abroad, imparting her expertise in couples' therapy to therapy practitioners.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/susan-heitler-life-work-471825</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:57:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Controversy Around ABA Therapy Finally Addressed]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/controversy-around-aba-therapy-finally-addressed-471823 <description><![CDATA[Rethinking autism therapy, a new approach focuses on compassionate, play-based methods that address the emotional and behavioral needs of children with autism, fostering a supportive and inclusive community for families.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/controversy-around-aba-therapy-finally-addressed-471823</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:53:43 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>