<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Updated COVID mRNA Vaccines Get FDA Approval: Here's What To Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/updated-covid-mrna-vaccines-get-fda-approval-heres-what-know-472180 <description><![CDATA[The updated COVID shots from Pfizer-BioNTech and Moderna target the current KP.2 strain of SARS-CoV-2, a descendant of the highly contagious Omicron subvariant JN.1.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/updated-covid-mrna-vaccines-get-fda-approval-heres-what-know-472180</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 03:13:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hot Flashes And Night Sweats? Experimental Non-Hormonal Pill Offers Hope For Menopause Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hot-flashes-night-sweats-experimental-non-hormonal-pill-offers-hope-menopause-relief-472177 <description><![CDATA[In a phase 3 clinical trial, researchers have found that the new non-hormonal drug, Elinzanetant, could reduce the frequency and severity of vasomotor symptoms in menopausal women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hot-flashes-night-sweats-experimental-non-hormonal-pill-offers-hope-menopause-relief-472177</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 01:18:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Importance of Early Detection in Preventive Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/importance-early-detection-preventive-health-472172 <description><![CDATA[Catching potential health issues early can make a world of difference in overall well-being and quality of life down the road.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/importance-early-detection-preventive-health-472172</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 10:42:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Selenium Supplements And Why You Must Include Them In Your Diet]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-selenium-supplements-why-you-must-include-them-your-diet-472153 <description><![CDATA[Selenium is a trace mineral which essentially implies that our body needs it only in small amounts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-selenium-supplements-why-you-must-include-them-your-diet-472153</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 09:17:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Melatonin Supplements: The Top Picks for Better Sleep and Overall Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-melatonin-supplements-top-picks-better-sleep-overall-health-472155 <description><![CDATA[Melatonin supplements are natural aids that help regulate sleep cycles, improve sleep quality, and support overall well-being. Ideal for those struggling with insomnia, jet lag, or irregular sleep patterns, these supplements are a powerful tool for achieving restful sleep and waking up refreshed. Choose wisely to enhance your sleep health effectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-melatonin-supplements-top-picks-better-sleep-overall-health-472155</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 09:16:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Higher Incidence Of Mental Illness After Severe COVID In Unvaccinated Adults, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-incidence-mental-illness-after-severe-covid-unvaccinated-adults-says-study-472168 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that elevated incidence of mental illnesses after COVID-19 infection was mainly observed among cases where there were hospitalizations. The risk remained high for up to a year following severe COVID-19 in unvaccinated individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-incidence-mental-illness-after-severe-covid-unvaccinated-adults-says-study-472168</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 04:14:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Flexibility Key To Longevity? Study Links It To Survival In Middle-Aged Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flexibility-key-longevity-study-links-it-survival-middle-ged-adults-472166 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now found that flexibility affects survival in middle-aged adults, with a particularly high risk of death for women with low flexibility.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flexibility-key-longevity-study-links-it-survival-middle-ged-adults-472166</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 03:18:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[60% Of US Baby Food Lacks Nutrients; Many Exceed Sugar And Salt Limits: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/60-us-baby-food-lacks-nutritions-many-exceed-sugar-salt-limits-study-472164 <description><![CDATA[The study examined 651 products sold across the top 10 U.S. grocery chains and found that none of these products met promotional requirements set by the WHO guidelines.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/60-us-baby-food-lacks-nutritions-many-exceed-sugar-salt-limits-study-472164</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Aug 2024 02:21:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['No Safe Levels': Study Says Even Light Smoking During Pregnancy Affects Newborn's Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-safe-levels-study-says-even-light-smoking-during-pregnancy-affects-newborns-health-472161 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests "that there is no safe period and no safe level of cigarette smoking shortly before or during pregnancy."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-safe-levels-study-says-even-light-smoking-during-pregnancy-affects-newborns-health-472161</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Aug 2024 05:21:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Lose Weight? New Diet Suggests Eating More Protein, Fiber While Limiting Calories]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-lose-weight-new-diet-suggests-eating-more- Protein-Fiber-while-limiting-calories-472158 <description><![CDATA[The study tested a new weight loss program called the Individualized Diet Improvement Program (iDip) which involves increasing protein and fiber intake while consuming 1,500 calories or less daily for one year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-lose-weight-new-diet-suggests-eating-more- Protein-Fiber-while-limiting-calories-472158</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Aug 2024 04:08:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tirzepatide Cuts Diabetes Risk By 94% In Prediabetic, Obese Individuals: Trial Results]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tirzepatide-cuts-diabetes-risk-94-prediabetic-obese-individuals-Trial-results-472156 <description><![CDATA[The three-year trial results revealed that a once-a-week tirzepatide injection for adults who are prediabetic, obese, or overweight reduced their risk of progressing to type 2 diabetes by 94%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tirzepatide-cuts-diabetes-risk-94-prediabetic-obese-individuals-Trial-results-472156</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Aug 2024 01:44:28 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>