<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh</language><item><title><![CDATA[Beyond Childhood: Expert Unmasks Hidden Struggles Of Adult ADHD]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-childhood-expert-unmasks-hidden-struggles-adult-adhd-472010 <description><![CDATA[In adults, ADHD may go unrecognized and undiagnosed, with symptoms masked or mistaken for other issues.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-childhood-expert-unmasks-hidden-struggles-adult-adhd-472010</guid><pubDate> Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:45:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Treatment For Male Pattern Baldness? Study Identifies Body Sugar That Holds Key]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-treatment-male-pattern-baldness-study-identizes-body-sugar-that-holds-key-472007 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that a naturally occurring sugar in the human body, known as 2-deoxy-D-ribose (2dDR), could stimulate hair growth.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-treatment-male-pattern-baldness-study-identizes-body-sugar-that-holds-key-472007</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Jul 2024 04:21:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Indian Teen Dies From Nipah Virus: Know About Deadly Infection With No Vaccine, Cure]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/indian-teen-dies-nipah-virus-know-about-deadly-infection-no-vaccine-cure-472005 <description><![CDATA[With no available vaccine or cure, the World Health Organization has classified Nipah as a priority pathogen due to its high potential to cause an epidemic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/indian-teen-dies-nipah-virus-know-about-deadly-infection-no-vaccine-cure-472005</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Jul 2024 03:08:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eat More Fruits In Middle Age To Ward Off Depressive Symptoms Later, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eat-more-fruits-middle-ages-ward-off-depressive-symptoms-later-says-study-472002 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that individuals who consumed higher quantities of fruits earlier in life had a reduced risk of experiencing depressive symptoms as they aged.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eat-more-fruits-middle-ages-ward-off-depressive-symptoms-later-says-study-472002</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:59:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Fiber In Common Cereals That Aids Weight Loss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-fibre-common-cereals-that-aids-weight-loss-472001 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have identified the type of fiber commonly found in oats and barley that shows significant potential for weight loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-fibre-common-cereals-that-aids-weight-loss-472001</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jul 2024 05:27:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Prenatal Diet Linked To Autism? Study Says 'Healthy' Eating Cuts Risk By 22%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prenatal-diet-linked-autism-study-says-healthy-eating-cuts-risk-22-471998 <description><![CDATA[The researchers discovered that a "healthy" diet during pregnancy — rich in vegetables, fruits, nuts, fish, and whole grains while avoiding high-fat foods, processed meats, soft drinks, and refined carbohydrates — can reduce the risk of autism by 22%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prenatal-diet-linked-autism-study-says-healthy-eating-cuts-risk-22-471998</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jul 2024 03:30:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Listeria Outbreak Linked To Deli Meats Claims 2 Lives, Sickens 28: CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/listeria-outbreak-linked-deli-meats-claims-2-lives-sickens-28-cdc-warns-471996 <description><![CDATA[An investigation revealed that those affected by the current outbreak were more likely to have consumed deli-sliced turkey and liverwurst.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/listeria-outbreak-linked-deli-meats-claims-2-lives-sickens-28-cdc-warns-471996</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:23:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Delayed Dinner, Long Eating Hours Linked To Depression, Anxiety In Shift Workers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/delayed-dinner-long-eating-hours-linked-depression-anxiety-shift-workers-471995 <description><![CDATA[A study revealed that meal timing, long eating window (over 12 hours), and delayed dinner have links to increased risk of depression and anxiety, regardless of work shift.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/delayed-dinner-long-eating-hours-linked-depression-anxiety-shift-workers-471995</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jul 2024 05:23:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Brain-Boosting Mushroom Gummies May Contain Illegal Hallucinogens, Experts Warn]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brain-boosting-mushroom-gummies-may-contain-illegal-hallucinogens-experts-warn-471992 <description><![CDATA[The researchers tested the mushroom gummies marketed for brain-boosting benefits after five individuals, including a 3-year-old, fell ill from consuming them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brain-boosting-mushroom-gummies-may-contain-illegal-hallucinogens-experts-warn-471992</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jul 2024 03:38:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Obesity Affects Sperm Count: Study Uncovers Brain Mechanism Behind Fertility Decline]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-affects-sperm-count-study-uncovers-brain-mechanism-behind-fertility-decline-471991 <description><![CDATA[The researchers discovered in a mice study that obesity causes chronic changes in the brain, which affects sperm count.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-affects-sperm-count-study-uncovers-brain-mechanism-behind-fertility-decline-471991</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jul 2024 01:55:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Endometriosis Raises Risk Of Ovarian Cancer, Severe Types Most Vulnerable: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-raises-risk-ovarian-cancer-severe-types-most-vulnerable-study-471988 <description><![CDATA[Individuals with severe forms of endometriosis, such as deep infiltrating endometriosis or ovarian endometriomas, face a staggering 9.7-fold increase in the likelihood of developing ovarian cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-raises-risk-ovarian-cancer-severe-types-most-vulnerable-study-471988</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:17:36 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>