<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[An Alternative Approach To Treat Obesity? Scientists Develop Vibrating, Ingestible Capsule That Makes You Feel Full]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alternative-approach-treat-obesity-scientists-develop-vibrating-ingestible-capsule-that-makes-471219 <description><![CDATA[The new capsule could emerge as a minimally invasive and cost-effective way to treat obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alternative-approach-treat-obesity-scientists-develop-vibrating-ingestible-capsule-that-makes-471219</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:10:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Zombie Deer Disease: Know All About The Fatal Infection As Scientists Fear It May Jump To Humans]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/zombie-deer-disease-know-all-about-fatal-infection-scientists-fear-it-may-jump- humans-471218 <description><![CDATA[Although no cases have yet been reported in humans, scientists share concerns that the infection with no cure may jump to humans, which they should be prepared for.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/zombie-deer-disease-know-all-about-fatal-infection-scientists-fear-it-may-jump- humans-471218</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Dec 2023 03:02:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hospital Admissions For Pediatric RSV Far Higher Than Omicron Or Flu: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospital-admissions-pediatric-rsv-far-higher-omicron-flu-study-471217 <description><![CDATA[The study showed that in children, the hospitalization rate was highest for RSV (81.7%), while it was only 31.5% for omicron and 27.7% for influenza.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospital-admissions-pediatric-rsv-far-higher-omicron-flu-study-471217</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Dec 2023 02:20:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Year's Resolutions: Here Are Some Practical Goals You Can Set For A Healthy 2024]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-years-resolutions-here-are-some-practical-goals-you-can-set-healthy-2024-471202 <description><![CDATA[Although resolutions are easy to make, most often, they fail within weeks as the spirit and excitement of the New Year fade. Setting achievable, specific and measurable goals can help you stick to your resolutions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-years-resolutions-here-are-some-practical-goals-you-can-set-healthy-2024-471202</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Dec 2023 08:23:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Art Of Eating With Hands: Ayurveda Expert Explains Science Behind It, Potential Health Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/art-eating-hands-ayurveda-expert-explains-science-behind-it-pottial-health-benefits-471213 <description><![CDATA[It's not just what you eat that matters, but also how you experience it. If you're interested in experimenting with the tactile art of eating, it is better to understand its potential health advantages.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/art-eating-hands-ayurveda-expert-explains-science-behind-it-pottial-health-benefits-471213</guid><pubDate> Tue, 26 Dec 2023 06:01:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Holiday Leftovers: Know How To Safely Store, Reheat Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/holiday-leftovers-know-how-safely-store-reheat-them-471198 <description><![CDATA[Having a small leftover stash in the fridge can be handy when you recover from the fatigue of celebrations. For a healthy and enjoyable holiday experience, learn how to safely store and reheat leftovers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/holiday-leftovers-know-how-safely-store-reheat-them-471198</guid><pubDate> Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:41:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unleashing The Power Of Gold With GLO24K Best-In-Class LED Beauty Devices]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/unleashing-power-gold-glo24k-best-class-led-beauty-devices-471207 <description><![CDATA[GLO24K's award-winning LED beauty devices are a revolutionary approach to light therapy]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/unleashing-power-gold-glo24k-best-class-led-beauty-devices-471207</guid><pubDate> Mon, 25 Dec 2023 03:46:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleep Loss May Reduce Positivity, Increase Your Risk Of Anxiety]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-loss-may-reduce-positivity-increase-your-risk-anxiety-471216 <description><![CDATA[Lack of proper sleep not only makes you feel tired and groggy but can also have far-reaching effects on your mental health. A new study suggests that sleep loss reduces positivity and increases the risk of anxiety symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-loss-may-reduce-positivity-increase-your-risk-anxiety-471216</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 06:06:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Acetaminophen Use During Pregnancy Linked To Language Delays In Early Childhood: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/acetaminophen-use-during-pregnancy-linked-language-delays-early-childhood-study-471215 <description><![CDATA[The study does not prove a causative relationship between acetaminophen usage in pregnancy and language delay in children. More research is required to understand if other factors are involved.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/acetaminophen-use-during-pregnancy-linked-language-delays-early-childhood-study-471215</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 01:32:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Overeating This Holiday Season? Experts Share Tips To Avoid Weight Gain]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-overeating-this-holiday-season-experts-share-tips-avoid-weight-gain-471214 <description><![CDATA[Learn some valuable tips from experts on how to avoid overeating and prevent weight gain while still enjoying the holiday festivities.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-overeating-this-holiday-season-experts-share-tips-avoid-weight-gain-471214</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 01:01:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily Toothbrushing Reduces Risk Of Hospital-Acquired Pneumonia: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-toothbrushing-reduces-risk-hospital-acquired-pneumonia-study-471210 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say patients should brush their teeth a minimum of two times daily as a preventive measure against hospital-acquired pneumonia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-toothbrushing-reduces-risk-hospital-acquired-pneumonia-study-471210</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:48:47 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>