<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies A Factor That Affects Aging- But It's Out Of Your Control]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-factor-that-affects-aging-its-out-your-control-472202 <description><![CDATA[A new study suggests that a person's biological age may also be influenced by whether their grandparent attended college.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-factor-that-affects-aging-its-out-your-control-472202</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Aug 2024 04:13:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People Living With Brain Aneurysm At High Risk Of Anxiety, Depression: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-living-brain-aneurysm-high-risk-anxiety-depression-study-472200 <description><![CDATA[Being aware of the aneurysm diagnosis was linked to a 10% higher risk of a mental health condition such as anxiety, stress, depression, eating disorders, bipolar disorder, insomnia, and alcohol or drug misuse.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-living-brain-aneurysm-high-risk-anxiety-depression-study-472200</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Aug 2024 02:56:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dengue Survivors Face Higher Long-Term Risks Than COVID-19 Recovery Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dengue-survivors-face-higher-long-term-risks-covid-19-recovery-病人-study-472197 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that those recovering from dengue had a 55% higher risk of any heart complications, 213% increased risk of cognition or memory disorders, and 198% increased risk of movement disorders compared to COVID-19 patients.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dengue-survivors-face-higher-long-term-risks-covid-19-recovery-病人-study-472197</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Aug 2024 01:01:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Chlorella Supplements: Uses, Benefits And Side Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-Chlorella-supplements-uses-benefits-side-effects-472181 <description><![CDATA[Chlorella supplementation in humans is known to work as antidiabetic, antihypertensive and antihyperlipidemic. Some studies have even suggested that it improves total cholesterol levels, systolic blood pressure, diastolic blood pressure, and fasting blood glucose levels.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-Chlorella-supplements-uses-benefits-side-effects-472181</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Aug 2024 09:52:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Kudoz Root Supplements For Heart, Liver And Brain Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-kudoz-root-supplements-heart-liver-brain-health-472183 <description><![CDATA[Kudoz Root, derived from the Pueraria lobata plant, offers numerous health benefits, including cardiovascular support, liver detoxification, alcohol dependency reduction, cognitive enhancement, and menopausal symptom relief. Rich in isoflavones, this natural supplement can be easily incorporated into daily routines to promote overall well-being and improve quality of life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-kudoz-root-supplements-heart-liver-brain-health-472183</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Aug 2024 09:50:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Every Extra Hour Of TV In Your 20's Raises Heart Disease Risk, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/every-extra-hour-tv-your-20s-raises-heart-disease-risk-study-says-472193 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that every additional hour spent watching TV could increase the risk of heart disease by 26% in young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/every-extra-hour-tv-your-20s-raises-heart-disease-risk-study-says-472193</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Aug 2024 05:05:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[HPV Infection Affects Male Fertility, High-Risk Strains Linked To Sperm Death, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hpv-infection-affects-male-fertility-high-risk-strains-linked-sperm-death-says-study-472191 <description><![CDATA[The study analyzed the impact of both high-risk and low-risk HPV strains on male fertility and found that high-risk strains are more prevalent and pose a greater threat to sperm quality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hpv-infection-affects-male-fertility-high-risk-strains-linked-sperm-death-says-study-472191</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Aug 2024 03:32:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[EEE In Massachusetts: Rare Deadly Mosquito-Borne Illness Puts Towns Under Vigilance]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eee-massachusetts-rare-deadly-mosquito-borne-illness-puts-towns-under-vigilance-472190 <description><![CDATA[Eastern equine encephalitis (EEE) typically spreads through mosquito bites and has no vaccines or drugs for prevention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eee-massachusetts-rare-deadly-mosquito-borne-illness-puts-towns-under-vigilance-472190</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Aug 2024 01:33:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Milk Thistle Supplements: Discover the Top Choices For Liver Health And Detoxification]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-milk-thistle-supplements-discover-top-choices-liver-health-detoxification-472175 <description><![CDATA[Milk thistle, renowned for liver support, detoxification, and skin health, is backed by scientific research. Studies highlight its protective and regenerative effects on the liver, enhance detoxification, and provide antioxidant benefits for skin health. Choosing a high-quality supplement can support overall wellness effectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-milk-thistle-supplements-discover-top-choices-liver-health-detoxification-472175</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:33:39 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Biotin Supplements For Healthier Hair, Skin And Nails]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-biotin-supplements-healthier-hair-skin-nails-472173 <description><![CDATA[Biotin, or Vitamin B7, is essential for healthy hair, skin, and nails, aiding in the metabolism of fats and proteins. A deficiency can cause thinning hair and brittle nails. Supplements can enhance these benefits, and incorporating biotin into your routine, along with a balanced diet, supports overall beauty and health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-biotin-supplements-healthier-hair-skin-nails-472173</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:15:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Tyrosine Supplements: Improve Focus, Relieve Stress With These Top Picks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tyrosine-supplements-improve-focus-relieve-stress-these-top-picks-472170 <description><![CDATA[Tyrosine, also known as L-tyrosine, is an amino acid that serves as a building block for all proteins in the body. It is synthesized when the body obtains sufficient amounts of another essential amino acid, phenylalanine. Tyrosine is crucial for various bodily functions, including neurotransmission and hormone regulation, and is commonly used as a supplement to boost mood-enhancing dopamine, reduce stress, and improve focus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tyrosine-supplements-improve-focus-relieve-stress-these-top-picks-472170</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:12:20 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>