<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Snack On Nuts: Study Says Including Almonds In Diet Aids Weight Loss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/snack-nuts-study-says-include-almonds-diet-aids-weight-loss-470824 <description><![CDATA[Including almonds in an energy-restricted diet not only helps in weight loss but also improves cardiometabolic health, the study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/snack-nuts-study-says-include-almonds-diet-aids-weight-loss-470824</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:38:09 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best At-Home Whitening Treatments]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-home-whitening-treatments-470774 <description><![CDATA[Explore the most effective at-home teeth whitening solutions in this comprehensive article.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-home-whitening-treatments-470774</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Sep 2023 23:11:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tips From Your Dentist: Switch To An Electric Toothbrush]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tips-your-dentist-switch-electric-toothbrush-470771 <description><![CDATA[Discover valuable dental advice on transitioning to an electric toothbrush from your dentist in this informative article.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tips-your-dentist-switch-electric-toothbrush-470771</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Sep 2023 22:45:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Moderate Coffee Intake Reduce Risk Of Anxiety, Depression? New Study Says Yes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-moderate-coffee-intake-reduce-risk-anxiety-depression-new-study-says-yes-470821 <description><![CDATA[The research indicated that the risk of developing anxiety and depression was lowest among individuals who consumed two to three cups of coffee daily.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-moderate-coffee-intake-reduce-risk-anxiety-depression-new-study-says-yes-470821</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Sep 2023 07:05:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teachers Can Play A Significant Role In Addressing Childhood Obesity: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teachers-can-play-significant-role-addressing-childhood-obesity-study-470818 <description><![CDATA[A five-year study conducted by researchers at the American University, Washington, evaluated the role of teachers in addressing childhood obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teachers-can-play-significant-role-addressing-childhood-obesity-study-470818</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Sep 2023 05:43:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Happy Feet: 10 Best Off-The-Shelf Insoles For Ultimate Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/happy-feet-10-best-off-shelf-insoles-ultimate-support-470803 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top 10 off-the-shelf insoles that provide ultimate support for happy and comfortable feet.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/happy-feet-10-best-off-shelf-insoles-ultimate-support-470803</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:50:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women Can 'Grow' Benefits Of Exercise Like Bank Savings For Better Heart Health: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-can-grow-benefits-exercise-like-bank- savings-better-heart-health-study-470816 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say women can "grow" the benefits of exercise like bank savings and enjoy better heart health later in life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-can-grow-benefits-exercise-like-bank- savings-better-heart-health-study-470816</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:26:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breast Cancer: Study Says Tumor Can Be Detected Early Through Breast Milk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-study-says-tumor-can-Detected-early-through-breast-milk-470813 <description><![CDATA[The new study showed that breast milk from breast cancer patients diagnosed during pregnancy or postpartum contains circulating tumor DNA that can be detected using liquid biopsy in the future.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-study-says-tumor-can-Detected-early-through-breast-milk-470813</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Sep 2023 03:15:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Transplantation Induce Aging In Patients? Researchers Say A New Drug Class Can Help Prevent It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-transplantation-induce-aging-病人-researchers-say-new-drug-class-can-help-prevent-it-470810 <description><![CDATA[Treatment with a new class of drugs, called senolytics, in donors improved the physical fitness of the recipients, a new study has shown.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-transplantation-induce-aging-病人-researchers-say-new-drug-class-can-help-prevent-it-470810</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Sep 2023 01:39:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[US Surgeons Report Longest Successful Pig-To-Human Kidney Transplant]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/us-surgeons-report-longest-successful-pig- human-kidney-transplant-470809 <description><![CDATA[US surgeons who transplanted a genetically modified pig kidney into a brain-dead patient announced Thursday they had ended their experiment after a record-breaking 61 days.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/us-surgeons-report-longest-successful-pig- human-kidney-transplant-470809</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Sep 2023 06:20:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Brain Hemorrhage Transmit Through Blood Transfusions? Study Says There Is A Slight Chance]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-brain-hemorriage-transmit-through-blood-transfusions-study-says-there-slight-chance-470807 <description><![CDATA[Cerebral amyloid angiopathy, a cause of spontaneous hemorrhage, could be transmitted through donated blood. However, it is highly unlikely that people would suffer a brain hemorrhage as a direct result of receiving donated blood, researchers say.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-brain-hemorriage-transmit-through-blood-transfusions-study-says-there-slight-chance-470807</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Sep 2023 03:29:04 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>