<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一个</language><item><title><![CDATA[Multistate E-Coli Outbreak Linked To Organic Carrots Claims One Life, Sickens Dozens: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multistate-e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-carrots-claims-one-life-sickens-dozens-cdc-472691 <description><![CDATA[The current multistate outbreak, identified since September, is linked to multiple brands of recalled organic bagged carrots, including whole and baby carrots sold by Grimmway Farms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multistate-e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-carrots-claims-one-life-sickens-dozens-cdc-472691</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Nov 2024 01:02:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Every Extra Hour Of Walking In Your 40's Adds Time To Lifespan: Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/every-extra-hour-walking-your-40s-adds-time-lifespan-study-suggests-472689 <description><![CDATA[The study found that on average, every extra hour of walking in your 40s adds around 3 hours (169 minutes) to lifespan.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/every-extra-hour-walking-your-40s-adds-time-lifespan-study-suggests-472689</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Nov 2024 05:17:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Screen Time Triggers Early Puberty, Rapid Bone Growth, Potentially Limiting Height: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-triggers-early-puberty-rapid-bone-growth-pottially-limiting-height-study-472687 <description><![CDATA[The results of the rat study highlight how exposure to screens from a very young age affects children's height and physical maturity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-triggers-early-puberty-rapid-bone-growth-pottially-limiting-height-study-472687</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:54:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Magnesium Bath Flakes For Muscle Recovery, Stress Relief And Skin Hydration]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-magnesium-bath-flakes-muscle-recovery-stress-relief-skin-Hydration-472655 <description><![CDATA[Whether you're looking for a natural way to support muscle recovery, reduce stress, or improve your skin's hydration, magnesium bath flakes are an accessible and effective option to explore.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-magnesium-bath-flakes-muscle-recovery-stress-relief-skin-Hydration-472655</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:57:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Fitness Belts To Support For Core Strength, Posture And Injury Prevention]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-fitness-belts-support-core-strength-posture-injury-prevention-472664 <description><![CDATA[Fitness belts enhance core stability, support proper posture, and prevent injury during heavy lifting. Ideal for weightlifters, they provide added security, ensuring safe movement while promoting balanced muscle engagement for improved performance.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-fitness-belts-support-core-strength-posture-injury-prevention-472664</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:55:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Florida City Leaders Vote to Eliminate Fluoride from Water Supply Because of RFK Jr.: 'I Can Get False Teeth If Needed']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-city-leaders-vote-eliminate-fluide-water-supply-because-rfk-jr-i-can-get-false-472683 <description><![CDATA[Government officials in Winter Haven City voted to eliminate fluoride from its water supply, citing Robert F. Kennedy, Jr.'s national campaign to remove it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-city-leaders-vote-eliminate-fluide-water-supply-because-rfk-jr-i-can-get-false-472683</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:19:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Walk For 10 Minutes After Every Hour Of Sitting To Reduce Blood Pressure, Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/walk-10-mines-after-every-hour-sitting-reduce-blood-Pressure-study-suggests-472681 <description><![CDATA[The study found that sitting for more than six hours per day during childhood and continuing the habit into adulthood can raise blood pressure by 4mmHg.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/walk-10-mines-after-every-hour-sitting-reduce-blood-Pressure-study-suggests-472681</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 03:10:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Resurges As Vaccination Declines, Most Deaths Among Unvaccinated Young Children: WHO, CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-resurges-vaccination-declines-most-deaths-among-unvaccinated-young-children-who-cdc-472680 <description><![CDATA[Around 10.3 million cases were reported in 2023, marking an alarming 20% increase from the previous year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-resurges-vaccination-declines-most-deaths-among-unvaccinated-young-children-who-cdc-472680</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:07:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stress During Pregnancy Linked To Higher Risk Of Epilepsy In Children]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-during-pregnancy-linked-higher-risk-epilepsy-children-472677 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed a striking 70% increased risk of epilepsy among children aged 1 to 3 when their mothers experienced continuous psychological distress during pregnancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-during-pregnancy-linked-higher-risk-epilepsy-children-472677</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:59:32 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Discovers Shocking Source of 20-Year-Old Stomach Pain: A Needle Left Inside Her During Vaginal Surgery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-discovers-shocking-source-20-year-old-stomach-pain-needle-left-inside-her-during-vaginal-472675 <description><![CDATA[A woman in Thailand recently discovered the source of her decades-long abdominal pain: a surgical needle allegedly left in her vaginal area during childbirth.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-discovers-shocking-source-20-year-old-stomach-pain-needle-left-inside-her-during-vaginal-472675</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 12:29:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[G.tec Medical Engineering's Innovative RecoveriX BCI Treatment Now Available In Hospitals &amp; Neurorehabilitation Centers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gtec-medical-engineerings-innovative-recoverix-bci-treatment-now-available-hospitals-472673 <description><![CDATA[Using recoveriX improves neuroplasticity, which helps rewire nervous pathways and replace damaged neurons that were affected by the stroke, multiple sclerosis, or Parkinson's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gtec-medical-engineerings-innovative-recoverix-bci-treatment-now-available-hospitals-472673</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 12:28:46 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>