<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Whooping Cough Hits Decade High: Know Symptoms, Learn How To Protect Yourself]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/whooping-cough-hits-decade-high-know-symptoms-learn-how-protect-yourself-472548 <description><![CDATA[The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) warns that pertussis, which saw a decline during the pandemic, is now returning to pre-pandemic levels or even exceeding them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/whooping-cough-hits-decade-high-know-symptoms-learn-how-protect-yourself-472548</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Oct 2024 01:41:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Under Eye Patches: Your Solution For Puffiness, Dark Circles, And Fine Lines]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-under-eye-patches-your-solution-puffiness-dark-circles-fine-lines-472478 <description><![CDATA[This article explores the 25 best under-eye patches available today, detailing their effectiveness in reducing puffiness, dark circles, and fine lines. Under-eye patches are a convenient skincare solution designed to hydrate, rejuvenate, and brighten the delicate skin around the eyes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-under-eye-patches-your-solution-puffiness-dark-circles-fine-lines-472478</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:13:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Take Breaks Between Walks: Researchers Say It Helps Burn More Calories]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-breaks- Between-walks-researchers-say-it-helps-burn-more-calories-472544 <description><![CDATA[Doing short bouts of walking or climbing stairs requires more oxygen and energy compared to long strolls, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-breaks- Between-walks-researchers-say-it-helps-burn-more-calories-472544</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Oct 2024 05:15:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Are Airport And Luggage Malaria? Discover Rare Infection Sources Rising In Europe]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-are-airport-luggage-malaria-discover-rare-infection-sources-rising-europe-472542 <description><![CDATA[A recent study cautions against the growing threat of "airport" and "luggage" malaria, commonly called Odyssean malaria where mosquitoes carrying the malaria parasite are unknowingly transported to non-endemic areas, sparking local infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-are-airport-luggage-malaria-discover-rare-infection-sources-rising-europe-472542</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Oct 2024 03:25:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Hormonal IUD For Contraception Raises Breast Cancer Risk: Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-hormonal-iud-contraception-raises-breast-cancer-risk-study-finds-472539 <description><![CDATA[The study found that Levonorgestrel-Releasing Intrauterine Systems (LNG-IUS) was linked to 14 extra cases of breast cancer per 10,000 women compared to those not using contraceptive medication.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-hormonal-iud-contraception-raises-breast-cancer-risk-study-finds-472539</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Oct 2024 01:57:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Keep Kids Active: Childhood Fitness Linked To Lower Stress And Depression In Teen Years]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keep-kids-active-childhood-fitness-linked-lower-stress-depression-teen-years-472538 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that maintaining good physical fitness from childhood to adolescence is associated with reduced stress and depression during the teenage years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keep-kids-active-childhood-fitness-linked-lower-stress-depression-teen-years-472538</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:42:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Seizures In Kids From Prescription Medications, Illegal Substances Doubled In 15 Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/seizures-kids-prescription-medications-illegal-substances-doubled-15-years-study-472537 <description><![CDATA[The researchers stressed the need for better awareness among parents and elders about the safe handling of over-the-counter medications.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/seizures-kids-prescription-medications-illegal-substances-doubled-15-years-study-472537</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Oct 2024 03:14:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Breast Cancer Type Linked To Excess Body Fat: Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-breast-cancer-type-linked-excess-body-fat-study-reveals-472534 <description><![CDATA[Excess body fat may be responsible for 40% of postmenopausal hormone-positive breast cancer cases. The new study findings suggest the need to rethink the effectiveness of BMI in assessing cancer risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-breast-cancer-type-linked-excess-body-fat-study-reveals-472534</guid><pubDate> Wed, 16 Oct 2024 01:48:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Or Too Little Folate During Pregnancy May Raise the Risk of Congenital Heart Defects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-too-little-folate-during-pregnancy-may-raise-risk-congenital-heart-defects-472532 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted a U-shaped association between maternal serum folate levels and congenital heart defect risk in offspring, meaning both low and high maternal folate were linked to a higher risk of heart defect.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-too-little-folate-during-pregnancy-may-raise-risk-congenital-heart-defects-472532</guid><pubDate> Tue, 15 Oct 2024 04:08:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Loss Without Diet Or Exercise? New Fat-Absorbing Nanotherapy Could Be A Game Changer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-without-diet-exercise-new-fat-bearing-nanotherapy-could-game-changer-472531 <description><![CDATA[The breakthrough oral nanotherapy interacts directly with the small intestine to decrease its capacity to absorb fat from the food consumed, making it a game-changer for those looking to manage their weight with minimal lifestyle changes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-without-diet-exercise-new-fat-bearing-nanotherapy-could-game-changer-472531</guid><pubDate> Tue, 15 Oct 2024 02:45:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Children Who Had COVID-19 At Higher Risk Of Type 2 Diabetes: Study Finds]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-who-had-covid-19-higher-risk-type-2-diabetes-study-finds-472529 <description><![CDATA[The study noted an increased risk of type 2 diabetes in pediatric patients after a bout of COVID-19 infection compared to other respiratory infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-who-had-covid-19-higher-risk-type-2-diabetes-study-finds-472529</guid><pubDate> Tue, 15 Oct 2024 01:34:43 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>