<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Low Testosterone In Men Affects Heart Health, Raises Risk Of Death: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-testosterone-men-affects-heart-health-raises-risk-death-study-471736 <description><![CDATA[Men who have testosterone levels below the normal range are at a 40 percent higher risk of death from all causes, and those with extremely low T are at a 60% higher risk of death from heart disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-testosterone-men-affects-heart-health-raises-risk-death-study-471736</guid><pubDate> Tue, 14 May 2024 01:49:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smokers Gain Weight When They Quit Smoking: Here's Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smokers-gain-weight-when-they-quit-smoking-heres-why-471733 <description><![CDATA[The study found that smokers tend to eat less and stick to unhealthy eating habits compared to nonsmokers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smokers-gain-weight-when-they-quit-smoking-heres-why-471733</guid><pubDate> Mon, 13 May 2024 04:04:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID Vaccine May Help Heart Failure Patients Live Longer: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-vaccine-may-help-heart-failure-病人-live-longer-study-471735 <description><![CDATA[Getting vaccinated against COVID-19 can improve the longevity of heart failure patients by 82% compared to those who are unvaccinated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-vaccine-may-help-heart-failure-病人-live-longer-study-471735</guid><pubDate> Mon, 13 May 2024 03:34:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Discrimination Linked To Faster Aging; White People Experience More Impact: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/discrimination-linked-faster-aging-white-people-experience-more-impact-study-471729 <description><![CDATA[Interpersonal discrimination is linked to molecular-level changes that speed up aging, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/discrimination-linked-faster-aging-white-people-experience-more-impact-study-471729</guid><pubDate> Fri, 10 May 2024 04:51:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Explains How Night Shift Workers Are Prone To Diabetes, Obesity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-explains-how-night-shift-workers-are-prone-diabetes-obesity-471727 <description><![CDATA[Working on the night shift for as little as three days can disrupt the protein rhythms, raising the risk of diabetes, a recent study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-explains-how-night-shift-workers-are-prone-diabetes-obesity-471727</guid><pubDate> Fri, 10 May 2024 03:21:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eating Disorder Affects 24% Of People With Insulin Dependent Diabetes: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-disorder-affects-24-people-insulin-dependent-diabetes-study-471725 <description><![CDATA[Researchers also noted that 21% of insulin-dependent adults suffer from a unique form of eating disorder called insulin omission, where patients intentionally restrict or skip insulin doses due to fears of weight gain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-disorder-affects-24-people-insulin-dependent-diabetes-study-471725</guid><pubDate> Fri, 10 May 2024 01:29:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[90% Of US Adults At Risk Of Heart Disease, At Various Stages of CKM Syndrome: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/90-us-adults-risk-heart-disease-various-stages-ckm-syndrome-study-471724 <description><![CDATA[A shocking majority of U.S. adults are at an early, middle, or late stage of cardiovascular, kidney, and metabolic (CKM) syndrome, a new study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/90-us-adults-risk-heart-disease-various-stages-ckm-syndrome-study-471724</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 May 2024 04:51:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra Processed Food Linked To Early Death, Study Identifies Items With Highest Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-linked-early-death-study-identizes-items-highest-risk-471723 <description><![CDATA[Researchers noted that not all ultra-processed products have the same risk, and not all products call for restricted usage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-linked-early-death-study-identizes-items-highest-risk-471723</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 May 2024 02:42:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Olive Oil In Diet Reduces Risk Of Death From Dementia: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/olive-oil-diet-reduces-risk-death-dementia-study-471721 <description><![CDATA[Daily consumption of at least 7 g of olive oil was linked to a 28% reduced risk of death from dementia-related illnesses.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/olive-oil-diet-reduces-risk-death-dementia-study-471721</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 May 2024 02:09:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Potentially Cancerous Air Detected In Car Interiors, Study Warns]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/pottially-cancerous-air-Detected-car-interiors-study-warns-471720 <description><![CDATA[According to a study, flame retardants used in car seats to meet an outdated federal flammability standard raise the risk of exposure to potentially cancerous air, particularly in summer when temperatures are high.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pottially-cancerous-air-Detected-car-interiors-study-warns-471720</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 May 2024 04:56:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sedentary Lifestyle In Childhood Linked To Progressing Heart Enlargement, Light Activity Reverses Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sedentary-lifestyle-childhood-linked-progressing-heart-enlargement-light-activity-reverses-risk-471718 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that a sedentary lifestyle in childhood increases the risk of progressing left ventricular hypertrophy, a heart enlargement condition that raises the likelihood of heart attacks, stroke, and premature death in adulthood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sedentary-lifestyle-childhood-linked-progressing-heart-enlargement-light-activity-reverses-risk-471718</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 May 2024 03:36:27 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>