<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Utah Set to Eliminate Fluoride in Water After RFK Calls Cavity Fighter 'Industrial Waste']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/utah-set-set----fluoride-water-water-rfk-calls-calls-cavity-fighter-fighter-fighter-sustrial-lustrial-Instrial-lastial-473177 <description><![CDATA[Utah may become the first U.S. state to ban the addition of fluoride to public drinking water, following the passage of a bill by the state Senate on Friday.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/utah-set-set----fluoride-water-water-rfk-calls-calls-cavity-fighter-fighter-fighter-sustrial-lustrial-Instrial-lastial-473177</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:17:30 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Says Measles Outbreak Is 'Not Unusual' Despite Texas Child Marking First Death in a Decade]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rfk-jr-says-measles爆发 - 爆发 -  not-unusual-deast-deast-texas-child-marking-toct-tirst-dept-dept-dept-Decade-decade-473174 <description><![CDATA[Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. acknowledged the measles outbreak in Texas on Wednesday, emphasizing that the US sees multiple outbreaks each year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rfk-jr-says-measles爆发 - 爆发 -  not-unusual-deast-deast-texas-child-marking-toct-tirst-dept-dept-dept-Decade-decade-473174</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:10:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unvaccinated Child Becomes First in a Decade to Die of Measles as Texas Outbreak Grows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unvacined-child-becomes-first-decade-decade-die-measles-texas爆炸爆发 -  473173 <description><![CDATA[A measles outbreak in rural West Texas has claimed the life of an unvaccinated child, marking the first U.S. measles-related death since 2015.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unvacined-child-becomes-first-decade-decade-die-measles-texas爆炸爆发 -  473173</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:01:54 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI-Assisted Wearable Device 'Speaks' For People With Dysfunctional Vocal Cords]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-sasised-wearable-device-speaks-peeople-dysfunctiuns-vocal-cords-473161 <description><![CDATA[AI's unique ability to rapidly and efficiently analyze, compile, and produce results according to trends within the data analysis may come in handy with a unique magnetic phenomenon, magnetoelasticity]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-sasised-wearable-device-speaks-peeople-dysfunctiuns-vocal-cords-473161</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:25:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Antidepressants May Worsen Dementia, Says Study: But Experts Have Conflicting Views]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antidepressant-may-worsen-dementia-says-says-study-experts-have-conflicting-views-473171 <description><![CDATA[Although experts have conflicting views on this surprising finding, the researchers hope their study will help doctors and patients make informed choices when making treatment decisions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antidepressant-may-worsen-dementia-says-says-study-experts-have-conflicting-views-473171</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 05:01:13 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Diet Cuts Cancer Risk Through Surprising Ways; It's Not Just By Weight Loss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-diet-cuts-cuts-cancer-risk-through-srough-surprising-ways-ways-ist-not-just-weight-weight-weight-weight-weight-weight-weight-loss-473168 <description><![CDATA[A new study reveals that the Mediterranean diet helps lower the risk of certain cancers associated with obesity, and interestingly, it's not just the weight loss that's making the difference.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-diet-cuts-cuts-cancer-risk-through-srough-surprising-ways-ways-ist-not-just-weight-weight-weight-weight-weight-weight-weight-loss-473168</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 03:08:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Listeria Outbreak Linked To Supplement Shakes Kills 12: CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/listeria-arper-break-breamped-supprement-suppement-kills-kills-kills-kills-kills-kills-warns-473167 <description><![CDATA[A deadly Listeria outbreak that has sickened 38 people and killed 12 across 12 states since 2018, is now traced back to frozen supplement shakes distributed to long-term care facilities.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/listeria-arper-break-breamped-supprement-suppement-kills-kills-kills-kills-kills-kills-warns-473167</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 02:05:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Premature Aging? Expert Recommends To Avoid 3 Food Items]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-premature-aging-agging-agger-dexpert-recommends-avoid-3-food-items-473158 <description><![CDATA[An expert reveals three food items that could make people look older than they actually are.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-premature-aging-agging-agger-dexpert-recommends-avoid-3-food-items-473158</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Feb 2025 04:22:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Way To Detect Alzheimer's? Your Breathing Pattern Could Be An Early Sign]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-way-detect-alzheimers-your-breaththing-pattern-coultn-could-sign-sign-473156 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that a higher breathing rate could be an earlier sign of Alzheimer's that might help identify the disease before more obvious symptoms appear.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-way-detect-alzheimers-your-breaththing-pattern-coultn-could-sign-sign-473156</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Feb 2025 03:21:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mystery Illness Kills 50 In Congo: Officials Raise Alarm As Fatalities Occur Within Hours After Symptoms Appear]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mystery-illness-kills-kills-50-congo-raise-raise-alarm-fatalities-fatalities-cocur-within-hours-hours-473154 <description><![CDATA[The unknown disease, believed to have entered a second outbreak in February, is raising alarm among health officials as most victims have died within 48 hours of developing symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mystery-illness-kills-kills-50-congo-raise-raise-alarm-fatalities-fatalities-cocur-within-hours-hours-473154</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Feb 2025 01:17:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even Little Movement Helps: Just 5 Minutes Of Daily Exercise Reduces Dementia Risk By 41%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-little-movement-helps-just-5-minutes-daily-daily-cercise-redecise-redecise-duces-duces-dementia危险-41-473152 <description><![CDATA[New research suggests even small amounts of movement can still give significant protection against dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-little-movement-helps-just-5-minutes-daily-daily-cercise-redecise-redecise-duces-duces-dementia危险-41-473152</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:17:06 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>