<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Unlock Excellence In Fitness: A Dive Into Huge Supplements' Premium Formulas]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/unlock-excellence-fitness-dive-huge-supplements-premium-formulas-471252 <description><![CDATA[Explore the world of Huge Supplements and elevate your fitness to new heights.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/unlock-excellence-fitness-dive-huge-supplements-premium-formulas-471252</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Feb 2024 13:02:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smokers Who Quit Before 40 Have Similar Life-Expectancy Of Non-smokers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smokers-who-quit-before-age-40-have-similar-life-expectancy-non-smokers-study-471393 <description><![CDATA[The study also revealed that individuals who quit smoking, regardless of age, can achieve a life expectancy similar to non-smokers within approximately 10 years after quitting, and nearly half of this benefit can be noticed within just three years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smokers-who-quit-before-age-40-have-similar-life-expectancy-non-smokers-study-471393</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Feb 2024 03:11:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Oregon Reports Human Plague Linked To Pet Cat: Learn All About The Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/oregon-reports- human-plague-linked-pet-cat-learn-all-about-disease-471394 <description><![CDATA[The officials noted that plague occurrence is rare in Oregon, with the last case reported in 2015.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/oregon-reports- human-plague-linked-pet-cat-learn-all-about-disease-471394</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:29:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Heart-Healthy Eating: Expert Recommendations for American Heart Month]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-healthy-eating-expert-recommendations-american-heart-month-471369 <description><![CDATA[As we mark American Heart Month, know from a heart health dietitian ways to improve heart health through mindful eating.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-healthy-eating-expert-recommendations-american-heart-month-471369</guid><pubDate> Sat, 10 Feb 2024 04:30:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Optimal Gut Wellness: The Ultimate Guide To Top 5 Supplements]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/optimal-gut-wellness-ultimate-guide-top-5-supplements-471389 <description><![CDATA[Improving your health starts with the gut. Check these top 5 supplements that will not just boost your digestive health bit also your overall well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/optimal-gut-wellness-ultimate-guide-top-5-supplements-471389</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:07:22 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Eye Drops For 2024: Revitalize Your Vision]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-eye-drops-revitalize-your-vision-471368 <description><![CDATA[Eye drops effectively relieve various eye conditions like dry eyes, allergies, and redness. Selecting the appropriate type and using them properly can alleviate discomfort, enhance vision, and maintain eye health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-eye-drops-revitalize-your-vision-471368</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Feb 2024 04:50:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Thermal Earring To Monitor Temperature: Experts Say It Could Also Track Ovulation And Stress]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ Thermal-earring-monitor-Temperature-experts-say-it-could-also-track-ovulation-stress-471382 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have developed smart earrings that could continuously monitor a person's earlobe temperature. The innovation known as Thermal Earring could also be potentially used to track signs of ovulation, stress, eating, and exercise.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ Thermal-earring-monitor-Temperature-experts-say-it-could-also-track-ovulation-stress-471382</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Feb 2024 02:23:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Benefits Of Atlantic Diet: Researchers Say It Reduces Risk Of Metabolic Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-atlantic-diet-researchers-say-it-reduces-risk-metabolic-syndrome-471381 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found that the Atlantic Diet, a traditional diet pattern in Portugal and Galicia, a region in northwest Spain could help reduce the risk of metabolic syndrome.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-atlantic-diet-researchers-say-it-reduces-risk-metabolic-syndrome-471381</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:55:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Green Juice Products For Nutrient-Rich Refreshment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-green-juice-products- Nutrition-rich-refreshment-471212 <description><![CDATA[Each of these offerings presents a unique and flavorful approach to nutrient-rich refreshment]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-green-juice-products- Nutrition-rich-refreshment-471212</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:14:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gentle Relief: Navigating Interstitial Cystitis With CYSTASOLV IC/PBS Dietary Supplement]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/gentle-relief-navigating-interstitial-cystitis-cystasolv-ic-pbs-dietary-supplement-471211 <description><![CDATA[CYSTASOLV is altering the story for individuals seeking relief from the agony of Interstitial Cystitis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/gentle-relief-navigating-interstitial-cystitis-cystasolv-ic-pbs-dietary-supplement-471211</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:01:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exploring The Power Of Oral Probiotics For Immune And Oral Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-power-oral-probiotics-immune-oral-health-471251 <description><![CDATA[Explore how oral probiotics can boost your immune and oral health. Learn about the best oral probiotics out there.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-power-oral-probiotics-immune-oral-health-471251</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:45:10 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>