<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Know How Well You're Aging? New Cheek Swab Test Predicts Mortality Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-know-how-well-youre-aging-new-cheek-swab-test-predicts-mortality-risk-472482 <description><![CDATA[Using a next-generation epigenetic clock called CheekAge, the researchers used methylation data from cheek cells to predict mortality from any cause.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-know-how-well-youre-aging-new-cheek-swab-test-predicts-mortality-risk-472482</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Oct 2024 03:38:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Metabolic Syndrome Affects One-Third Of U.S. Adults: Study Reveals Effective Diet Strategy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-syndrome-affects-one-third-us-adults-study-reveals- effective-diet-strategy-472481 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that time-restricted eating, a popular diet strategy known for weight loss, could be a game-changer for those with metabolic syndrome.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-syndrome-affects-one-third-us-adults-study-reveals- effective-diet-strategy-472481</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Oct 2024 01:36:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Who Hacked Off Own Genitals While High on Mushrooms Undergoes Successful Penis 'Replantation' in Historic First]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-who-hacked-off-own-genitals-while-high-mushrooms-undergoes-successful-penis-replantation-472479 <description><![CDATA[Doctors in Austria have documented the first known occurrence of psilocybin-induced penile amputation according to an unprecedented case report.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-who-hacked-off-own-genitals-while-high-mushrooms-undergoes-successful-penis-replantation-472479</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:39:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Read Aloud To Kids: AAP Recommends Shared Reading To Strengthen Bonds, Boost Brain Development]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/read-aloud-kids-aap-recommends-shared-reading-strengthen-bonds-boost-brain-development-472476 <description><![CDATA[The latest updated policy statement from the AAP suggests "literacy promotion as a universal primary prevention strategy to strengthen families and support healthy development."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/read-aloud-kids-aap-recommends-shared-reading-strengthen-bonds-boost-brain-development-472476</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Sep 2024 05:58:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Poor Sleep During Pregnancy Linked To Developmental Delays In Children: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poor-sleep-during-pregnancy-linked-developmental-delays-children-study-472473 <description><![CDATA[The study explored how short sleep duration during pregnancy, meaning sleeping less than seven hours daily, is linked to neurodevelopmental delays in offspring.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poor-sleep-during-pregnancy-linked-developmental-delays-children-study-472473</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Sep 2024 03:10:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Marburg Virus Outbreak Kills 6 In Rwanda: What To Know About Contagious Hemorrhagic Fever]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/marburg-virus-outbreak-kills-6-rwanda-what-know-about-contagious-hemorrhagic-fever-472471 <description><![CDATA[Currently, there is no available treatment or vaccine for Marburg disease. The expected fatality is around 88%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/marburg-virus-outbreak-kills-6-rwanda-what-know-about-contagious-hemorrhagic-fever-472471</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Sep 2024 02:13:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Elastic Bandage Wraps For Injury Prevention And Recovery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-elastic-bandage-wraps-injury-prevention-recovery-472451 <description><![CDATA[Elastic adhesive bandages are a practical solution for injury management and prevention. Their ability to provide flexible support, reduce swelling, and stabilize joints makes them a valuable tool for athletes and everyday users alike.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-elastic-bandage-wraps-injury-prevention-recovery-472451</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Sep 2024 15:26:22 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Massage Guns To Soothe Your Aching Muscles]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-massage-guns-soothe-your-aching-muscles-472438 <description><![CDATA[Regular use of a massage gun can help improve circulation, reduce muscle stiffness, alleviate pain, and even contribute to better sleep quality. Massage guns are a cost-effective and convenient investment for those with sedentary lifestyles or jobs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-massage-guns-soothe-your-aching-muscles-472438</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:52:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Nebulizers For Your Respiratory Health: Here's How To Use Them Effectively]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-nebulizers-your-respiratory-health-heres-how-use-them-efficiently-472415 <description><![CDATA[Nebulizers are simple devices designed to deliver medications to the lungs directly, making them crucial for treating everything from common colds to more serious conditions like asthma and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD). In this guide, we explore the various types of nebulizers, their unique benefits, and practical tips for using them effectively. Whether you need relief from a mild respiratory infection or long-term support for a chronic condition, understanding nebulizers will help you choose the right one for your needs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-nebulizers-your-respiratory-health-heres-how-use-them-efficiently-472415</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:39:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cobenfy Gets FDA Approval: New Drug Offers Novel Treatment Mechanism For Schizophrenia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cobenfy-gets-fda-approval-new-drug-offers-novel-treatment-mechanism-schizophrenia-472465 <description><![CDATA[The new drug Cobenfy promises to revolutionize treatment for schizophrenia with its novel mechanism, the first of its kind in decades.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cobenfy-gets-fda-approval-new-drug-offers-novel-treatment-mechanism-schizophrenia-472465</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Sep 2024 03:19:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[14% Of U.S. Adults Have Inadequate Iron, Study Finds: Here's How To Spot Deficiency]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/14-us-adults-have-inadequate-iron-study-finds-heres-how-spot-deficiency-472463 <description><![CDATA[The study found that 14% of U.S. adults lack adequate iron, while 15% have functional iron deficiency, where their bodies can't properly use the iron they have.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/14-us-adults-have-inadequate-iron-study-finds-heres-how-spot-deficiency-472463</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Sep 2024 01:42:07 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>