<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Mystery Illness Kills 50 In Congo: Officials Raise Alarm As Fatalities Occur Within Hours After Symptoms Appear]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mystery-illness-kills-kills-50-congo-raise-raise-alarm-fatalities-fatalities-cocur-within-hours-hours-473154 <description><![CDATA[The unknown disease, believed to have entered a second outbreak in February, is raising alarm among health officials as most victims have died within 48 hours of developing symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mystery-illness-kills-kills-50-congo-raise-raise-alarm-fatalities-fatalities-cocur-within-hours-hours-473154</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Feb 2025 01:17:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even Little Movement Helps: Just 5 Minutes Of Daily Exercise Reduces Dementia Risk By 41%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-little-movement-helps-just-5-minutes-daily-daily-cercise-redecise-redecise-duces-duces-dementia危险-41-473152 <description><![CDATA[New research suggests even small amounts of movement can still give significant protection against dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-little-movement-helps-just-5-minutes-daily-daily-cercise-redecise-redecise-duces-duces-dementia危险-41-473152</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:17:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Drinks For Children: Here's How Much They Need]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-drinks-children-heres-how-much-much-they-need-473150 <description><![CDATA[What children drink is just as important as what they eat. To help parents make informed choices, an expert panel has issued healthy beverage recommendations for kids.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-drinks-children-heres-how-much-much-they-need-473150</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Feb 2025 02:26:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[123-Year-Old 'World's Oldest' Woman Shares Two Simple Foods Items As Her Secret To Longevity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/123年历史的worlds-worlds-worlds-wormest-shares-two-simple-foods-items-her-secret-longevity-473148 <description><![CDATA[Looking for longevity secrets? Learn from a 123-year-old woman from Colombia who is believed to be the world's oldest living person.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/123年历史的worlds-worlds-worlds-wormest-shares-two-simple-foods-items-her-secret-longevity-473148</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:20:44 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Artificial Sweetener In Diet Sodas May Raise Risk Of Heart Attacks, Strokes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-Antrover-sweetener-diet-sodas-sodas-may-raise-risk-hens-sathacks-strokes-473145 <description><![CDATA[Results of a recent mice trial revealed that mice fed with aspartame had increased inflammation and "larger and more fatty plaques" in their arteries, two main factors that could raise the risk of cardiovascular diseases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-Antrover-sweetener-diet-sodas-sodas-may-raise-risk-hens-sathacks-strokes-473145</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:37:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Loses Sight After Parasites Burrow Into Eyes: Common Mistake While Swimming To Blame]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-loses-sight-sight-after-parasites-burrow-eyes-common-mistake-mistake-willile-swimming-blame-473143 <description><![CDATA[The woman lost her eyesight to acanthamoeba keratitis, a rare infection caused by parasites burrowing into her cornea and permanently damaging her right eye.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-loses-sight-sight-after-parasites-burrow-eyes-common-mistake-mistake-willile-swimming-blame-473143</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:16:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman's Skin Turns Yellow, Develops Flu-Like Symptoms Before Shocking Terminal Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/womans-skin-turns-yelly-develops-flu-like-symptoms-be shocking-terminal-terminal-dienngnosis-473142 <description><![CDATA[When the 38-year-old developed strange flu-like symptoms and noticed her skin turning yellow, little did she imagine that it would lead to a devastating diagnosis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/womans-skin-turns-yelly-develops-flu-like-symptoms-be shocking-terminal-terminal-dienngnosis-473142</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:17:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Hospitalized With Fever, Recurrent Falls Diagnosed With Rare Infection Linked To Lake Swimming In Iowa]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-hospitalized-fever-recurrent-falls-falls-negned-rare-infection-infection-infection-swimming-iowa-iowa-473141 <description><![CDATA[The man's mysterious symptoms left doctors puzzled for days until they diagnosed him with a potentially fatal Legionnaires' disease, linked to his vacation swimming in an Iowa lake.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-hospitalized-fever-recurrent-falls-falls-negned-rare-infection-infection-infection-swimming-iowa-iowa-473141</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Feb 2025 04:47:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Feeling Groggy After A Full Night's Sleep? A Doctor Explains Simple Math To Find Your Ideal Bedtime]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/feeling-groggy-after-full-nights-nights-sleep-doctor-xplains-simple-math-math-find-find-your-bed-bed-bedtime-473140 <description><![CDATA[You get a full night's sleep but still wake up feeling groggy, while a short nap leaves you feeling refreshed. Ever wondered why?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/feeling-groggy-after-full-nights-nights-sleep-doctor-xplains-simple-math-math-find-find-your-bed-bed-bedtime-473140</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:51:36 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Autistic 3-Year-Old Speaks First Words Days After Starting Inexpensive Generic Drug Given For Chemo Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/autistic-3岁时，speaks-first-words-days-word-s-per-starting- inter-nixenting-nixeneric-generic-drug-grug-given-given-chemo-473139 <description><![CDATA[The parents of a nonverbal autistic boy in Arizona vouch for the drug after their son spoke his first words just days after taking it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/autistic-3岁时，speaks-first-words-days-word-s-per-starting- inter-nixenting-nixeneric-generic-drug-grug-given-given-chemo-473139</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Feb 2025 01:22:48 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Water Allergy Causes Excruciating Pain For Woman—From Drinking To Showering, She Shares Her Daily Struggle]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-water-allergy-causes-cruciating-pain-woman-drinking-showering-shopering-she-shares-shares-her-her-daily-473137 <description><![CDATA[An extremely rare condition called aquagenic urticaria makes the life of the young mother a daily struggle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-water-allergy-causes-cruciating-pain-woman-drinking-showering-shopering-she-shares-shares-her-her-daily-473137</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Feb 2025 04:45:38 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>