<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Trimethylglycine (TMG) Supplements For Heart Health And Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-trimethylglycine-tmg-supplements-heart-health-wellness-472247 <description><![CDATA[Trimethylglycine (TMG) is a nutrient that supports heart health by reducing homocysteine levels, enhances liver function by aiding detoxification, and improves athletic performance through better muscle oxygenation. With its role in methylation, TMG offers significant health benefits, making it a valuable addition to a balanced wellness regimen.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-trimethylglycine-tmg-supplements-heart-health-wellness-472247</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:38:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Betaine HCL Supplements for Digestive Health and Overall Well-being]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-betaine-hcl-supplements-digestive-health-overall-well-being-472231 <description><![CDATA[This article explores Betaine HCL supplements, highlighting their role in improving digestive health, enhancing nutrient absorption, supporting liver function, and boosting overall well-being. It provides guidance on selecting high-quality supplements, considering factors like purity, dosage, and additional ingredients. Betaine HCL helps ensure proper digestion and promotes a healthy gut environment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-betaine-hcl-supplements-digestive-health-overall-well-being-472231</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Sep 2024 08:44:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Alpha Lipoic Acid Supplements for Optimal Health: Enhance Energy, Skin, and Cognitive Function]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-alpha-lipoic-acid-supplements-optimal-health-enhance-energy-skin-cognitive-function-472213 <description><![CDATA[Alpha Lipoic Acid (ALA) is a potent antioxidant that supports metabolic health, reduces inflammation, and enhances skin and cognitive function. Found in supplements, ALA helps protect cells from oxidative damage and improves overall well-being. Choosing high-quality, bioavailable ALA supplements ensures optimal benefits for health and longevity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-alpha-lipoic-acid-supplements-optimal-health-enhance-energy-skin-cognitive-function-472213</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Sep 2024 08:44:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alcohol And Gout: Study Says Men At Higher Risk, Beer And Cider Most Harmful]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-gout-study-says-men-higher-risk-beer-cider-most-harmful-472260 <description><![CDATA[Alcohol consumption increases the risk of gout in both men and women, with men being more significantly affected, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-gout-study-says-men-higher-risk-beer-cider-most-harmful-472260</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Sep 2024 03:16:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Endometriosis Raises Women's Risk Of Heart Attacks, Strokes: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-raises-womens-risk-heart-attacks-lines-study-472259 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that those with endometriosis face a 20% higher risk of serious cardiac events, including heart attacks and strokes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-raises-womens-risk-heart-attacks-lines-study-472259</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Sep 2024 01:20:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Riboflavin Supplements: Your Key To Energy, Blood Health And Nervous System Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-riboflavin-supplements-your-key-energy-blood-health-nervous-system-support-472237 <description><![CDATA[Riboflavin supplements, commonly known as vitamin B2, are used to support various physiological functions, including energy metabolism, red blood cell production, and the maintenance of a healthy nervous system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-riboflavin-supplements-your-key-energy-blood-health-nervous-system-support-472237</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Sep 2024 09:53:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Sea Moss Supplements And Their Numerous Health Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-sea-moss-supplements-their-numerous-health-benefits-472229 <description><![CDATA[Sea moss supplements are largely safe if they are taken in appropriate amounts. And one should take professional advice before including it in their daily routine. Overall, it can play an important role in improving your overall health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-sea-moss-supplements-their-numerous-health-benefits-472229</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Sep 2024 09:47:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best L-Arginine Supplements For Improved Sexual Health, BP And Blood Sugar Levels]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-l-arginine-supplements-improved- Sex-health-bp-blood-sugar-levels-472203 <description><![CDATA[L-arginine is an amino acid, a chemical building block necessary for the body to make proteins. These proteins help your body repair new cells, damages tissues, break down and digest food.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-l-arginine-supplements-improved- Sex-health-bp-blood-sugar-levels-472203</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Sep 2024 07:48:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[One Unit Temperature Drop Over 2-6 Days Raises Heart Attack Risk By 10%: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/one-unit-Temperature-drop-over-2-6-days-raises-heart-attack-risk-10-study-472252 <description><![CDATA[The latest study examined the short-term effects of lower air temperature and cold spells on the risk of hospitalization from various types of myocardial infarction.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/one-unit-Temperature-drop-over-2-6-days-raises-heart-attack-risk-10-study-472252</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:16:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Single Blood Test Could Predict Women's Heart Disease Risk Over 30 Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/single-blood-test-could-predict-womens-heart-disease-risk-over-30-years-study-472249 <description><![CDATA[Researchers suggest that a one-time measurement of three biomarkers could accurately forecast the risk of major cardiovascular events in the decades to come.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/single-blood-test-could-predict-womens-heart-disease-risk-over-30-years-study-472249</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:14:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Busy Week? 'Weekend Warriors' Still Reap Brain Health Benefits, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/busy-week-weekend-warriors-still-reap-brain-health-benefits-says-study-472244 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that weekend warriors- those who pack their physical activity into one or two days of the week, typically on the weekend-can still reap the same brain health benefits of a regularly active pattern.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/busy-week-weekend-warriors-still-reap-brain-health-benefits-says-study-472244</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Sep 2024 01:15:03 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>