<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Can Food Choices Affect Brain? Study Says Balanced Diet Linked To Better Cognition, Mental Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-food-choices-affect-brain-study-says-balanced-diet-linked-better-cognition-mental-health-471584 <description><![CDATA[A balanced diet is associated with better cognitive function and mental health, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-food-choices-affect-brain-study-says-balanced-diet-linked-better-cognition-mental-health-471584</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Apr 2024 03:27:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[E-Cigarette Use Linked To High Risk Of Heart Failure: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-香烟-use-linked-high-risk-heart-failure-study-471582 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that e-cigarette users were 19% more at risk of developing heart failure compared with people who never used them]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-香烟-use-linked-high-risk-heart-failure-study-471582</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Apr 2024 01:26:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fungi for Fitness: 5 Best Mushroom Supplements Can Boost Your Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fungi-fitness-5-best-mushroom-supplements-can-boost-your-health-471545 <description><![CDATA[Explore the world of mushroom supplements with Fungi for Fitness, where health and vitality meet through the power of nature's fungi.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fungi-fitness-5-best-mushroom-supplements-can-boost-your-health-471545</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:38:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 5 Electrolyte Products: Recharge and Rehydrate with These Essential Picks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5- electrolyte-products-recharge-reHydrate-these-essential-picks-471544 <description><![CDATA[Whether you're an athlete striving for peak performance or just someone trying to stay hydrated, these top 5 electrolyte products will definitely help you out.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5- electrolyte-products-recharge-reHydrate-these-essential-picks-471544</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:34:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Explore The Healing Power Of Expressive Arts With Wellness Coach Karen Corona]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/explore-healing-power-expressive-arts-wellness-coach-karen-corona-471579 <description><![CDATA[With over two decades under her belt, Wellness Coach Karen Corona is not just a practitioner but a testament to the transformative power of expressive arts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/explore-healing-power-expressive-arts-wellness-coach-karen-corona-471579</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Apr 2024 14:57:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Dry Shampoo For 2024: For Fresh, Clean Hair Every Time]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-dry-shampoo-fresh-clean-hair-every-time-471574 <description><![CDATA[With its convenience and effectiveness, dry shampoo has become a staple in many people's hair care routines, providing a quick and easy way to keep hair looking and feeling its best.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-dry-shampoo-fresh-clean-hair-every-time-471574</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Apr 2024 09:53:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Gut Bacteria That Cut Cholesterol Level, Heart Disease Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-gut-bacteria-that-c​​ut-cholesterol-level-heart-disease-risk-471572 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that certain bacteria species called Oscillibacter can consume cholesterol in the gut and lower the risk of heart disease in individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-gut-bacteria-that-c​​ut-cholesterol-level-heart-disease-risk-471572</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Apr 2024 03:36:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitamin D Deficiency Linked To Increased Eczema Risk In Children: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-deficiency-linked-increased-eczema-risk-children-study-471571 <description><![CDATA[The study explored the link between vitamin D serum levels and allergen sensitization, and how this link influences the likelihood of developing atopic dermatitis in young children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-deficiency-linked-increased-eczema-risk-children-study-471571</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Apr 2024 01:37:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[From Persecution To Patron Saints The Remarkable Stories Of Medical Icons]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/persecution-patron-saints-remarkable-stories-medical-icons-471570 <description><![CDATA[L.D. George Angus's latest book, Unveiling the Legends: Celebrating Medical Visionaries, Their Revolutionary Contributions, and Sacred Resting Grounds, will take readers on a journey through the lives and work of medical pioneers who changed the world across generations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/persecution-patron-saints-remarkable-stories-medical-icons-471570</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:44:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Ketogenic Diet Improve Severe Mental Illness? Pilot Study Indicates Positive Results]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-ketogenic-diet-improve-severe-mental-illness-pilot-study-indicates-positive-results-471568 <description><![CDATA[Adopting a ketogenic diet while continuing medication restores metabolic health and improves psychiatric conditions, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-ketogenic-diet-improve-severe-mental-illness-pilot-study-indicates-positive-results-471568</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Apr 2024 04:19:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Autism Awareness Day: Know Symptoms For Early Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-autism-awareness-day-know-symptoms-early-diagnosis-471566 <description><![CDATA[On this World Autism Awareness Day, it is important to learn more about this disorder that affects the brain, its characteristics, and the telltale signs associated with it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-autism-awareness-day-know-symptoms-early-diagnosis-471566</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:23:11 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>