<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Just 1 Year Of This Exercise Could Preserve Leg Strength In Retirees, Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/just-1-year-this-exercise-could-preserve-leg-strength-retirees-study-reveals-471866 <description><![CDATA[The researchers discovered that doing twelve months of heavy resistance training around retirement age induces long-term beneficial effects on leg strength, lasting up to four years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/just-1-year-this-exercise-could-preserve-leg-strength-retirees-study-reveals-471866</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jun 2024 01:04:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[American Diet Quality Improved Modestly But Still Long Way To Go: Report]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/american-diet-quality-improved-modestly-still-long-way-go-report-471863 <description><![CDATA[A new report suggests that the number of Americans with poor diet quality remains stubbornly high, and dietary disparities persist or are worsening.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/american-diet-quality-improved-modestly-still-long-way-go-report-471863</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:00:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fasting Boosts Natural Immune Cells, Helps Body Fight Off Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fasting-boosts-natural-immune-cells-helps-body-fight-off-cancer-study-471861 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now found that periods of fasting could boost the immune system's natural killer cells to fight off cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fasting-boosts-natural-immune-cells-helps-body-fight-off-cancer-study-471861</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jun 2024 03:15:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[STSS: Rare Flesh-Eating Bacteria That Kills Within 48 Hours Spreads In Japan]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stss-rare-flesh-eating-bacteria-that-kills-within-48-hours-spreads-japan-471859 <description><![CDATA[Streptococcal Toxic Shock Syndrome (STSS), caused by Group A Streptococcus, can result in severe complications including low blood pressure, irregular heart rate, rapid breathing, necrotizing fasciitis potentially leading to limb loss, organ failure, and toxic shock.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stss-rare-flesh-eating-bacteria-that-kills-within-48-hours-spreads-japan-471859</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jun 2024 01:49:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Small Fish Intake Reduces Risk Of All-Cause Mortality, Death From Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/small-fish-intake-reduces-risk-all-cause-mortality-death-cancer-study-471857 <description><![CDATA[A group of researchers from Japan discovered potential life-extending benefits of habitually eating small fish eaten whole, particularly among women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/small-fish-intake-reduces-risk-all-cause-mortality-death-cancer-study-471857</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:59:06 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Turning To Junk Food During Stress? Study Says It Increases Anxiety]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/turning-junk-food-during-stress-study-says-it-increases-anxiety-471856 <description><![CDATA[The study investigated the underlying factors behind the connection between a high-fat diet and anxiety.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/turning-junk-food-during-stress-study-says-it-increases-anxiety-471856</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jun 2024 01:50:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Kickstart Your Health Journey? Get Your Cholesterol Checked At Home Today!]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-kickstart-your-health-journey-get-your-cholesterol-checked-home-today-471845 <description><![CDATA[To proactively combat abnormal cholesterol, it's essential to have a test. This allows you to detect early signs that may affect your overall health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-kickstart-your-health-journey-get-your-cholesterol-checked-home-today-471845</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:29:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Delivering Low Birth Weight Babies May Heighten Women's Risk Of Dementia]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/delivering-low-birth-weight-babies-may-heighten-womens-risk-dementia-471855 <description><![CDATA[Individuals who give birth to infants weighing less than 5.5 pounds are at a higher risk of experiencing memory and cognitive problems later in life, in contrast to those who deliver infants without low birth weight, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/delivering-low-birth-weight-babies-may-heighten-womens-risk-dementia-471855</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 04:39:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[9/11 First Responders At Elevated Risk Of Early Onset Dementia, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-11-first-responders-elevated-risk-early-onset-dementia-study-says-471853 <description><![CDATA[There is a higher likelihood of developing dementia before reaching the age of 65 in the first responders to the 9/11 site who experienced severe exposure to toxic debris in contrast to minimally exposed responders or those who utilized personal protective equipment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-11-first-responders-elevated-risk-early-onset-dementia-study-says-471853</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 03:24:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Reduce TV Watching And Get Off The Couch: Study Reveals Secret To Healthy Aging]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reduce-tv-watching-get-off-couch-study-reveals-secret-healthy-aging-471852 <description><![CDATA[Swapping just one hour of daily TV watching for light physical activity at home can improve the odds of reaching a healthy age of 70 or beyond by 8%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reduce-tv-watching-get-off-couch-study-reveals-secret-healthy-aging-471852</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:56:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Levels Of Toxic Cancer-Causing Ethylene Oxide Detected In Louisiana: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-有毒-癌症-导致-乙烯-氧化物-检测到-路易斯安那-报告-471850 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that the air in the industrialized stretch of southeast Louisiana dubbed "cancer alley" has 20 times higher concentrations of carcinogenic ethylene oxide than previously expected.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-有毒-癌症-导致-乙烯-氧化物-检测到-路易斯安那-报告-471850</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jun 2024 03:47:19 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>