<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>母亲</title><link/>https：/www.was.com.com<description>在救世主上</description><language>曾是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Eyeing A Sunny State For Retirement? You Might Experience Accelerated Aging]]></title><link/> httops：/wowing.complational.com启动状态状态 - 状态 - 睡眠 - 赛车。 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that living in hotter environments may accelerate the aging process.]]></description><guid> httops：/wowing.complational.com启动状态状态 - 状态 - 睡眠 - 赛车。</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 04:53:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Know Your Breast Cancer Risk: Here Are States With Highest Risk For Young Woman]]></title><link/> htts：/wowwasch uo-skuo-skuo-souno-dot-dot-gorg-suading-suading-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orge <description><![CDATA[A recent study has identified the states with highest and lowest risks of breast cancer in the U.S.]]></description><guid> htts：/wowwasch uo-skuo-skuo-souno-dot-dot-gorg-suading-suading-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orget-orge</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 02:50:58 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Belly Fat Protect Your Brain Health? It Depends—Here's Who Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-belly-fat-protect-your-brain-health-health-ipenderes-who-benefits-473180 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that belly fat may support brain health earlier in life, however, this protective effect diminishes with age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-belly-fat-protect-your-brain-health-health-ipenderes-who-benefits-473180</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 01:31:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Utah Set to Eliminate Fluoride in Water After RFK Calls Cavity Fighter 'Industrial Waste']]></title><link/> httops:/wowwas.comdalymy.com/shot-state-state-flade-fardr-state-sfine-start-start-start-start-start-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-fladrum-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-sale-state-coins777777777 <description><![CDATA[Utah may become the first U.S. state to ban the addition of fluoride to public drinking water, following the passage of a bill by the state Senate on Friday.]]></description><guid> httops:/wowwas.comdalymy.com/shot-state-state-flade-fardr-state-sfine-start-start-start-start-start-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-stest-fladrum-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-salty-sale-state-coins777777777</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:17:30 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Says Measles Outbreak Is 'Not Unusual' Despite Texas Child Marking First Death in a Decade]]></title><link/> htts：/wowing <description><![CDATA[Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. acknowledged the measles outbreak in Texas on Wednesday, emphasizing that the US sees multiple outbreaks each year.]]></description><guid> htts：/wowing</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:10:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unvaccinated Child Becomes First in a Decade to Die of Measles as Texas Outbreak Grows]]></title><link/> httops:/wowldal.saly.com/univational-family-fail-flad-frest-fids-profit-flakes-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-subsk-profit-offborks-profius-offbork-of-fluduk-oft-offborks-profit-profit-flakes-offbork-of-flukuo-duk and 473173. <description><![CDATA[A measles outbreak in rural West Texas has claimed the life of an unvaccinated child, marking the first U.S. measles-related death since 2015.]]></description><guid> httops:/wowldal.saly.com/univational-family-fail-flad-frest-fids-profit-flakes-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-outs-subsk-profit-offborks-profius-offbork-of-fluduk-oft-offborks-profit-profit-flakes-offbork-of-flukuo-duk and 473173.</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:01:54 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI-Assisted Wearable Device 'Speaks' For People With Dysfunctional Vocal Cords]]></title><link/> htts：/wowl。 <description><![CDATA[AI's unique ability to rapidly and efficiently analyze, compile, and produce results according to trends within the data analysis may come in handy with a unique magnetic phenomenon, magnetoelasticity]]></description><guid> htts：/wowl。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:25:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Antidepressants May Worsen Dementia, Says Study: But Experts Have Conflicting Views]]></title><link/> httops：/wowlist.silly.com/anologanant-sengys-wasen-start-start start-start-felt-felt-a peak the Peaks-viet-a峰。 <description><![CDATA[Although experts have conflicting views on this surprising finding, the researchers hope their study will help doctors and patients make informed choices when making treatment decisions.]]></description><guid> httops：/wowlist.silly.com/anologanant-sengys-wasen-start-start start-start-felt-felt-a peak the Peaks-viet-a峰。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 05:01:13 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Diet Cuts Cancer Risk Through Surprising Ways; It's Not Just By Weight Loss]]></title><link/> hetps:/wowing.comdical,com/pular-platar-changing-cards-to-surprising-to-sorps-to-tight-to-chil-to-to-tight-to-to-test-stest-to-test-stest-to-trunt-to-flat-from-to-floor-fil-to-floor-fil-to-tar-floor-flat-floor number-stest-to-test-to-test-to-test-to-test-to-trump-to-trump-to-trunt-test-to-test-to-trip. <description><![CDATA[A new study reveals that the Mediterranean diet helps lower the risk of certain cancers associated with obesity, and interestingly, it's not just the weight loss that's making the difference.]]></description><guid> hetps:/wowing.comdical,com/pular-platar-changing-cards-to-surprising-to-sorps-to-tight-to-chil-to-to-tight-to-to-test-stest-to-test-stest-to-trunt-to-flat-from-to-floor-fil-to-floor-fil-to-tar-floor-flat-floor number-stest-to-test-to-test-to-test-to-test-to-trump-to-trump-to-trunt-test-to-test-to-trip.</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 03:08:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Listeria Outbreak Linked To Supplement Shakes Kills 12: CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https：/wows。 <description><![CDATA[A deadly Listeria outbreak that has sickened 38 people and killed 12 across 12 states since 2018, is now traced back to frozen supplement shakes distributed to long-term care facilities.]]></description><guid> https：/wows。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 02:05:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Premature Aging? Expert Recommends To Avoid 3 Food Items]]></title><link/> httops：/wowl。 <description><![CDATA[An expert reveals three food items that could make people look older than they actually are.]]></description><guid> httops：/wowl。</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Feb 2025 04:22:16 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>