<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Hospital Called Cops on Woman Who Suffered Horrific Miscarriage in Bathroom: Lawsuit]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-hospital- Called-cops-woman-who-suffered-horrific-miscarriage-bathroom-lawsuit-472984 <description><![CDATA[An Ohio woman is suing her hometown, her healthcare providers and law enforcement after she was arrested for having a miscarriage about a year ago.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-hospital- Called-cops-woman-who-suffered-horrific-miscarriage-bathroom-lawsuit-472984</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:22:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Green Tea Protect Brain? Here's How Much To Drink Daily For Beneficial Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-green-tea-protect-brain-heres-how-much-drink-daily-beneficial-effects-472981 <description><![CDATA[New research suggests that drinking green tea every day may help reduce white matter lesions in the brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-green-tea-protect-brain-heres-how-much-drink-daily-beneficial-effects-472981</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 03:55:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Died After Pharmacy Ran Out Of Epilepsy Drug, Left Him With An 'IOU' Note]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-died-after-pharmacy-ran-out-epilepsy-drug-left-him-iou-note-472978 <description><![CDATA[A recent coroner's report concluded that epilepsy was a contributory factor in the man's death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-died-after-pharmacy-ran-out-epilepsy-drug-left-him-iou-note-472978</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 02:48:21 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Suffered Severe Injuries After Going Through MRI Scan With Inserted Sex Toy, Butt Plug 'Dragged' Through Body: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-suffered-severe-injuries-after-going-through-mri-scan-inserted-sex-toy-butt-plug-dragged-472975 <description><![CDATA[The young woman reportedly went into the scan without realizing the silicone sex toy she was using had metal in its core.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-suffered-severe-injuries-after-going-through-mri-scan-inserted-sex-toy-butt-plug-dragged-472975</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Jan 2025 01:02:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Supplements Increase Cancer Risk? Here's What Cancer Dietitian Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-supplements-increase-cancer-risk-heres-what-c​​ancer-dietitian-says-472973 <description><![CDATA[A seemingly harmless wellness trend is now being questioned by a cancer dietitian, who advises you to evaluate whether you really need to take supplements or if whole foods might be a better choice.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-supplements-increase-cancer-risk-heres-what-c​​ancer-dietitian-says-472973</guid><pubDate> Tue, 14 Jan 2025 02:55:47 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Coffee, Soda Or Wine? Dentist Reveals Drink That Stains Your Teeth Most]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/coffee-soda-wine-dentists-reveals-drink-that-stains-your-teeth-most-472971 <description><![CDATA[In a viral TikTok experiment, a California-based dentist unveiled the unexpected culprit behind tooth stains, and the surprising results left him "shocked.']]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/coffee-soda-wine-dentists-reveals-drink-that-stains-your-teeth-most-472971</guid><pubDate> Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:40:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Dismiss Bad Memories? Never Skip A Good Night's Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-dismiss-bad-memories-never-skip-good-nights-sleep-472969 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that sleep deprivation could be the culprit behind your mind's inability to lock away unwanted memories.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-dismiss-bad-memories-never-skip-good-nights-sleep-472969</guid><pubDate> Mon, 13 Jan 2025 02:40:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Shocking Reveal: Protein Powders May Contain Cancer-Causing Toxic Metals, Here're Products At Highest Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/shocking-reveal- Protein-powders-may-contain-cancer-causing-毒-金属-herere-products-highest-472968 <description><![CDATA[A recent report revealed that 47% of protein powders investigated contained heavy metals, at levels that exceeded government food safety regulations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/shocking-reveal- Protein-powders-may-contain-cancer-causing-毒-金属-herere-products-highest-472968</guid><pubDate> Mon, 13 Jan 2025 01:00:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Doctor Accused of Being High During Surgeries Loses License After Testing Positive for Cocaine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doctor-accused-being-high-during-surgeries-loses-license-after-testing-positive-cocaine-472965 <description><![CDATA[A Houston urologist lost his medical license after testing positive for cocaine and kratom amid allegations of performing surgeries while impaired.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doctor-accused-being-high-during-surgeries-loses-license-after-testing-positive-cocaine-472965</guid><pubDate> Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:49:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Virginia Woman Forced to Raise Money for Prosthetic Hand After Insurance Refuses to Cover It Despite Doctor Recommendation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virginia-woman-forced-raise-money-prosthetic-hand-after-insurance-refuses-cover-it-despite-472962 <description><![CDATA[Elisabeth Foley, a Virginia mother who lost her hand in a shark attack, is turning to crowdfunding after her insurance company denied coverage for a $73,000 prosthetic her doctors recommended.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virginia-woman-forced-raise-money-prosthetic-hand-after-insurance-refuses-cover-it-despite-472962</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 18:21:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Thousands of Doctors Come Out Against Letting RFK Jr. Become Health Secretary: 'He Is Actively Dangerous']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/thousands-doctors-come-out-against-letting-rfk-jr-become-health-secretary-he-actively-472959 <description><![CDATA[More than 15,000 doctors are urging the Senate to vote against confirming Robert F. Kennedy Jr. as the Secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/thousands-doctors-come-out-against-letting-rfk-jr-become-health-secretary-he-actively-472959</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:25:06 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>