<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>他</language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Tryptophan Supplements For Boosting Mood, Sleep And Overall Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tryptophan-supplements-boosting-mood-sleep-overall-health-472258 <description><![CDATA[Tryptophan is an essential amino acid that plays a vital role in producing serotonin, a neurotransmitter that regulates mood, sleep, and appetite. Incorporating tryptophan supplements into your routine can support relaxation, enhance sleep quality, and improve overall mental well-being, making it a popular choice for those seeking natural health support.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tryptophan-supplements-boosting-mood-sleep-overall-health-472258</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 10:07:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Air Pollution Impacts Male Fertility, Noise Harms Female Reproductive Health: Study Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-impacts-male-fertility-noise-harms-female-reproductive-health-study-warns-472285 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that long-term exposure to particulate matter from air pollution adversely affects male fertility, and noise pollution poses a significant threat to female reproductive health in women over 35.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-impacts-male-fertility-noise-harms-female-reproductive-health-study-warns-472285</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 04:21:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Heat Affects Disproportionately: Study Finds Women In 40s As Vulnerable As Men At 65]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heat-affects-disproportionately-study-finds-women-40s-vulnerable-men-65-472284 <description><![CDATA[The study found that middle-aged and older women are physiologically more vulnerable to high heat and humidity than older men, and this increased risk is not simply due to their longer lifespan.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heat-affects-disproportionately-study-finds-women-40s-vulnerable-men-65-472284</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 03:05:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Low-Carb Diets Be Nutritious? Study Says Well-Constructed Plans Even Exceed Nutrient Needs]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-low-carb-diets-nutritious-study-says-well-constructed-plans-even-exceed- Nutrition-needs-472282 <description><![CDATA[Researchers of the latest study tested the safety and efficacy of three low-carb, seven-day meal plans, specifically focusing on nutrient adequacy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-low-carb-diets-nutritious-study-says-well-constructed-plans-even-exceed- Nutrition-needs-472282</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 01:45:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Lactase Supplements For Effective Lactose Intolerance Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lactase-supplements- effective-lactose-intolerance-relief-472253 <description><![CDATA[This article reviews the best lactase supplements available for managing lactose intolerance. It evaluates their effectiveness in alleviating symptoms such as bloating, gas, and digestive discomfort.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lactase-supplements- effective-lactose-intolerance-relief-472253</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Sep 2024 09:36:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Serotonin Supplements: Top Picks For Mood And Sleep Support]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-serotonin-supplements-top-picks-mood-sleep-support-472263 <description><![CDATA[5-HTP is a powerful supplement that offers a range of health benefits, particularly for mood enhancement and sleep support. By boosting serotonin levels in the body, 5-HTP can help improve overall well-being, reduce anxiety, promote better sleep, and aid in appetite control.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-serotonin-supplements-top-picks-mood-sleep-support-472263</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Sep 2024 09:32:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Echinacea Supplements: Here Are Top Choices For Your Immunity Needs]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-echinacea-supplements-here-are-top-choices-your-immunity-needs-472255 <description><![CDATA[Immunity boosters are becoming increasingly popular as more people seek effective ways to enhance their defenses against common colds, flu, and other viral infections. If you are looking to strengthen your immune system, Echinacea, a supplement derived from the coneflower, is worth considering. Echinacea not only helps reduce the frequency of illness, but helps fight off colds, flu, and upper respiratory infections, reducing the need for antibiotics. Apart from immunity, the powerful herb supplement has broader benefits, including reducing inflammation and improving skin health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-echinacea-supplements-here-are-top-choices-your-immunity-needs-472255</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Sep 2024 09:30:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra-Processed Foods Linked To Heart Disease: Study Reveals Most and Least Harmful Items]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-foods-linked-heart-disease-study-reveals-most-least-harmful-items-472273 <description><![CDATA[While ultra-processed foods are associated with heart disease, the level of risk varies depending on the specific type of food, and not all of them have the same detrimental effects.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-foods-linked-heart-disease-study-reveals-most-least-harmful-items-472273</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Sep 2024 04:56:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Trait Keeps You Going, Reduces Risk Of Death In Old Age: Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-trait-keeps-you-going-reduces-risk-death-old-age-study-reveals-472271 <description><![CDATA[The key to a longer, healthier life may be mental resilience, the ability to adapt and cope with life's challenges.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-trait-keeps-you-going-reduces-risk-death-old-age-study-reveals-472271</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Sep 2024 03:25:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Regular Cellphone Use Tied To Heart Disease: Smokers, Diabetics At Greater Risk, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/regular-cellphone-use-tied-heart-disease-smokers-diabetics-greater-risk-says-study-472269 <description><![CDATA[The increased heart disease risk is partly due to the poor sleep, psychological distress, and neuroticism associated with mobile use, the research revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/regular-cellphone-use-tied-heart-disease-smokers-diabetics-greater-risk-says-study-472269</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:05:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Trimethylglycine (TMG) Supplements For Heart Health And Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-trimethylglycine-tmg-supplements-heart-health-wellness-472247 <description><![CDATA[Trimethylglycine (TMG) is a nutrient that supports heart health by reducing homocysteine levels, enhances liver function by aiding detoxification, and improves athletic performance through better muscle oxygenation. With its role in methylation, TMG offers significant health benefits, making it a valuable addition to a balanced wellness regimen.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-trimethylglycine-tmg-supplements-heart-health-wellness-472247</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:38:57 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>