<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Triple Protection: Flu, COVID, RSV Vaccines To Help Prevent Resurgence Of Respiratory Illnesses This Fall]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/triple-protection-flu-covid-rsv-vaccines-help-prevent-resurgence-respiratory-illnesses-this-470425 <description><![CDATA[Three vaccines against respiratory illnesses are coming this fall.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/triple-protection-flu-covid-rsv-vaccines-help-prevent-resurgence-respiratory-illnesses-this-470425</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:12:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Shows Link Between Physical Activity And Quality Of Life In Older Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-shows-link- Between-physical-activity-quality-life-older-adults-470424 <description><![CDATA[The study highlighted the importance of encouraging older adults to stay active and minimize sedentary behavior.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-shows-link- Between-physical-activity-quality-life-older-adults-470424</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:07:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Benefits Of Daytime Napping For Brain Health: Study Reveals Fascinating Insights]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-daytime-napping-brain-health-study-reveals-fascinating-insights-470423 <description><![CDATA[Taking short naps during the day may have a positive impact on the brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-daytime-napping-brain-health-study-reveals-fascinating-insights-470423</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:04:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Being Overweight Not Directly Linked To Increased Mortality Risk, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-overweight-not-directly-linked-increased-mortality-risk-study-finds-470421 <description><![CDATA[A new study claims being overweight does not translate to a higher mortality risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-overweight-not-directly-linked-increased-mortality-risk-study-finds-470421</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 19:57:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Cortisol Levels: Know The Causes, Warning Signs Of Cushing Syndrome]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-cortisol-levels-know-causes-warning-signs-cushing-syndrome-470419 <description><![CDATA[High levels of cortisol can increase the risk of weight gain, anxiety, depression, headaches, diabetes, heart disease and memory and concentration problems.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-cortisol-levels-know-causes-warning-signs-cushing-syndrome-470419</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 05:05:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Meal Timing Matter? Eating At Night May Boost Endurance, Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-meal-timing-matter-eating-night-may-boost-endurance-study-suggests-470417 <description><![CDATA[The latest study shows that restricting food intake during the active cycle – when individuals are most active and alert – offers health benefits such as weight loss and improved blood sugar control in mice.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-meal-timing-matter-eating-night-may-boost-endurance-study-suggests-470417</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 04:02:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Icodec Insulin Vs Degludec: Study Says Weekly Treatment More Effective Than Daily Injections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/icodec-insulin-vs-degludec-study-says-weekly-treatment-more- effective-daily-injections-470418 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that icodec insulin or once-weekly treatment reduces hemoglobin A1c (HBA1c) levels in diabetes better than daily injections of degludec.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/icodec-insulin-vs-degludec-study-says-weekly-treatment-more- effective-daily-injections-470418</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 02:43:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleep Deprivation Helps Depression? Study Says It May Enhance Mood In Some People]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-deprivation-helps-depression-study-says-it-may-enhance-mood-some-people-470416 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has found that one night of total sleep deprivation may help enhance mood in some healthy, as well as depressed individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-deprivation-helps-depression-study-says-it-may-enhance-mood-some-people-470416</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 01:20:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New York's $64 Million COVID-19 Vaccination App To Shut Down This July]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-yorks-64-million-covid-19-vaccination-app-shut-down-this-july-470415<description><![CDATA[The Excelsior Pass app was initially launched in 2021.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-yorks-64-million-covid-19-vaccination-app-shut-down-this-july-470415</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:13:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[North Korea Relaxes COVID-19 Mask Mandate; Crowds Gather Sans Masks In Public Places]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/north-korea-relaxes-covid-19-mask-mandate-crowds-gather-sans-masks-public-spaces-470412 <description><![CDATA[North Korea has seemingly eased its strict COVID-19 mask mandate, according to reports.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/north-korea-relaxes-covid-19-mask-mandate-crowds-gather-sans-masks-public-spaces-470412</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:09:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Impact of Indoor Air Quality in Homes on Respiratory Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/impact-indoor-air-quality-homes-respiratory-health-470409 <description><![CDATA[Indoor air quality, which is often abbreviated as IAQ, refers to the quality of air within buildings and structures (including your home). Generally speaking, when you hear IAQ being discussed, it's within the context of poor indoor air quality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/impact-indoor-air-quality-homes-respiratory-health-470409</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 10:42:37 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>