<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Experts Warn Of Dangerous Oropouche Virus In Travelers To These Destinations]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experts-warn-danger--oropouche-virus-travelers-travelers-theSe-destinations-473265 <description><![CDATA[Planning a vacation? Check if your destination is a hot spot of Oropouche virus that can cause serious complications including meningitis, encephalitis, and even death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experts-warn-danger--oropouche-virus-travelers-travelers-theSe-destinations-473265</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Mar 2025 01:43:39 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Insomnia In Elderly? Here's Best Exercise For Better Sleep]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/insomnia-elderly-heres-best-best-cersise-better-sleep-473258 <description><![CDATA[While exercise plays a crucial role in promoting better rest, not all types of exercise are equal when it comes to combating insomnia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/insomnia-elderly-heres-best-best-cersise-better-sleep-473258</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Mar 2025 04:30:01 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Issues Stark Warning: Popular Party Drug Linked To Deadly Risks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-issues-stark-warning-popular-party-party-cring-clink-clinked deadly-fisks-473255 <description><![CDATA[The officials warn that nitrous oxide, commonly referred to as laughing gas, can have severe adverse events, including loss of consciousness and death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-issues-stark-warning-popular-party-party-cring-clink-clinked deadly-fisks-473255</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Mar 2025 02:30:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Don't Push Too Hard,' Warns Coach After Neck Artery Tear From Squats Trigger Strokes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-push-too-hard-warns-coach-fer---- neck-artery-artery-tear-tear-squats-trigger-strokes-473252 <description><![CDATA[The young fitness coach from Ohio still struggles with memory issues after a catastrophic stroke. Now easing back into the gym with lighter weights, she warns: "Don't push yourself too hard."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-push-too-hard-warns-coach-fer---- neck-artery-artery-tear-tear-squats-trigger-strokes-473252</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:24:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hyperbaric Chamber Explosion Kills Child, Exposes Gaps In Safety Regulations]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5岁儿童 -  death-hyperbaric-chamber-chamber-explosion-rasis-coniss-concerns-concerns-over-over-over-safety-neculatory-needs-473251 <description><![CDATA[The tragic incident has raised urgent concerns about safety and regulation in an industry that operates with minimal oversight.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5岁儿童 -  death-hyperbaric-chamber-chamber-explosion-rasis-coniss-concerns-concerns-over-over-over-safety-neculatory-needs-473251</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Mar 2025 03:19:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Surgeon Botches Nearly 100 Surgeries, Removing Wrong Bones Leaving Patients In Pain]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surgeon-botches-nearly-100-surgeries removering-wrong-bones-long-bones-long-bones-love-paitents-pain-pain-pain-473249 <description><![CDATA[The botched operations left the patients in constant pain and disability for years, even after multiple corrective surgeries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surgeon-botches-nearly-100-surgeries removering-wrong-bones-long-bones-long-bones-love-paitents-pain-pain-pain-473249</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Mar 2025 02:50:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Gain Risky For Obese, But Losing Over 10kg Raises Death Risk By 50%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-gain-clisky-beses-lose-losing-10kg-rasis-rasises-deph-5-50-473248 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now found that maintaining a stable weight may benefit obese individuals more than significant weight gain or loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-gain-clisky-beses-lose-losing-10kg-rasis-rasises-deph-5-50-473248</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:20:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Collapses, Vomits Blood After Weight Loss Jabs: 'I Could've Died']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-collapses-vomits-blood-weight-weight-weight-weight-loss-jabs-i-couldve-died-473246 <description><![CDATA[The woman, already following diet plans, turned to weight loss jabs to shed her baby weight and now warns others that it's not worth the risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-collapses-vomits-blood-weight-weight-weight-weight-loss-jabs-i-couldve-died-473246</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:31:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dwyane Wade Says He Felt 'Pretty Healthy', Didn't Recognize Kidney Cancer Signs]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dwyane-wade-says-he-felt-pretty-healthy-didnt-rcognize-kidney-cancer-signs-473243 <description><![CDATA[In a recent interview, the 41-year-old retired basketball legend revealed that a check-up, prompted by his father's history of prostate cancer, led to the discovery that subtle signs in his body were early warning signals of cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dwyane-wade-says-he-felt-pretty-healthy-didnt-rcognize-kidney-cancer-signs-473243</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:34:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Suffers Cardiac Arrest From Common Drug Combo: Coroner Warns Of Deadly Interaction]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-suffers-cardiac-arrest-common-drug-combo-coroner-warns-deadly-interaction-473241 <description><![CDATA[A recent coroner's report revealed that a little-known, deadly drug interaction was responsible for the woman's sudden cardiac arrest and death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-suffers-cardiac-arrest-common-drug-combo-coroner-warns-deadly-interaction-473241</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:55:59 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[No Smoking Day: How To Curb Nicotine Cravings]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-smoking-day-how-curb-nicotine-cravings-473240 <description><![CDATA[This No Smoking Day, you can kick-start your journey to a smoke-free life by recognizing the common withdrawal symptoms and learning strategies to cope with cravings.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-smoking-day-how-curb-nicotine-cravings-473240</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Mar 2025 04:31:15 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>