<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Travel Pillows For Maximum Comfort And Support On Long Journeys]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-travel-pillows-maximum-comfort-support-long-journeys-472356 <description><![CDATA[A well-chosen travel pillow can make a world of difference on long journeys, offering comfort, support, and better sleep quality. Whether you're a frequent flyer or an occasional traveler, investing in the right travel pillow can turn uncomfortable trips into restful, enjoyable experiences.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-travel-pillows-maximum-comfort-support-long-journeys-472356</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Sep 2024 16:21:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Three cups of coffee daily boosts heart health, reduces cardiometabolic multimorbidity risk: study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ Three-cups-coffee-daily-boosts-heart-health-reduces-cardiometabolic-multimorbidity-risk-study-472384 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that any level of coffee and caffeine consumption could play an important protective role in all phases of cardiometabolic multimorbidity development.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ Three-cups-coffee-daily-boosts-heart-health-reduces-cardiometabolic-multimorbidity-risk-study-472384</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Sep 2024 01:18:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Childhood obesity linked to schizophrenia in adulthood: study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childhood-obesity-linked-schizophrenia-adulthood-study-472380 <description><![CDATA[Having more than the normal range of body mass index (BMI) in childhood could elevate the risk of developing schizophrenia in adulthood, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childhood-obesity-linked-schizophrenia-adulthood-study-472380</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:52:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Check electrolyte levels in people with eating disorders, study warns abnormalities increase death risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/check- electrolyte-levels-people-eating-disorders-study-warns-abnormalities-increase-death-risk-472377 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that monitoring electrolyte abnormalities in people with eating disorders is crucial, as these imbalances are linked to a significantly higher risk of death from any cause.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/check- electrolyte-levels-people-eating-disorders-study-warns-abnormalities-increase-death-risk-472377</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:31:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[MERIT Review Method: A Better Process For Better Results]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/merit-review-method-better-process-better-results-472374 <description><![CDATA[The core strength of the MERIT Review is its defined, standardized review process. Unlike the traditional system, which can be biased based on the reviewer's familiarity with the author or their academic institution, the MERIT Review Method introduces an objective evaluation criterion.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/merit-review-method-better-process-better-results-472374</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Sep 2024 15:28:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Exercise Balls For Stability, Balance And Core Strength]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-exercise-balls-stability-balance-core-strength-472354 <description><![CDATA[Yoga balls enhance balance, core strength, and posture, making them ideal for fitness and office use. They relieve back pain, support prenatal exercises, and accommodate various fitness levels. Their versatility makes them a beneficial tool for exercise, rehabilitation, and even daily activities like replacing office chairs to promote better spine alignment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-exercise-balls-stability-balance-core-strength-472354</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:37:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Smart Rings To Help You Keep A Track Of Your Fitness Parameters]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-smart-rings-help-you-keep-track-your-fitness-parameters-472350 <description><![CDATA[According to a global market research and management consulting company, Global Market Insights, the smart rings market is set to see a 24.1% growth rate and sales of $1 billion by 2032.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-smart-rings-help-you-keep-track-your-fitness-parameters-472350</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:35:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Compression Socks: Improve Circulation, Reduce Fatigue And Prevent Injuries]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-compression-socks-improve-circulation-reduce-fatigue-prevent-injuries-472352 <description><![CDATA[Compression socks enhance circulation, reduce fatigue, and support muscle recovery. Key features to consider include the level of compression, typically measured in mmHg, the material blend for stretch and breathability, and the fit to ensure all-day comfort.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-compression-socks-improve-circulation-reduce-fatigue-prevent-injuries-472352</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eli Lilly's Eczema Drug Gets FDA Approval, Injectable Treatment Available Within Weeks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eli-lillys-eczema-drug-gets-fda-approval-injectable-treatment-available-within-weeks-472371 <description><![CDATA[The new injectable drug, Lebrikizumab, branded as Ebglyss, is approved for treating atopic dermatitis in adults and children aged 12 and older who weigh at least 88 pounds.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eli-lillys-eczema-drug-gets-fda-approval-injectable-treatment-available-within-weeks-472371</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Sep 2024 03:45:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Antimicrobial Resistance Expected To Claim 39 Million Lives By 2050: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antimicrobial-resistance-expected-claim-39-million-lives-2050-study-472366 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted an interesting trend in the study: a drop in deaths from antimicrobial resistance by around 50% among children younger than 5 and an increase in the same by more than 80% among adults 70 and older.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antimicrobial-resistance-expected-claim-39-million-lives-2050-study-472366</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Sep 2024 02:52:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Finds Microplastics In Human Brain: Particles Likely Enter Through Breathing]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-micro Plastics- human-brain-articles-likely-enter-through-breathing-472363 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that these tiny floating microplastics in the air enter the brain likely through breathing.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-micro Plastics- human-brain-articles-likely-enter-through-breathing-472363</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Sep 2024 01:20:10 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>