<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Breakfast For Healthy Aging: Here's How Many Calories You Need For Morning Meal]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakfast-healthy-aging-heres-how-much-calories-you-need-morning-meal-472915 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now found that it's not only essential to have breakfast, but also to ensure that it is both high in quality and appropriate in quantity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakfast-healthy-aging-heres-how-much-calories-you-need-morning-meal-472915</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 Jan 2025 02:09:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[HMPV Cases Spike In China: Know About Highly Contagious Respiratory Illness Without A Vaccine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hmpv-cases-spike-china-know-about-highly-contagious-respiratory-illness-without-vaccine-472914 <description><![CDATA[Health officials worldwide are on high alert as China reports a surge in infections caused by human metapneumovirus (HMPV), a highly contagious respiratory virus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hmpv-cases-spike-china-know-about-highly-contagious-respiratory-illness-without-vaccine-472914</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 Jan 2025 01:09:30 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Quit Smoking? A Smartwatch App Can Make It Easier]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-quit-smoking-smartwatch-app-can-make-it-easier-472912 <description><![CDATA[A research team at the University of Bristol, England, developed an app that could detect the typical hand movements of someone holding a cigarette and alert the smoker with a message discouraging them from smoking.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-quit-smoking-smartwatch-app-can-make-it-easier-472912</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 Jan 2025 03:18:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What's Prosecco Smile? Here's How To Enjoy Wine Without Risking Teeth]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/whats-prosecco-smile-heres-how-enjoy-wine-without-risking-teeth-472911 <description><![CDATA[You don't have to give up your favorite glass to protect your smile. Here's how you can enjoy wine while keeping your teeth safe.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/whats-prosecco-smile-heres-how-enjoy-wine-without-risking-teeth-472911</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 Jan 2025 01:56:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Planning To Eat Clean In The New Year? Your Obsession With a Healthy Diet Shouldn't Turn Into Eating Disorder]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-eat-clean-new-year-your-obsession-healthy-diet-shouldnt-turn-eating-disorder-472908 <description><![CDATA[If you have already committed to eating clean in the coming year, be cautious—obsessing over healthy eating can take a toll on your mental health and potentially lead to eating disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-eat-clean-new-year-your-obsession-healthy-diet-shouldnt-turn-eating-disorder-472908</guid><pubDate> Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:06:56 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Prevent Heart Attacks Before 60: Cardiologist Shares Top 10 Tips]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/prevent-heart-attacks-before-60-cardiograph-shares-top-10-tips-472906 <description><![CDATA[In a viral TikTok video, Dr. Evan S. Levine, a cardiologist at Mount Sinai Health in Scarsdale outlines 10 practical tips, rooted in lifestyle changes and medical insights to help prevent heart attacks before 60.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prevent-heart-attacks-before-60-cardiograph-shares-top-10-tips-472906</guid><pubDate> Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:34:58 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fitness Trainer Gets Diagnosed With Rare Blood Cancer At 25 After Brushing Off Strange Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fitness-trainer-gets-diagnosed-rare-blood-cancer-25-after-brushing-off-strange-symptoms-472903 <description><![CDATA[The 25-year-old fitness trainer was diagnosed with Hodgkin lymphoma, a rare type of blood cancer after brushing off several strange symptoms for around two years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fitness-trainer-gets-diagnosed-rare-blood-cancer-25-after-brushing-off-strange-symptoms-472903</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Dec 2024 04:58:54 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Cup Might Be Brewing More Than You Expect: Tea Bags Release Billions Of Microplastics]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-cup-might-brewing-more-you-expect-tea-bags-release-billions-micro Plastics-472900 <description><![CDATA[A recent study found that a single tea bag can release more than 8 million nanoplastic particles into the drink during steeping.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-cup-might-brewing-more-you-expect-tea-bags-release-billions-micro Plastics-472900</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Dec 2024 02:49:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Holiday Weight Gain? Burn It Off With Just 150 Minutes Of Weekly Exercise]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-holiday-weight-gain-burn-it-off-just-150-mines-weekly-exercise-472896 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed a strong dose-response connection between aerobic exercise and reductions in weight, waist size, and body fat.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/worried-about-holiday-weight-gain-burn-it-off-just-150-mines-weekly-exercise-472896</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:48:13 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Improve Brain Health In The New Year: 12 Questions To Ask Your Doc]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/improve-brain-health-new-year-12-questions-ask-your-doc-472893 <description><![CDATA[The American Academy of Neurology has identified 12 key factors to protect your brain, and it all starts with a simple conversation with your neurologist or primary care physician.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/improve-brain-health-new-year-12-questions-ask-your-doc-472893</guid><pubDate> Thu, 26 Dec 2024 04:09:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eye Drops Recalled For Possible Fungal Contamination That May Affect Eyesight: FDA Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eye-drops-recalled-possible-fungal-contamination-that-may-affect-eyesight-fda-warns-472892 <description><![CDATA[Manufacturer Alcon Laboratories initiated the voluntary recall after a consumer reported foreign material inside a sealed single-use vial, which was later identified as fungal contamination.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eye-drops-recalled-possible-fungal-contamination-that-may-affect-eyesight-fda-warns-472892</guid><pubDate> Thu, 26 Dec 2024 02:04:19 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>