<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[New Deadly Virus Is Spreading Across Europe; May Cause Future Pandemic, Says WHO]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-deadly-virus-spreading-across-europe-may-cause-future-pandemic-says-who-470490 <description><![CDATA[The warmed environment has been conducive to the expansion of the habitat of ticks that can carry and transmit the nairovirus that causes CCHF.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-deadly-virus-spreading-across-europe-may-cause-future-pandemic-says-who-470490</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 05:38:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Sleep Divorce? It Turns Out A Lot Americans Are Doing It, Survey Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-sleep-divorce-it-turns-out-lot-americans-are-doing-it-survey-finds-470487 <description><![CDATA[Over a third of Americans reported opting for "sleep divorce" to accommodate their bed partner.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-sleep-divorce-it-turns-out-lot-americans-are-doing-it-survey-finds-470487</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 05:36:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Americans Transmit COVID-19 To Wild Deer, Leading To Mutated Variants: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-transmit-covid-19-wild-deer-leading-mutated-variants-study-470484<description><![CDATA[Americans may have transmitted COVID-19 to these animals hundreds of times.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-transmit-covid-19-wild-deer-leading-mutated-variants-study-470484</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 19:29:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even Slow Walks Can Help! Study Says Sitting Still Affects Quality Of Life In Elderly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-slow-walks-can-help-study-says-sitting-still-affects-quality-life-elderly-470482 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that cutting down on sedentary life, even by including slow walks in the daily routine, can help improve the mental and physical health and the overall quality of life in the elderly.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-slow-walks-can-help-study-says-sitting-still-affects-quality-life-elderly-470482</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 03:59:51 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Resistance Training May Help Delay, Relieve Symptoms Of Alzheimer's]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/resistance-training-may-help-delay-relieve-symptoms-alzheimers-470479 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has found that resistance training may help delay the onset of Alzheimer's and even relieve the symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/resistance-training-may-help-delay-relieve-symptoms-alzheimers-470479</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:30:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Guillain-Barré Syndrome: Know About The Rare Neurological Disorder That Forced Peru To Declare Emergency]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/guillain-barre-syndrome-know-about-rare-neurological-disorder-that-forced-peru-declare-emergency-470478 <description><![CDATA[Guillain-Barre syndrome (GBS) is a serious autoimmune disease that can result in muscle weakness, paralysis and even death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/guillain-barre-syndrome-know-about-rare-neurological-disorder-that-forced-peru-declare-emergency-470478</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 01:08:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Arcturus Coronavirus Strain Dominates US, Omicron Subvariants On The Rise]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/arcturus-coronavirus-strain-dominates-us-omicron-subvariants-rise-470476 <description><![CDATA[The Arcturus coronavirus strain has emerged as the leading variant circulating in the United States.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/arcturus-coronavirus-strain-dominates-us-omicron-subvariants-rise-470476</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:39:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Origins: Is There Reason To Believe The Virus Came From Wuhan Lab?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-origins-there-reason- believe-virus-came-wuhan-lab-470473 <description><![CDATA[An expert discussed the latest evidence on the lab leak origin theory of COVID-19.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-origins-there-reason- believe-virus-came-wuhan-lab-470473</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:35:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[England Records Alarming Pediatric Hospital Admissions Due To COVID-19]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/england-records-alarming-pediatric-hospital-admissions-due-covid-19-470471 <description><![CDATA[The study shed light on hospital admissions related to SARS-CoV-2 infection in pediatric patients.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/england-records-alarming-pediatric-hospital-admissions-due-covid-19-470471</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:26:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Chronic Disease Day: Healthy Habits To Prevent Long-Term Health Conditions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-disease-day-healthy-habits-prevent-long-term-health-conditions-470470 <description><![CDATA[Chronic Disease Day raises awareness about long-term health conditions that require medical attention for more than a year and restrict the daily activities of the patients.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-disease-day-healthy-habits-prevent-long-term-health-conditions-470470</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 03:49:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Sundowning? Tips To Help Dementia Patients Deal With The Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-sundowning-tips-help-dementia-病人-deal-symptoms-470468 <description><![CDATA[Some dementia patients tend to become more confused, agitated and anxious in the evenings due to a neurological phenomenon called sundowning.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-sundowning-tips-help-dementia-病人-deal-symptoms-470468</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:41:33 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>