<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一个</language><item><title><![CDATA[Florida City Leaders Vote to Eliminate Fluoride from Water Supply Because of RFK Jr.: 'I Can Get False Teeth If Needed']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-city-leaders-vote-eliminate-fluide-water-supply-because-rfk-jr-i-can-get-false-472683 <description><![CDATA[Government officials in Winter Haven City voted to eliminate fluoride from its water supply, citing Robert F. Kennedy, Jr.'s national campaign to remove it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-city-leaders-vote-eliminate-fluide-water-supply-because-rfk-jr-i-can-get-false-472683</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:19:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Walk For 10 Minutes After Every Hour Of Sitting To Reduce Blood Pressure, Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/walk-10-mines-after-every-hour-sitting-reduce-blood-Pressure-study-suggests-472681 <description><![CDATA[The study found that sitting for more than six hours per day during childhood and continuing the habit into adulthood can raise blood pressure by 4mmHg.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/walk-10-mines-after-every-hour-sitting-reduce-blood-Pressure-study-suggests-472681</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 03:10:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Resurges As Vaccination Declines, Most Deaths Among Unvaccinated Young Children: WHO, CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-resurges-vaccination-declines-most-deaths-among-unvaccinated-young-children-who-cdc-472680 <description><![CDATA[Around 10.3 million cases were reported in 2023, marking an alarming 20% increase from the previous year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-resurges-vaccination-declines-most-deaths-among-unvaccinated-young-children-who-cdc-472680</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:07:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stress During Pregnancy Linked To Higher Risk Of Epilepsy In Children]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-during-pregnancy-linked-higher-risk-epilepsy-children-472677 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed a striking 70% increased risk of epilepsy among children aged 1 to 3 when their mothers experienced continuous psychological distress during pregnancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-during-pregnancy-linked-higher-risk-epilepsy-children-472677</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:59:32 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Discovers Shocking Source of 20-Year-Old Stomach Pain: A Needle Left Inside Her During Vaginal Surgery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-discovers-shocking-source-20-year-old-stomach-pain-needle-left-inside-her-during-vaginal-472675 <description><![CDATA[A woman in Thailand recently discovered the source of her decades-long abdominal pain: a surgical needle allegedly left in her vaginal area during childbirth.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-discovers-shocking-source-20-year-old-stomach-pain-needle-left-inside-her-during-vaginal-472675</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 12:29:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[G.tec Medical Engineering's Innovative RecoveriX BCI Treatment Now Available In Hospitals &amp; Neurorehabilitation Centers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gtec-medical-engineerings-innovative-recoverix-bci-treatment-now-available-hospitals-472673 <description><![CDATA[Using recoveriX improves neuroplasticity, which helps rewire nervous pathways and replace damaged neurons that were affected by the stroke, multiple sclerosis, or Parkinson's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gtec-medical-engineerings-innovative-recoverix-bci-treatment-now-available-hospitals-472673</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 12:28:46 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI Detects Woman's Cancer After Doctors Tell Her She's Healthy, Likely Saves Her Life: 'This May Have Been My Last Mammogram']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-detects-womans-cancer-after-doctors-tell-her-shes-healthy-likely-saves-her-life-this-may-472672 <description><![CDATA[A UK woman is grateful to be alive after AI technology detected cancerous cells her doctors missed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-detects-womans-cancer-after-doctors-tell-her-shes-healthy-likely-saves-her-life-this-may-472672</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 11:40:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Intense Cold Therapy Daily May Improve Sleep Quality: Study Finds]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-intense-cold-therapy-daily-may-improve-sleep-quality-study-finds-472671 <description><![CDATA[The study found that undergoing daily cryostimulation, spending five minutes in a chamber cooled to -90°C, could improve sleep quality after five consecutive sessions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-intense-cold-therapy-daily-may-improve-sleep-quality-study-finds-472671</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 02:05:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Risk Factors Linked To Severe Stroke: Study Identifies Modifiable Lifestyle Choices, Manageable Conditions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/risk-factors-linked-severe-中风-study-identizes-modulated-lifestyle-choices-manageable-472670 <description><![CDATA[The study found that three risk factors: high blood pressure, atrial fibrillation, and smoking, not only increased the risk of stroke but were also linked to a higher risk of severe stroke.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/risk-factors-linked-severe-中风-study-identizes-modulated-lifestyle-choices-manageable-472670</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 01:16:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experimental Vaccine Shows Promising Results Against Aggressive Breast Cancer: Trial Results Reveal]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-vaccine-shows-promising-results-against-aggressive-breast-cancer-tri-results-reveal-472667 <description><![CDATA[The neoantigen DNA vaccine developed for preventing the recurrence of tumors in triple-negative breast cancer was found to be "well-tolerated" and effective in stimulating the immune system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-vaccine-shows-promising-results-against-aggressive-breast-cancer-tri-results-reveal-472667</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:35:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cut Back On Makeup During Pregnancy, Lactation: Study Links Increased Use To Harmful PFAS]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-back-makeup-during-pregnancy-lactation-study-links-increased-use-harmful-pfas-472662 <description><![CDATA[The study warns that increased use of personal care products during pregnancy and nursing is linked to higher levels of harmful chemicals such as per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS) in the blood plasma and breast milk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-back-makeup-during-pregnancy-lactation-study-links-increased-use-harmful-pfas-472662</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Nov 2024 04:33:12 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>