<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[New UTI Drug Gets FDA Approval: Alternative For Patients With Limited Antibacterial Treatment Options]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-uti-drug-gets-fda-approval-alternative-患者-limited-antibacterial-treatment-options-472596 <description><![CDATA[Orlynvah, an oral tablet from drug manufacturer Iterum Therapeutics, combining sulopenem etzadroxil and probenecid has been approved for use specifically for treating uncomplicated urinary tract infections (UTIs) in adult women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-uti-drug-gets-fda-approval-alternative-患者-limited-antibacterial-treatment-options-472596</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Oct 2024 06:01:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Stroke Day: Know Telltale Signs Of Brain Attack, Tips To Reduce Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-行程-day-know-telltale-signs-brain-attack-tips-reduce-risk-472595 <description><![CDATA[This World Stroke Day, under the theme 'Greater Than Stroke,' emphasizes the importance of awareness and proactive prevention in the fight against stroke.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-行程-day-know-telltale-signs-brain-attack-tips-reduce-risk-472595</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Oct 2024 04:09:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Suspected Lassa Fever Death In Iowa: Know Symptoms, Complications Of Rare Viral Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/suspected-lassa-fever-death-iowa-know-symptoms-complications-rare-viral-infection-472593 <description><![CDATA[The middle-aged eastern Iowa resident is believed to have contracted the infection after returning from travel to West Africa early this month.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/suspected-lassa-fever-death-iowa-know-symptoms-complications-rare-viral-infection-472593</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:00:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Nurse Married the Train Driver Who Stopped Her from Killing Herself on Railroad Tracks. She Returned the Favor by Saving His Life]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nurse-married-train-driver-who-stopped-her-killing-herself-railroad-tracks-she-returned-favor-472592 <description><![CDATA[Charlotte Lay repeatedly told Dave Lay to go to the doctor after complaining of a bad back. That visit led him to be diagnosed with testicular cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nurse-married-train-driver-who-stopped-her-killing-herself-railroad-tracks-she-returned-favor-472592</guid><pubDate> Mon, 28 Oct 2024 10:25:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[GLP-1 Drugs For Obesity Treatment Reduce Bariatric Surgeries By 25%: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/glp-1-drugs-obesity-treatment-reduce-bariatric-surgeries-25-study-472590 <description><![CDATA[The study noted that a vast majority of obese patients, strikingly 94.7%, received neither form of treatment, while 5% received GLP-1 RAs and 0.3% received surgery.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/glp-1-drugs-obesity-treatment-reduce-bariatric-surgeries-25-study-472590</guid><pubDate> Mon, 28 Oct 2024 05:26:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pistachios For Better Eyesight: Study Recommends Daily Intake To Boost Eye Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pistachios-better-eyesight-study-recommends-daily-intake-boost-eye-health-472588 <description><![CDATA[The latest study sheds light on the mechanisms behind the eye-boosting benefits of pistachios.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pistachios-better-eyesight-study-recommends-daily-intake-boost-eye-health-472588</guid><pubDate> Mon, 28 Oct 2024 03:50:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Meal Timing Matters For Diabetes: Study Recommends Time-Restricted Eating For Blood Sugar Control]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meal-timing-matters-diabetes-study-recommends-time-restricted-eating-blood-sugar-control-472586 <description><![CDATA[The researchers recommend adopting time-restricted eating as an alternative dietary strategy for diabetic patients were individualized dietary plans do not work or cannot be accessed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meal-timing-matters-diabetes-study-recommends-time-restricted-eating-blood-sugar-control-472586</guid><pubDate> Mon, 28 Oct 2024 01:56:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Understanding Traumatic Brain Injuries: Symptoms, Treatment, and Legal Rights]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/understand-traumatic-brain-injuries-symptoms-treatment-legal-rights-472584 <description><![CDATA[Traumatic brain injuries are serious, with long-term consequences for the victims. Learn the symptoms and treatment protocols to get ahead of it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/understand-traumatic-brain-injuries-symptoms-treatment-legal-rights-472584</guid><pubDate> Sun, 27 Oct 2024 21:09:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling With Hunger During Weight Loss? High-Intensity Workouts Could Be The Key]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-hunger-during-weight-loss-high-intensity-workouts-could-key-472581 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now suggest engaging in high-intensity workouts may help curb hunger more than moderate exercise, particularly in women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-hunger-during-weight-loss-high-intensity-workouts-could-key-472581</guid><pubDate> Fri, 25 Oct 2024 05:03:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Poor Sleep In 40s May Add Years To Your Brain Age: Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poor-sleep-40s-may-add-years-your-brain-age-study-finds-472579 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found that poor sleep in the middle ages is linked to accelerated brain aging in the next ten years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poor-sleep-40s-may-add-years-your-brain-age-study-finds-472579</guid><pubDate> Fri, 25 Oct 2024 04:05:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Diabetes Onset Before 40 Raises Risk Of Death To Four Times: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-onset-before-40-raises-risk-death-four-times-study-472578 <description><![CDATA[Diagnosing diabetes before 40 quadrupled the risk of early death and later onset was linked to a one-and-a-half times higher risk of death compared with the general population without the condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-onset-before-40-raises-risk-death-four-times-study-472578</guid><pubDate> Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:23:40 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>