<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Over 4 Hours Of Smartphone Use Linked To Higher Stress, Substance Use In Teens: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-4-hours-smartphone-use-linked-higher-stress-substance-use-teens-study-471178 <description><![CDATA[Participants who used a smartphone for more than four hours per day had higher rates of stress, thoughts of suicide and substance use compared to those with lesser usage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-4-hours-smartphone-use-linked-higher-stress-substance-use-teens-study-471178</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:22:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People Above 50 May Have Accelerated Aging In At Least 1 Organ; A Blood Test Could Detect It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-above-50-may-have-accelerated-aging-least-1-organ-blood-test-could-detect-it-471176 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now say around 18% of healthy adults above the age of 50 face accelerated aging in at least one of their organs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-above-50-may-have-accelerated-aging-least-1-organ-blood-test-could-detect-it-471176</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Dec 2023 03:54:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Concordant Hypertension: Researchers Say Many Couples Share High Blood Pressure]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/concordant-hypertension-researchers-say-many- Couples-share-high-blood-Pressure-471174 <description><![CDATA[Although hypertension is more common in the U.S. and the U.K., the likelihood of a wife having blood pressure when married to a person with hypertension is more prevalent in China and India. Researchers believe it could be due to cultural factors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/concordant-hypertension-researchers-say-many- Couples-share-high-blood-Pressure-471174</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Dec 2023 01:58:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Diet Soda Consumption Affect Your Liver? Study Says Excessive Intake Linked To Risk Of MASLD]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-diet-soda-conspiration-affect-your-liver-study-says-excessive-intake-linked-risk-masld-471173 <description><![CDATA[Excessive consumption of diet soda could raise the risk of metabolic dysfunction-associated Steatotic liver disease (MASLD), the most common form of chronic liver disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-diet-soda-conspiration-affect-your-liver-study-says-excessive-intake-linked-risk-masld-471173</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:25:46 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling With Stress? Consider Avoiding Fatty Food For Better Recovery]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-stress-consider-avoiding-fatty-foods-better-recovery-471171 <description><![CDATA[A new study found that consuming high-fat food could hinder the recovery of endothelial function.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-stress-consider-avoiding-fatty-foods-better-recovery-471171</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:38:36 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Early Menstruation Linked To Heightened Risk Of Type 2 Diabetes Later In Life: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-menstruation-linked-heightened-risk-type-2-diabetes-later-life-study-471170 <description><![CDATA[The study also suggests that girls who start menstruation before the age of 10 or younger, are at an increased risk of having a stroke before the age of 65.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-menstruation-linked-heightened-risk-type-2-diabetes-later-life-study-471170</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:19:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Skin Flooding? Here's What An Expert Says About The Extreme Hydration Technique]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-skin-flooding-heres-what-expert-says-about-extreme-Hydration-technique-471168 <description><![CDATA[Skin flooding is a skincare technique that promises an instant, radiant boost to the skin by layering multiple hydrating products.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-skin-flooding-heres-what-expert-says-about-extreme-Hydration-technique-471168</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:54:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bee&amp;You Rhinapi Nasal Spray: Your Gateway To Natural Nasal Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/beeyou-rhinapi-nasal-spray-your-gateway-natural-nasal-wellness-471157 <description><![CDATA[This nasal spray adopts a holistic approach to wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/beeyou-rhinapi-nasal-spray-your-gateway-natural-nasal-wellness-471157</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:40:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 6 Personalized Meal Plan Services: Tailor Your Diet For A Healthier And Happier You]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-6-personalized-meal-plan-services-tailor-your-diet-healthier-happier-you-471098 <description><![CDATA[Let's delve into the top six personalized meal planning and delivery services that combine convenience and customization.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-6-personalized-meal-plan-services-tailor-your-diet-healthier-happier-you-471098</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:39:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Yogurt For Mental Health? Study Uncovers How Fermented Food May Prevent Depression, Anxiety]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yogurt-mental-health-study-uncovers-how-fermented-food-may-prevent-depression-anxiety-471166 <description><![CDATA[A team of researchers has identified how bacteria in fermented foods such as yogurt can help manage stress and prevent depression and anxiety.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yogurt-mental-health-study-uncovers-how-fermented-food-may-prevent-depression-anxiety-471166</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 04:36:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Grief Awareness Week: Experts Share Tips To Support Someone Grieving]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-grief-awareness-week-experts-share-tips-support-someone-grieving-471164 <description><![CDATA[Many times, people genuinely want to help someone in grief, but a lack of knowledge about the process and uncertainty on how to communicate effectively can hold them back from offering support. This week, let's get some valuable insights from experts on how to help someone who is grieving.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-grief-awareness-week-experts-share-tips-support-someone-grieving-471164</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:31:33 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>