<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Eye Drops Recalled For Possible Fungal Contamination That May Affect Eyesight: FDA Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eye-drops-recalled-possible-fungal-contamination-that-may-affect-eyesight-fda-warns-472892 <description><![CDATA[Manufacturer Alcon Laboratories initiated the voluntary recall after a consumer reported foreign material inside a sealed single-use vial, which was later identified as fungal contamination.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eye-drops-recalled-possible-fungal-contamination-that-may-affect-eyesight-fda-warns-472892</guid><pubDate> Thu, 26 Dec 2024 02:04:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pregnant Woman And Baby Saved After Doctors Identify Her Bad Cough, Breathlessness Was Rare Tumor In Chest]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnant-woman-baby-saved-after-doctors-identify-her-bad-cough-breathiness-was-rare-tumor-472891 <description><![CDATA[The 26-year-old had a large tumor in her chest from stage 3 melanoma, blocking the artery to her right lung.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnant-woman-baby-saved-after-doctors-identify-her-bad-cough-breathiness-was-rare-tumor-472891</guid><pubDate> Wed, 25 Dec 2024 23:50:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[All Set For Holidays? Watch Out For Accidental Poisoning; Here's How To Keep Kids Safe]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/all-set-holidays-watch-out-accidental-poisoning-heres-how-keep-kids-safe-472889 <description><![CDATA[Taking a few simple precautions, such as those offered by the Nebraska Regional Poison Center can ensure your holidays remain stress-free, keeping your family safe from unexpected dangers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/all-set-holidays-watch-out-accidental-poisoning-heres-how-keep-kids-safe-472889</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Dec 2024 02:53:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Drinks That May Reduce Risk Of Head And Neck Cancers: How Much To Drink For Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinks-that-may-reduce-risk-head-neck-cancers-how-much-drink-benefits-472887 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed a reduced cancer risk among daily coffee and tea drinkers, including head and neck cancers, cancers of the oral cavity, and oropharyngeal cancers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinks-that-may-reduce-risk-head-neck-cancers-how-much-drink-benefits-472887</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Dec 2024 01:39:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman's Migraines, Motion Sickness Thought To Be From Phone Use Revealed Rare Brain Disorder]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/womans-migraines-motion-sickness-thought-phone-use-revealed-rare-brain-disorder-472885 <description><![CDATA[An MRI taken during a medical emergency revealed that her symptoms stemmed from a rare brain disorder from her skull pushing against the brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/womans-migraines-motion-sickness-thought-phone-use-revealed-rare-brain-disorder-472885</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:07:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dreaming of A Flat Stomach But Too Lazy? A Fitness Coach Shares 3 Simple Tips]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dreaming-flat-stomach-too-lazy-fitness-coach-shares-3-simple-tips-472882 <description><![CDATA[Dream bodies aren't just for those who spend hours in the gym; a fitness coach has created a "lazy girl guide" with three simple tips to slim the waist with minimal effort.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dreaming-flat-stomach-too-lazy-fitness-coach-shares-3-simple-tips-472882</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:38:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A British Grandma Started Speaking With an Italian Accent After Suffering a Stroke. Twist: She's Never Been to Italy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/british-grandma-started-speaking-italian-accent-after-suffering-中风-twist-shes-never-been-472879 <description><![CDATA[In addition to suddenly speaking with an Italian accent, the British grandma has found her body language and laugh have also changed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/british-grandma-started-speaking-italian-accent-after-suffering-中风-twist-shes-never-been-472879</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Dec 2024 18:02:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Promoting Covid, Flu Vaccines to Public Quietly Banned by Louisiana Department of Health: 'Unconscionable']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/promoting-covid-flu-vaccines-public-quietly-banned-louisiana-department-health-unconscionable-472877 <description><![CDATA[Louisiana public health officials are no longer permitted to promote vaccines, including those against illnesses such as COVID-19 and the flu, to members of the public in a new policy that was covertly implemented in the state.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/promoting-covid-flu-vaccines-public-quietly-banned-louisiana-department-health-unconscionable-472877</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:48:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Are Heart Attacks More Common On Christmas Day? Doctor Explains Winter Surge And Warning Signs]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-are-heart-attacks-more-common-christmas-day-doctor-explains-winter-surge-warning-signs-472874 <description><![CDATA[As the holiday season brings festive cheer and celebration, beware of a secret risk that quietly looms on Christmas Day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-are-heart-attacks-more-common-christmas-day-doctor-explains-winter-surge-warning-signs-472874</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:29:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling With Constipation? Try These Foods For Relief—One May Lower Colorectal Cancer Risk, Says Doctor]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-constipation-try-these-foods-reliefone-may-lower-colorectal-cancer-risk-says-doctor-472871 <description><![CDATA[For those tired of listening to age-old add more fiber to diet advice, here's something more specific that you can try.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-constipation-try-these-foods-reliefone-may-lower-colorectal-cancer-risk-says-doctor-472871</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Dec 2024 03:47:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Nutcracker Syndrome Puts 28-Year-Old In Excruciating Pain For Nearly A Decade, Docs Initially Dismissed It As Bad Periods]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-nutcracker-syndrome-puts-28-year-old-excruciating-pain-nearly-decade-docs-initially-472870 <description><![CDATA[The woman diagnosed with the rare and debilitating nutcracker syndrome struggles to imagine a life without pain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-nutcracker-syndrome-puts-28-year-old-excruciating-pain-nearly-decade-docs-initially-472870</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Dec 2024 01:04:51 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>