<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Diabetes, Pre-Diabetes Linked To Brain Aging, Healthy Lifestyle Counteracts The Effect: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-pre-diabetes-linked-brain-aging-healthy-lifestyle-counteracts-effect-study-472219 <description><![CDATA[The study showed that prediabetes was associated with a 0.5 increase in brain age and diabetes with a 2.3-year increase. However, by staying physically active, avoiding smoking, and moderating alcohol intake, you can significantly mitigate the impact.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-pre-diabetes-linked-brain-aging-healthy-lifestyle-counteracts-effect-study-472219</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Aug 2024 03:18:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Drug To Stop Migraine Before Onset? Study Says 73% Could Restore Normal Functioning]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-stop-migraine-before-onset-study-says-73-could-restore-normal-functioning-472216 <description><![CDATA[When taken at the onset of symptoms like sensitivity to light and sound, fatigue, neck pain, or dizziness, Ubrogepant helped 73% of migraine patients regain normal function, according to the study results.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-stop-migraine-before-onset-study-says-73-could-restore-normal-functioning-472216</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Aug 2024 01:50:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best L-Glutamine Supplements: Top Choices For Enhanced Recovery, Gut Health And Immune Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-l-谷氨酰胺-supplements-top-choices-enhanced-recovery-gut-health-immune-support-472211 <description><![CDATA[L-Glutamine is a vital amino acid that supports muscle recovery, gut health, and immune function. The best supplements offer high purity, effective dosages, and are free from unnecessary additives. Incorporating L-Glutamine into your routine can enhance overall wellness and performance, especially for athletes and those under physical stress.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-l-谷氨酰胺-supplements-top-choices-enhanced-recovery-gut-health-immune-support-472211</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:30:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Niacinamide Supplements: Top Choices To Support Your Skin Health Goals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-niacinamide-supplements-top-choices-support-your-skin-health-goals-472205 <description><![CDATA[Niacinamide, a form of vitamin B3, offers numerous benefits for skin health. It helps regulate oil production, reduce inflammation, and improve skin tone.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-niacinamide-supplements-top-choices-support-your-skin-health-goals-472205</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:29:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Obesity Raises Risk Of COVID Infection By 34%: Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-raises-risk-covid-infection-34-study-says-472209 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that obesity not only worsens the outcomes of COVID but also increases the risk for infection upon exposure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-raises-risk-covid-infection-34-study-says-472209</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Aug 2024 04:50:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Finds Reduced Academic Achievements In Kids Exposed To Prenatal Smoking]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-reduced-academic-achievements-kids-expose-prenatal-smoking-472208 <description><![CDATA[Maternal prenatal smoking puts the offsprings at a 49 % higher risk of reduced academic achievement, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-reduced-academic-achievements-kids-expose-prenatal-smoking-472208</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Aug 2024 03:10:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Mindset Could Shape Vaccine Response, Side Effects After COVID-19 Vaccination: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-mindset-could-shape-vaccine-response-side-effects-after-covid-19-vaccination-study-472207 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that the overall vaccine experience, including the immune response and side effects, may be shaped by your beliefs and assumptions about the vaccine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-mindset-could-shape-vaccine-response-side-effects-after-covid-19-vaccination-study-472207</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Aug 2024 01:30:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Preventive Healthcare Is So Important (And Why We Often Neglect It)]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-preventive-healthcare-so-important-why-we-often-neglect-it-472206 <description><![CDATA[Preventive healthcare is a crucial investment, both for individuals and for the medical system. The whole idea is to take proactive care of your body and mind, ultimately preventing or mitigating conditions that would otherwise jeopardize your health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-preventive-healthcare-so-important-why-we-often-neglect-it-472206</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:49:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best BCAAs For Muscle Growth And Recovery: Top Supplements For Peak Performance]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-bcaas-muscle-growth-recovery-top-supplements-peak-performance-472184 <description><![CDATA[Branched-Chain Amino Acids (BCAAs) are crucial for muscle repair, growth, and performance. They help reduce muscle soreness, prevent muscle breakdown, and enhance exercise endurance. BCAAs are found in high-protein foods and supplements, supporting overall muscle health and recovery.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-bcaas-muscle-growth-recovery-top-supplements-peak-performance-472184</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:05:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Moringa Supplements And Reasons To Include It In Your Diet]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-moringa-supplements-reasons-include-it-your-diet-472162 <description><![CDATA[People worldwide use moringa in their diets due to its therapeutic properties. Studies have shown that the plant is effective against several health problems.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-moringa-supplements-reasons-include-it-your-diet-472162</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Aug 2024 10:22:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Quercetin Supplements To Prevent Age-Related Diseases And Improve Overall Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-quercetin-supplements-prevent-age-lated-diseases-improve-overall-health-472187 <description><![CDATA[Quercetin is an antioxidant, especially abundant in onions and black tea, and ferulic acid, found in corn, tomatoes and rice bran.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-quercetin-supplements-prevent-age-lated-diseases-improve-overall-health-472187</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Aug 2024 10:09:19 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>