<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en</language><item><title><![CDATA[No Smoking Day: How To Curb Nicotine Cravings]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-smoking-day-how-curb-nicotine-cravings-473240 <description><![CDATA[This No Smoking Day, you can kick-start your journey to a smoke-free life by recognizing the common withdrawal symptoms and learning strategies to cope with cravings.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-smoking-day-how-curb-nicotine-cravings-473240</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Mar 2025 04:31:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Drink Poses Serious Risk For Kids Under 8, Experts Warn]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-drink-poses-serious-risk-kids-under-8-experts-warn-473238 <description><![CDATA[Researchers who reviewed 21 cases of adverse effects linked to the popular drink warn parents that they can trigger a toxic syndrome, causing loss of consciousness and a sudden drop in blood sugar levels.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-drink-poses-serious-risk-kids-under-8-experts-warn-473238</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:26:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Measles Parties' A Deadly Gamble, Officials Warn—Get Vaccinated]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-parties deadly-gamble-inficials-warnget-vaccination-473236 <description><![CDATA[Expert say going to measles parties "a foolish thing," as the virus is highly unpredictable, and there is no way to determine how severe an infection will be.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-parties deadly-gamble-inficials-warnget-vaccination-473236</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Mar 2025 03:11:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Short Sleep Harms Your Brain, But Regular Oversleeping Might Be An Even Bigger Red Flag]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/you-know-short-sleep-harms-your-brain-rain-regular-repsleepsleeping-might-even-even-bigger-red-flag-flag-473234 <description><![CDATA[Think sleeping in is harmless? New research shows that regularly getting too much sleep could be a major warning sign for your brain health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/you-know-short-sleep-harms-your-brain-rain-regular-repsleepsleeping-might-even-even-bigger-red-flag-flag-473234</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Mar 2025 01:24:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Common Lifestyle Habit In Preteens May Trigger Manic Symptoms, Researchers Find]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-common-lifestyle-habit-preteens-may-trigger-manic-symptoms-researchers-find-find-473233 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that excessive screen use in preteens through texting, watching videos, or playing video games could trigger manic symptoms in them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-common-lifestyle-habit-preteens-may-trigger-manic-symptoms-researchers-find-find-473233</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Mar 2025 05:49:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Young Woman 'Almost Died' While On Flight: Dangers Of Condition Linked To Prolonged Sitting]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-young-woman-almost-died-while-flight-dangers-condition-linked-prolonged-sitting-473232 <description><![CDATA[Diagnosed with a life-threatening blood clot in both lungs, 33-year-old content creator is now raising awareness about a deadly condition linked to prolonged sitting.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-young-woman-almost-died-while-flight-dangers-condition-linked-prolonged-sitting-473232</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Mar 2025 04:21:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[18-Year-Old Dies After Extreme Water Diet For Months: Know Signs And Risks Of Anorexia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/18岁-dies-dies-after-extreme-water-diet-months-knowns-know-signs-risks-anorexia-473230 <description><![CDATA[The teen, struggling with anorexia, had been following an extreme, unsupervised diet from YouTube, severely restricting her food intake for months.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/18岁-dies-dies-after-extreme-water-diet-months-knowns-know-signs-risks-anorexia-473230</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Mar 2025 02:44:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Snack A Choking Hazard For Kids, Pediatrician Warns: No Safe Way To Eat It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-snack-choking-hazard-kids-pediatrician-warns-no-safe-way-way-way-iat-it-473228 <description><![CDATA[A pediatrician is sounding the alarm about a hidden danger in what seems like an innocent, popular snack.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-snack-choking-hazard-kids-pediatrician-warns-no-safe-way-way-way-iat-it-473228</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Mar 2025 05:25:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Time Of Week Affect Your Risk Of Death From Surgery? Here's Worst Day For Operation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can time-week-aftect-aftect-your-cink-death-surgery-- heres-worst-day-day-operation-473225 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests an important trend known as the "weekend effect," in relation to surgeries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can time-week-aftect-aftect-your-cink-death-surgery-- heres-worst-day-day-operation-473225</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Mar 2025 03:59:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Pushes Unproven Measles Treatments Amid Surge; Experts Urge Vaccination]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-cases-spike-rfk-jr-promotes-unconventional-therapies-therapies-experts-warn-theyre-theyre-not-not-473223 <description><![CDATA[Kennedy Jr. endorsed the use of vitamin A, budesonide, clarithromycin, and cod liver oil for treating measles, claiming they produce "good results." However, health experts caution that these treatments should not replace vaccination and advise against relying on them alone.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-cases-spike-rfk-jr-promotes-unconventional-therapies-therapies-experts-warn-theyre-theyre-not-not-473223</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Mar 2025 01:39:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Safety of Tattoo Numbing Cream: What You Need to Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/safety-tattoo-numbing-cream-what-what-you-need-know-473220 <description><![CDATA[Getting a tattoo can be a painful experience, leading many to seek out tattoo numbing creams for relief. However, concerns about the safety and effectiveness of these products often arise.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/safety-tattoo-numbing-cream-what-what-you-need-know-473220</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:02:49 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>