<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>A </language><item><title><![CDATA[Having Belly Fat In Middle Age Linked To Alzheimer's Risk: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/having-belly-fat-middle-age-linked-alzheimers-risk-study-471124 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found a link between these hidden fats and changes in the brain associated with Alzheimer's, which might help to predict the condition even 15 years before the earliest symptoms appear.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/having-belly-fat-middle-age-linked-alzheimers-risk-study-471124</guid><pubDate> Tue, 21 Nov 2023 01:50:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Listeria Outbreak: Death, Preterm Delivery Reported; FDA Recalls Peaches, Nectarines, Plums Linked To Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/listeria-outbreak-death-preterm-delivery-reported-fda-recalls-peaches-nectarines-plums-linked-471122 <description><![CDATA[Eleven cases of Listeria infection, including one death and a premature delivery, have been reported across seven states, the CDC revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/listeria-outbreak-death-preterm-delivery-reported-fda-recalls-peaches-nectarines-plums-linked-471122</guid><pubDate> Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:45:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Long-Term Painkiller Use In Under 25s Raises Risk Of Mental Illness, Substance Abuse: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-term-painkiller-use-under-25s-raises-risk-mental-illness-substance-abuse-study-471121 <description><![CDATA[People with chronic pain who were on prescription painkillers were at 49% higher risk of mental illness and 82% higher risk of developing substance abuse.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-term-painkiller-use-under-25s-raises-risk-mental-illness-substance-abuse-study-471121</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 Nov 2023 03:58:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salmonella Outbreak Linked To Cantaloupes: FDA Warns Not To Eat, Sell Recalled Fruit Products]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-cantaloupes-fda-warns-not-eat-sell-recalled-fruit-products-471119 <description><![CDATA[The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has recalled the products linked to the outbreak and warned consumers not to eat, sell or serve them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-cantaloupes-fda-warns-not-eat-sell-recalled-fruit-products-471119</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 Nov 2023 01:58:54 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mysterious Respiratory Illness Sickens Hundreds Of Dogs: Here's What We Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mysterious-respiratory-illness-sickens-hundreds-dogs-heres-what-we-know-471118 <description><![CDATA[The unusual respiratory illness has been reported in many states, including Oregon, Colorado and New Hampshire. Veterinarians warn dog owners to take precautionary measures against the potentially deadly infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mysterious-respiratory-illness-sickens-hundreds-dogs-heres-what-we-know-471118</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:25:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Prematurity Day: Here's How You Can Prevent Infections In Preterm Babies At Home]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-prematurity-day-heres-how-you-can-prevent-infections-preterm-babies-home-471117 <description><![CDATA[Even after discharge from the NICU, premature babies need special attention and care at home as their bodies are sensitive and prone to infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-prematurity-day-heres-how-you-can-prevent-infections-preterm-babies-home-471117</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 Nov 2023 03:39:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nearly 450 Patients Potentially Exposed To HIV, Hepatitis At Massachusetts Hospital]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nearly-450-病人-潜在-暴露-hiv-hepatitis-massachusetts-hospital-471116 <description><![CDATA[Hospital officials said the expected infection risk from the incidents is "extremely small" and no case connected to it has been reported yet.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nearly-450-病人-潜在-暴露-hiv-hepatitis-massachusetts-hospital-471116</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 Nov 2023 01:52:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Lung Cancer Awareness Month: Expert Dispels Common Misconceptions About The Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lung-cancer-awareness-month-expert-dispels-common-misconceptions-about-disease-471115 <description><![CDATA[It is the third most common type of cancer in the U.S. Nearly 240,000 Americans will be diagnosed with lung cancer this year, according to the American Cancer Society.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lung-cancer-awareness-month-expert-dispels-common-misconceptions-about-disease-471115</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:31:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World COPD Day: Know Symptoms, Risk Factors, Ways To Prevent Chronic Lung Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-copd-day-know-symptoms-risk-factors-ways-prevent-chronic-lung-disease-471113 <description><![CDATA[People with COPD are at high risk of developing heart disease, lung cancer and other complications, including depression and high blood pressure in the lung arteries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-copd-day-know-symptoms-risk-factors-ways-prevent-chronic-lung-disease-471113</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:38:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Intermittent Fasting: A 10-Hour Eating Window May Reduce Hunger, Improve Mood And Energy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intermittent-fasting-10-hour-eating-window-may-reduce-hunger-improve-mood-energy-471112 <description><![CDATA[A recent large-scale trial showed that people who were consistent with their eating window had greater benefits, compared to those who changed them daily.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intermittent-fasting-10-hour-eating-window-may-reduce-hunger-improve-mood-energy-471112</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 01:40:47 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Over 20% Of COVID Patients Treated With Paxlovid Suffer Virologic Rebound: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-20-covid-病人-treatment-paxlovid-suffer-virologic-rebound-study-471111 <description><![CDATA[Over 20% of patients taking Nirmatrelvir-ritonavir therapy, commonly known as Paxlovid, suffer from the rebound, compared to less than the 2% chance seen in other treatment groups, a Harvard Medical School study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-20-covid-病人-treatment-paxlovid-suffer-virologic-rebound-study-471111</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:03:55 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>