<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Woman With Rare Condition Suffers Constant Arousal, Multiple Orgasms: 'It's Pain, Not Pleasure,' Know More About PGAD]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-rare-condition-suffers-constant-constant-arousal-mustiple-multiple-orgasms-ist-pain-pain-not-pleasure-know-473096 <description><![CDATA[The 36-year-old shares her story to raise awareness about this often misunderstood and stigmatized condition that has completely disrupted her life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-rare-condition-suffers-constant-constant-arousal-mustiple-multiple-orgasms-ist-pain-pain-not-pleasure-know-473096</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Feb 2025 01:37:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teen Dies From Rare Brain Tumor After Unusual Symptoms; Heartbroken Mom Urges Others To Recognize Signs]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen-dies-rare-brain-brain-tumor-after-unusual-symptoms-heartbroken-mom-urges-hothers-others-toshers-toblots-signize-signs-473093 <description><![CDATA[After years of battling the disease, the young girl passed away at the age of 16, and her heartbroken mother now raises awareness about the cancer, hoping that parents could spot the signs as soon as possible.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen-dies-rare-brain-brain-tumor-after-unusual-symptoms-heartbroken-mom-urges-hothers-others-toshers-toblots-signize-signs-473093</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:41:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fat Or Carbs? Identical Twins Followed Different Diets For 12 Weeks; Results Will Surprise You]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fat-carbs-nedical-twins-followed-diwents-diets-diets-12-weeks-results-results-will-sirprise-you-473090 <description><![CDATA[In a fascinating experiment, a pair of identical twins followed two different diets, one loaded with fat and the other with carbs, for 12 weeks. The results may surprise you.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fat-carbs-nedical-twins-followed-diwents-diets-diets-12-weeks-results-results-will-sirprise-you-473090</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:22:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stuck On Your Weight Loss Journey? Here's Nutritionist's Cheat Code To Shed Pounds In 3 Months]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stuck-your-weight-weight-loss-journey-heres-nutritionists-cheat-cheat-code-sheed-shed-und-t-bounds-3-Months-473089 <description><![CDATA[For those looking to kickstart their weight loss journey or those struggling along the way, here are some practical tips from a nutritionist.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stuck-your-weight-weight-loss-journey-heres-nutritionists-cheat-cheat-code-sheed-shed-und-t-bounds-3-Months-473089</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Feb 2025 05:18:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can't Solve A Problem? Sleep On It—It's Backed By Science, Here's Best Nap For Better Thinking]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cant-solve-problem-sleep-sleep-sleep-science-science-heres--------- best-better-better-better-better-inking-473087 <description><![CDATA[A recent study investigated how a specific type of sleep, afternoon naps, helps in creative problem-solving.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cant-solve-problem-sleep-sleep-sleep-science-science-heres--------- best-better-better-better-better-inking-473087</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Feb 2025 02:37:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ebola Outbreak In Uganda: CDC Warns Travelers Of Deadly Virus That Has No Approved Vaccines Or Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ebola-astbreak-uganda-cdc-warns-warns-travelers-deadly-virus-thathas-no-no-no-no-spraved-vaccines-vaccines-treatment-473085 <description><![CDATA[The CDC raised the alert to Level 2, urging travelers to "Practice Enhanced Precautions," against the deadly infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ebola-astbreak-uganda-cdc-warns-warns-travelers-deadly-virus-thathas-no-no-no-no-spraved-vaccines-vaccines-treatment-473085</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:55:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dad Dies Year After Brain Tumor Diagnosis, Doctor Initially Dismissed Symptoms As Stress, Accused Him Of Faking]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dad-dad-dies--fer-brain-brain-tumor-dumor-diangensis-doctor inti-intimissed-dimissed-dimissed-symbscers termants surs targcuscuscuscuscused-him-473083 <description><![CDATA[Now, his daughter is running a marathon to raise awareness and money for cancer research.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dad-dad-dies--fer-brain-brain-tumor-dumor-diangensis-doctor inti-intimissed-dimissed-dimissed-symbscers termants surs targcuscuscuscuscused-him-473083</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Feb 2025 02:29:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Declared Clinically Dead For 14 Minutes, Wakes Up To Discover She Delivered A 'Miracle Baby']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-declared-clinally-dead-14毫米 - 沃克斯 - 沃克斯 - 沃克斯 - 戴上 - 送达的麦克莱 - 巴贝-473081 <description><![CDATA[A 30-year-old mother and her unborn child were saved thanks to the timely effort of doctors at a hospital where she collapsed from cardiac arrest.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-declared-clinally-dead-14毫米 - 沃克斯 - 沃克斯 - 沃克斯 - 戴上 - 送达的麦克莱 - 巴贝-473081</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:30:52 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Never Take These Supplements Together, Says Expert: Plus, Combinations That Boost Absorption]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/never-take-take-take-supplements-together-says-expert-plus-plus-combinations-that-boost-absorption-473079 <description><![CDATA[The benefits of supplements do not just depend on what you take, but also how you take them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/never-take-take-take-supplements-together-says-expert-plus-plus-combinations-that-boost-absorption-473079</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Feb 2025 05:04:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[20-Year-Old Has Seizures, Multiple Cardiac Arrests After Energy Drink At Gym, Leaving Her On Life Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20岁的has-seizures-multiple-cardiac-arrests-after-energy-energy-energy-drink-gym-leaving-leaving-life-life-473078 <description><![CDATA[She had no diagnosed heart conditions prior to the incident. However, experts have not yet confirmed whether the energy drink contributed to the medical emergency.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20岁的has-seizures-multiple-cardiac-arrests-after-energy-energy-energy-drink-gym-leaving-leaving-life-life-473078</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Feb 2025 02:55:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Toddler Suffers Brain Damage After Swallowing Popular Toy: Now Her Mom Wants It Banned]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doddler-suffers-brain-damage-damage-fer-swallowwallow-topular-toy-toy-now-her-her-her-mom-wants-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it 473077 <description><![CDATA[A 13-month-old baby accidentally swallowed a popular sensory toy marketed as non-toxic. The ingestion led to intestinal blockage and triggered toxic brain encephalopathy, causing severe neurological complications and long-term developmental delays.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doddler-suffers-brain-damage-damage-fer-swallowwallow-topular-toy-toy-now-her-her-her-mom-wants-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it 473077</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Feb 2025 01:21:46 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>