<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medictallaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Are Hormonal Birth Control Methods Safe? Contraceptives That May Increase Risk Of Heart Attack And Stroke]]></title><link/> https://www.medictaldaily.com/are-hormonal-birth-control-mmethods-safe-contraceptives-That-May-increas-risk-heart-night-night-night-night-night-night-night-night-夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚，夜晚夜风-473112 <description><![CDATA[For those considering different contraceptive methods, the results of a recent study may help them make informed choices.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictaldaily.com/are-hormonal-birth-control-mmethods-safe-contraceptives-That-May-increas-risk-heart-night-night-night-night-night-night-night-night-夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚夜晚，夜晚夜风-473112</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:58:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Common Painkiller Use During Pregnancy Raise ADHD Risk In Kids? Here's What Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/can-common-painkiller-use-during-prapriation-raise-adhd-risk-kids-heres-heres-what study-says-says-473111 <description><![CDATA[The results showed that children whose mothers had acetaminophen in their blood during the second trimester were over three times more likely to be diagnosed with ADHD.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/can-common-painkiller-use-during-prapriation-raise-adhd-risk-kids-heres-heres-what study-says-says-473111</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:52:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Hangover? Have This Before Drinks, Says Doctor]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/worried-about-hangover-have------------ this-befor  -  drinks-says-says-doctor-473108 <description><![CDATA[Here's a simple trick to prevent the unpleasant aftermath of drinking alcohol.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/worried-about-hangover-have------------ this-befor  -  drinks-says-says-doctor-473108</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:51:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Have This Gut Healthy Snack Twice A Week, It Can Protect You From Aggressive Colorectal Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medictaldaily.com/have---this-gut-healthy-snack--week-it-can-PROTECT-YOUGGRESSPE <description><![CDATA[A new study discovered that a popular gut-healthy snack could offer protection against colorectal cancer, a finding that offers hope as cases rise, particularly among young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictaldaily.com/have---this-gut-healthy-snack--week-it-can-PROTECT-YOUGGRESSPE</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:45:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Warns: Avoid These Foods If You Take Medications, Eating This Fruit Can Even Be Toxic]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/doctor-warns-avoid-sosis-foods-f-y-tou-take-medications-theating-theating-thisthis-cann-can-can-can-can-even-even-even-even-even-even toxic-47310 <description><![CDATA[A doctor now warns that certain food items can interfere with the absorption of medications, affecting their effectiveness, or in rare cases causing toxicity when combined with pills.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/doctor-warns-avoid-sosis-foods-f-y-tou-take-medications-theating-theating-thisthis-cann-can-can-can-can-even-even-even-even-even-even toxic-47310</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:40:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Lose Weight? Nutritionist Shares Foods That Naturally Mimic Ozempic]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/want-lose-weight-nutrition-s-s-s-foods-tat-tat-tnatrally-mimic-ozempic-473104 <description><![CDATA[A nutritionist shares 8 high-quality foods that naturally mimic the effects of Ozempic by boosting satiety, balancing blood sugar, reducing cravings, and helping make fat loss easier.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/want-lose-weight-nutrition-s-s-s-foods-tat-tat-tnatrally-mimic-ozempic-473104</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Feb 2025 03:51:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[6-Year-Old's Weight Doubles In A Year, And Mom Thinks It's Lockdown Gain Before Fatal Cancer Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/6岁的sweight-doubled-double-mom-thinks-thinks-thinks-lockdown-beain-be-be-be-be-befor-fatal-cancer-diengnosis-47310 <description><![CDATA[The boy's mother now realizes his weight gain and other unusual signs were early warnings of cancer, and now shares his story to raise awareness about brain tumor symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/6岁的sweight-doubled-double-mom-thinks-thinks-thinks-lockdown-beain-be-be-be-be-befor-fatal-cancer-diengnosis-47310</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:54:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Indiana Doctors Go To Court To Keep Terminated Pregnancy Reports From Being Released To The Public]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/indiana-doctors-go-court- keep-termed-printing-pregnancy-repnancy-repports-将释放释放的public-473100 <description><![CDATA[Two abortion providers in Indiana advocating against the release of individual terminated pregnancy reports have filed a lawsuit to keep the records private.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/indiana-doctors-go-court- keep-termed-printing-pregnancy-repnancy-repports-将释放释放的public-473100</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:59:36 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is 'Lemonading'? When Life Gives You Lemons, Having This Personality Trait Helps]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/what-libonading-when-life-gives-gives-y-hou-lemans-porting-this-this-this this-this thrait-trait-helps-473097 <description><![CDATA[Researchers find scientific proof for the benefits of being playful during adversities.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/what-libonading-when-life-gives-gives-y-hou-lemans-porting-this-this-this-this-this thrait-trait-helps-helps-473097</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Feb 2025 04:49:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman With Rare Condition Suffers Constant Arousal, Multiple Orgasms: 'It's Pain, Not Pleasure,' Know More About PGAD]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/woman-rare-condition-suffers-constant-constant-arousal-mustiple-orgasmsm-note-note-not not not not not not-not not-not not-not not-not not-not not-not not-not-not-not-not-not-not-not-not-并非没有不是没有不是没有不是没有不是没有，没有不是没有，没有 - 没有 - 没有-nov-473096 <description><![CDATA[The 36-year-old shares her story to raise awareness about this often misunderstood and stigmatized condition that has completely disrupted her life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/woman-rare-condition-suffers-constant-constant-arousal-mustiple-orgasmsm-note-note-not not not not not not-not not-not not-not not-not not-not not-not not-not-not-not-not-not-not-not-not-not-not-not-并非没有不是没有不是没有不是没有，没有不是没有，没有不是没有，没有什么，没有什么</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 01:37:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teen Dies From Rare Brain Tumor After Unusual Symptoms; Heartbroken Mom Urges Others To Recognize Signs]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/teen-dies-rare-brain-tumor-tumor-after-unusual-symptoms-hendbrokent obloken-mom-ugurges-thers-thersthers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-signize-signs-473093 <description><![CDATA[After years of battling the disease, the young girl passed away at the age of 16, and her heartbroken mother now raises awareness about the cancer, hoping that parents could spot the signs as soon as possible.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/teen-dies-rare-brain-tumor-tumor-after-unusual-symptoms-hendbrokent obloken-mom-ugurges-thers-thersthers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-thers-signize-signs-473093</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:41:33 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>