<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Lack Of Deep Sleep May Raise Risk Of Dementia In Elderly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lack-deep-sleep-may-raise-risk-dementia-elderly-471049 <description><![CDATA[For people over the age of 60, getting 1% less deep sleep a year could increase the risk of dementia by 27%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lack-deep-sleep-may-raise-risk-dementia-elderly-471049</guid><pubDate> Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:45:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Autism And ADHD: Study Says Excessive Screen Time May Be A Warning Sign]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/autism-adhd-study-says-excessive-screen-time-may-warning-sign-471046 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say some people may have a genetic disposition to use screens because of autism spectrum disorder.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/autism-adhd-study-says-excessive-screen-time-may-warning-sign-471046</guid><pubDate> Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:48:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Issues Warning Against 26 Eye Drop Products; Says They Could Lead To Infections, Vision Loss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-issues-warning-against-26-eye-drop-products-says-they-could-lead-infections-vision-loss-471045 <description><![CDATA[The FDA has recommended 26 eye drop products for a recall after federal investigators found unsanitary conditions and positive bacterial test results from critical drug production areas.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-issues-warning-against-26-eye-drop-products-says-they-could-lead-infections-vision-loss-471045</guid><pubDate> Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:23:53 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is There A Medication That will Eliminate Obesity?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/there-medication-that-will-eliminate-obesity-471042 <description><![CDATA[There are two glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) receptor agonists that have been approved for the treatment of obesity in the United States: semaglutide and liraglutide. Both of these medications are injectable. The brand names for semaglutide include: Ozempic, Rybelsus, and Wegovy. The brand names for liraglutide include: Saxenda and Victoza.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/there-medication-that-will-eliminate-obesity-471042</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:07:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A New Syndrome? Common Birth Anomalies Found In Babies Born To Mothers Who Use Fentanyl]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-syndrome-common-birth-anomalies-found-babies-born-mothers-who-use-fentanyl-471041 <description><![CDATA[Researchers identified similar facial and musculoskeletal abnormalities in infants whose mothers used fentanyl during pregnancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-syndrome-common-birth-anomalies-found-babies-born-mothers-who-use-fentanyl-471041</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Oct 2023 04:57:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Traditional Chinese Medicine 'Tongxinluo' As An Add-On Therapy May Help Patients Recover After Heart Attack]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/traditional-chinese-medicine-tongxinluo-add-therapy-may-help-患者-recover-after-heart-471040 <description><![CDATA[Tongxinluo, a compound made from extracts of plants and insects, has been in use in Chinese medicine for treating heart attacks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/traditional-chinese-medicine-tongxinluo-add-therapy-may-help-患者-recover-after-heart-471040</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:21:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Vaccine Against Cocaine? Scientists Say New Jab May Help Break Cycle Of Addiction]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaccine-against-cocaine-scientists-say-new-jab-may-help-break-cycle-addiction-471037 <description><![CDATA[When tested on animals, the Calixcoca vaccine induced a significant amount of antibodies with a few side effects. Researchers are now set to begin the final stage of the trials, where it will be tested on humans.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaccine-against-cocaine-scientists-say-new-jab-may-help-break-cycle-addiction-471037</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Oct 2023 01:34:52 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[World Stroke Day: Know Warning Signs, Steps To Prevent Brain Attack]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-行程-day-know-warning-signs-steps-prevent-brain-attack-471036 <description><![CDATA[This year's theme, "Together we are #Greater Than Stroke," focuses on preventing stroke by addressing the risk factors responsible for it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-行程-day-know-warning-signs-steps-prevent-brain-attack-471036</guid><pubDate> Sun, 29 Oct 2023 06:32:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Portfolio Diet? American Heart Association Recommends It To Reduce Heart Disease And Stroke Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-portfolio-diet-american-heart-association-recommends-it-reduce-heart-disease-中风-risk-471034 <description><![CDATA[A portfolio diet is a nutritional strategy that focuses on reducing LDL, or "bad" cholesterol, a leading risk factor for cardiovascular disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-portfolio-diet-american-heart-association-recommends-it-reduce-heart-disease-中风-risk-471034</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:56:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salmonella Outbreak In 22 States Linked To Fresh Diced Onions: Know Signs Of Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-22-states-linked-fresh-diced-onions-know-signs-infection-471032 <description><![CDATA[The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has issued a warning and recall notice for fresh diced onions linked to the outbreak.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-22-states-linked-fresh-diced-onions-know-signs-infection-471032</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Oct 2023 01:21:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[ADHD Awareness Month: Expert Dispels Common Misconceptions About The Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adhd-awareness-month-expert-dispels-common-misconceptions-about-condition-471029 <description><![CDATA[Attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder is often misunderstood and sometimes, people even fail to recognize it as a real disorder.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adhd-awareness-month-expert-dispels-common-misconceptions-about-condition-471029</guid><pubDate> Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:06:01 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>