<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Beauty from Within: Top 5 Collagen Powder Drinks To Boost and Improve Skin Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beauty-within-top-5-collagen-powder-drinks-boost-improve-skin-health-471706 <description><![CDATA[Discover the secret to radiant, youthful skin with collagen power drinks – the ultimate skincare booster packed with all the goodness your skin craves.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beauty-within-top-5-collagen-powder-drinks-boost-improve-skin-health-471706</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 15:56:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women Are 40% More At Risk Of Depression During Perimenopause: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-40-more-risk-depression-during-perimenopause-study-471705 <description><![CDATA[There is a 40% increased risk of depression at the perimenopausal stage compared to the premenopausal stage, a study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-40-more-risk-depression-during-perimenopause-study-471705</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 03:56:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Control Your Anger: Study Says It Damages Blood Vessel, Raising Heart Disease Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/control-your-anger-study-says-it-damages-blood-vessel-raise-heart-disease-risk-471704 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that a brief period of anger can damage your blood vessels and elevate the risk of heart disease and stroke.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/control-your-anger-study-says-it-damages-blood-vessel-raise-heart-disease-risk-471704</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 03:18:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Combine Intense Workout With Intermittent Fasting For Fat Loss, Cardiometabolic Health: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/combine-intense-workout-intermittent-fasting-fat-loss-cardiometabolic-health-study-says-471702 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that adopting intermittent fasting with an eating period between 8 am and 4 pm, combined with high-intensity functional training during the fasting window, could lead to significant transformations in body composition and cardiometabolic measures.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/combine-intense-workout-intermittent-fasting-fat-loss-cardiometabolic-health-study-says-471702</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 02:08:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[EVL BCAA Energy: The Perfect Pre-Workout Energy Drink To Boost Exercise Productivity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/evl-bcaa-energy-perfect-pre-workout-energy-drink-boost-exercise-productivity-471684 <description><![CDATA[Introducing EVL BCAA Energy: A natural pre-workout drink with green coffee for focus, BCAAs for performance, and essential vitamins.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/evl-bcaa-energy-perfect-pre-workout-energy-drink-boost-exercise-productivity-471684</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 12:45:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[E-Coli Outbreak Linked To Organic Walnuts Sickens 12: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-walnuts-sickens-12-cdc-471699 <description><![CDATA[The outbreak linked to contaminated organic walnuts sold in bulk bins has led to 12 reported cases of illness and seven hospitalizations in California and Washington.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-walnuts-sickens-12-cdc-471699</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 04:08:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[An Omega-6 Fatty Acid Linked To Reduced Risk Of Bipolar Disorder: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-6-fatty-acid-linked-reduced-risk-bipolar-disorder-study-471697 <description><![CDATA[The new study also indicates the possibility of using dietary intervention to prevent or slow down the progression of psychiatric disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-6-fatty-acid-linked-reduced-risk-bipolar-disorder-study-471697</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 03:10:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Guidelines Recommend Mammograms at 40, Biennial Breast Cancer Screening For Women]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-guidelines-recommend-mammograms-40-biennial-breast-cancer-screening-women-471696 <description><![CDATA[The new guidelines by the U.S. Preventive Services Task Force (USPSTF) lower the screening age to include all individuals assigned female at birth who are at an average risk of breast cancer, extending beyond the previous threshold of 50.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-guidelines-recommend-mammograms-40-biennial-breast-cancer-screening-women-471696</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 01:50:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teens At Risk Of Exposure To Toxic Lead And Uranium From Frequent Vaping: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-risk-exposure-token-uranium-frequent-vaping-study-471694 <description><![CDATA[Teenagers who frequently vape may face increased exposure to harmful metals like lead and uranium, which could potentially impact brain and organ development adversely, a study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-risk-exposure-token-uranium-frequent-vaping-study-471694</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Apr 2024 04:20:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Reveals Ideal Duration You May Stand, Sit, Sleep, And Exercise For Optimal Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-ideal-duration-you-may-stand-sit-sleep-exercise-optimal-health-471693 <description><![CDATA[The researchers have identified the ideal number of hours you should spend standing, sitting, sleeping, and engaging in physical activities for optimal heart health and diabetic control.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-ideal-duration-you-may-stand-sit-sleep-exercise-optimal-health-471693</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:38:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Lifestyle At 40 Adds 5 Years To Life, Offsets Genetic Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-lifestyle-40-adds-5-years-life-offsets-genic-risk-study-471691 <description><![CDATA[People with a strong genetic risk of shorter lifespans could add almost 5.5 years to their lives if they adopt a healthy lifestyle at 40, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-lifestyle-40-adds-5-years-life-offsets-genic-risk-study-471691</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Apr 2024 02:15:02 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>