<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA[International Nystagmus Day: Know All About The Dancing Eye Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-nystagmus-day-know-all-about-dancing-eye-syndrome-470204 <description><![CDATA[Nystagmus is a condition that results in uncontrolled eye movements causing issues with vision, depth perception, balance and coordination.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-nystagmus-day-know-all-about-dancing-eye-syndrome-470204</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 03:15:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Low-Dose Aspirin Linked To Anemia, Blood Iron Decline In Older Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-dose-aspirin-linked-anemia-blood-iron-decline-older-adults-study-470198 <description><![CDATA[Low-dose aspirin use reduces iron levels, causing anemia, a condition characterized by low red blood cell count.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-dose-aspirin-linked-anemia-blood-iron-decline-older-adults-study-470198</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 02:18:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Says Night Owls Likely To Die Sooner, But Not Due To Late Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-night-owls-likely-die-sooner-not-due-late-sleep-470201 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that late sleepers are likely to die sooner, not due to late bedtime, but from smoking and drinking-related disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-night-owls-likely-die-sooner-not-due-late-sleep-470201</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:39:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[2 Cancer Drug Trials Put On Hold After 6 Participants Died During Testing]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/2-cancer-drug-trials-put-hold-after-6-participants-died-during-testing-470197 <description><![CDATA[The two unrelated clinical trials were put on hold after six participants, including one child, died while testing new cancer drugs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/2-cancer-drug-trials-put-hold-after-6-participants-died-during-testing-470197</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:00:45 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Loneliness Increase Premature Death Risk?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-loneliness-increase-premature-death-risk-470194 <description><![CDATA[Loneliness and social isolation have been associated with a higher risk of early death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-loneliness-increase-premature-death-risk-470194</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:32:42 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[West Nile Virus: What You Need To Know To Stay Safe]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-virus-what-you-need-know-stay-safe-470193 <description><![CDATA[Here's everything you need to know to stay safe amid the mosquito season.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-virus-what-you-need-know-stay-safe-470193</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:21:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exercise Alone Not Effective For Weight Loss, Expert Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-alone-not-effective-weight-loss-expert-says-470191 <description><![CDATA[An expert has challenged the idea that exercise could help ensure significant weight loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-alone-not-effective-weight-loss-expert-says-470191</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:10:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Did US Help Fund Coronavirus Research In Controversial Wuhan Lab?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/did-us-help-fund-coronavirus-research-controversial-wuhan-lab-470188 <description><![CDATA[Congress has mandated the declassification of information related to the COVID-19 pandemic's origin.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/did-us-help-fund-coronavirus-research-controversial-wuhan-lab-470188</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:01:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Age Of Autism Diagnosis Has No Impact On Quality of Life, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/age-autism-diagnosis-has-no-impact-quality-life-study-finds-470185 <description><![CDATA["For some people, finding out they are autistic sooner rather than later was linked to a better quality of life. For others, finding out later was better. Overall, there was no overall link between the age they found out and their quality of life," one of the researchers said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/age-autism-diagnosis-has-no-impact-quality-life-study-finds-470185</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 05:50:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gas Stoves Emit Cancer-Causing Benzene, Study Shows; Here's What You Can Do About It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gas-stoves-emit-cancer-causing-benzene-study-shows-heres-what-you-can-do-about-it-470182 <description><![CDATA[The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention warns that prolonged exposure to benzene can lead to the development of blood cancer. Gas stoves have also gained notoriety for potentially causing childhood health issues due to benzene leakage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gas-stoves-emit-cancer-causing-benzene-study-shows-heres-what-you-can-do-about-it-470182</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 04:59:44 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tips To Take Care Of Your Eyes While Traveling]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tips-take-care-your-eyes-while-traveling-470179 <description><![CDATA[Taking good care of the eyes can make travel more enjoyable.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tips-take-care-your-eyes-while-traveling-470179</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 03:34:39 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>