<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Meat Allergy From Tick Spit Is Getting Common, CDC Warns; Know Symptoms Of Alpha-Gal Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meat-allergy-tick-spit-getting-common-cdc-warns-know-symptoms-alpha-gal-syndrome-470575 <description><![CDATA[Around 110,000 suspected cases of alpha-gal syndrome have been identified in the U.S., but officials believe the actual number of cases might be more than 450,000.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meat-allergy-tick-spit-getting-common-cdc-warns-know-symptoms-alpha-gal-syndrome-470575</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 01:55:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Hepatitis Day: Types Of Liver Infections And Tips To Prevent Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-hepatitis-day-types-liver-infections-tips-prevent-them-470573<description><![CDATA[The theme for this year is "one life, one liver."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-hepatitis-day-types-liver-infections-tips-prevent-them-470573</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:35:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Korean Red Ginseng Shows Promise in Alleviating Alcohol Addiction Effects: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/korean-red-ginseng-shows-promise-alleviating-alcohol-addiction-effects-study-470571 <description><![CDATA[Ginseng, a remarkable Chinese herb, could reduce alcohol addiction by targeting specific brain pathways and reducing inflammation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/korean-red-ginseng-shows-promise-alleviating-alcohol-addiction-effects-study-470571</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:15:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women Tend To Get Risky On Stairs; Researchers Identify Behaviors In Young Adults That Result In Fall]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-tend-get-risky-stairs-researchers-identify-behaviors-young-adults-that-result-fall-470570 <description><![CDATA[The researchers have identified eight risky behaviors that increased the risk of falls from stairs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-tend-get-risky-stairs-researchers-identify-behaviors-young-adults-that-result-fall-470570</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 02:43:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Improving Gut Health May Help Slow Progression Of HIV: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/improving-gut-health-may-help-slow-progression-hiv-study-470567 <description><![CDATA[The study has revealed that the root cause of HIV progression and the key to recovery could be gut health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/improving-gut-health-may-help-slow-progression-hiv-study-470567</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 01:10:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[MIND Diet May Enhance Focus, Cognitive Performance In Young Students: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mind-diet-may-enhance-focus-cognitive-performance-young-students-study-470564 <description><![CDATA[The MIND diet improves focus and brain health in students while preventing cognitive decline in older adults, researchers say.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mind-diet-may-enhance-focus-cognitive-performance-young-students-study-470564</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 05:55:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[8 Healthy Lifestyle Habits That Could Add More Than 20 Years To Your Life]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-healthy-lifestyle-habits-that-c​​ould-add-more-20-years-your-life-470561 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has specifically identified eight lifestyle habits that when adopted by the middle ages, can improve longevity by more than 20 years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-healthy-lifestyle-habits-that-c​​ould-add-more-20-years-your-life-470561</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 04:41:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[An Unusual Type Of Red Wine Can Improve Skin Elasticity, Slow Aging, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unusual-type-red-wine-can-improve-skin-elasticity-slow-aging-study-finds-470560 <description><![CDATA[Drinking dealcoholized muscadine wine may help improve elasticity and make the skin look younger.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unusual-type-red-wine-can-improve-skin-elasticity-slow-aging-study-finds-470560</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 02:16:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Allergic March? Study Says Kids With Eczema May Develop More Allergies As They Grow]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-allergic-march-study-says-kids-eczema-may-develop-more-allergies-they-grow-470558 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say the development of allergies in kids follow a predictable pattern, called an "allergic march."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-allergic-march-study-says-kids-eczema-may-develop-more-allergies-they-grow-470558</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 01:31:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Omega-3 Fatty Acid Linked To Lower Risk Of Age-Related Hearing Loss, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-fatty-acid-linked-lower-risk-age-lated-hearing-loss-study-finds-470556 <description><![CDATA[New research shows that higher levels of docosahexaenoic acid may help reduce hearing challenges in older adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-fatty-acid-linked-lower-risk-age-lated-hearing-loss-study-finds-470556</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 04:51:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Olive Oil For Brain Health? Study Says It Could Lower Risk Of Death From Dementia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/olive-oil-brain-health-study-says-it-could-lower-risk-death-dementia-470555 <description><![CDATA[A new study shows that olive oil is not just beneficial for the heart but can also improve brain health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/olive-oil-brain-health-study-says-it-could-lower-risk-death-dementia-470555</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:57:30 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>