<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Never Take These Supplements Together, Says Expert: Plus, Combinations That Boost Absorption]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/never-take-take-take-supplements-together-says-expert-plus-plus-combinations-that-boost-absorption-473079 <description><![CDATA[The benefits of supplements do not just depend on what you take, but also how you take them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/never-take-take-take-supplements-together-says-expert-plus-plus-combinations-that-boost-absorption-473079</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Feb 2025 05:04:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[20-Year-Old Has Seizures, Multiple Cardiac Arrests After Energy Drink At Gym, Leaving Her On Life Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20岁的has-seizures-multiple-cardiac-arrests-after-energy-energy-energy-drink-gym-leaving-leaving-life-life-473078 <description><![CDATA[She had no diagnosed heart conditions prior to the incident. However, experts have not yet confirmed whether the energy drink contributed to the medical emergency.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20岁的has-seizures-multiple-cardiac-arrests-after-energy-energy-energy-drink-gym-leaving-leaving-life-life-473078</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Feb 2025 02:55:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Toddler Suffers Brain Damage After Swallowing Popular Toy: Now Her Mom Wants It Banned]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doddler-suffers-brain-damage-damage-fer-swallowwallow-topular-toy-toy-now-her-her-her-mom-wants-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it 473077 <description><![CDATA[A 13-month-old baby accidentally swallowed a popular sensory toy marketed as non-toxic. The ingestion led to intestinal blockage and triggered toxic brain encephalopathy, causing severe neurological complications and long-term developmental delays.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doddler-suffers-brain-damage-damage-fer-swallowwallow-topular-toy-toy-now-her-her-her-mom-wants-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it-it 473077</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Feb 2025 01:21:46 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Who Burned His Thumb While Cooking Forced To Amputate Both Legs Due To Sepsis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-who-burned-his-thumb-thumb-while-cooking-forced-amputate-amputate-both-legs-legs-due-sepsis-473076 <description><![CDATA[What started as a small burn on his thumb while cooking dinner during a camping trip turned into a life-threatening ordeal for a 40-year-old Colorado man.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-who-burned-his-thumb-thumb-while-cooking-forced-amputate-amputate-both-legs-legs-due-sepsis-473076</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Feb 2025 04:19:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Ailment Linked To Higher Suicide Risk: Know Type That Poses Greatest Danger]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-ailment-link----------------------- know-type-thut-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-greatest-danger-473074 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests a troubling link between a common ailment and a significantly higher risk of suicide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-ailment-link----------------------- know-type-thut-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-that-greatest-danger-473074</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Feb 2025 02:19:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman's Vape Explodes, Leaving Her 'Looking Like A Zombie': Now She's Warning Others To Quit]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/womans-vape-explodes-leaving-her-her------ zombie-now-now-shes-warning-bothers-quit-473071 <description><![CDATA[The 32-year-old Alabama woman, a former avid vaper, now warns others of the hidden dangers of vaping after the terrifying incident left her permanently scarred.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/womans-vape-explodes-leaving-her-her------ zombie-now-now-shes-warning-bothers-quit-473071</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Feb 2025 01:21:44 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Republican Anti-Abortion Bill May Block Access to Chemotherapy, Life-Saving Surgeries in Wyoming: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/republican-anti-aforti--bill-bill-may-block-access-chemotheraphy-shoper-life-sasve-save------------ bill-access-chemotheraphy-fife-fife-save-save-save-save-surgeries-wyoming-report-473069 <description><![CDATA[A Republican bill seeking to challenge abortion access may also block access to chemotherapy and life-saving surgeries in Wyoming.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/republican-anti-aforti--bill-bill-may-block-access-chemotheraphy-shoper-life-sasve-save------------ bill-access-chemotheraphy-fife-fife-save-save-save-save-surgeries-wyoming-report-473069</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Feb 2025 10:23:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[20-Year-Old Mother Dies Of Asphyxiation At Her Child's Birthday: A Common Party Trick Turns Deadly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20岁的莫特 -  dies-asphyxiation-her-childs-birthday-day-common-party-party-trick-trick-trick-turns therns therns neweadly-473067 <description><![CDATA[The family of the young mother along with the coroner are issuing a stark warning about the dangers of this seemingly harmless party trick that claimed the life of a young mother.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20岁的莫特 -  dies-asphyxiation-her-childs-birthday-day-common-party-party-trick-trick-trick-turns therns therns neweadly-473067</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:44:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Never Fly With A Cold: It's Not Just About Spreading It, Pilot Explains Ear Barotrauma]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/never-fly-cold-its-not-just-just-about-spreading-it-pilot-explains-ear-barotrauma-473064 <description><![CDATA[While traveling with a common cold may seem harmless, a pilot advises against it, as it may put you at risk of ear barotrauma, which has the potential to cause hearing loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/never-fly-cold-its-not-just-just-about-spreading-it-pilot-explains-ear-barotrauma-473064</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Feb 2025 02:21:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Loses His 'Land Legs' After 25 Years In Cruise Ships: Know About This Rare Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-loses-his-land-legs-after-25年 - 克鲁斯船-CRUISE-SHIPS-KNOW-ABOUT-ABOUT-THIS-RARE SYNDROME-473061 <description><![CDATA[The long stint at sea has led to a rare health condition called Mal de débarquement syndrome (MdDS).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-loses-his-land-legs-after-25年 - 克鲁斯船-CRUISE-SHIPS-KNOW-ABOUT-ABOUT-THIS-RARE SYNDROME-473061</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Feb 2025 01:53:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Simple Oral Hygiene Habit May Help Protect You From Stroke]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-simple-oral-hygiene-habit-may-help-protect-you-stroke-stroke-473060 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that flossing at least once a week can significantly reduce stroke risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-simple-oral-hygiene-habit-may-help-protect-you-stroke-stroke-473060</guid><pubDate> Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:01:00 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>