<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>A </language><item><title><![CDATA[Food Allergies Affect Heart Health? Study Says Antibodies To Cow's Milk Elevate Cardiovascular Mortality Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/food-allergies-affect-heart-health-study-says-antibodies-cows-milk-elevate-cardioangio-471092 <description><![CDATA[The strongest link with cardiovascular death was found in people who had the antibodies but continued to consume the food regularly.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/food-allergies-affect-heart-health-study-says-antibodies-cows-milk-elevate-cardioangio-471092</guid><pubDate> Fri, 10 Nov 2023 02:22:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sitting Too Much? Any Activity, Even Sleeping, Is Better For Your Heart Health Than That]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sitting-too-much-any-activity-even-sleeping-better-your-heart-health-that-471090 <description><![CDATA[The study found that replacing sedentary behavior, at least for five minutes a day, with moderate exercise brought in maximum heart health benefits, followed by light activity, standing, and sleeping.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sitting-too-much-any-activity-even-sleeping-better-your-heart-health-that-471090</guid><pubDate> Fri, 10 Nov 2023 01:08:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Regular Marijuana Use Linked To Elevated Risk Of Heart Attack, Stroke]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/regular-marijuana-use-linked-elevated-risk-heart-attack-中风-471087 <description><![CDATA[People who use marijuana regularly are at increased risk of heart failure, stroke and heart attack, according to two independent preliminary studies that will be presented at the American Heart Association's Scientific Sessions 2023.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/regular-marijuana-use-linked-elevated-risk-heart-attack-中风-471087</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:44:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Contraceptive Pills May Affect Women's Brains, Impair Fear Regulating Regions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/contraceptive-pills-may-affect-womens-brains-impair-fear-regulate-regions-471085 <description><![CDATA[The study found that the part of the brain associated with emotion regulation, including fear and anxiety extinction, was thinner in women who used combined oral contraceptives compared to men.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/contraceptive-pills-may-affect-womens-brains-impair-fear-regulate-regions-471085</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Nov 2023 02:37:58 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Obesity In Teens Raises Risk Of 17 Types Of Cancers: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-teens-can-lead-17-types-cancers-study-471083 <description><![CDATA[The link between high BMI and cancers was strongest for abdominal cancers, including esophagus, stomach and kidney cancers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-teens-can-lead-17-types-cancers-study-471083</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:21:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women With PCOS, Painful Periods At High Risk Of Cardiovascular Diseases: Studies]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-pcos-painful-periods-high-risk-cardioangio-diseases-studies-471080 <description><![CDATA[The studies that evaluated the link between the common reproductive health conditions and cardiovascular disease will be presented at the American Heart Association's Scientific Sessions 2023 this month.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-pcos-painful-periods-high-risk-cardioangio-diseases-studies-471080</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 03:14:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Newborn Syphilis Cases Surging At Alarming Rate; CDC Analysis Shows Tenfold Increase In Last Decade]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/newborn-syphilis-cases-surging-alarming-rate-cdc-analysis-shows-tenfold-increase-last-decade-471078 <description><![CDATA[Health officials believe timely testing and adequate treatment during pregnancy could have prevented nine out of 10 newborn syphilis cases in 2022.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/newborn-syphilis-cases-surging-alarming-rate-cdc-analysis-shows-tenfold-increase-last-decade-471078</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 02:43:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Diabetes Month: Expert Shares Diet Tips To Effectively Manage Blood Sugar]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-diabetes-month-expert-shares-diet-tips- effectively-manage-blood-sugar-471077 <description><![CDATA[November is marked as National Diabetes Month to raise awareness about diabetes and provide valuable information to patients on ways to effectively manage their health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-diabetes-month-expert-shares-diet-tips- effectively-manage-blood-sugar-471077</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:43:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Says High Levels Of Pollution Elevates Parkinson's Risk; Know The Hotspots In US]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-poor-air-quality-elevates-parkinsons-risk-know-pollution-hotspots-us-471075 <description><![CDATA[People who live in areas with high levels of air pollution are at 56% higher risk of developing the condition compared to those living in regions with better air quality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-poor-air-quality-elevates-parkinsons-risk-know-pollution-hotspots-us-471075</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 02:40:52 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Heart Health Linked To Biological Aging; Here's How You Can Grow Younger By 6 Years]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-health-linked-biological-aging-heres-how-you-can-grow-younger-6-years-471073 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that those who follow "Life's Essential 8," the heart-healthy behaviors recommended by the American Heart Association, can delay the biological aging process by six years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-health-linked-biological-aging-heres-how-you-can-grow-younger-6-years-471073</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 01:51:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women Who Get False-Positive Mammograms More Likely To Develop Breast Cancer Later: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-who-get-false-positive-mammograms-more-likely-develop-breast-cancer-later-study-471071 <description><![CDATA[The link between false-positive mammograms and future breast cancer risk is highest among women between 60 and 75 years old and those with low breast density.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-who-get-false-positive-mammograms-more-likely-develop-breast-cancer-later-study-471071</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:14:53 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>