<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>母亲</title><link/>https：/www.was.com.com<description>在救世主上</description><language>曾是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Stick To Your Resolutions? It Takes At Least Two Months To Build A Habit]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stick-your-resolutions-it-takes-least-two-two-months-build-habit-473055 <description><![CDATA[The researchers believe that the current findings would help "people set realistic expectations" about habit formation, encouraging them to stay committed even if progress feels slow.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stick-your-resolutions-it-takes-least-two-two-months-build-habit-473055</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Jan 2025 05:10:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Food Noise? Weight Loss Doctor Shares Ways To Manage It Without Medications]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-food-noise-weight-weight-loss-doctor-shares-ways-manage-manage-it-without-without-without-473053 <description><![CDATA[Struggling to lose weight but constantly thinking about food? You might be dealing with "food noise"]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-food-noise-weight-weight-loss-doctor-shares-ways-manage-manage-it-without-without-without-473053</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:23:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Neuroscientist Warns: 3 Drinks That May Harm Your Memory, And What To Sip Instead]]></title><link/> hetps：/wowing。 <description><![CDATA[What you drink could be quietly affecting your brain health, warns a leading neuroscientist specialized in Alzheimer's prevention.]]></description><guid> hetps：/wowing。</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Jan 2025 00:42:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Kansas Tuberculosis Outbreak That Killed Two, Sickened Dozens, Among Largest In U.S. History]]></title><link/> httops：/wowwins.damicy.com/salgs-to-to-to-to-build-out-out-screen-screen-scert-scert-door-door-doubs-onsor-nobroken-broken-ther-ongors 730。 <description><![CDATA[As of Jan. 24, the Kansas Department of Health and Environment reported 67 confirmed cases of active tuberculosis, along with 79 latent infections.]]></description><guid> httops：/wowwins.damicy.com/salgs-to-to-to-to-build-out-out-screen-screen-scert-scert-door-door-doubs-onsor-nobroken-broken-ther-ongors 730。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Jan 2025 04:56:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is 1:1 Diet? Woman Drops 83 Pounds After Declining Gastric Sleeve, Feels Like 'Walking On Air']]></title><link/> httops：/wown <description><![CDATA[Instead of opting for gastric sleeve surgery, which she feared due to potential side effects, she chose a simple diet—a decision she calls the "best" she's ever made, completely transforming her life.]]></description><guid> httops：/wown</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:14:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[29-Year-Old Died After Chiropractor Adjusted 'Crack In Her Neck', Coroner Questions Lack Of Medical History Review]]></title><link/> httops：/wowing。 <description><![CDATA[A recent coroner's report on the patient's death is raising concerns over whether chiropractors should be required to review patients' medical histories before treatment.]]></description><guid> httops：/wowing。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:59:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Curex Is Making Food Allergy Care Easier Than Ever, Backed by Science]]></title><link/> httops：/wowmical.com <description><![CDATA[Fewer severe reactions and the ability to enjoy meals without fear are two key benefits of using SLIT drops for food allergies.]]></description><guid> httops：/wowmical.com</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 12:29:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Ergin's Holistic Diabetes Care: How SugarMD Is Empowering Women To Take Control]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-ergins-holistic-daibetes-care-how-sugarmd-empowering-womentake-take-take-control-473041 <description><![CDATA[SugarMD offers a lifeline of hope for women seeking a holistic approach. This transformative care is now reaching women worldwide, including those in Australia, where access to innovative diabetes solutions is increasingly vital.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-ergins-holistic-daibetes-care-how-sugarmd-empowering-womentake-take-take-control-473041</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 12:24:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Got a Desk Job? Skip The Hours In Gym—Doctor Recommends Doing This Every 45 Minutes]]></title><link/> httops：/wowling.dmicaly.com/sko-skob-skop-gymo-gymo-gymy-sody-sody-sings 47303。 <description><![CDATA[According to a well-known doctor with millions of followers on social media, the secret may lie in just one simple task that you can do every 45 minutes.]]></description><guid> httops：/wowling.dmicaly.com/sko-skob-skops-gymo-socomn-sody-仅47303。</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 05:13:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Think Being Overweight Hurts Happiness? Study Reveals Surprising Twist]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/think-being-being-beover-warts-happiness-study-reveals-scrprising-twist-473038 <description><![CDATA[A recent study reveals that the relationship between body weight and emotional well-being is more complex than previously thought.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/think-being-being-beover-warts-happiness-study-reveals-scrprising-twist-473038</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 02:45:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is LATE? Know All About Memory Loss Condition Often Mistaken For Alzheimer's]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-late-know-know-all-about-memory-loss-condition-forten-misten-mistaken-alzheimers-473035 <description><![CDATA[Researchers are now sounding the alarm about LATE, a little-known memory loss condition that closely resembles Alzheimer's.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-late-know-know-all-about-memory-loss-condition-forten-misten-mistaken-alzheimers-473035</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 01:07:50 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>