<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[This Common Lifestyle Habit In Preteens May Trigger Manic Symptoms, Researchers Find]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-common-lifestyle-habit-preteens may-manic-sympoms-sympoms-researchers-find-473233 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that excessive screen use in preteens through texting, watching videos, or playing video games could trigger manic symptoms in them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-common-lifestyle-habit-preteens may-manic-sympoms-sympoms-researchers-find-473233</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Mar 2025 05:49:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Young Woman 'Almost Died' While On Flight: Dangers Of Condition Linked To Prolonged Sitting]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthyy-young-woman--------------------------------------------------条件挂钩 - 链接 -  47323232323232323232322 <description><![CDATA[Diagnosed with a life-threatening blood clot in both lungs, 33-year-old content creator is now raising awareness about a deadly condition linked to prolonged sitting.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthyy-young-woman--------------------------------------------------条件挂钩 - 链接 -  47323232323232323232322</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Mar 2025 04:21:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[18-Year-Old Dies After Extreme Water Diet For Months: Know Signs And Risks Of Anorexia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/18岁-dies--afeter-extreme-water-diet-months-know-signs-signs-signs-signs-anorexia-473230 <description><![CDATA[The teen, struggling with anorexia, had been following an extreme, unsupervised diet from YouTube, severely restricting her food intake for months.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/18岁-dies--afeter-extreme-water-diet-months-know-signs-signs-signs-signs-anorexia-473230</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Mar 2025 02:44:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Snack A Choking Hazard For Kids, Pediatrician Warns: No Safe Way To Eat It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/populalar-snack-choking-hazard-kids-petiatrician-warns-no-safe-way-way-way-way-eat-it-47328 <description><![CDATA[A pediatrician is sounding the alarm about a hidden danger in what seems like an innocent, popular snack.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/populalar-snack-choking-hazard-kids-petiatrician-warns-no-safe-way-way-way-way-eat-it-47328</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Mar 2025 05:25:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Time Of Week Affect Your Risk Of Death From Surgery? Here's Worst Day For Operation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-tetime-week-aftect-your----危险手术 - 卫生纪念日 - 播放日期-47325 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests an important trend known as the "weekend effect," in relation to surgeries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-tetime-week-aftect-your----危险手术 - 卫生纪念日 - 播放日期-47325</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Mar 2025 03:59:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Pushes Unproven Measles Treatments Amid Surge; Experts Urge Vaccination]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-cases-spike-rfk-jr-promotes-unconvental-therapies-therapies-experts-warn-theyre-neyre-ney-not-47323 <description><![CDATA[Kennedy Jr. endorsed the use of vitamin A, budesonide, clarithromycin, and cod liver oil for treating measles, claiming they produce "good results." However, health experts caution that these treatments should not replace vaccination and advise against relying on them alone.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-cases-spike-rfk-jr-promotes-unconvental-therapies-therapies-experts-warn-theyre-neyre-ney-not-47323</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Mar 2025 01:39:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Safety of Tattoo Numbing Cream: What You Need to Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/safety-tattoo-numbing-cream-what-what-you-need-know-473220 <description><![CDATA[Getting a tattoo can be a painful experience, leading many to seek out tattoo numbing creams for relief. However, concerns about the safety and effectiveness of these products often arise.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/safety-tattoo-numbing-cream-what-what-you-need-know-473220</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:02:49 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teen Undergoes Complex Surgery To Remove Extremely Rare Parasitic Twin Attached To His Stomach]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen--sendergoes-complex-surgery-remover-extremely-arre-parasitic-twin actathed-twin-twin-his-starch-starch-473217 <description><![CDATA[The underdeveloped 30-pound twin, which consisted of two fully formed legs, buttocks, and external genitalia, grew directly from the teen's abdomen.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen--sendergoes-complex-surgery-remover-extremely-arre-parasitic-twin actathed-twin-twin-his-starch-starch-473217</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:52:46 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Simple Change In Your Drinking Habit Can Cut Microplastics By 90%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-simple-change-your-drinking-habit-can-cut-cut-microplastics-90-473215 <description><![CDATA[A scientific paper suggests that switching to filtered tap water from bottled water can reduce the intake of microplastics from 90,000 to 4,000 particles each year,]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-simple-change-your-drinking-habit-can-cut-cut-microplastics-90-473215</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Mar 2025 02:11:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eureka Moment: Scientists Find How A Common Low-Cost Drug May Prevent Cancer From Spreading]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eureka-moment-scientists-find-how-common-low-cost-cost-drug-may-prevent-spreding-473214 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that aspirin works against cancer spread by stimulating the immune system, a finding they made by chance while investigating the process of cancer spread.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eureka-moment-scientists-find-how-common-low-cost-cost-drug-may-prevent-spreding-473214</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:49:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump Applauds 13-Year-Old Cancer Survivor After Slashing Funding for Pediatric Cancer Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trump-applauds-13岁，Cancer-survivor-surver-s-Slashing-slashing-slashing-pediatric-cancer-cancer-research-473212 <description><![CDATA[President Donald Trump honored and applauded a young cancer survivor during his recent joint address to Congress despite his numerous attempts to cut funding for healthcare, including pediatric cancer research.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trump-applauds-13岁，Cancer-survivor-surver-s-Slashing-slashing-slashing-pediatric-cancer-cancer-research-473212</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:42:57 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>