<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[California Norovirus Outbreak: Over 200 Cases Reported; Officials Warn To Avoid Eating Raw Oysters From Mexico]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-norovirus-outbreak-over-200-cases-reported-officials-warn-avoid-eating-raw-oysters-471292 <description><![CDATA[Health officials in Southern California have issued a warning to avoid eating raw oysters imported from certain areas of Mexico after more than 200 people got sick from suspected norovirus infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-norovirus-outbreak-over-200-cases-reported-officials-warn-avoid-eating-raw-oysters-471292</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:36:34 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Happens To Your Body In Extreme Cold? Know Hypothermia Signs, Treatments]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-happens-your-body-extreme-cold-know-signs-treatments-hypothermia-471290 <description><![CDATA[Hypothermia, a dangerous condition that can occur when a person gets exposed to extreme cold climates, has the potential to lead to organ failure and even death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-happens-your-body-extreme-cold-know-signs-treatments-hypothermia-471290</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jan 2024 03:33:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Energy Drinks Associated With Depression, ADHD, And Anxiety In Kids, Young Adults: Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/energy-drinks- Associated-depression-adhd-anxiety-kids-young-adults-research-471289 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has identified a series of health effects associated with energy drinks, including disrupted sleep, depression, suicide, ADHD, and anxiety, particularly in children and young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/energy-drinks- Associated-depression-adhd-anxiety-kids-young-adults-research-471289</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:13:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Multivitamins For Memory Loss: Researchers Say Daily Intake Could Slow Cognitive Aging By Around 2 Years]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multivitamins-memory-loss-researchers-say-daily-intake-could-slow-cognitive-aging-around-2-years-471287 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that daily supplementation of multivitamins could slow cognitive decline in older adults by around two years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multivitamins-memory-loss-researchers-say-daily-intake-could-slow-cognitive-aging-around-2-years-471287</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:28:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Neurotechnology-Based RecoveriX Treatment Provides Safer Alternative To Medications For Stroke And MS Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neurotechnology-based-recoverix-treatment-provides-safer-alternative-medications-中风-ms-471285 <description><![CDATA[Unlike most medications for stroke and MS on the market, recoveriX has been shown to aid in the rehabilitation of stroke and multiple sclerosis patients.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neurotechnology-based-recoverix-treatment-provides-safer-alternative-medications-中风-ms-471285</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 12:10:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Antifungal Body Wash For 2024: Experience Healthy, Happy Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-antifungal-body-wash-experience-healthy-happy-skin-471284 <description><![CDATA[We have compiled the list of best fungus body wash in the market today, and some things to consider while buying one.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-antifungal-body-wash-experience-healthy-happy-skin-471284</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 10:39:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Organic Castor Oils Of 2024: Nourish, Strengthen And Shine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-organic-castor-oil-nourish-strengthen-shine-471278 <description><![CDATA[As a key ingredient in beauty routines, castor oil is celebrated for its ability to address various concerns, including dry skin, damaged hair, and even aiding in the maintenance of healthy lashes and brows.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-organic-castor-oil-nourish-strengthen-shine-471278</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:16:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Nail Fungus Treatments For 2024: Cutting-Edge Options For Lasting Health And Beauty]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-nail-fungus-treatments-cutting-edge-options- permanent-health-beauty-471281 <description><![CDATA[Here are some great options to promote the restoration of healthy, clear nails, by avoiding costly and invasive measures.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-nail-fungus-treatments-cutting-edge-options- permanent-health-beauty-471281</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 08:34:42 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Hinged Braces Of 2024: Ultimate Guide To Experience Unparalleled Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hinged-braces-ultimate-guide-experience-unparalleled-support-471283 <description><![CDATA[Knee injuries have the tendency to debilitate you. However, finding the best hinged brace could be your first step to regaining some normalcy after an injury.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hinged-braces-ultimate-guide-experience-unparalleled-support-471283</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 08:13:21 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Retinol Eye Sticks Of 2024: Embrace The Restorative Magic]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-retinol-eye-sticks-embrace-restorative-magic-471280 <description><![CDATA[Unleash the power of retinol, your skincare superhero for combating aging signs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-retinol-eye-sticks-embrace-restorative-magic-471280</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:52:13 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 5 Back Braces Of 2024: Discover The Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-back-braces-discover-relief-471274 <description><![CDATA[Say goodbye to slouching and welcome a more confident, pain-free you as we explore the key features of the top five back braces]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-back-braces-discover-relief-471274</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 05:05:29 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>