<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Harnessing Nature's Power: The 7 Best Tongkat Ali Supplements]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/harnessing-natures-power-7-best-tongkat-ali-supplements-471700 <description><![CDATA[Discover the benefits of Tongkat Ali with these supplements that harness nature's power to boost testosterone levels and enhance men's vitality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/harnessing-natures-power-7-best-tongkat-ali-supplements-471700</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 11:16:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Metformin Reduces COVID-19 Hospitalizations, Long COVID: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-reduces-covid-19-hospitalizations-long-covid-study-471710 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that metformin can reduce the amount of COVID-19 virus in the body and lower the risk of viral rebound.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-reduces-covid-19-hospitalizations-long-covid-study-471710</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 03:50:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tuberculosis Outbreak: 1 Dead, 9 Hospitalized In Long Beach; Officials Declare Health Emergency]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tuberculosis-outbreak-1-dead-9-hospitalized-long-beach-officials-declare-health-emergency-471709 <description><![CDATA[An investigation revealed that approximately 170 people have likely been exposed to TB.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tuberculosis-outbreak-1-dead-9-hospitalized-long-beach-officials-declare-health-emergency-471709</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 03:35:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Liver Patients Can Benefit By Going Meatless For Just One Meal, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/liver-病人-can-benefit-just-going-meatless-one-meal-says-study-471708 <description><![CDATA[Adults with permanent liver damage can lower the levels of harmful ammonia by substituting one meal with a vegan or vegetarian option, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/liver-病人-can-benefit-just-going-meatless-one-meal-says-study-471708</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 02:01:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Beauty from Within: Top 5 Collagen Powder Drinks To Boost and Improve Skin Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beauty-within-top-5-collagen-powder-drinks-boost-improve-skin-health-471706 <description><![CDATA[Discover the secret to radiant, youthful skin with collagen power drinks – the ultimate skincare booster packed with all the goodness your skin craves.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beauty-within-top-5-collagen-powder-drinks-boost-improve-skin-health-471706</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 15:56:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women Are 40% More At Risk Of Depression During Perimenopause: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-40-more-risk-of-depression-during-perimenopause-study-471705 <description><![CDATA[There is a 40% increased risk of depression at the perimenopausal stage compared to the premenopausal stage, a study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-40-more-risk-of-depression-during-perimenopause-study-471705</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 03:56:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Control Your Anger: Study Says It Damages Blood Vessel, Raising Heart Disease Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/control-your-anger-study-says-it-damages-blood-vessels-raise-heart-disease-risk-471704 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that a brief period of anger can damage your blood vessels and elevate the risk of heart disease and stroke.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/control-your-anger-study-says-it-damages-blood-vessels-raise-heart-disease-risk-471704</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 03:18:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Combine Intense Workout With Intermittent Fasting For Fat Loss, Cardiometabolic Health: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/combine-intense-workout-intermittent-fasting-fat-loss-cardiometabolic-health-study-says-471702 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that adopting intermittent fasting with an eating period between 8 am and 4 pm, combined with high-intensity functional training during the fasting window, could lead to significant transformations in body composition and cardiometabolic measures.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/combine-intense-workout-intermittent-fasting-fat-loss-cardiometabolic-health-study-says-471702</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 02:08:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[EVL BCAA Energy: The Perfect Pre-Workout Energy Drink To Boost Exercise Productivity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/evl-bcaa-energy-perfect-pre-workout-energy-drink-boost-exercise-productivity-471684 <description><![CDATA[Introducing EVL BCAA Energy: A natural pre-workout drink with green coffee for focus, BCAAs for performance, and essential vitamins.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/evl-bcaa-energy-perfect-pre-workout-energy-drink-boost-exercise-productivity-471684</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 12:45:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[E-Coli Outbreak Linked To Organic Walnuts Sickens 12: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-walnuts-sickens-12-cdc-471699 <description><![CDATA[The outbreak linked to contaminated organic walnuts sold in bulk bins has led to 12 reported cases of illness and seven hospitalizations in California and Washington.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-walnuts-sickens-12-cdc-471699</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 04:08:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[An Omega-6 Fatty Acid Linked To Reduced Risk Of Bipolar Disorder: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-6-fatty-acid-linked-reduced-risk-bipolar-disorder-study-471697 <description><![CDATA[The new study also indicates the possibility of using dietary intervention to prevent or slow down the progression of psychiatric disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-6-fatty-acid-linked-reduced-risk-bipolar-disorder-study-471697</guid><pubDate> Wed, 01 May 2024 03:10:09 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>