<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Antidepressants During Pregnancy Can Affect Fetal Brain Development: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-antidepressants-during-pregnancy-can-affect-fetal-brain-development-study-471412 <description><![CDATA[The use of antidepressants, particularly fluoxetine, could affect the development of the prefrontal cortex of the infant's brain, potentially raising the risk of mental health disorders later in their life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-antidepressants-during-pregnancy-can-affect-fetal-brain-development-study-471412</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:53:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Vaccination Or Booster During Pregnancy Protects Infants For 6 Months: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-vaccination-booster-protects-infants-6-months-during-pregnancy-study-4 <description><![CDATA[The findings of the study underscore the importance of getting vaccinated against COVID-19 during pregnancy to ensure that infants are born with strong protection until they are old enough to be vaccinated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-vaccination-booster-protects-infants-6-months-during-pregnancy-study-4</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Feb 2024 02:30:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mouthwash Use May Improve Blood Sugar Levels In Some Diabetic Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mouthwash-use-may-improve-blood-sugar-levels-in-some-diabetic-病人-study-471408 <description><![CDATA[Researchers believe that if patients who are likely to respond well to antiseptic mouthwash could be identified, it would be an easy-to-use treatment for people with periodontic-linked diseases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mouthwash-use-may-improve-blood-sugar-levels-in-some-diabetic-病人-study-471408</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:18:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[ColonBroom: Your Ultimate Solution To Say Goodbye To Bloating]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/colonbroom-your-ultimate-solution-say-goodbye-bloating-471387 <description><![CDATA[Ready to bid farewell to bloating and enjoy effortless digestion? Discover the transformation with ColonBroom.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/colonbroom-your-ultimate-solution-say-goodbye-bloating-471387</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 16:30:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unlock Excellence In Fitness: A Dive Into Huge Supplements' Premium Formulas]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unlock-excellence-fitness-dive-huge-supplements-premium-formulas-471392 <description><![CDATA[Explore the world of huge supplements and elevate your fitness to new heights.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unlock-excellence-fitness-dive-huge-supplements-premium-formulas-471392</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 16:27:12 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[8 Best Probiotic Products: What They Are, How They Work And Why You Need Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-best-probiotic-products-what-they-are-how-they-work-why-you-need-them-471380 <description><![CDATA[Delve into the world of probiotics and uncover why these 8 top probiotic products are the essential health boost you've been searching for.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-best-probiotic-products-what-they-are-how-they-work-why-you-need-them-471380</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 16:16:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gut-Brain Connection: 13 Top Mood Probiotics For Emotional Well-Being]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-brain-connection-13-top-mood-probiotics-emotional-well-being-471383 <description><![CDATA[Are you looking for probiotics to boost your emotional well-being? Explore our curated list of the top 13 mood probiotics known for enhancing digestion and promoting brain health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-brain-connection-13-top-mood-probiotics-emotional-well-being-471383</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 15:43:52 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Must-Try Vegan Protein Powders For A Strong And Healthy Body]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-must-try-vegan- Protein-powders-strong-healthy-body-471385 <description><![CDATA[Are you aiming to achieve a strong and healthy body the vegan way? Here are 5 must-try vegan protein powders to boost your well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-must-try-vegan- Protein-powders-strong-healthy-body-471385</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 15:34:46 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Coughing Even Weeks After Infection? Here's What Researchers Say]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/coughing-even-weeks-after-infection-here-what-researchers-say-471406 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say post-infectious cough is a rather common condition that affects around 11 to 25% of adults after a bout of respiratory illness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/coughing-even-weeks-after-infection-here-what-researchers-say-471406</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:47:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exercise For Treating Depression? Researchers Identify Activities That May Be As Effective As Therapy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-treating-depression-researchers-identify-activities-that-may-be- effective-therapy-471405 <description><![CDATA[Researchers noted that the intensity of the activity was directly linked to the extent of improvement in depression symptoms. However, certain low-intensity activities also had significant benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-treating-depression-researchers-identify-activities-that-may-be- effective-therapy-471405</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:16:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Childhood Bullying Can Increase Mental Health Risk By Three Times: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-thirdfold-increase-in-mental-health-risk-linked-to-childhood-bullying-471403 <description><![CDATA[Children who get bullied by the age of 11 develop strong interpersonal distrust as they grow, and are at threefold risk of developing mental health issues by their late teens, a study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-thirdfold-increase-in-mental-health-risk-linked-to-childhood-bullying-471403</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:59:02 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>