<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Peter Rentrop Shares Medical Technology That Is Revolutionizing The Future Of Heart Health In Cardiology]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/dr-peter-rentrop-shares-medical-technology-that-revolutionizing-future-heart-health-cardiology-471633 <description><![CDATA[The world of cardiology is witnessing a remarkable transformation driven by cutting-edge medical technologies, says Dr. Peter Rentrop.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/dr-peter-rentrop-shares-medical-technology-that-revolutionizing-future-heart-health-cardiology-471633</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 19:10:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nathan Guerette: A Pioneer in Pelvic Reconstructive Surgery and Academic Excellence]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/nathan-guerette-pioneer-pelvic-reconstructive-surgery-academic-excellence-471631 <description><![CDATA[From individualized care to ongoing efforts to integrate innovative techniques, those seeking the best care can expect unparalleled care from Nathan Guerette, MD.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/nathan-guerette-pioneer-pelvic-reconstructive-surgery-academic-excellence-471631</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 19:04:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Empowering Moms: Navigating the Choices in Wearable Breast Pump - Efficiently]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/empowering-moms-navigating-choices-wearable-breast-pump-efficiently-471619 <description><![CDATA[Breastfeeding mothers now have a reliable ally in technology with wearable breast pumps]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/empowering-moms-navigating-choices-wearable-breast-pump-efficiently-471619</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 15:05:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Seafood Diet Raises Exposure To 'Forever Chemicals': Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-seafood-diet-raises-exposure-forever-chemicals-study-471629 <description><![CDATA[The results showed that shrimp and lobster had the highest concentrations of certain PFAS compounds, with averages ranging as high as 1.74 and 3.30 nanograms per gram of flesh, respectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-seafood-diet-raises-exposure-forever-chemicals-study-471629</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 03:50:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Single Low-Dose Esketamine Injection May Reduce Postpartum Depression In New Mothers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/single-low-dose-esketamine-injection-may-reduce-postpartum-depression-new-mothers-study-471627 <description><![CDATA[The study found that a single low-dose injection of esketamine given just after childbirth could reduce the risk of postpartum depression in new mothers who experienced prenatal depression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/single-low-dose-esketamine-injection-may-reduce-postpartum-depression-new-mothers-study-471627</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:15:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[No Link Between COVID-19 Virus And Asthma Risk In Kids, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-link- Between-covid-19-virus-asthma-risk-kids-says-study-471625 <description><![CDATA[Since respiratory viral infections are known to increase asthma risk in young children, researchers of a new study investigated if contracting the SARS-COV-2 virus could bring in a similar outcome, and determined no association exists between the two.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/no-link- Between-covid-19-virus-asthma-risk-kids-says-study-471625</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Apr 2024 01:24:03 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Overweight Children At High Risk Of Iron Deficiency: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/overweight-children-high-risk-iron-deficiency-study-471622 <description><![CDATA[The researchers believe that iron deficiency in overweight children is probably due to inflammation-disrupting mechanisms that regulate iron absorption.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/overweight-children-high-risk-iron-deficiency-study-471622</guid><pubDate> Fri, 12 Apr 2024 03:13:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hypertensive Disorders In Pregnancy Linked To Fatal Heart Disease Risk After Giving Birth: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hypertential-disorders-pregnancy-linked-fatal-heart-disease-risk-after-giving-birth-study-471623 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that the conditions that typically cause dangerously high blood pressure in pregnancy except gestational diabetes doubled the fatal cardiovascular disease risk in women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hypertential-disorders-pregnancy-linked-fatal-heart-disease-risk-after-giving-birth-study-471623</guid><pubDate> Fri, 12 Apr 2024 02:49:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stress Awareness Month: Expert Recommends Self-Care To Manage The Silent Killer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-awareness-month-expert-recommends-self-care-manage-silent-killer-471620 <description><![CDATA[During this Stress Awareness Month, an expert explains the negative consequences of stress and techniques to manage this silent killer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-awareness-month-expert-recommends-self-care-manage-silent-killer-471620</guid><pubDate> Fri, 12 Apr 2024 02:15:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Kieran Slevin On AI And Its Potential In Pain Detection And Patient Care]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/dr-kieran-slevin-ai-its-潜在-疼痛-检测-病人-护理-471618 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Kieran Slevin is keeping a close eye on artificial intelligence (AI), a tool not only with myriad applications across the healthcare landscape but one rapidly proving invaluable in delivering optimum patient care levels.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/dr-kieran-slevin-ai-its-潜在-疼痛-检测-病人-护理-471618</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Apr 2024 16:13:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Swapping Red Meat With Forage Fish Could Prevent 750,000 Deaths Annually In 2050: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/swapping-red-meat-forage-fish-could-prevent-750000-deaths-annually-2050-study-471615 <description><![CDATA[Incorporating forage fish or prey fish such as herring, sardines, and anchovies into diets could also potentially lower the prevalence of disability caused by diet-related diseases, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/swapping-red-meat-forage-fish-could-prevent-750000-deaths-annually-2050-study-471615</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Apr 2024 04:09:50 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>