<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Alcohol-Dependency Treatment Should Be Different For Men And Women: Study Explains Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-dependency-treatment-should- Different-men-women-study-explains-why-472420 <description><![CDATA[The latest study suggests that hormonal and biochemical factors play a crucial role in shaping patterns of alcohol use and dependence in men and women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alcohol-dependency-treatment-should- Different-men-women-study-explains-why-472420</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Sep 2024 04:18:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Anti-Depressants May Improve Brain Function, Verbal Memory: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anti-depressants-may-improve-brain-function-verbal-memory-study-472418 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found that the use of antidepressant medications SSRI (Selective Serotonin Reuptake Inhibitors) can help improve brain function, particularly verbal memory.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/anti-depressants-may-improve-brain-function-verbal-memory-study-472418</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Sep 2024 02:51:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[First Self-Administered Flu Vaccine For Home Use Gets FDA Approval]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-self-administered-flu-vaccine-home-use-gets-fda-approval-472417 <description><![CDATA[FluMist nasal spray manufactured by AstraZeneca is now approved for home use against influenza infection caused by subtypes A and B from ages 2 through 49.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-self-administered-flu-vaccine-home-use-gets-fda-approval-472417</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:37:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Face Masks For Skincare: Hydration, Cleansing, And Anti-Aging]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-face-masks-skincare-Hydration-cleansing-anti-aging-472369 <description><![CDATA[Face masks are popular skincare treatments designed to hydrate, cleanse, and rejuvenate the skin. They come in various forms like sheet masks, clay masks, and gel-based options, each serving specific skincare needs. Whether you're looking to address dryness, acne, or signs of aging, the right mask can enhance your routine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-face-masks-skincare-Hydration-cleansing-anti-aging-472369</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:21:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Facial Hair Removing Tools For Women: Elevate Your Beauty Routine And Skin Texture]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-facial-hair-removing-tools-women-elevate-your-beauty-routine-skin-texture-472386 <description><![CDATA[If you are someone who is looking for a way to get rid of that unwanted peach fuzz, unruly brows, and chin hairs, you have to invest your money in good facial hair removing products that are available in different forms and cater to various skin types.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-facial-hair-removing-tools-women-elevate-your-beauty-routine-skin-texture-472386</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:20:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Face Serums For Hydration, Anti-aging And Radiance]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-face-serums-Hydration-anti-aging-radiance-472388 <description><![CDATA[Face serums are concentrated treatments designed to target specific skin concerns, offering benefits that range from hydration to anti-aging and brightening. The best face serums on the market are formulated with potent ingredients that address various skin issues effectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-face-serums-Hydration-anti-aging-radiance-472388</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:06:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Nicotine Patches to Help You Quit Smoking for Good: 9 Benefits And How To Use Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-nicotine-patches-help-you-quit-smoking-good-9-benefits-how-use-them-472383 <description><![CDATA[Nicotine patches offer a simple yet powerful way to quit smoking by delivering a controlled, consistent dose of nicotine through the skin, helping to ease withdrawal symptoms and cravings. For many, this small patch represents the first step toward a smoke-free life, offering support every hour of the day. Here's your guide to pick the most effective one available on the market.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-nicotine-patches-help-you-quit-smoking-good-9-benefits-how-use-them-472383</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:03:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Longer Breastfeeding Reduces Risk Of Asthma Via Healthy Microbiome In Gut, Nasal Cavity: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/longer-breastfeeding-reduces-risk-asthma-via-healthy-microbiome-gut-nasal-cavity-study-472408 <description><![CDATA[The researchers of the latest study underscore the importance of extended breastfeeding for respiratory health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/longer-breastfeeding-reduces-risk-asthma-via-healthy-microbiome-gut-nasal-cavity-study-472408</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 04:17:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Class Of Diabetes Drugs That Cuts Risk Of Dementia, Parkinson's Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-class-diabetes-drugs-that-c​​uts-risk-dementia-parkinsons-disease-472406 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that sodium-glucose cotransporter-2 (SGLT2) inhibitors may help reduce the risk of dementia and Parkinson's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-class-diabetes-drugs-that-c​​uts-risk-dementia-parkinsons-disease-472406</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:33:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fussy Eating In Toddlers Linked To Genetics, May Persist Into Early Adolescence: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fussy-eating-toddlers-linked-genics-may-persist-early-adolescent-study-472405 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that picky eating is largely influenced by genetics and children with such traits may continue the habit into early adolescence.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fussy-eating-toddlers-linked-genics-may-persist-early-adolescent-study-472405</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:04:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Pulse Oximeters: Essential Tools For Monitoring Oxygen Levels And Heart Rate]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-pulse-oximeters-essential-tools-monitoring-oxygen-levels-heart-rate-472395 <description><![CDATA[Pulse oximeters are essential devices for monitoring blood oxygen saturation and heart rate. They are commonly used by individuals managing respiratory conditions, athletes tracking their performance, and those undergoing medical treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-pulse-oximeters-essential-tools-monitoring-oxygen-levels-heart-rate-472395</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:29:41 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>