<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Water Allergy Causes Excruciating Pain For Woman—From Drinking To Showering, She Shares Her Daily Struggle]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-water-allergy-causes-cruciating-pain-woman-drinking-showering-shopering-she-shares-shares-her-her-daily-473137 <description><![CDATA[An extremely rare condition called aquagenic urticaria makes the life of the young mother a daily struggle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-water-allergy-causes-cruciating-pain-woman-drinking-showering-shopering-she-shares-shares-her-her-daily-473137</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Feb 2025 04:45:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Diet Pattern Effective For Many May Be Harmful For Teens: Here's How]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-diet-pattern-effective-many-may-harmful-teens-heres-heres-heres-how-473134 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that long-term intermittent fasting affected insulin production in young mice.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/popular-diet-pattern-effective-many-may-harmful-teens-heres-heres-heres-how-473134</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Feb 2025 03:15:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Drives To Hospital Feeling Unwell, Hours Later Develops Hallucinations, Seizures: He's Now Battling Rare 'Brain On Fire' Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-drives-hospital-feeling-unwell-hours-later-later-nater-hallucinations-hallucinations-seizures-seizures-hes-now-473131 <description><![CDATA[The 48-year-old from California was diagnosed with Anti-NMDA Encephalitis, also known as "Brain on Fire" disease, an auto-immune condition where the body attacks the brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-drives-hospital-feeling-unwell-hours-later-later-nater-hallucinations-hallucinations-seizures-seizures-hes-now-473131</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Feb 2025 01:26:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Craving Sugary Treat After Meals? Here's Why You Always Have Room For Dessert]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/craving-sugary-treat-ter-meals-heres-heres-why---------------------------------------------- <description><![CDATA[In a recent study researchers explain how "dessert stomach" is linked to the brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/craving-sugary-treat-ter-meals-heres-heres-why----------------------------------------------</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Feb 2025 03:40:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Taste Predict Early Death? If You Can't Sense These Two Flavors, Your Risk May Be High]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-taste-predict-early-death-if-you-cant-sense-these-two-flavors-your-risk-may-high-473128 <description><![CDATA[A recent study found that people who lose their sense of taste have a 47% higher risk of early death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-taste-predict-early-death-if-you-cant-sense-these-two-flavors-your-risk-may-high-473128</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Feb 2025 02:19:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Returns From Vacation With Headache, Strange Leg Symptoms, Doctors Find Brain Worms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-returns-vacation-headache-strange-leg-symptoms-doctors-find-brain-worms-473126 <description><![CDATA[The woman was diagnosed with eosinophilic meningitis from rat lungworm, a parasitic worm that gets into the human body typically through contaminated food.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-returns-vacation-headache-strange-leg-symptoms-doctors-find-brain-worms-473126</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:02:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Outbreak in Texas County With Low Vaccination Rate Multiplies, More Cases 'Likely']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/Measles-stream-texas-county-low-vaccination-rat-rate-multiplies-more-cases-cases-473123 <description><![CDATA[A rapidly growing measles outbreak in Gaines County, Texas, linked to low vaccination rates, has reached 48 cases, prompting urgent health warnings and vaccination efforts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/Measles-stream-texas-county-low-vaccination-rat-rate-multiplies-more-cases-cases-473123</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:54:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Outbreak in Texas County With Low Vaccination Rate Multiplies, More Cases 'Likely']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/Measles-stream-texas-county-low-vaccination-rate-rate-multiplies-more-cases-cases-473121 <description><![CDATA[A rapidly growing measles outbreak in Gaines County, Texas, linked to low vaccination rates, has reached 48 cases, prompting urgent health warnings and vaccination efforts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/Measles-stream-texas-county-low-vaccination-rate-rate-multiplies-more-cases-cases-473121</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:50:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Louisiana Health Department Orders Employees to Stop Promoting Mass Vaccinations As it Accuses CDC of Being 'Woefully Out of Touch']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/louisiana-health-department-orders-ormployees-stop-pop-promoting-mass-vaccinations-it-accuses-cdc-cdc-473119 <description><![CDATA[Louisiana's Health Department has ordered employees to stop promoting mass vaccinations, which experts say could lead to declining immunization rates.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/louisiana-health-department-orders-ormployees-stop-pop-promoting-mass-vaccinations-it-accuses-cdc-cdc-473119</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:30:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiac Doctor Realizes He's Having a Heart Attack After Comparing Symptoms to Patient He Had Just Helped]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-doctor-realizes-hes-hes-having-having-having-having-having-having-having-ferfter-comparpering-comparting-toctoms-patient-patient-patient-he-just-just-just-just-473118 <description><![CDATA[A cardiac doctor unknowingly suffered a heart attack while treating a patient with identical symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-doctor-realizes-hes-hes-having-having-having-having-having-having-having-ferfter-comparpering-comparting-toctoms-patient-patient-patient-he-just-just-just-just-473118</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:08:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Real Housewives' Star Teddi Mellencamp Hospitalized After Severe Headaches Lead To Multiple Tumor Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/real-housewives-star-teddi-mellencamp-hospitalized-- fer-sever-sever-headaches-headaches-multiph-multiph-multiphiple-tumer-473115 <description><![CDATA[Mellencamp was experiencing "severe and debilitating headaches" for the last several weeks before getting hospitalized.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/real-housewives-star-teddi-mellencamp-hospitalized-- fer-sever-sever-headaches-headaches-multiph-multiph-multiphiple-tumer-473115</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Feb 2025 04:08:47 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>