<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Virginia Woman Forced to Raise Money for Prosthetic Hand After Insurance Refuses to Cover It Despite Doctor Recommendation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virginia-woman-forced-raise-money-prosthetic-hand-after-insurance-refuses-cover-it-despite-472962 <description><![CDATA[Elisabeth Foley, a Virginia mother who lost her hand in a shark attack, is turning to crowdfunding after her insurance company denied coverage for a $73,000 prosthetic her doctors recommended.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virginia-woman-forced-raise-money-prosthetic-hand-after-insurance-refuses-cover-it-despite-472962</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 18:21:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Thousands of Doctors Come Out Against Letting RFK Jr. Become Health Secretary: 'He Is Actively Dangerous']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/thousands-doctors-come-out-against-letting-rfk-jr-become-health-secretary-he-actively-472959 <description><![CDATA[More than 15,000 doctors are urging the Senate to vote against confirming Robert F. Kennedy Jr. as the Secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/thousands-doctors-come-out-against-letting-rfk-jr-become-health-secretary-he-actively-472959</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:25:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Baby Hygiene Made Easy: Here's What We Think of Papablic's 4-in-1 Bottle Cleaner That Does It All]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/baby-hygiene-made-easy-heres-what-we-think-papablics-4-1-bottle-cleaner-that-does-it-all472947 <description><![CDATA[Instead of juggling scrubbing brushes, sterilizers, and drying racks, this all-in-one system takes care of everything in one compact package]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/baby-hygiene-made-easy-heres-what-we-think-papablics-4-1-bottle-cleaner-that-does-it-all472947</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 12:49:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Beyond Bleeding: The Best Period Tracker Isn't Just For Tracking Periods]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-bleeding-best-period-tracker-isnt-just-tracking-periods-472946 <description><![CDATA[If you're looking for more tools to understand how your cycle-related experiences impact your mental and physical health, you'll need an app that goes beyond just bleeding]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-bleeding-best-period-tracker-isnt-just-tracking-periods-472946</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 12:48:56 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Juice From This 'Underappreciated' Berry May Help You Lose Weight, Improve Metabolic Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/juice-this-underappreciated-berry-may-help-you-lose-weight-improve-metabolic-health-472956 <description><![CDATA[Researchers are now turning to these dark purple berries from the elder tree, native to Europe, as a promising tool for weight management and metabolic health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/juice-this-underappreciated-berry-may-help-you-lose-weight-improve-metabolic-health-472956</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 05:04:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Shares A Rare Side Effect Of GLP-1 Weight Loss Drugs, Ways To Break A Stall]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-shares-rare-side-effect-glp-1weight-loss-drugs-ways-break-stall-472953 <description><![CDATA[As more people turn to these weight loss solutions, it's important to understand not only how to use them effectively but also to stay alert to even the rare side effects that could arise.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-shares-rare-side-effect-glp-1weight-loss-drugs-ways-break-stall-472953</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 03:23:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Two Common Drinks And Bowel Cancer: One Reduces Risk By 17%, The Other Raises It By Similar Amount]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/two-common-drinks-bowel-cancer-one-reduces-risk-17-other-raises-it-similar-amount-472950 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that drinking a glass of milk reduces the risk of bowel cancer by nearly a fifth, while drinking a glass of wine could elevate the risk by 15%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/two-common-drinks-bowel-cancer-one-reduces-risk-17-other-raises-it-similar-amount-472950</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:29:30 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealthcare Interrupted Cancer Patient's Surgery to Demand Justification for Overnight Hospital Stay: 'Insurance Is Out of Control']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unitedhealthcare-interrupted-cancer-患者-surgery-demand-justification-overnight-hospital-472945 <description><![CDATA[A surgeon shared her frustration after her patient's operation was interrupted by UnitedHealthcare's demand to justify the patient's overnight hospital stay.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unitedhealthcare-interrupted-cancer-患者-surgery-demand-justification-overnight-hospital-472945</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 16:31:18 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Kansas Set a New State Record for Abortions in 2023. Most of the Patients Were from Texas]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kansas-set-new-state-record-abortions-2023-most-患者-were-texas-472944 <description><![CDATA[The largest group of patients to receive an abortion in Kansas were Texas residents, according to a report released by the Kansas Department of Health and Environment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kansas-set-new-state-record-abortions-2023-most-患者-were-texas-472944</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 15:19:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New FDA Guidelines On Lead In Baby Food 'Insufficient', Say Health Advocates, Calling For Stricter Limits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-fda-guidelines-lead-baby-food-insufficient-say-health-advocates-calling-stricter-limits-472942 <description><![CDATA[As part of its "Closer to Zero" initiative to reduce toxic elements like lead in foods, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration unveiled new guidelines for lead in baby food this week.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-fda-guidelines-lead-baby-food-insufficient-say-health-advocates-calling-stricter-limits-472942</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 04:38:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gastroenterologist's Fruit Washing Tip: One Simple Inexpensive Ingredient You Already Have In Your Kitchen]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gastroenterologies-fruit-washing-tip-one-simple-inexpective-ingredient-you-already-have-your-472940 <description><![CDATA[For those seeking the right technique to wash fruits, you don't need expensive fruit-washing liquids. All you need is one simple, inexpensive ingredient already in your kitchen.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gastroenterologies-fruit-washing-tip-one-simple-inexpective-ingredient-you-already-have-your-472940</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 Jan 2025 03:01:43 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>