<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Wants To Further Reduce Salt Levels In Packaged, Processed Food]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-wants-further-reduce-salt-levels-packaged-processed-food-472135 <description><![CDATA[After the successful execution of the Phase I target, the FDA plans to further reduce sodium levels by 20%, to bring the average intake to about 2,750 milligrams per day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-wants-further-reduce-salt-levels-packaged-processed-food-472135</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Aug 2024 05:19:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Untreated Hypertension Linked To 42% Higher Risk Of Alzheimer's Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/untreatment-hypertension-linked-42-higher-risk-alzheimers-disease-study-472134 <description><![CDATA[Untreated hypertension is linked to a 42% higher risk of Alzheimer's disease in adults aged 60 or older, a study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/untreatment-hypertension-linked-42-higher-risk-alzheimers-disease-study-472134</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:17:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Chronic High Coffee Consumption Raises Heart Disease Risk, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-high-coffee-conspiration-raises-heart-disease-risk-says-study-472132 <description><![CDATA[The study found that drinking more than 400 mg of caffeine most days raises the risk of heart disease in otherwise healthy individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-high-coffee-conspiration-raises-heart-disease-risk-says-study-472132</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Aug 2024 02:19:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Dandelion Extract Supplements: A Natural Medicine Staple]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-dandelion-extract-supplements-natural-medicine-staple-472117 <description><![CDATA[Dandelion supplements offer numerous health benefits, including liver support, digestive aid, and anti-inflammatory effects. Rich in vitamins and antioxidants, they help detoxify the body and regulate blood sugar levels. Available in forms like capsules, teas, and extracts, dandelion supplements are versatile and easy to incorporate into wellness routines.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-dandelion-extract-supplements-natural-medicine-staple-472117</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:58:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Whey Protein Supplements Of 2024: Boost Muscle Strength, Aid Weight Loss, And More]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-whey- Protein-supplements-2024-boost-muscle-strength-aid-weight-loss-more-472104 <description><![CDATA[Whey protein, which is rich in essential amino acids, supports muscle repair, and aids in weight management, making it a popular choice for athletes and fitness enthusiasts. Here are some of the best whey proteins available in the market today.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-whey- Protein-supplements-2024-boost-muscle-strength-aid-weight-loss-more-472104</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:23:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Single Episode Of Shingles Raises Cognitive Decline By 20%, Says Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/single-episode-shingles-raises-cognitive-decline-20-says-study-472130 <description><![CDATA[The pain and complications of shingles do not end with the episode, as a new study suggests that its impact could be long-term.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/single-episode-shingles-raises-cognitive-decline-20-says-study-472130</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:33:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Chemicals In Common Makeup, Personal Care Products Raise Hypertension Risk In Pregnancy: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chemicals-common-makeup-personal-care-products-raise-hypertension-risk-pregnancy-study-472125 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that phenols and parabens could raise the risk of developing high blood pressure by 57%, and the risk is particularly high between 24 and 28 weeks of gestation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chemicals-common-makeup-personal-care-products-raise-hypertension-risk-pregnancy-study-472125</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:11:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Heme Iron And Diabetes: Study Says Reducing Red Meat Could Lower Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heme-iron-diabetes-study-says-reducing-red-meat-could-lower-risk-472122 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that heme iron, which is present in red meat and other animal products, could increase the risk of type 2 diabetes. In contrast, non-heme iron in plant-based food does not pose a similar risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heme-iron-diabetes-study-says-reducing-red-meat-could-lower-risk-472122</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Aug 2024 05:08:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cancer Risk 'From The First Drop': Study Warns Even Light Drinking Risky To Elderly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cancer-risk-first-drop-study-warns-even-light-drinking-risky-elderly-472119 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that no amount of alcohol could help heart health, and even light drinking could increase cancer deaths among elderly adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cancer-risk-first-drop-study-warns-even-light-drinking-risky-elderly-472119</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:29:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Human Parvovirus B19 Cases Surge, Certain Groups At High Risk, CDC Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ human-parvovirus-b19-cases-surge-certain-groups-high-risk-cdc-says-472116 <description><![CDATA[The CDC reports a surge in highly contagious human parvovirus B19 infections in the U.S., particularly among children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ human-parvovirus-b19-cases-surge-certain-groups-high-risk-cdc-says-472116</guid><pubDate> Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:10:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Guide to Ginseng's Benefits, Uses and Varieties]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/compressive-guide-ginsengs-benefits-uses-varieties-472112 <description><![CDATA[Ginseng, a potent herb in traditional medicine, is prized for boosting energy, enhancing immunity, and improving mental clarity. The main types—Asian, American, and Siberian—each offer unique benefits. Ginseng supports energy, cognitive function, immune health, and cardiovascular wellness while reducing inflammation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/compressive-guide-ginsengs-benefits-uses-varieties-472112</guid><pubDate> Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:42:34 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>