<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[New York Requires Health Insurers to Cover EpiPens as Cost of Life-Saving Device Skyrockets]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-york-requires-health-insurers-cover-epipens-cost-life- saving-device-skyrockets-472838 <description><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking move to combat rising healthcare costs, New York Governor Kathy Hochul signed a law mandating health insurers cover EpiPens as they surge in price.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-york-requires-health-insurers-cover-epipens-cost-life- saving-device-skyrockets-472838</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Dec 2024 18:21:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Child's Snoring Isn't Just A Noise, It's A Signal': Dentist Cautions Parents About Dangers Of Sleep Apnea]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childs-snoring-isnt-just-noise-its-signal-dentist-cautions-parents-about-dangers-sleep-472836 <description><![CDATA[Snoring in children might seem like an innocent quirk, but a California dentist warns it could signal a hidden health issue.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childs-snoring-isnt-just-noise-its-signal-dentist-cautions-parents-about-dangers-sleep-472836</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Dec 2024 04:43:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[UCLA Student Sues Doctors, Claims She Was Misdiagnosed Of Gender Dysphoria, And 'Fast-Tracked' Into Transgender Surgery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ucla-student-sues-doctors-claims-she-was-misdiagnosed-gender-dysphoria-fast-tracked-472834 <description><![CDATA[The 20-year-old filed a lawsuit against multiple healthcare providers in California as she was reportedly misdiagnosed with gender dysphoria at age 12 and "fast-tracked onto a conveyor belt" of irreversible gender transition treatments.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ucla-student-sues-doctors-claims-she-was-misdiagnosed-gender-dysphoria-fast-tracked-472834</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Dec 2024 03:08:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are Babies In U.S. Sleeping Safely? Over 3,000 Infants Die Annually From Incorrect Sleep Positions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-babies-us-sleeping-safely-over-3000-infants-die-annually-in Correct-sleep-positions-472831 <description><![CDATA[Many of the sleep-related deaths such as those from accidental strangulation or sudden infant death syndrome (SIDS) could be prevented through safe sleep practices.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-babies-us-sleeping-safely-over-3000-infants-die-annually-in Correct-sleep-positions-472831</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Dec 2024 01:22:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Child Flu Vaccinations Decline by Double Digits as Pediatric Deaths Soar: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/child-flu-vaccinations-decline-double-digits-pediatric-deaths-soar-cdc-472829 <description><![CDATA[A dramatically fewer number of children in the U.S. have received flu vaccinations in 2024, compared to last year, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/child-flu-vaccinations-decline-double-digits-pediatric-deaths-soar-cdc-472829</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Dec 2024 16:00:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Republican Seeks to Ban Sex Toys from Pharmacies to Keep Kids from 'Being Exposed to Obscene Devices While Shopping for Toothpaste']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-republican-seeks-ban-sex-toys-pharmacies-keep-kids-being-expose-obscene-devices-while-472826 <description><![CDATA[A Republican lawmaker from Texas has voiced her concerns regarding the presence of sex toys and sexually explicit items within common grocery stores and supermarkets such as Walmart and Target.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-republican-seeks-ban-sex-toys-pharmacies-keep-kids-being-expose-obscene-devices-while-472826</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:41:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Americans Are Sicker for Longer Than Any Other Country, New Bombshell Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-are-sicker-longer-any-other-country-new-bombshel​​l-study-finds-472824 <description><![CDATA[While people are living longer, they're also spending more time sick, according to the American Medical Association]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-are-sicker-longer-any-other-country-new-bombshel​​l-study-finds-472824</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:48:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump Floats Getting Rid of 'Some' Vaccinations: 'If I Think It's Dangerous']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trump-floats-getting-rid-some-vaccinations-if-i-think-its-dangerous-472822 <description><![CDATA[President-elect Donald Trump floated the idea of getting rid of "some" vaccinations if he believes they are "dangerous."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trump-floats-getting-rid-some-vaccinations-if-i-think-its-dangerous-472822</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:17:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Crossed 35? You Need To Watch Your Weight To Reduce Breast Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/crossed-35-you-need-watch-your-weight-reduce-breast-cancer-risk-472819 <description><![CDATA[The study found that women who gained more than 10 kg after age 35 had a 41% higher risk of developing breast cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/crossed-35-you-need-watch-your-weight-reduce-breast-cancer-risk-472819</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Dec 2024 04:31:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are You Blowing Nose Correctly? Doctor Reveals How Incorrect Technique Leads To Nose Bleeds And Ear Infections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-you-blowing-nose- Correctly-doctor-reveals-how-in Correct-technique-leads-nose-bleeds-ear-472818 <description><![CDATA[For those puzzled about whether there's a correct way to bow the nose, a board-certified pediatric allergist cautions that an incorrect technique can lead to nose bleeds and ear infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-you-blowing-nose- Correctly-doctor-reveals-how-in Correct-technique-leads-nose-bleeds-ear-472818</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Dec 2024 03:29:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Young Mom Diagnosed With Stage 4 Breast Cancer Weeks After Clear Mammogram Reveals Overlooked Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/young-mom-diagnosed-stage-4-breast-cancer-weeks-after-clear-mammogram-reveals-overlooked-symptoms-472815 <description><![CDATA[The 31-year-old nurse and mother from New Jersey received the news of stage 4 breast cancer diagnosis, weeks after her mammogram cleared her of the disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/young-mom-diagnosed-stage-4-breast-cancer-weeks-after-clear-mammogram-reveals-overlooked-symptoms-472815</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Dec 2024 01:34:37 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>