<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一个</language><item><title><![CDATA[Behavioral Therapy For Insomnia May Lower Risk Of Postpartum Depression: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/behavioral-therapy-insomnia-may-lower-risk-postpartum-depression-study-472614 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that getting cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBTi) may serve as a protective factor against postpartum depression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/behavioral-therapy-insomnia-may-lower-risk-postpartum-depression-study-472614</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:32:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Less Sugar In First 1000 Days Of Life Slashes Diabetes, Hypertension Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-sugar-first-1000-days-life-slashes-diabetes-hypertension-risk-study-472612 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that limiting sugar intake during early life could cut the diabetes risk by 35% and the risk of hypertension by 20%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-sugar-first-1000-days-life-slashes-diabetes-hypertension-risk-study-472612</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:07:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Red and Infrared Light Therapy Devices for Enhanced Health and Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-red-infrared-light-therapy-devices-enhanced-health-wellness-472547 <description><![CDATA[Red and infrared light therapy devices offer a plethora of benefits for those seeking to enhance their health and well-being. From promoting wound healing to improving skin health and alleviating pain, these innovative tools are paving the way for a holistic approach to health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-red-infrared-light-therapy-devices-enhanced-health-wellness-472547</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:35:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Electric Toothbrushes for Superior Cleaning and Personalized Dental Care]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-electric-toothbrushes-superior-cleaning-personalized-dental-care-472545 <description><![CDATA[Electric toothbrushes offer superior cleaning with features like multiple brushing modes, built-in timers, and pressure sensors. They provide personalized care through smart technology and are ideal for sensitive teeth. With oscillating movements, replaceable heads, and long battery life, they make professional-level dental care accessible at home.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-electric-toothbrushes-superior-cleaning-personalized-dental-care-472545</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:33:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Autism Rates Surge: U.S. Cases Nearly Tripled Over Past Decade, Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/autism-rates-surge-us-cases-nearly-tripled-over-past-decade-study-reveals-472610 <description><![CDATA[The study examined autism diagnosis trends in the U.S. from 2011 to 2022, revealing a significant 175% spike in rates.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/autism-rates-surge-us-cases-nearly-tripled-over-past-decade-study-reveals-472610</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Oct 2024 03:39:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bird Flu Virus Detected In U.S. Pig For First Time, H5N1 Case In Oregon]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-virus-Detected-us-pig-first-time-h5n1-case-oregon-472608 <description><![CDATA[Officials are investigating the case of the H5N1 virus on an Oregon farm where the virus was found in a pig.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-virus-Detected-us-pig-first-time-h5n1-case-oregon-472608</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Oct 2024 02:37:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Doctors Forced a Miscarrying Woman to Wait Nearly 2 Days Before Receiving Treatment. She Died of a Preventable Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doctors-forced-miscarrying-woman-wait-nearly-2-days-before-receiving-treatment-she-died-472606 <description><![CDATA[A Texas woman died from a preventable infection infection because doctors "had to wait until there was no heartbeat," per state law, before treating her miscarriage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doctors-forced-miscarrying-woman-wait-nearly-2-days-before-receiving-treatment-she-died-472606</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Oct 2024 11:08:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Late Menopause Linked To Greater Risk Of Asthma: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/late-menopause-linked-greater-risk-asthma-study-472603 <description><![CDATA[Entering menopause at a later age is linked to a greater risk for asthma, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/late-menopause-linked-greater-risk-asthma-study-472603</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Oct 2024 04:35:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Over 8 Million New Cases Reported As Tuberculosis Resurges As Top Killer: WHO]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-8-million-new-cases-reported-tuberculosis-resurges-top-killer-who-472600 <description><![CDATA[Tuberculosis is making a resurgence, infecting an estimated 8.2 million people in 2023; the highest surge in new cases since 1995, a WHO report reveals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-8-million-new-cases-reported-tuberculosis-resurges-top-killer-who-472600</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Oct 2024 04:12:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Weekend Warriors' Reap Cognitive Benefits Comparable To Regular Gym Goers: Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weekend-warriors-reap-cognitive-benefits-comparable-regular-gym-goers-study-finds-472598 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that 13% of mild dementia cases might be avoided if all middle-aged adults exercised at least once or twice a week.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weekend-warriors-reap-cognitive-benefits-comparable-regular-gym-goers-study-finds-472598</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Oct 2024 01:37:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New UTI Drug Gets FDA Approval: Alternative For Patients With Limited Antibacterial Treatment Options]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-uti-drug-gets-fda-approval-alternative-患者-limited-antibacterial-treatment-options-472596 <description><![CDATA[Orlynvah, an oral tablet from drug manufacturer Iterum Therapeutics, combining sulopenem etzadroxil and probenecid has been approved for use specifically for treating uncomplicated urinary tract infections (UTIs) in adult women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-uti-drug-gets-fda-approval-alternative-患者-limited-antibacterial-treatment-options-472596</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Oct 2024 06:01:36 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>