<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[8-hour Time-Restricted Eating Associated With Higher Risk Of Death From Heart Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-hour-time-restricted-eating-linked-higher-risk-death-heart-disease-study-471523 <description><![CDATA[The study found that people who followed an 8-hour time-restricted eating schedule had a 91% higher risk of cardiovascular death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-hour-time-restricted-eating-linked-higher-risk-death-heart-disease-study-471523</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Mar 2024 04:15:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Says 129,000 Kids In Chicago Under 6 Exposed To Lead-Contaminated Water]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-129000-kids-chicago-under-6-expose-lead-contamerated-water-471522 <description><![CDATA[The study also identified disparities in exposure levels and testing rates among different racial groups, highlighting racial inequities in the context of lead exposure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-129000-kids-chicago-under-6-expose-lead-contamerated-water-471522</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Mar 2024 02:51:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Urges Vaccination, Updates Travel Advisory Amid Surge In Measles Cases]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-urges-vaccination-updates-travel-advisory-amid-surge-measles-cases-471521 <description><![CDATA[In the revised guideline, the CDC has advised one dose of MMR vaccine for children aged 6 to 11 months if they are traveling abroad.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-urges-vaccination-updates-travel-advisory-amid-surge-measles-cases-471521</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Mar 2024 01:49:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Intense Exercise Boosts Hormone In Breast Milk That Protects Babies Against Diabetes: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intense-exercise-boosts-hormone-breast-milk-that-regulates-metabolism-prevent-diabetes-study-471520 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that breast milk becomes particularly beneficial for babies when mothers engage in high-intensity exercise.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intense-exercise-boosts-hormone-breast-milk-that-regulates-metabolism-prevent-diabetes-study-471520</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:35:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare, Dangerous Bacterial Infection Surges In Japan: Know All About Streptococcal Toxic Shock Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-dangerous-bacterial-infection-surges-japan-know-all-about-streptococcal-毒-shock-syndrome-471518 <description><![CDATA[A dangerous bacterial infection causing tissue damage is on the rise in Japan, with authorities facing challenges in determining its cause.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-dangerous-bacterial-infection-surges-japan-know-all-about-streptococcal-毒-shock-syndrome-471518</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:00:11 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Women More At Risk Of Shock In Car Crashes Than Men: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-more-risk-shock-car-crashes-men-study-471516 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that female victims surpassed a shock index greater than 1.0 more frequently than men, even in cases when they had fewer total or less severe injuries compared to men.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-more-risk-shock-car-crashes-men-study-471516</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:58:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eczema Linked To Learning, Memory Difficulties In Children With Neurodevelopmental Comorbidities: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eczema-linked-learning-memory-difficulties-children-neurodevelopmental-comorbidities-study-471514 <description><![CDATA[In children with neurodevelopmental comorbidities such as learning disabilities, eczema raised the risk of cognitive impairment two to threefold times compared to those without eczema.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eczema-linked-learning-memory-difficulties-children-neurodevelopmental-comorbidities-study-471514</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Mar 2024 04:20:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Sleep Day: Here's What Happens When You Don't Get Enough Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-sleep-day-heres-what-happens-when-you-dont-get-enough-sleep-471512 <description><![CDATA[During this World Sleep Day, it's crucial to understand the importance of sleep and know the consequences of inadequate sleep.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-sleep-day-heres-what-happens-when-you-dont-get-enough-sleep-471512</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Mar 2024 02:48:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Animal Vs Plant Protein: Study Suggests The Better Choice For Quality Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/animal-vs-plant- Protein-study-suggests-better-choice-quality-sleep-471510 <description><![CDATA[Researchers of a recent study investigated how protein intake impacts sleep quality and identified the superior protein source that could improve sleep.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/animal-vs-plant- Protein-study-suggests-better-choice-quality-sleep-471510</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Mar 2024 01:21:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Spending Quality Time With A Dog Can Reduce Stress, Improve Concentration: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spending-quality-time-dog-can-reduce-stress-improve-concentration-study-471509 <description><![CDATA[The study analyzed how various types of interactions with dogs can affect human brainwave patterns.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spending-quality-time-dog-can-reduce-stress-improve-concentration-study-471509</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Mar 2024 05:18:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tapeworm Found In Man's Brain From Eating Undercooked Bacon: Know Risks Of Neurocysticercosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tapeworm-found-mans-brain-eating-undercooked-bacon-know-risks-neurocysticercosis-471508 <description><![CDATA[A 52-year-old man in Florida with severe migraines was diagnosed with neurocysticercosis after doctors discovered tapeworm larvae in his brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tapeworm-found-mans-brain-eating-undercooked-bacon-know-risks-neurocysticercosis-471508</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:37:24 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>