<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Plant-Based Milk Alternatives Linked To Increased Risk Of Depression: Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/plant-based-milk-alternatives-linked-increased-risk-depression-study-reveals-472932 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that drinking plant-based milk alternatives, such as soy, oat, and almond milk, is linked to an increased risk of depression, while semi-skimmed cow's milk may offer protective benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/plant-based-milk-alternatives-linked-increased-risk-depression-study-reveals-472932</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 04:12:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teen's Breast Grew To Triple G-Cup Size After COVID Vaccinations: Researchers Call It 'Exceedingly Rare']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-breast-grew-triple-g-cup-size-after-covid-vaccinations-researchers-call-it-exceedingly-472931 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have identified the condition as Pseudoangiomatous stromal hyperplasia (PASH)-associated gigantomastia, an "exceedingly rare" condition linked to COVID-19 vaccination.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-breast-grew-triple-g-cup-size-after-covid-vaccinations-researchers-call-it-exceedingly-472931</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:43:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bird Flu Claims First US Victim As Louisiana Man Dies in Hospital]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-claims-first-us-victim-louisiana-man-dies-hospital-472929 <description><![CDATA[A patient that had been hospitalized with avian influenza, otherwise known as bird flu, has died following a stay in the hospital.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-claims-first-us-victim-louisiana-man-dies-hospital-472929</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:45:48 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Governor Blocks Bill Allowing Doctors to Disagree with the Medical Opinions of State Officials]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-governor-blocks-bill-allowing-doctors-disagree-medical-opinions-state-officials-472928 <description><![CDATA[Gov. Mike DeWine blocked a bill seeking to protect medical professionals from disciplinary action for stating opinions that contradict state health officials.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-governor-blocks-bill-allowing-doctors-disagree-medical-opinions-state-officials-472928</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:39:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Revolutionizing Men's Health: A Deep Dive Into Justin Pulliam's Innovative Approach To Sexual Wellness And Hormone Therapy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/revolutionizing-mens-health-deep-dive-justin-pulliams-innovative-approach- Sex-wellness-472926 <description><![CDATA[Nearly 40 percent of men over the age of 40 experience some degree of erectile dysfunction, according to the Cleveland Clinic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/revolutionizing-mens-health-deep-dive-justin-pulliams-innovative-approach- Sex-wellness-472926</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:39:32 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[It Is Now Illegal to Use AI to Deny a Medically Necessary Health Insurance Claim in California]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/it-now-illegal-use-ai-deny-medically-necessary-health-insurance-claim-california-472923 <description><![CDATA[It is now illegal to use artificial intelligence to deny any medically necessary health insurance claims in California now that a new bill has gone into effect.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/it-now-illegal-use-ai-deny-medically-necessary-health-insurance-claim-california-472923</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:06:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sitting Isn't Always Bad: Here Are Activities Beneficial For Brain Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sitting-isnt-always-bad-here-are-activities-beneficial-brain-health-472919 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that the effects of sedentary behavior on brain health depend largely on the type of activity that you engage in.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sitting-isnt-always-bad-here-are-activities-beneficial-brain-health-472919</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 Jan 2025 04:59:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Starting A New Diet For 2025? Nearly Half Of Americans Make It Their New Year's Resolution]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/starting-new-diet-2025-nearly-half-americans-make-it-their-new-years-resolution-472918 <description><![CDATA[The survey conducted by the Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine/Morning Consult revealed that 46% of U.S. adults plan to start a new diet for the New Year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/starting-new-diet-2025-nearly-half-americans-make-it-their-new-years-resolution-472918</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:30:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tularemia Cases Surge 56% In U.S., CDC Reports: What To Know About Rabbit Fever]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tularemia-cases-surge-56-us-cdc-reports-what-know-about-rabbit-fever-472916 <description><![CDATA[Tularemia or Rabbit fever is a rare but serious zoonotic disease that poses significant risks to human health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tularemia-cases-surge-56-us-cdc-reports-what-know-about-rabbit-fever-472916</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:05:56 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breakfast For Healthy Aging: Here's How Many Calories You Need For Morning Meal]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakfast-healthy-aging-heres-how-much-calories-you-need-morning-meal-472915 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now found that it's not only essential to have breakfast, but also to ensure that it is both high in quality and appropriate in quantity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakfast-healthy-aging-heres-how-much-calories-you-need-morning-meal-472915</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 Jan 2025 02:09:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[HMPV Cases Spike In China: Know About Highly Contagious Respiratory Illness Without A Vaccine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hmpv-cases-spike-china-know-about-highly-contagious-respiratory-illness-without-vaccine-472914 <description><![CDATA[Health officials worldwide are on high alert as China reports a surge in infections caused by human metapneumovirus (HMPV), a highly contagious respiratory virus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hmpv-cases-spike-china-know-about-highly-contagious-respiratory-illness-without-vaccine-472914</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 Jan 2025 01:09:30 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>