<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Why Are Heart Attacks More Common On Christmas Day? Doctor Explains Winter Surge And Warning Signs]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-are-heart-attacks-more-common-christmas-day-doctor-explains-winter-surge-warning-signs-472874 <description><![CDATA[As the holiday season brings festive cheer and celebration, beware of a secret risk that quietly looms on Christmas Day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-are-heart-attacks-more-common-christmas-day-doctor-explains-winter-surge-warning-signs-472874</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:29:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling With Constipation? Try These Foods For Relief—One May Lower Colorectal Cancer Risk, Says Doctor]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-constipation-try-these-foods-reliefone-may-lower-colorectal-cancer-risk-says-doctor-472871 <description><![CDATA[For those tired of listening to age-old add more fiber to diet advice, here's something more specific that you can try.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-constipation-try-these-foods-reliefone-may-lower-colorectal-cancer-risk-says-doctor-472871</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Dec 2024 03:47:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Nutcracker Syndrome Puts 28-Year-Old In Excruciating Pain For Nearly A Decade, Docs Initially Dismissed It As Bad Periods]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-nutcracker-syndrome-puts-28-year-old-excruciating-pain-nearly-decade-docs-initially-472870 <description><![CDATA[The woman diagnosed with the rare and debilitating nutcracker syndrome struggles to imagine a life without pain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-nutcracker-syndrome-puts-28-year-old-excruciating-pain-nearly-decade-docs-initially-472870</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Dec 2024 01:04:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Who Spent Days in Hospital with Painful Open Wound Waiting to Be Stitched Up Ends Up Losing Entire Leg]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-spent-days-hospital-painful-open-wound-loses-leg-canada-472868 <description><![CDATA[A Canadian woman lost her right leg after spending days in the hospital with an untreated infection following a knee replacement surgery.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-spent-days-hospital-painful-open-wound-loses-leg-canada-472868</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:28:46 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Not Just For Smokers: Young Non-Smoker Died Of Terminal Lung Cancer After Symptoms Were Initially Dismissed As Anxiety]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-just-smokers-young-non-smoker-died-terminal-lung-cancer-after-symptoms-were-initially-472865 <description><![CDATA[When the 36-year-old fit and healthy man who never smoked experienced complaints of chest pain, doctors initially attributed it to anxiety and increased his medication.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-just-smokers-young-non-smoker-died-terminal-lung-cancer-after-symptoms-were-initially-472865</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Dec 2024 04:02:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Felt Trapped In My Own Body': Kimberly Williams-Paisley Opens Up About Losing Voice To Muscle Tension Dysphonia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/felt-trapped-my-own-body-kimberly-williams-paisley-opens-about-losing-voice-muscle-tension-472863 <description><![CDATA[Williams-Paisley who was diagnosed with muscle tension dysphonia in 2023, regained her voice through a life-changing surgery this year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/felt-trapped-my-own-body-kimberly-williams-paisley-opens-about-losing-voice-muscle-tension-472863</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:36:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bird Flu Crisis: Louisiana Reports First Severe Human Case, California Declares Emergency Over Dairy Outbreak]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-crisis-louisiana-reports-first-severe- human-case-california-declares-emergency-over-472860 <description><![CDATA[California, the nation's most populous state, has declared a state of emergency after the virus struck hundreds of dairy herds, while Louisiana reports the first severe human case in a hospitalized patient.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-crisis-louisiana-reports-first-severe- human-case-california-declares-emergency-over-472860</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:51:56 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A 9-Year-Old Girl Raised $30K for a Prosthetic Arm After Being Denied Coverage. Then She Gave It All Away to Help Someone Else]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-year-old-girl-raised-30k-prosthetic-arm-after-being-denied-coverage-then-she-gave-it-all-472858 <description><![CDATA[A young girl is using her GoFundMe donations to pay for two other limb-different kids whose insurance claims for prosthetic arms were denied.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-year-old-girl-raised-30k-prosthetic-arm-after-being-denied-coverage-then-she-gave-it-all-472858</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Dec 2024 10:31:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Jobs That Save Lives? People In Certain Professions May Be At Reduced Risk Of Alzheimer's Death]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/jobs-that-save-lives-people-certain-professions-may-reduced-risk-alzheimers-death-472857 <description><![CDATA[Professions requiring constant navigation, such as taxi and ambulance drivers, might be at an advantage as a recent study found these workers have a reduced risk of death from Alzheimer's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/jobs-that-save-lives-people-certain-professions-may-reduced-risk-alzheimers-death-472857</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Dec 2024 02:50:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mom Mistakes Bloating For Period Symptoms, Told She's Too Young—Then Diagnosed With Terminal Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mom-mistakes-bloating-period-symptoms-told-shes-too-youngthen-diagnosed-terminal-cancer-472855 <description><![CDATA[The 28-year-old mother diagnosed with terminal ovarian cancer urges women not to ignore symptoms like bloating, which she initially mistook for a sign of her period.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mom-mistakes-bloating-period-symptoms-told-shes-too-youngthen-diagnosed-terminal-cancer-472855</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:43:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Pills For Hot Flashes? FDA Issues Strongest Warning On A Menopausal Drug Linked To Serious Liver Injury]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-pills-hot-flashes-fda-issues-strongest-warning-menopausal-drug-linked-serious-liver-472853 <description><![CDATA[The FDA has issued its strongest safety alert, a boxed warning, on a menopausal drug linked to severe liver injury.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-pills-hot-flashes-fda-issues-strongest-warning-menopausal-drug-linked-serious-liver-472853</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Dec 2024 00:31:16 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>