<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA[How Does Magnesium Deficiency Affect Health? Watch Out For Signs]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-does-magnesium-deficiency-affect-health-watch-out-signs-470174 <description><![CDATA[From supporting muscle and nerve function to energy production, regulation of blood pressure and enzyme reactions, magnesium is essential for staying fit and healthy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-does-magnesium-deficiency-affect-health-watch-out-signs-470174</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:29:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mounting Evidence Points To Wuhan Lab As Source Of COVID-19 Outbreak]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mounting-evidence-points-wuhan-lab-source-covid-19-outbreak-470173 <description><![CDATA[U.S. taxpayer funds might have been allocated to the controversial Wuhan laboratory before the pandemic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mounting-evidence-points-wuhan-lab-source-covid-19-outbreak-470173</guid><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:59:37 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[North Korea Faces Severe Food Crisis Amid Ongoing COVID-19 Measures]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/north-korea-faces-severe-food-crisis-amid-ongoing-covid-19-measures-470171 <description><![CDATA[North Korea reportedly faces its most severe food crisis since the 1990s famine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/north-korea-faces-severe-food-crisis-amid-ongoing-covid-19-measures-470171</guid><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:51:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[West Nile Virus Cases Reported Across Multiple States, Health Officials Urge Vigilance]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-virus-cases-reported-across-multiple-states-health-officials-urge-vigilance-470169 <description><![CDATA[There has been an alarming uptick in West Nile virus cases in the country.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-virus-cases-reported-across-multiple-states-health-officials-urge-vigilance-470169</guid><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:46:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Florida Could Be The Epicenter Of Mpox Summer Outbreak: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-could-epicenter-mpox-summer-outbreak-report-470167 <description><![CDATA[Recent data point to Florida being at the highest risk of seeing the most mpox cases this summer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-could-epicenter-mpox-summer-outbreak-report-470167</guid><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:43:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[China's Omission Of Cremation Data Raises Questions About COVID-19 Impact]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chinas-omission-cremation-data-raises-questions-about-covid-19-impact-470166 <description><![CDATA[The absence of data suggested that the number of excess deaths could be significant.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chinas-omission-cremation-data-raises-questions-about-covid-19-impact-470166</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:44:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Reveals Alarming Mortality Rates For COVID-Associated Fungal Infections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-alarming-mortality-rates-covid-associated-fungal-infections-470164 <description><![CDATA[A study uncovered alarming mortality rates among people who had COVID-associated fungal infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-alarming-mortality-rates-covid-associated-fungal-infections-470164</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:41:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Gut Bacteria Could Be Causing Endometriosis, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-gut-bacteria-could-causing-endometriosis-study-says-470163 <description><![CDATA[Research suggests antibiotics could target the bacteria associated with gut bacteria, affecting 10% of women and girls worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-gut-bacteria-could-causing-endometriosis-study-says-470163</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:38:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Overdose Deaths: Men In The US At Higher Risk Than Women, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/overdose-deaths-men-us-higher-risk-women-says-study-470156 <description><![CDATA[Men are 2-3 times more likely to die from drug overdose than women, according to Icahn School of Medicine and the U.S.  National Institute on Drug Abuse.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/overdose-deaths-men-us-higher-risk-women-says-study-470156</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:38:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fresh Veggies Day: 5 Healthy Greens To Include In Your Diet]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fresh-veggies-day-5-healthy-greens-include-your-diet-470160 <description><![CDATA[Fresh Veggies Day is observed on June 16 every year to encourage people to increase their daily intake of fresh vegetables and to recognize their nutritional role in boosting human health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fresh-veggies-day-5-healthy-greens-include-your-diet-470160</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:55:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Light Exercise After Concussion Reduces Healing Time: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/light-exercise-after-concussion-reduces-healing-time-study-470158 <description><![CDATA[The athletes who do light exercise within 48 hours of a concussion are more likely to resolve the symptoms than those who do not exercise.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/light-exercise-after-concussion-reduces-healing-time-study-470158</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 01:50:59 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>