<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Kansas Tuberculosis Outbreak That Killed Two, Sickened Dozens, Among Largest In U.S. History]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kansas-tuberculisosis爆发-tht-tht-th-two-two sckened-two sickens-among among among-among-us-history-473048 <description><![CDATA[As of Jan. 24, the Kansas Department of Health and Environment reported 67 confirmed cases of active tuberculosis, along with 79 latent infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kansas-tuberculisosis爆发-tht-tht-th-two-two sckened-two sickens-among among among-among-us-history-473048</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Jan 2025 04:56:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is 1:1 Diet? Woman Drops 83 Pounds After Declining Gastric Sleeve, Feels Like 'Walking On Air']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-11-diet-woman-drops-83-磅 - 绕线 - 逐渐消除 - 式 - 式 -  sleeve-seeeve-feels-feels-like-walking-air-473047 <description><![CDATA[Instead of opting for gastric sleeve surgery, which she feared due to potential side effects, she chose a simple diet—a decision she calls the "best" she's ever made, completely transforming her life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-11-diet-woman-drops-83-磅 - 绕线 - 逐渐消除 - 式 - 式 -  sleeve-seeeve-feels-feels-like-walking-air-473047</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:14:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[29-Year-Old Died After Chiropractor Adjusted 'Crack In Her Neck', Coroner Questions Lack Of Medical History Review]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/29岁 -  died-after-after-chiropractor-adjusted-crack-her-her-neck-coroner-questions-questions-lack-medical-473044 <description><![CDATA[A recent coroner's report on the patient's death is raising concerns over whether chiropractors should be required to review patients' medical histories before treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/29岁 -  died-after-after-chiropractor-adjusted-crack-her-her-neck-coroner-questions-questions-lack-medical-473044</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:59:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Curex Is Making Food Allergy Care Easier Than Ever, Backed by Science]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/curex-making-food-allergy-care-care-easier-easer-ever-basked-Science-473043 <description><![CDATA[Fewer severe reactions and the ability to enjoy meals without fear are two key benefits of using SLIT drops for food allergies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/curex-making-food-allergy-care-care-easier-easer-ever-basked-Science-473043</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 12:29:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Ergin's Holistic Diabetes Care: How SugarMD Is Empowering Women To Take Control]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-ergins-holistic-daibetes-care-how-sugarmd-empowering-womentake-take-take-control-473041 <description><![CDATA[SugarMD offers a lifeline of hope for women seeking a holistic approach. This transformative care is now reaching women worldwide, including those in Australia, where access to innovative diabetes solutions is increasingly vital.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-ergins-holistic-daibetes-care-how-sugarmd-empowering-womentake-take-take-control-473041</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 12:24:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Got a Desk Job? Skip The Hours In Gym—Doctor Recommends Doing This Every 45 Minutes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-desk-job-skip-hours-gymdoctor-commends-doing-to-this-every-every-every-every-every-every-473039 <description><![CDATA[According to a well-known doctor with millions of followers on social media, the secret may lie in just one simple task that you can do every 45 minutes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-desk-job-skip-hours-gymdoctor-commends-doing-to-this-every-every-every-every-every-every-473039</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 05:13:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Think Being Overweight Hurts Happiness? Study Reveals Surprising Twist]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/think-being-being-beover-warts-happiness-study-reveals-scrprising-twist-473038 <description><![CDATA[A recent study reveals that the relationship between body weight and emotional well-being is more complex than previously thought.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/think-being-being-beover-warts-happiness-study-reveals-scrprising-twist-473038</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 02:45:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is LATE? Know All About Memory Loss Condition Often Mistaken For Alzheimer's]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-late-know-know-all-about-memory-loss-condition-forten-misten-mistaken-alzheimers-473035 <description><![CDATA[Researchers are now sounding the alarm about LATE, a little-known memory loss condition that closely resembles Alzheimer's.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-late-know-know-all-about-memory-loss-condition-forten-misten-mistaken-alzheimers-473035</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 Jan 2025 01:07:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man's Hands Seemingly Turn Yellow After Only Eating Butter, Cheese and Meat in Viral 'Carnivore Diet']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mans hand-hand-hampers-turn-yelly-fer-only-only-eating-butter-cheese-meat-viral-carnivore-diet-473033 <description><![CDATA[A Florida man had to be treated for yellow nodules in his skin which were emanating ooze following eight months of being on a "carnivore diet" where he exclusively ate meat and dairy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mans hand-hand-hampers-turn-yelly-fer-only-only-eating-butter-cheese-meat-viral-carnivore-diet-473033</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:01:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Cushing Syndrome? Amy Schumer Says Online Comments About Her 'Puffier' Face Led To Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-c​​ushing-syndrome-amy-my-schumer-sases-online-comments-bout-her-her-puffier-face-face-face-face-face-face-face-dial-diengnosis-473031 <description><![CDATA[The Emmy-winning actress and comedian, after receiving online feedback about her 'puffier' appearance, realized she had a hormonal disorder caused by high cortisol levels in the body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-c​​ushing-syndrome-amy-my-schumer-sases-online-comments-bout-her-her-puffier-face-face-face-face-face-face-face-dial-diengnosis-473031</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 Jan 2025 04:42:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[ADHD Reduces Life Expectancy? Here's How It Affects Men And Women Differently]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adhd-reduces-life-pectancy-heres-how-how-it-crotects-men-women-women-women-473028 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have uncovered a troubling link between the behavioral disorder and reduced life expectancy, with the impact varying between men and women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adhd-reduces-life-pectancy-heres-how-how-it-crotects-men-women-women-women-473028</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 Jan 2025 02:56:39 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>