<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Vitamin D Deficiency In Kids Raises Risk Of Auto-Immune Disorders: Study Explains How]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-deficiency-kids-raises-risk-auto-immune-disorders-study-explains-how-472563 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed how a deficiency of vitamin D in young children can raise the risk of developing autoimmune disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-deficiency-kids-raises-risk-auto-immune-disorders-study-explains-how-472563</guid><pubDate> Tue, 22 Oct 2024 05:22:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Warns Of Unusual Rise In Walking Pneumonia Cases Among Young Children]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-unusual-rise-walking-pneumonia-cases-among-young-children-472561 <description><![CDATA[According to the latest CDC report, this year has seen a spike in cases since late spring, particularly among young children, a shift from previous years when most cases were reported in school-aged children and adolescents.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-unusual-rise-walking-pneumonia-cases-among-young-children-472561</guid><pubDate> Tue, 22 Oct 2024 03:48:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Strokes Can Be Deadly But Preventable: Guidelines To Reduce Your Risk Of First Stroke]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/中风-can-deadly-preventable-guidelines-reduce-your-risk-first-中风-472559 <description><![CDATA[The current stroke prevention guidelines issued by the American Stroke Association replace the 2014 guidelines and target the prevention of the first stroke.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/中风-can-deadly-preventable-guidelines-reduce-your-risk-first-中风-472559</guid><pubDate> Tue, 22 Oct 2024 02:11:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[RSV Vaccine Effective In Cutting Hospitalization In Older Adults, Immunocompromised Individuals: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rsv-vaccine- effective-cutting-hospitalization-older-adults-immunocompromished-individuals-study-472558 <description><![CDATA[The analysis showed that the RSV vaccine is highly effective, reducing the risk of hospitalization due to infection complications by 80%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rsv-vaccine- effective-cutting-hospitalization-older-adults-immunocompromished-individuals-study-472558</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Oct 2024 05:39:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Simple Blood Test Before Labor May Help Predict Preeclampsia: Researchers Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-blood-test-before-labor-may-help-predict-preeclampsia-researchers-say-472557 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that a simple blood work ratio can predict a woman's risk of developing preeclampsia as she enters the hospital in labor.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-blood-test-before-labor-may-help-predict-preeclampsia-researchers-say-472557</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Oct 2024 03:46:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Florida Sees Spike In Flesh-Eating Bacteria Cases After Hurricanes, Health Officials Warn]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-sees-spike-flesh-eating-bacteria-cases-after-hurricanes-health-officials-warn-472554 <description><![CDATA[Florida health officials are warning residents to stay out of floodwaters, as cases of flesh-eating bacteria have surged following hurricanes Helene and Milton.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-sees-spike-flesh-eating-bacteria-cases-after-hurricanes-health-officials-warn-472554</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Oct 2024 02:10:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Standing No Better Than Sitting: No Cardiovascular Benefits, Raises Circulatory Risks; Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stand-no-better-sitting-no-cardioangio-benefits-raises-circulatory-risks-study-finds-472553 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that for every additional 30 minutes spent standing beyond two hours, the risk of circulatory disease increased by 11 percent]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stand-no-better-sitting-no-cardioangio-benefits-raises-circulatory-risks-study-finds-472553</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Oct 2024 06:27:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Vaccine Linked To Elevated Risk Of Facial Palsy: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-vaccine-linked-elevated-risk-facial-palsy-study-472551 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed a 12% increase in the risk of facial palsy within 1 to 28 days after any COVID-19 vaccine dose.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-vaccine-linked-elevated-risk-facial-palsy-study-472551</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Oct 2024 03:34:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Whooping Cough Hits Decade High: Know Symptoms, Learn How To Protect Yourself]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/whooping-cough-hits-decade-high-know-symptoms-learn-how-protect-yourself-472548 <description><![CDATA[The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) warns that pertussis, which saw a decline during the pandemic, is now returning to pre-pandemic levels or even exceeding them.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/whooping-cough-hits-decade-high-know-symptoms-learn-how-protect-yourself-472548</guid><pubDate> Fri, 18 Oct 2024 01:41:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Under Eye Patches: Your Solution For Puffiness, Dark Circles, And Fine Lines]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-under-eye-patches-your-solution-puffiness-dark-circles-fine-lines-472478 <description><![CDATA[This article explores the 25 best under-eye patches available today, detailing their effectiveness in reducing puffiness, dark circles, and fine lines. Under-eye patches are a convenient skincare solution designed to hydrate, rejuvenate, and brighten the delicate skin around the eyes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-under-eye-patches-your-solution-puffiness-dark-circles-fine-lines-472478</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:13:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Take Breaks Between Walks: Researchers Say It Helps Burn More Calories]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-breaks- Between-walks-researchers-say-it-helps-burn-more-calories-472544 <description><![CDATA[Doing short bouts of walking or climbing stairs requires more oxygen and energy compared to long strolls, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-breaks- Between-walks-researchers-say-it-helps-burn-more-calories-472544</guid><pubDate> Thu, 17 Oct 2024 05:15:18 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>