<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Can Eggs Prevent Dementia? Here's How Many To Eat For Beneficial Effects]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-eggs-prevent-dementia-heres-how-many-eat-beneficial-effects-472507 <description><![CDATA[Eating more than two eggs per day, or not consuming eggs at all, will not help with dementia risk, the study suggests]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-eggs-prevent-dementia-heres-how-many-eat-beneficial-effects-472507</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Oct 2024 05:12:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling With Sleep? Study Says Forever Chemicals Could Be Factor Among Young Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-sleep-study-says-forever-chemicals-could-factor-among-young-adults-472506 <description><![CDATA[The study found that higher levels of four specific types of PFAs  namely PFDA, PFHxS, PFOA, and PFOS could be linked to worsened sleep in young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-sleep-study-says-forever-chemicals-could-factor-among-young-adults-472506</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Oct 2024 03:25:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Flu Shots Less Effective In South: Why CDC Urges Vaccination Despite Similar U.S. Forecast]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-shots-less- effective-south-why-cdc-urges-vaccination-despite-similar-us-forecast-472504 <description><![CDATA[The flu shot reduced the risk of hospitalization among high-risk groups by 35% in five South American countries, Argentina, Brazil, Chile, Paraguay, and Uruguay, according to the interim vaccine effectiveness report by the CDC.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-shots-less- effective-south-why-cdc-urges-vaccination-despite-similar-us-forecast-472504</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Oct 2024 01:51:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Being Overweight Raises Pregnancy Complications Regardless Of Women's Country Of Birth: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-overweight-raises-pregnancy-complications-regardless-womens-country-birth-study-472501 <description><![CDATA[The findings suggest that promoting a healthy weight has the potential to prevent pregnancy complications for all women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-overweight-raises-pregnancy-complications-regardless-womens-country-birth-study-472501</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:54:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Promising Alzheimer's Drug May Prevent Tau Build-Up, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-promising-alzheimers-drug-may-prevent-tau-build-study-finds-472500 <description><![CDATA[The latest drug, RI-AG03, is a peptide inhibitor that blocks tau-build-up, acting at two regions of the protein, preventing it from sticking together.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-promising-alzheimers-drug-may-prevent-tau-build-study-finds-472500</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Oct 2024 03:56:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Warns Of Dangerous Counterfeit Drugs From Online Pharmacies, Highlighting Overdose Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-dangerous-counterfeit-drugs-online-pharmacies-highlighting-overdose-risk-472497 <description><![CDATA[The warning follows last week's U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) indictment of illegal online pharmacies selling counterfeit prescription pills laced with fentanyl and methamphetamine to tens of thousands of people in the U.S., leading to at least nine deaths.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-dangerous-counterfeit-drugs-online-pharmacies-highlighting-overdose-risk-472497</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Oct 2024 01:58:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Over Half Of Americans Follow Pro-Inflammatory Diets, Study Says: Here's What To Eat Instead]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-half-americans-follow-pro-炎症-diets-study-says-heres-what-eat-instead-472496 <description><![CDATA[According to the study, 57% of participants followed pro-inflammatory diets, while only 34% maintained anti-inflammatory diets.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-half-americans-follow-pro-炎症-diets-study-says-heres-what-eat-instead-472496</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Oct 2024 05:12:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Choose Water: Fizzy Drinks, Juices, And Excessive Coffee May Increase Stroke Risk, Study Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/choose-water-fizzy-drinks-juices-excessive-coffee-may-increase-中风-risk-study-warns-472493 <description><![CDATA[The researchers conducted two separate analyses, one exploring the effect of fizzy drinks, fruit juices, and water, and another related to tea and coffee consumption.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/choose-water-fizzy-drinks-juices-excessive-coffee-may-increase-中风-risk-study-warns-472493</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Oct 2024 02:49:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Reducing Smoking Prevalence To 5% Improves Longevity, Saves Millions Of Lives Worldwide: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reducing-smoking-prevalence-5-improves-longevity-saves-millions-lives-worldwide-study-472491 <description><![CDATA[By lowering the prevalence of smoking from current levels to just 5% everywhere, there will be a significant boost in life expectancy and prevent millions of premature deaths worldwide by 2050.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reducing-smoking-prevalence-5-improves-longevity-saves-millions-lives-worldwide-study-472491</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Oct 2024 01:26:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Acupressure Mats For Pain Relief, Stress Reduction And Enhanced Relaxation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-acuPressure-mats-pain-relief-stress-reduction-enhanced-relaxation-472448 <description><![CDATA[Acupressure mats are designed to promote relaxation, alleviate pain, and enhance overall well-being by stimulating pressure points throughout the body. These mats typically feature thousands of small, plastic spikes that apply gentle pressure to the skin, mimicking the effects of traditional acupressure therapy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-acuPressure-mats-pain-relief-stress-reduction-enhanced-relaxation-472448</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:14:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breast Cancer Deaths In U.S. Drop, But Cases Among Young Women On Rise, Study Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-deaths-us-drop-cases-among-young-women-rise-study-warns-472489 <description><![CDATA[According to the report, breast cancer rates increased by 1% annually from 2012 to 2021, with sharper rises among women under the age of 50 (1.4%).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-deaths-us-drop-cases-among-young-women-rise-study-warns-472489</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Oct 2024 02:20:39 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>