<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Busy Week? 'Weekend Warriors' Still Reap Brain Health Benefits, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/busy-week-weekend-warriors-still-reap-brain-health-benefits-says-study-472244 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that weekend warriors- those who pack their physical activity into one or two days of the week, typically on the weekend-can still reap the same brain health benefits of a regularly active pattern.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/busy-week-weekend-warriors-still-reap-brain-health-benefits-says-study-472244</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Sep 2024 01:15:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Glucomannan Supplements: Your Key To Weight Loss, Blood Sugar And Cholesterol Control]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-glucomannan-supplements-your-key-weight-loss-blood-sugar-cholesterol-control-472195 <description><![CDATA[Glucomannan is a dietary fiber derived from the root of the elephant yam, also known as the konjac plant, which is native to Asia. Traditionally, it has been used in Chinese medicine to treat intestinal disorders, prevent tumors, and soothe burns. It also has applications as a remedy for coughs, asthma, hernias, breast pain, and various blood and skin conditions. Modern research supports its use as a supplement for weight loss, cholesterol management, blood sugar control, and constipation relief.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-glucomannan-supplements-your-key-weight-loss-blood-sugar-cholesterol-control-472195</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:03:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Massage Chairs For Your Needs: Elevate Your Self-Care Routine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-massage-chairs-your-needs-elevate-your-self-care-routine-472215 <description><![CDATA[Best Massage Chairs offer a luxurious and therapeutic experience, providing relaxation and relief from muscle tension. They come with various features such as deep tissue massage, heat therapy, zero gravity reclining, and foot rollers. Some chairs even offer personalized massage experiences through body scanning technology.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-massage-chairs-your-needs-elevate-your-self-care-routine-472215</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:02:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Towel Warmers: Efficient Heating For Ultimate Comfort And Versatility]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-towel-warmers-efficient-heating-ultimate-comfort-versatility-472225 <description><![CDATA[Towel warmers come in various sizes and designs, efficiently heating towels to provide comfort and relaxation. Key features include rapid heating, adjustable timers, and large capacities. They are suitable for home use, spas, and salons, offering safety with automatic shut-off and versatility for heating towels and beauty tools.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-towel-warmers-efficient-heating-ultimate-comfort-versatility-472225</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:00:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Recent Recreational Drug Use In ICU Patients Triples Risk Of Repeat Cardiovascular Events: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/recent-recreational-drug-use-icu-病人-三重-风险-重复-心血管-事件-研究-472235 <description><![CDATA[The study explored how recent recreational drug use affects the risk of serious cardiovascular events, including death, over a year in nearly 1,400 patients admitted to ICUs across France.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/recent-recreational-drug-use-icu-病人-三重-风险-重复-心血管-事件-研究-472235</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Aug 2024 04:31:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Diabetes Treatment? Study Identifies Aquatic Plant That May Lower Blood Sugar Levels]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-diabetes-treatment-study-identizes-aquatic-plant-that-may-lower-blood-sugar-levels-472233 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered that supplementing with Mankai, a cultivated aquatic duckweed, after meals may help lower blood sugar levels in diabetic patients.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-diabetes-treatment-study-identizes-aquatic-plant-that-may-lower-blood-sugar-levels-472233</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:01:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[More Than Half Of World Faces Micronutrient Deficiencies: Study Warns Billions At Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-half-world-faces-micro Nutrition-deficiency-study-warns-billions-risk-472232 <description><![CDATA[The study provides the first global estimates of inadequate consumption of 15 micronutrients critical to human health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-half-world-faces-micro Nutrition-deficiency-study-warns-billions-risk-472232</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Aug 2024 01:30:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Andor Health Shifts Healthcare From Point-Based Solutions To Platform Play For Strategic Care Delivery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/andor-health-shifts-healthcare-point-based-solutions-platform-play-strategic-care-delivery-472226 <description><![CDATA[As healthcare delivery becomes more complex, providers are increasingly seeking a more integrated and strategic approach, one that not only meets immediate needs but also aligns with long-term goals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/andor-health-shifts-healthcare-point-based-solutions-platform-play-strategic-care-delivery-472226</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:14:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleep Debt Raises Heart Disease Risk, Study Says Here's How To Mitigate It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-debt-raises-heart-disease-risk-study-says-heres-how-mitigate-it-472222 <description><![CDATA[Catching up on lost sleep over the weekends might help offset sleep deficits from the week, and mitigate heart disease risk, the study suggests.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-debt-raises-heart-disease-risk-study-says-heres-how-mitigate-it-472222</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Aug 2024 04:30:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Diabetes, Pre-Diabetes Linked To Brain Aging, Healthy Lifestyle Counteracts The Effect: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-pre-diabetes-linked-brain-aging-healthy-lifestyle-counteracts-effect-study-472219 <description><![CDATA[The study showed that prediabetes was associated with a 0.5 increase in brain age and diabetes with a 2.3-year increase. However, by staying physically active, avoiding smoking, and moderating alcohol intake, you can significantly mitigate the impact.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diabetes-pre-diabetes-linked-brain-aging-healthy-lifestyle-counteracts-effect-study-472219</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Aug 2024 03:18:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Drug To Stop Migraine Before Onset? Study Says 73% Could Restore Normal Functioning]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-stop-migraine-before-onset-study-says-73-could-restore-normal-functioning-472216 <description><![CDATA[When taken at the onset of symptoms like sensitivity to light and sound, fatigue, neck pain, or dizziness, Ubrogepant helped 73% of migraine patients regain normal function, according to the study results.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-stop-migraine-before-onset-study-says-73-could-restore-normal-functioning-472216</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Aug 2024 01:50:08 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>