<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Don't Skip Vaccines: New Study Says Routine Shots May Protect You From Alzheimer's]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-skip-vaccines-new-study-says-routine-shots-may-protect-you-alzheimers-470705 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that people vaccinated against shingles, pneumococcus, tetanus and diphtheria, with or without an added pertussis vaccine, are at a 25% to 30% reduced risk of developing Alzheimer's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-skip-vaccines-new-study-says-routine-shots-may-protect-you-alzheimers-470705</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:19:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gut Health Revolution: Unveiling The Top 10 Probiotics Powerhouses Of 2023]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-health-revolution-unveiling-top-10-probiotics-powerhouses-2023-470459 <description><![CDATA[Embark on a gut health revolution as we unveil the top 10 probiotic powerhouses of 2023, offering insights into the world of digestive wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-health-revolution-unveiling-top-10-probiotics-powerhouses-2023-470459</guid><pubDate> Wed, 23 Aug 2023 04:49:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eye Scans To Detect Parkinson's? Researchers Say Retinal Imaging Can Diagnose It Years Before Symptoms Appear]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eye-scans-detect-parkinsons-researchers-say-retinal-imaging-can-diagnose-it-years-before-470702 <description><![CDATA[With the use of retinal imaging, Parkinson's disease can be diagnosed in people seven years before symptoms appear, researchers say.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eye-scans-detect-parkinsons-researchers-say-retinal-imaging-can-diagnose-it-years-before-470702</guid><pubDate> Wed, 23 Aug 2023 04:24:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Powassan Virus: Know About The Tick-Borne Illness That Transmits In No Time]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/powassan-virus-know-about-tick-borne-illness-that-transmits-no-time-470700 <description><![CDATA[Four people have tested positive for Powassan virus in Connecticut this year, health officials say. The virus gets transmitted in as little as 15 minutes following a tick bite.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/powassan-virus-know-about-tick-borne-illness-that-transmits-no-time-470700</guid><pubDate> Wed, 23 Aug 2023 02:44:47 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Mosquito-Borne Disease Detected In Alabama; Know All About EEE]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-mosquito-borne-disease-Detected-alabama-know-all-about-eee-470698 <description><![CDATA[Two cases of a rare mosquito-borne disease, called Eastern equine encephalitis (EEE), have been reported in Alabama. One of the patients has died.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-mosquito-borne-disease-Detected-alabama-know-all-about-eee-470698</guid><pubDate> Wed, 23 Aug 2023 01:52:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Simple Blood Test Can Help Identify Heart, Kidney Disease In Diabetes Patients, Researchers Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-blood-test-can-help-identify-heart-kidney-disease-diabetes-病人-researchers-say-470697 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have developed a blood test based on biomarkers that could detect heart attacks and kidney disease in patients with Type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-blood-test-can-help-identify-heart-kidney-disease-diabetes-病人-researchers-say-470697</guid><pubDate> Tue, 22 Aug 2023 03:13:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ayurveda For Stress Relief? Here's What Experts Have To Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ayurveda-stress-relief-heres-what-experts-have-say-470696 <description><![CDATA[Ayurveda, a traditional system of medicine that originated in India thousands of years ago, is based on the idea that wellness depends on the balance between the mind, body and spirit.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ayurveda-stress-relief-heres-what-experts-have-say-470696</guid><pubDate> Tue, 22 Aug 2023 01:34:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experience The Blissful Realm Of Rejuvenating Slumber With These 5 Innovative Sleep Products]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experience-blissful-realm-rejuvenating-slumber-these-5-innovative-sleep-products-470508 <description><![CDATA[Discover the transformative power of restful sleep through an exploration of five cutting-edge sleep products that promise to immerse you in a realm of revitalizing tranquility.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experience-blissful-realm-rejuvenating-slumber-these-5-innovative-sleep-products-470508</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:43:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[8 Signs That Suggest You May Have A Weak Immune System; Tips To Stay Healthy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-signs-that-suggest-you-may-have-weak-immune-system-tips-stay-healthy-470694 <description><![CDATA[Certain red flags such as frequent infections and fatigue should not be overlooked as they are warning signs of a weak immune system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-signs-that-suggest-you-may-have-weak-immune-system-tips-stay-healthy-470694</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:15:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A 30-Second Oral Rinse Could Detect Heart Disease Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/30-second-oral-rinse-could-detect-heart-disease-risk-470691 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now claim they can predict heart disease using a 30-second oral saline rinse in young, otherwise healthy people.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/30-second-oral-rinse-could-detect-heart-disease-risk-470691</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:56:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Maryland Reports First Case Of Locally Acquired Malaria After 40 Years; Know All About The Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maryland-reports-first-case-locally-acquired-malaria-after-40-years-know-all-about-disease-470689 <description><![CDATA[The unidentified patient from Maryland's National Capital Region is recovering after being hospitalized with the infection, health officials said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maryland-reports-first-case-locally-acquired-malaria-after-40-years-know-all-about-disease-470689</guid><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 01:02:44 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>