<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Acupressure Mats For Pain Relief, Stress Reduction And Enhanced Relaxation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-acuPressure-mats-pain-relief-stress-reduction-enhanced-relaxation-472448 <description><![CDATA[Acupressure mats are designed to promote relaxation, alleviate pain, and enhance overall well-being by stimulating pressure points throughout the body. These mats typically feature thousands of small, plastic spikes that apply gentle pressure to the skin, mimicking the effects of traditional acupressure therapy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-acuPressure-mats-pain-relief-stress-reduction-enhanced-relaxation-472448</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:14:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breast Cancer Deaths In U.S. Drop, But Cases Among Young Women On Rise, Study Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-deaths-us-drop-cases-among-young-women-rise-study-warns-472489 <description><![CDATA[According to the report, breast cancer rates increased by 1% annually from 2012 to 2021, with sharper rises among women under the age of 50 (1.4%).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-deaths-us-drop-cases-among-young-women-rise-study-warns-472489</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Oct 2024 02:20:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bedwetting In Kids? Watch Out For Vitamin Deficiencies, Researchers Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bedwetting-kids-watch-out-vitamin-deficiency-researchers-say-472487 <description><![CDATA[Children with primary nocturnal enuresis may be more likely to have vitamin D insufficiency and deficiency, and a deficiency in vitamin B12, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bedwetting-kids-watch-out-vitamin-deficiency-researchers-say-472487</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Oct 2024 01:37:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Babies Born Via Assisted Reproductive Technology At Higher Risk Of Heart Defects: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/babies-born-via-auxiliary-reproductive-technology-higher-risk-heart-defects-study-472486 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that compared to those conceived naturally, babies conceived through ART have a 36% higher risk of being born with a major heart defect.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/babies-born-via-auxiliary-reproductive-technology-higher-risk-heart-defects-study-472486</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:51:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Ear Wax Removers: Safe, Effective Solutions For Clear And Healthy Ears]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-ear-wax-removers-safe- effective-solutions-clear-healthy-ears-472452 <description><![CDATA[Without earwax, our ears would be more prone to infections, irritation, and injury. It's essential for maintaining overall ear health. However, in some cases, earwax can build up due to overproduction or improper cleaning methods, leading to blockages and other problems.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-ear-wax-removers-safe- effective-solutions-clear-healthy-ears-472452</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:18:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[California Bans 6 Harmful Dyes In School Food Linked To Behavioral Issues]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-bans-6-harmful-dyes-school-food-linked-behavioral-issues-472485 <description><![CDATA[The new law, part of the California School Food Safety Act, bans the use of six artificial dyes: Red 40, Yellow 5, Yellow 6, Blue 1, Blue 2, and Green 3, in food and drinks served at public schools.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-bans-6-harmful-dyes-school-food-linked-behavioral-issues-472485</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Oct 2024 04:52:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Know How Well You're Aging? New Cheek Swab Test Predicts Mortality Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-know-how-well-youre-aging-new-cheek-swab-test-predicts-mortality-risk-472482 <description><![CDATA[Using a next-generation epigenetic clock called CheekAge, the researchers used methylation data from cheek cells to predict mortality from any cause.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-know-how-well-youre-aging-new-cheek-swab-test-predicts-mortality-risk-472482</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Oct 2024 03:38:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Metabolic Syndrome Affects One-Third Of U.S. Adults: Study Reveals Effective Diet Strategy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-syndrome-affects-one-third-us-adults-study-reveals- effective-diet-strategy-472481 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that time-restricted eating, a popular diet strategy known for weight loss, could be a game-changer for those with metabolic syndrome.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-syndrome-affects-one-third-us-adults-study-reveals- effective-diet-strategy-472481</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Oct 2024 01:36:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Who Hacked Off Own Genitals While High on Mushrooms Undergoes Successful Penis 'Replantation' in Historic First]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-who-hacked-off-own-genitals-while-high-mushrooms-undergoes-successful-penis-replantation-472479 <description><![CDATA[Doctors in Austria have documented the first known occurrence of psilocybin-induced penile amputation according to an unprecedented case report.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-who-hacked-off-own-genitals-while-high-mushrooms-undergoes-successful-penis-replantation-472479</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:39:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Read Aloud To Kids: AAP Recommends Shared Reading To Strengthen Bonds, Boost Brain Development]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/read-aloud-kids-aap-recommends-shared-reading-strengthen-bonds-boost-brain-development-472476 <description><![CDATA[The latest updated policy statement from the AAP suggests "literacy promotion as a universal primary prevention strategy to strengthen families and support healthy development."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/read-aloud-kids-aap-recommends-shared-reading-strengthen-bonds-boost-brain-development-472476</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Sep 2024 05:58:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Poor Sleep During Pregnancy Linked To Developmental Delays In Children: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poor-sleep-during-pregnancy-linked-developmental-delays-children-study-472473 <description><![CDATA[The study explored how short sleep duration during pregnancy, meaning sleeping less than seven hours daily, is linked to neurodevelopmental delays in offspring.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poor-sleep-during-pregnancy-linked-developmental-delays-children-study-472473</guid><pubDate> Mon, 30 Sep 2024 03:10:40 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>