<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>他</language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Orthopedic Ergonomic Chairs For Spine Support, Back Pain]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-orthopedic-ergonomic-chairs-spine-support-back-pain-472276 <description><![CDATA[Investing in good-quality ergonomic chairs may save you a lot of pain in the future. These orthopedic chairs can support your lower back, align your spine, and give your neck the comfort it needs while working.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-orthopedic-ergonomic-chairs-spine-support-back-pain-472276</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:10:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Ankle Braces: Enhance Stability And Speed Up Recovery With These Top Picks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-ankle-braces-enhance-stability-speed-recovery-these-top-picks-472290 <description><![CDATA[Choosing the right ankle brace can significantly impact injury recovery and overall support during physical activities. This article explores the top ankle braces on the market, evaluating their features, benefits, and user experiences.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-ankle-braces-enhance-stability-speed-recovery-these-top-picks-472290</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:05:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Knee Braces For Arthritis And Injuries: A Guide To Pain Relief And Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-knee-braces-arthritis-injuries-guide-pain-relief-support-472279 <description><![CDATA[When managing knee pain or injury, selecting the right knee brace can significantly impact your comfort and recovery. This article explores the top knee braces on the market, highlighting their features, benefits, and suitability for various conditions such as arthritis, ACL injuries, and meniscus tears.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-knee-braces-arthritis-injuries-guide-pain-relief-support-472279</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:03:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Inositol Supplements To Manage PCOS, Menstruation Cycle And Boost Fertility]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-inositol-supplements-manage-pcos-menstruation-cycle-boost-fertility-472264 <description><![CDATA[Some studies have found that inositol reduces panic attacks if it is taken in high doses.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-inositol-supplements-manage-pcos-menstruation-cycle-boost-fertility-472264</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 10:36:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Krill Oil Supplements To Improve Heart And Skin Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-krill-oil-supplements-improve-heart-skin-health-472243 <description><![CDATA[Krill oil is a rich and important source of Omega-3s. It has been found beneficial in preventing several lifestyle diseases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-krill-oil-supplements-improve-heart-skin-health-472243</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 10:21:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Tryptophan Supplements For Boosting Mood, Sleep And Overall Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tryptophan-supplements-boosting-mood-sleep-overall-health-472258 <description><![CDATA[Tryptophan is an essential amino acid that plays a vital role in producing serotonin, a neurotransmitter that regulates mood, sleep, and appetite. Incorporating tryptophan supplements into your routine can support relaxation, enhance sleep quality, and improve overall mental well-being, making it a popular choice for those seeking natural health support.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-tryptophan-supplements-boosting-mood-sleep-overall-health-472258</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 10:07:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Air Pollution Impacts Male Fertility, Noise Harms Female Reproductive Health: Study Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-impacts-male-fertility-noise-harms-female-reproductive-health-study-warns-472285 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that long-term exposure to particulate matter from air pollution adversely affects male fertility, and noise pollution poses a significant threat to female reproductive health in women over 35.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-impacts-male-fertility-noise-harms-female-reproductive-health-study-warns-472285</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 04:21:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Heat Affects Disproportionately: Study Finds Women In 40s As Vulnerable As Men At 65]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heat-affects-disproportionately-study-finds-women-40s-vulnerable-men-65-472284 <description><![CDATA[The study found that middle-aged and older women are physiologically more vulnerable to high heat and humidity than older men, and this increased risk is not simply due to their longer lifespan.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heat-affects-disproportionately-study-finds-women-40s-vulnerable-men-65-472284</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 03:05:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Low-Carb Diets Be Nutritious? Study Says Well-Constructed Plans Even Exceed Nutrient Needs]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-low-carb-diets-nutritious-study-says-well-constructed-plans-even-exceed- Nutrition-needs-472282 <description><![CDATA[Researchers of the latest study tested the safety and efficacy of three low-carb, seven-day meal plans, specifically focusing on nutrient adequacy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-low-carb-diets-nutritious-study-says-well-constructed-plans-even-exceed- Nutrition-needs-472282</guid><pubDate> Thu, 05 Sep 2024 01:45:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Lactase Supplements For Effective Lactose Intolerance Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lactase-supplements- effective-lactose-intolerance-relief-472253 <description><![CDATA[This article reviews the best lactase supplements available for managing lactose intolerance. It evaluates their effectiveness in alleviating symptoms such as bloating, gas, and digestive discomfort.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-lactase-supplements- effective-lactose-intolerance-relief-472253</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Sep 2024 09:36:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Serotonin Supplements: Top Picks For Mood And Sleep Support]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-serotonin-supplements-top-picks-mood-sleep-support-472263 <description><![CDATA[5-HTP is a powerful supplement that offers a range of health benefits, particularly for mood enhancement and sleep support. By boosting serotonin levels in the body, 5-HTP can help improve overall well-being, reduce anxiety, promote better sleep, and aid in appetite control.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-serotonin-supplements-top-picks-mood-sleep-support-472263</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Sep 2024 09:32:34 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>