<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Exploring The Benefits Of Ashwagandha: An Ancient Herb With Modern Potential]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-benefits-ashwagandha-ancient-herb-modern-pottial-472068 <description><![CDATA[Ashwagandha supplements, made from the Withania somnifera plant, come in capsules, powders, and extracts. They're commonly used to help reduce stress, boost physical performance, and enhance cognitive function. For the best results, choose high-quality products from reputable brands and consult a healthcare professional before starting any new supplement.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-benefits-ashwagandha-ancient-herb-modern-pottial-472068</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:32:21 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Guide To Collagen Supplements]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/compressive-guide-collagen-supplements-472061 <description><![CDATA[Collagen is the most abundant protein in the human body, essential for maintaining the structure and elasticity of skin, bones, tendons, and cartilage. As we age, collagen production naturally decreases, leading to signs of aging like wrinkles and joint discomfort. This decline can be exacerbated by factors such as smoking and excessive sun exposure. To combat these effects, many people turn to collagen supplements, which can promote skin elasticity, improve joint health, and support overall wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/compressive-guide-collagen-supplements-472061</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:49:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[More Than 15 Million US Adults Consume Botanicals With Liver Harming Potential: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-15-million-us-adults-consume-botanicals-liver-harming-pottial-study-472066 <description><![CDATA[The researchers observed that the lack of regulations for botanicals often leads to discrepancies between product labels and actual ingredients, which can mislead consumers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-15-million-us-adults-consume-botanicals-liver-harming-pottial-study-472066</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:58:14 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Drinking From Plastic Water Bottles May Raise Blood Pressure: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking- Plastic-water-bottles-may-raise-blood-Pressure-study-472064 <description><![CDATA[The new study found that drinking from plastic bottles can cause microplastics to enter the bloodstream, potentially leading to increased blood pressure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking- Plastic-water-bottles-may-raise-blood-Pressure-study-472064</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:43:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Keto Diet 'May Not Suit Everyone': Study Says It Raises Cholesterol Levels, Disrupts Gut Bacteria]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keto-diet-may-not-suit-everyone-study-says-it-raises-cholesterol-levels-disrupts-gut-bacteria-472063 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noticed that the keto diet reduced glucose tolerance levels, altered gut microbiome composition, and raised cholesterol levels, particularly small and medium-sized low-density lipoprotein (LDL) particles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keto-diet-may-not-suit-everyone-study-says-it-raises-cholesterol-levels-disrupts-gut-bacteria-472063</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:02:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top Magnesium Glycinate Supplements In 2024: From Strong Bones To Restful Sleep, Discover Health Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-magnesium-glycinate-supplements-2024-strong-bones-restful-sleep-discover-health-benefits-472055 <description><![CDATA[Magnesium is an essential mineral that works wonders by helping you sleep better, reducing anxiety, strengthening your bones, regulating blood pressure, and boosting your heart health. Even though you can get magnesium from foods like whole grains, legumes, nuts, fruits, and veggies, nearly half of Americans still don't get enough from their diet. Those with health issues are even more at risk of deficiency. This is where magnesium supplements come to the rescue. Among them, magnesium glycinate becomes an excellent choice as it is super easy for your body to absorb the nutrient.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-magnesium-glycinate-supplements-2024-strong-bones-restful-sleep-discover-health-benefits-472055</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:28:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Strive For Happiness, But Constant Concerns About It Affects Well-Being: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strive-happiness-constant-concerns-about-it-affects-well-being-study-472060 <description><![CDATA[While it is important to strive for happiness, constant obsession, overthinking, and concerns about one's happiness can affect well-being, a study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strive-happiness-constant-concerns-about-it-affects-well-being-study-472060</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:46:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Folate Intake Affect Aging? Here's What Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-folate-intake-affect-aging-heres-what-study-says-472059 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that folate requirements depend on your age. Decreasing folate intake can support healthier metabolisms in aging animal models.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-folate-intake-affect-aging-heres-what-study-says-472059</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:38:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hospitalization From Heart Diseases Raises Mental Health Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospitalization-heart-diseases-raises-mental-health-risk-study-472056 <description><![CDATA[The study highlights the heightened risk for mental health issues, including anxiety, depression, and self-harm, during the recovery years, especially within the first year after hospitalization for cardiovascular diseases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospitalization-heart-diseases-raises-mental-health-risk-study-472056</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:17:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top Picks For Amino Acid Supplements In 2024: Boost Your Fitness Goals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-picks-amino-acid-supplements-2024-boost-your-fitness-goals-472052 <description><![CDATA[Amino acids are the building blocks of proteins, vital for muscle repair, hormone production and immune support. Of the 20 amino acids, nine are essential and must be obtained from foods like meat, fish, eggs, dairy, beans and nuts. A balanced intake of these nutrients is crucial for energy, tissue repair and overall health, making amino acids important for everyone, from athletes to those simply aiming to stay healthy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-picks-amino-acid-supplements-2024-boost-your-fitness-goals-472052</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:15:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Fish Oil Benefit Older Adult Brains? Here's What Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-fish-oil-benefit-older-adult-brains-heres-what-study-says-472048 <description><![CDATA[According to the study, omega-3 fatty acid use could benefit those with a genetic predisposition to Alzheimer's. However, researchers did not find significant benefits for all older adults in general.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-fish-oil-benefit-older-adult-brains-heres-what-study-says-472048</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Aug 2024 03:29:56 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>