<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Child's Exposure To Air Pollution In Womb Raises Mental Health Risks During Adolescence]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childs-exposure-air-pollution-womb-raises-mental-health-risks-during-adolescent-471787 <description><![CDATA[The study investigated how air and noise pollution during pregnancy impact a child's mental health at different stages of development, such as early childhood and adolescence.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childs-exposure-air-pollution-womb-raises-mental-health-risks-during-adolescent-471787</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 May 2024 02:20:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Recommends Adding More Fruits And Veggies In Diet For Optimum Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-recommends-adding-more-fruits-veggies-diet-optimum-sleep-471785 <description><![CDATA[The researchers examined how sleep duration affects fruit and vegetable consumption and vice-versa.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-recommends-adding-more-fruits-veggies-diet-optimum-sleep-471785</guid><pubDate> Tue, 28 May 2024 03:58:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Getting Inked Could Elevate Lymphoma Risk Regardless Of Tattoo Size: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/getting-inked-could-elevate-lymphoma-risk-regardless-tattoo-size-study-471784 <description><![CDATA[Tattoos raise the risk of cancer affecting the lymphatic system by 12% and risk prevails irrespective of the size of the tattoo, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/getting-inked-could-elevate-lymphoma-risk-regardless-tattoo-size-study-471784</guid><pubDate> Tue, 28 May 2024 02:55:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Asthma Awareness Month: Expert Insights On Myths and Facts About The Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/asthma-awareness-month-expert-insights-myths-facts-about-condition-471782 <description><![CDATA[During this Asthma Awareness Month, take the opportunity to educate yourself by learning from an expert about the myths and facts surrounding this chronic respiratory disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/asthma-awareness-month-expert-insights-myths-facts-about-condition-471782</guid><pubDate> Tue, 28 May 2024 01:34:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[These Red Light Therapy Solutions Can Improve Skin Collagen Production Even At Home]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/these-red-light-therapy-solutions-can-improve-skin-collagen-production-even-home-471762 <description><![CDATA[Red light therapy, once exclusive to clinics, now offers convenient at-home solutions that enhance skin health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/these-red-light-therapy-solutions-can-improve-skin-collagen-production-even-home-471762</guid><pubDate> Mon, 27 May 2024 13:10:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Mental Disorders Spread? Study Says They Can Among Adolescent Social Groups]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-mental-disorders-spread-study-says-they-can-among-adolescent-social-groups-471781 <description><![CDATA[The greater the number of classmates diagnosed with a mental disorder, the higher the risk of an individual receiving a mental disorder diagnosis later in life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-mental-disorders-spread-study-says-they-can-among-adolescent-social-groups-471781</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 May 2024 04:22:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Exposure In Womb Or As Newborn May Elevate Children's Social, Breathing Issues]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-exposure-womb-newborn-may-elevate-childrens-social-breathing-issues-471779 <description><![CDATA[The study investigated if exposure to COVID-19 during pregnancy or right after birth has a long-term impact on the development and breathing of babies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-exposure-womb-newborn-may-elevate-childrens-social-breathing-issues-471779</guid><pubDate> Fri, 24 May 2024 01:23:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Conquer Leg Cramps with These Proven Relief Solutions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/conquer-leg-cramps-these-proven-relief-solutions-471776 <description><![CDATA[Athletes and normal people alike have discovered effective relief solutions for leg cramps, ranging from creams to supplements that provide immediate relief.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/conquer-leg-cramps-these-proven-relief-solutions-471776</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 15:16:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want Better Digestive Health This Year? Try These Fiber Supplements ASAP]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-better-digestive-health-this-year-try-these-fibre-supplements-asap-471770 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top fiber supplements of 2024 that simplify daily nutrition and promote digestive health for a vibrant lifestyle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-better-digestive-health-this-year-try-these-fibre-supplements-asap-471770</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 12:55:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vulnerability To Stress In Adolescence Raises Men's Risk Of Psoriasis Later: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vulnerability-stress-adolescent-raises-mens-risk-psoriasis-later-study-471777 <description><![CDATA[Adolescent men with greater vulnerability to stress experience a 31% higher risk of developing psoriasis compared to those with high-stress resilience, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vulnerability-stress-adolescent-raises-mens-risk-psoriasis-later-study-471777</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 04:34:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Epidural Use Linked To Reduced Risk Of Complications In Mothers After Childbirth]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/epidural-use-linked-reduced-risk-complications-mothers-after-childbirth-471774 <description><![CDATA[The benefit was particularly seen in those women who had a "medical indication" for epidural analgesia during labor and those who had a premature delivery.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/epidural-use-linked-reduced-risk-complications-mothers-after-childbirth-471774</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 03:22:02 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>