<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Teen Boys Who Smoke Pass On Damaged Genes To Future Offsprings: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen-boys-who-smoke-pass-damaging-genes-future-offsprings-study-470731 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that smoking in the teenage years causes DNA changes in the sperm, which lead to alterations in the DNA of their future babies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen-boys-who-smoke-pass-damaging-genes-future-offsprings-study-470731</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 04:13:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Strive For A Balanced Diet: Study Says Extreme Dietary Habits Involving Carbs And Fats Affect Longevity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strive-balanced-diet-study-says-extreme-dietary-habits-involving-carbs-fats-affect-longevity-470729 <description><![CDATA[The key to longevity is following a balanced diet rather than putting the body through extreme dietary habits involving carbs and fats, according to a new study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strive-balanced-diet-study-says-extreme-dietary-habits-involving-carbs-fats-affect-longevity-470729</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:58:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Key To Longevity? Women Who Maintain Body Weight After 60 Likely To Live Longer, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-longevity-women-who-maintain-body-weight-after-60-likely-live-longer-says-study-470728 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has found that maintaining a steady weight after the age of 60 could bring "exceptional longevity" in women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-longevity-women-who-maintain-body-weight-after-60-likely-live-longer-says-study-470728</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 04:26:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Flu Shots: Importance, Right Time To Get Them; Expert Debunks Common Misconceptions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-shots-importance-right-time-get-them-expert-debunks-common-misconceptions-470727 <description><![CDATA[Flu season is around the corner, so health officials are reminding people to get vaccinated at the right time to get the maximum protection against the influenza virus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-shots-importance-right-time-get-them-expert-debunks-common-misconceptions-470727</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:59:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Collagen Peptides Enhance Active Lifestyle and Beauty]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/collagen-peptides-enhance-active-lifestyle-beauty-470687 <description><![CDATA[Discover how collagen peptides can synergistically amplify an active lifestyle while promoting enhanced beauty in this enlightening article.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/collagen-peptides-enhance-active-lifestyle-beauty-470687</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:17:57 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 10 Best Collagen Products Of 2023]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-collagen-products-2023-470684 <description><![CDATA[Explore the finest collagen products of 2023 with our curated list of the top 10, designed to rejuvenate and enhance your skincare and wellness routine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-collagen-products-2023-470684</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 23:49:59 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stay At Ease: The 8 Baby Monitors With Advanced Features For Safety]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-ease-8-baby-monitors-advanced-features-safety-470615 <description><![CDATA[Explore a comprehensive list of eight cutting-edge baby monitors designed to ensure utmost safety and convenience, offering advanced features for peace of mind.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-ease-8-baby-monitors-advanced-features-safety-470615</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 22:31:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Neighborhood's Quality Influences Risk Of Pediatric Asthma, Finds Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neighborhoods-quality-influences-risk-pediatric-asthma-finds-study-470725 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that children who were raised in neighborhoods offering higher opportunities and lower vulnerabilities during their early years had a reduced likelihood of developing asthma.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neighborhoods-quality-influences-risk-pediatric-asthma-finds-study-470725</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 07:07:57 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID Is Making A Comeback. Is It Time To Worry?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-making-comeback-it-time-worry-470724 <description><![CDATA[While the pandemic, and the panic, are over, COVID-19 cases are rising across the U.S. prompting concern about a return to mass vaccination, masking and even lockdowns.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-making-comeback-it-time-worry-470724</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 05:35:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Air Pollution Greatest Global Threat To Human Health, Says Benchmark Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-greatest-global-threat- human-health-says-benchmark-study-470721 <description><![CDATA[If the world were to permanently reduce the pollutants to meet the WHO guideline limit, the average person would add 2.3 years onto his or her life expectancy, according to the data.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-greatest-global-threat- human-health-says-benchmark-study-470721</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 04:36:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiac Arrest: Study Says Warning Signs Can Be Different In Men And Women]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-arrest-study-says-warning-signs-can- Different-men-women-470719 <description><![CDATA[Shortness of breath is reportedly its most prominent symptom in women, while for men, it is chest pain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-arrest-study-says-warning-signs-can- Different-men-women-470719</guid><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 03:43:17 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>