<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Music For Brain Health: Researchers Say Singing, Playing Instruments Linked To Better Memory In Old Age]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/music-brain-health-researchers-say-singing-playing-instruments-linked-better-memory-old-age-471328 <description><![CDATA[The findings of a recent large-scale study suggest that lifelong exposure to music could help improve a person's memory and brain health in old age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/music-brain-health-researchers-say-singing-playing-instruments-linked-better-memory-old-age-471328</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:54:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exploring Non-Surgical Solutions For Neuromas And Chronic Plantar Fasciitis: Dr. Alan Shih's Approach]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exploring-non-surgical-solutions-neuromas-chronic-plantar-fasciitis-dr-alan-shihs-approach-471325 <description><![CDATA[While surgical interventions are often the go-to option for recalcitrant neuromas and plantar fasciitis, Dr. Shih introduces Radiofrequency Ablation (RFA) as a viable alternative.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exploring-non-surgical-solutions-neuromas-chronic-plantar-fasciitis-dr-alan-shihs-approach-471325</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Jan 2024 12:08:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Collagen Powder For 2024: Revitalize Your Beauty Routine And Glow From Within]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-collagen-powder-revitalize-your-beauty-routine-glow-within-471323 <description><![CDATA[Collagen powders are supplements rich in amino acids, which promote skin elasticity and joint health. Here, we have compiled a list of collagen powders for you to unlock radiant skin and joint health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-collagen-powder-revitalize-your-beauty-routine-glow-within-471323</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Jan 2024 10:35:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Multivitamins For Women In 2024: Prioritizing One's Health At Every Age]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-multivitamins-women-prioritizing-ones-health-every-age-471321 <description><![CDATA[Embrace the best multivitamin for women tailored to meet your unique nutritional needs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-multivitamins-women-prioritizing-ones-health-every-age-471321</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Jan 2024 05:57:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Quick Fix For Your Mood: Researchers Say Eating Kiwifruit Could Improve Mental Health In Just 4 Days]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quick-fix-your-mood-researchers-say-eating-kiwifruit-could-improve-mental-health-just-4-days-471322 <description><![CDATA[Incorporating kiwifruit into the diet could boost mood and vitality in four days, reaching peak benefits within approximately two weeks, as per a recent study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quick-fix-your-mood-researchers-say-eating-kiwifruit-could-improve-mental-health-just-4-days-471322</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Jan 2024 02:16:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Metabolic Dysfunction In Women: Study Identifies Reproductive Factors That Raise Risk Of Diabetes, High Cholesterol]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-dysfunction-women-study-identizes-reproductive-factors-that-raise-risk-diabetes-high-471320 <description><![CDATA[Certain reproductive characteristics in females are key risk factors for metabolic dysfunction, potentially increasing the likelihood of developing diabetes and high cholesterol in later stages of life, according to a new study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-dysfunction-women-study-identizes-reproductive-factors-that-raise-risk-diabetes-high-471320</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:27:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Leprosy Day: Break Stigma, Know Facts Behind Common Myths About Hansen's Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-leprosy-day-break-stigma-know-facts-behind-common-myths-about-hansens-disease-471308 <description><![CDATA[This World Leprosy Day, let us break the stigma by knowing the facts and debunking the common misconceptions about the disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-leprosy-day-break-stigma-know-facts-behind-common-myths-about-hansens-disease-471308</guid><pubDate> Sun, 28 Jan 2024 06:05:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Shoes For Plantar Fasciitis In 2024: Find Comfort And Embrace Pain-Free Steps]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shoes-plantar-fasciitis-find-comfort-embrace-pain-free-steps-471309 <description><![CDATA[Finding the best shoes for plantar fasciitis involves looking for footwear that provides proper arch support, cushioning, and stability. Here, we have compiled some of the best models known for their comfort and support.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shoes-plantar-fasciitis-find-comfort-embrace-pain-free-steps-471309</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jan 2024 07:04:32 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Writing By Hand Or Typing On Keyboard? Study Identifies Best Way To Improve Brain Connectivity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/writing-hand-typing-keyboard-study-identizes-best-way-improve-brain-connectivity-471315 <description><![CDATA[Typing on a keyboard has become a faster and more convenient alternative to writing by hand, but could there be a downside? Read about what researchers have found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/writing-hand-typing-keyboard-study-identizes-best-way-improve-brain-connectivity-471315</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jan 2024 04:58:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Robitussin Cough Syrups Recalled Due To Microbial Contamination]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/robitussin-cough-syrups-recalled-due-microbial-contamination-471314 <description><![CDATA[The distributors have been notified and provided with instructions for the return of all recalled products.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/robitussin-cough-syrups-recalled-due-microbial-contamination-471314</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jan 2024 03:03:56 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Should You Put The Toilet Lid Up Or Down While Flushing? Here's What A Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/should-you-put-toilet-lid-down-while-flushing-heres-what-study-says-471312 <description><![CDATA[The research team examined the spread of viral particles during toilet flushing in both scenarios — while the lids were open and closed. The study was conducted both in household and public toilets.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/should-you-put-toilet-lid-down-while-flushing-heres-what-study-says-471312</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:44:25 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>