<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Trump Applauds 13-Year-Old Cancer Survivor After Slashing Funding for Pediatric Cancer Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trump-applauds-13岁，Cancer-survivor-surver-s-Slashing-slashing-slashing-pediatric-cancer-cancer-research-473212 <description><![CDATA[President Donald Trump honored and applauded a young cancer survivor during his recent joint address to Congress despite his numerous attempts to cut funding for healthcare, including pediatric cancer research.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trump-applauds-13岁，Cancer-survivor-surver-s-Slashing-slashing-slashing-pediatric-cancer-cancer-research-473212</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:42:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Think Before You Ink: Study Suggests Tattoos May Increase Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/think-be-be--be-------------suggests tattoos-may-may-may-may-may-cancers-cancer-Cancer-473210 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that tattoos may increase the risk of skin cancer and lymph node cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/think-be-be--be-------------suggests tattoos-may-may-may-may-may-cancers-cancer-Cancer-473210</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Mar 2025 05:39:12 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Gynecological Issues Raise Risk Of Heart Diseases? Here're Two Conditions That Pose Greatest Danger]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-gynecologic-sissues-raise-risk---------- herere-therere-two-conditions-最糟糕的 - 最高的473208 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that two common gynecological issues are linked to a higher risk of cardiovascular diseases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-gynecologic-sissues-raise-risk---------- herere-therere-two-conditions-最糟糕的 - 最高的473208</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:41:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Therapist Shares Simple Eye Exercise To 'Knock Out' Panic Attack]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/therapist-shares-simple-eye-eccise-eccise-knock-panic-panic-Attack-473205 <description><![CDATA[Here's a surprisingly simple eye trick to stop a panic attack in its tracks, and all it takes is a pen, and a few minutes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/therapist-shares-simple-eye-eccise-eccise-knock-panic-panic-Attack-473205</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:36:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Health Officials Beg Texas Families Not to Attend 'Measles Parties' As Push to Get Kids Vaccinated Continues]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-inficials-beg-texas-families-not-antend-measles-parties-parties-parties-push-get-get-kids-vaccined-473202 <description><![CDATA[Texas health officials have pleaded with families in the state to avoid attending "measles parties" and ensure that their children are vaccinated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-inficials-beg-texas-families-not-antend-measles-parties-parties-parties-push-get-get-kids-vaccined-473202</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:47:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Act Now: By 2050 Over Half Of Adults, A Third Of Children Will Be Obese]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/act-now-2050-over-half-adults-third-children-will-will-obese-473199 <description><![CDATA[Researchers are calling for urgent action and global policy reforms to address widespread global obesity pandemic by 2050.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/act-now-2050-over-half-adults-third-children-will-will-obese-473199</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 03:47:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Eat Less After Holiday Indulgence? Here's How 5 Days Of Sugary Diet Affects Brain]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-eat-leas------ holiday-induliday-indulgence-heres-how-how-5-Days-sugary-days-sugary-diet-aftects-brain-brain-473197 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that just five days of a high-calorie diet can trigger brain changes even before a person begins to notice weight gain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-eat-leas------ holiday-induliday-indulgence-heres-how-how-5-Days-sugary-days-sugary-diet-aftects-brain-brain-473197</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 02:57:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Woman Says Routine Manicure 'Saved Her Life' After Spotting Strange Sign On Thumb]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-woman-says-says-routine-manicure-saved-her-life-life-ferfter-spotting-spotting-strange-sign-thumb-473195 <description><![CDATA[The unusual symptom she noticed during manicure session was an early warning sign of deadly melanoma.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-woman-says-says-routine-manicure-saved-her-life-life-ferfter-spotting-spotting-strange-sign-thumb-473195</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:50:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Young Man Nearly Dies From Stroke After Violent Sneeze Ruptures His Neck Artery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthyy-young-man-nearly-dies-sstroke-stroke-fer-fer-violent-sneek-ruptures-His-neck-artery-473194 <description><![CDATA[The 35-year-old man is struggling to recover from a severe stroke that has damaged his left side.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthyy-young-man-nearly-dies-sstroke-stroke-fer-fer-violent-sneek-ruptures-His-neck-artery-473194</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Mar 2025 04:23:34 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[It's Not Just Sugar; This Food Type Can Cause Cavities, Especially In People With Particular Genes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/its-not-just-just-sugar-this-this-type-can-can-can-cause-cavities-尤其是people-particular-particular-genes-473193 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that starchy foods may contribute to cavities, with the risk varying based on specific genetic factors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/its-not-just-just-sugar-this-this-type-can-can-can-cause-cavities-尤其是people-particular-particular-genes-473193</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:58:12 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Breakfast Foods Kids Should Avoid: Doctor Recommends Healthier Alternatives]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-breakfast-foods-kids-kids-should-avoid-doctor-recmends-healthier-anternatives-473191 <description><![CDATA["Give them real food," the doctor advised, highlighting five foods to avoid and recommending wholesome alternatives.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-breakfast-foods-kids-kids-should-avoid-doctor-recmends-healthier-anternatives-473191</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:44:35 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>