<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Discovers Shocking Source of 20-Year-Old Stomach Pain: A Needle Left Inside Her During Vaginal Surgery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-discovers-shocking-source-20-year-old-stomach-pain-needle-left-inside-her-during-vaginal-472675 <description><![CDATA[A woman in Thailand recently discovered the source of her decades-long abdominal pain: a surgical needle allegedly left in her vaginal area during childbirth.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-discovers-shocking-source-20-year-old-stomach-pain-needle-left-inside-her-during-vaginal-472675</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 12:29:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[G.tec Medical Engineering's Innovative RecoveriX BCI Treatment Now Available In Hospitals &amp; Neurorehabilitation Centers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gtec-medical-engineerings-innovative-recoverix-bci-treatment-now-available-hospitals-472673 <description><![CDATA[Using recoveriX improves neuroplasticity, which helps rewire nervous pathways and replace damaged neurons that were affected by the stroke, multiple sclerosis, or Parkinson's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gtec-medical-engineerings-innovative-recoverix-bci-treatment-now-available-hospitals-472673</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 12:28:46 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI Detects Woman's Cancer After Doctors Tell Her She's Healthy, Likely Saves Her Life: 'This May Have Been My Last Mammogram']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-detects-womans-cancer-after-doctors-tell-her-shes-healthy-likely-saves-her-life-this-may-472672 <description><![CDATA[A UK woman is grateful to be alive after AI technology detected cancerous cells her doctors missed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-detects-womans-cancer-after-doctors-tell-her-shes-healthy-likely-saves-her-life-this-may-472672</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 11:40:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Intense Cold Therapy Daily May Improve Sleep Quality: Study Finds]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-intense-cold-therapy-daily-may-improve-sleep-quality-study-finds-472671 <description><![CDATA[The study found that undergoing daily cryostimulation, spending five minutes in a chamber cooled to -90°C, could improve sleep quality after five consecutive sessions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-intense-cold-therapy-daily-may-improve-sleep-quality-study-finds-472671</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 02:05:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Risk Factors Linked To Severe Stroke: Study Identifies Modifiable Lifestyle Choices, Manageable Conditions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/risk-factors-linked-severe-中风-study-identizes-modulated-lifestyle-choices-manageable-472670 <description><![CDATA[The study found that three risk factors: high blood pressure, atrial fibrillation, and smoking, not only increased the risk of stroke but were also linked to a higher risk of severe stroke.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/risk-factors-linked-severe-中风-study-identizes-modulated-lifestyle-choices-manageable-472670</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 01:16:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experimental Vaccine Shows Promising Results Against Aggressive Breast Cancer: Trial Results Reveal]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-vaccine-shows-promising-results-against-aggressive-breast-cancer-tri-results-reveal-472667 <description><![CDATA[The neoantigen DNA vaccine developed for preventing the recurrence of tumors in triple-negative breast cancer was found to be "well-tolerated" and effective in stimulating the immune system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-vaccine-shows-promising-results-against-aggressive-breast-cancer-tri-results-reveal-472667</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:35:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cut Back On Makeup During Pregnancy, Lactation: Study Links Increased Use To Harmful PFAS]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-back-makeup-during-pregnancy-lactation-study-links-increased-use-harmful-pfas-472662 <description><![CDATA[The study warns that increased use of personal care products during pregnancy and nursing is linked to higher levels of harmful chemicals such as per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS) in the blood plasma and breast milk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-back-makeup-during-pregnancy-lactation-study-links-increased-use-harmful-pfas-472662</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Nov 2024 04:33:12 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitamin D Supplements May Help Lower Blood Pressure In Older Adults With Obesity; Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-supplements-may-help-lower-blood-Pressure-older-adults-obesity-study-finds-472660 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now suggest that vitamin D supplementation may be an effective, simple way to lower blood pressure levels in elderly adults with obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-supplements-may-help-lower-blood-Pressure-older-adults-obesity-study-finds-472660</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Nov 2024 02:58:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Metformin Use In Pregnancy Linked To Fetal Growth Issues, Obesity And Diabetes Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-use-pregnancy-linked-fetal-growth-issues-obesity-diabetes-risk-study-472659 <description><![CDATA[Although metformin is prescribed during pregnancy to lower the risk of diabetes-related complications, such as obesity and diabetes in children, the study suggests that the drug itself may contribute to these same risks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-use-pregnancy-linked-fetal-growth-issues-obesity-diabetes-risk-study-472659</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Nov 2024 01:05:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Best Time To Get RSV Vaccine During Pregnancy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-time-get-rsv-vaccine-during-pregnancy-472658 <description><![CDATA[Researchers of a recent study found that getting vaccinated earlier in the recommended timeframe, closer to 32 weeks, may offer the best protection for newborns against RSV.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-time-get-rsv-vaccine-during-pregnancy-472658</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Nov 2024 04:34:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Regular Bedtime More Important Than Sleep Quality, Duration For Kid's Behavior: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/regular-bedtime-more-important-sleep-quality-duration-kids-behavior-study-472657 <description><![CDATA[Children with consistent sleep schedules have better control of their emotions and behavior when they work with others or while they are under situations of stress, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/regular-bedtime-more-important-sleep-quality-duration-kids-behavior-study-472657</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Nov 2024 23:21:46 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>