<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Left Paralyzed Neck Down From Rare Deficiency After Weight Loss Surgery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-left-paralyzed-neck-down-rare-deficition-weight-weight-weight-weight-surergery-473340 <description><![CDATA[The woman suffered severe nerve damage from nutritional neuropathy, a rare but serious side effect of gastric sleeve surgery.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-left-paralyzed-neck-down-rare-deficition-weight-weight-weight-weight-surergery-473340</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:09:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Second Child Dies Of Measles In Texas;Victim Was Unvaccinated]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/second-child-dies-measles-texas-victim-was-was-unvaccind-prod-phaccin-phaccin--phacsine-phealthy-healthy-47338 <description><![CDATA[The unvaccinated school-aged child, who had no underlying health conditions, tragically died from lung failure while receiving treatment for measles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/second-child-dies-measles-texas-victim-was-was-unvaccind-prod-phaccin-phaccin--phacsine-phealthy-healthy-47338</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:04:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Too Young For Alzheimer's? Easy To Dismiss Symptoms 41-Year-Old Had Before Diagnosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/too-young-alzheimers-easy-dismiss-41岁的had-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be 47335 <description><![CDATA[After being diagnosed at 41, an Australian dad is raising awareness that Alzheimer's isn't just a disease of old age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/too-young-alzheimers-easy-dismiss-41岁的had-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be 47335</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:35:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[25-Year-Old Left With Painful 'Peeing Jelly' After Using Popular Party Drug]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/25-year-old-left-painful-peeing-jelly-after-using-popular-drug-4733333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333 <description><![CDATA[The ketamine addiction severely damaged the woman's bladder, and the 'jelly-like' substance she was passing was her own bladder lining.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/25-year-old-left-painful-peeing-jelly-after-using-popular-drug-4733333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:22:42 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here's What A 'Widow-Maker' Heart Attack Really Looks Like]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/heres-whatwhathwidow-widow-maker-heart-attack-really-looks-like-like-47331 <description><![CDATA[For those wondering how a heart attack might look, a couple in Arizona captured a chilling moment on their home security camera when the husband suffered a deadly "widow maker" heart attack]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heres-whatwhathwidow-widow-maker-heart-attack-really-looks-like-like-47331</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:18:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vaccine To Protect Against Dementia? This One Reduces Risk By 20%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaccine-protect-against-dementia-this-this-one-ned-resces------20-473330 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that shingles vaccine, which protects against the painful viral rash, may also reduce the risk of dementia in older adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaccine-protect-against-dementia-this-this-one-ned-resces------20-473330</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:21:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Nurse Influencer Dies During Childbirth 'After Years of Fertility Struggles': 'Her Spirit Will Live On Through Our Son']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/populalar-nurse-inurse-influenter-dies-diring-childbirth-childbirth-- Yars-Yars-Yars-Yars-Yars-corttility-fruggluggles-her-spirit-473328 <description><![CDATA[Nursing and social media communities are mourning the tragic loss of Hailey Okula, an influencer and educator, who passed away due to childbirth complications.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/populalar-nurse-inurse-influenter-dies-diring-childbirth-childbirth-- Yars-Yars-Yars-Yars-Yars-corttility-fruggluggles-her-spirit-473328</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:50:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tiny Ears, Big Protection: The Ultimate Guide to Safeguarding Your Baby's Hearing]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tiny-ears-big-protection-ratimate-guide-safeguarding-your-babys-herning-473279 <description><![CDATA[Protect your baby's delicate hearing with Decibel Defense earmuffs, offering comfort, style, and top-tier noise protection for little ears in any environment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tiny-ears-big-protection-ratimate-guide-safeguarding-your-babys-herning-473279</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:14:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Probiotic Supplements Help With Autism Symptoms?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-probiotic-supplements-help-autism-symptoms-473326 <description><![CDATA[A recent trial revealed that probiotic supplements may help ease both behavioral and digestive symptoms of children with autism, offering new hope for millions of children struggling with the condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-probiotic-supplements-help-autism-symptoms-473326</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Apr 2025 05:00:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experimental Drug Shows Promise In Eliminating Hard-To-Treat Deadly Cholesterol]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experiment-drug-shows-promis-eliminting-hard-treat-deadly-cholesterol-473323 <description><![CDATA[A single dose of lepodisiran dramatically lowered dangerous lipoprotein(a) levels for up to a year, offering new hope for heart disease treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experiment-drug-shows-promis-eliminting-hard-treat-deadly-cholesterol-473323</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Apr 2025 04:44:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Yerba Mate Nature's Ozempic? Weighing In Risk Vs. Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yerba-mate-natures-natures-ozempic-weighing-clisk-benefits-473320 <description><![CDATA[Hailed as "Nature's Ozempic," yerba mate may aid weight loss and metabolism, but is it a true alternative—or a risky trend?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yerba-mate-natures-natures-ozempic-weighing-clisk-benefits-473320</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Apr 2025 02:09:03 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>