<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Does Meal Timing Matter? Eating At Night May Boost Endurance, Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-meal-timing-matter-eating-night-may-boost-endurance-study-suggests-470417 <description><![CDATA[The latest study shows that restricting food intake during the active cycle – when individuals are most active and alert – offers health benefits such as weight loss and improved blood sugar control in mice.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-meal-timing-matter-eating-night-may-boost-endurance-study-suggests-470417</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 04:02:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Icodec Insulin Vs Degludec: Study Says Weekly Treatment More Effective Than Daily Injections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/icodec-insulin-vs-degludec-study-says-weekly-treatment-more- effective-daily-injections-470418 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that icodec insulin or once-weekly treatment reduces hemoglobin A1c (HBA1c) levels in diabetes better than daily injections of degludec.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/icodec-insulin-vs-degludec-study-says-weekly-treatment-more- effective-daily-injections-470418</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 02:43:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleep Deprivation Helps Depression? Study Says It May Enhance Mood In Some People]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-deprivation-helps-depression-study-says-it-may-enhance-mood-some-people-470416 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has found that one night of total sleep deprivation may help enhance mood in some healthy, as well as depressed individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-deprivation-helps-depression-study-says-it-may-enhance-mood-some-people-470416</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 01:20:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New York's $64 Million COVID-19 Vaccination App To Shut Down This July]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-yorks-64-million-covid-19-vaccination-app-shut-down-this-july-470415<description><![CDATA[The Excelsior Pass app was initially launched in 2021.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-yorks-64-million-covid-19-vaccination-app-shut-down-this-july-470415</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:13:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[North Korea Relaxes COVID-19 Mask Mandate; Crowds Gather Sans Masks In Public Places]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/north-korea-relaxes-covid-19-mask-mandate-crowds-gather-sans-masks-public-spaces-470412 <description><![CDATA[North Korea has seemingly eased its strict COVID-19 mask mandate, according to reports.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/north-korea-relaxes-covid-19-mask-mandate-crowds-gather-sans-masks-public-spaces-470412</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:09:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Impact of Indoor Air Quality in Homes on Respiratory Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/impact-indoor-air-quality-homes-respiratory-health-470409 <description><![CDATA[Indoor air quality, which is often abbreviated as IAQ, refers to the quality of air within buildings and structures (including your home). Generally speaking, when you hear IAQ being discussed, it's within the context of poor indoor air quality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/impact-indoor-air-quality-homes-respiratory-health-470409</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 10:42:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Brushing Your Teeth Before Bedtime May Be Crucial For A Healthy Heart]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brushing-your-teeth-before-bedtime-may-crucial-healthy-heart-470408 <description><![CDATA[Multiple studies emphasize oral care's significance before and after surgery, but its potential connection to heart problems remains unexplored. The latest study focuses on this area.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brushing-your-teeth-before-bedtime-may-crucial-healthy-heart-470408</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 05:51:21 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiorespiratory Fitness Reduces Colon And Lung Cancer Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiorespiratory-fitness-reduces-colon-lung-cancer-risk-study-470405 <description><![CDATA[The study showed that individuals with higher levels of cardiorespiratory fitness had a 2% lower risk of developing colon and lung cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiorespiratory-fitness-reduces-colon-lung-cancer-risk-study-470405</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 04:50:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Young Cancer Survivors May Be At Increased Risk Of Mental Disorders; Ways To Support Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/young-cancer-survivors-may-increased-risk-mental-disorders-ways-support-them-470403 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that young cancer survivors are at an increased risk of developing mental health disorders such as depression and anxiety.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/young-cancer-survivors-may-increased-risk-mental-disorders-ways-support-them-470403</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 03:26:12 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Smoothie Recipes To Ease Constipation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/6-smoothie-recipes-ease-constipation-470402 <description><![CDATA[You can relieve constipation by seamlessly incorporating nutrient-rich smoothies into your daily diet.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/6-smoothie-recipes-ease-constipation-470402</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 03:06:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Decreased Sense Of Smell In Elderly May Increase Risk Of Depression, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/decreased-sense-smell-elderly-may-increase-risk-depression-study-says-470399 <description><![CDATA[The study evaluated factors that affect the relationship between olfaction and depression, including poor cognition and inflammation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/decreased-sense-smell-elderly-may-increase-risk-depression-study-says-470399</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 02:29:17 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>