<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Chronic Disease Day: Healthy Habits To Prevent Long-Term Health Conditions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-disease-day-healthy-habits-prevent-long-term-health-conditions-470470 <description><![CDATA[Chronic Disease Day raises awareness about long-term health conditions that require medical attention for more than a year and restrict the daily activities of the patients.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-disease-day-healthy-habits-prevent-long-term-health-conditions-470470</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 03:49:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Sundowning? Tips To Help Dementia Patients Deal With The Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-sundowning-tips-help-dementia-病人-deal-symptoms-470468 <description><![CDATA[Some dementia patients tend to become more confused, agitated and anxious in the evenings due to a neurological phenomenon called sundowning.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-sundowning-tips-help-dementia-病人-deal-symptoms-470468</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:41:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Which Is The Best Time To Retrieve Eggs? Study Says IVF Success Varies With Season]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/which-best-time-retrieve-eggs-study-says-ivf-success-varies-season-470465 <description><![CDATA[In the latest study, researchers evaluated the impact of seasons, temperatures and the number of hours of bright sunshine on IVF success.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/which-best-time-retrieve-eggs-study-says-ivf-success-varies-season-470465</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:54:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Black Women With Hypertensive Disorders Of Pregnancy More At Risk of Stroke, Study Shows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/black-women-hypertense-disorders-pregnancy-more-risk-中风-study-shows-470454 <description><![CDATA[The link between HDOP history and stroke risk was found in both younger and older women, regardless of their weight status during young adulthood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/black-women-hypertense-disorders-pregnancy-more-risk-中风-study-shows-470454</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 05:12:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Drug To Regrow Teeth? Trials Set To Start For Medicine That May Help In Regrowth]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-regrow-teeth-trials-set-start-medicine-that-may-help-regrowth-470451 <description><![CDATA[If the clinical trials go well, the first medicine that allows people to grow a new set of teeth would be available for use in 2030.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-regrow-teeth-trials-set-start-medicine-that-may-help-regrowth-470451</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:25:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Group Activities Like Dancing And Art Therapy Could Alleviate Depression, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/group-activities-like-dancing-art-therapy-could-alleviate-depression-study-finds-470448 <description><![CDATA[The researchers looked at different types of performance art like dance therapy, music therapy, art therapy, martial arts-based therapies, and theater with an aim to understand how these art forms can help improve mental health and reduce feelings of anxiety and depression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/group-activities-like-dancing-art-therapy-could-alleviate-depression-study-finds-470448</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 02:44:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Researchers Recommend These 6 Foods To Reduce Risk Of Heart Attack And Stroke]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/researchers-recommend-these-6-foods-reduce-risk-heart-attack-中风-470445 <description><![CDATA[According to a recent study, not getting enough fruits, vegetables, legumes, nuts, fish, and whole-fat dairy products in the diet raises the risk of cardiovascular diseases in adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/researchers-recommend-these-6-foods-reduce-risk-heart-attack-中风-470445</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 01:21:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare But Deadly Mosquito-Borne Disease Detected In Michigan, Urging Precautions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-deadly-mosquito-borne-disease-Detected-michigan-urging-precautions-470444 <description><![CDATA[Michigan faces concerns after detecting a rare but fatal mosquito-borne disease in the area.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-deadly-mosquito-borne-disease-Detected-michigan-urging-precautions-470444</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 19:52:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Novavax COVID-19 Vaccine Shows Promise In Study, Gets Full Approval In Europe]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-novavax-covid-19-vaccine-shows-promise-study-gets-full-approval-europe-470442 <description><![CDATA[The new Novavax vaccine for COVID-19 showed promise in a trial.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-novavax-covid-19-vaccine-shows-promise-study-gets-full-approval-europe-470442</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 19:45:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[China Reports Rise In COVID-19 Deaths In June After Easing Containment Measures]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/china-reports-rise-covid-19-deaths-june-after-easing-containment-measures-470440<description><![CDATA[China has reported an increase in COVID-19 deaths during the month of June.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/china-reports-rise-covid-19-deaths-june-after-easing-containment-measures-470440</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 19:35:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mpox Resurgence Update: Minnesota, Coachella Valley Record New Infections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-resurgence-update-minnesota-coachella-valley-record-new-infections-470443 <description><![CDATA[Public health officials reported new cases amid the anticipated mpox resurgence in the country.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-resurgence-update-minnesota-coachella-valley-record-new-infections-470443</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 19:31:25 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>