<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一个</language><item><title><![CDATA[What Is 'Aeronutrients'? Researchers Say You Can Breathe In Nutrients And Vitamins]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-aero Nutritions-researchers-say-you-can-breathe- Nutritions-vitamins-472700 <description><![CDATA[A recent study investigated the concept of "aeronutrients" and the mechanisms by which they are absorbed for human health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-aero Nutritions-researchers-say-you-can-breathe- Nutritions-vitamins-472700</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Nov 2024 03:08:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Avoid Late, Heavy Dinners: They Affect More Than Just Your Weight]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-late-heavy-dinners-they-affect-more-just-your-weight-472697 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that having heavy meals late in the evening can have harmful effects, even for those without weight issues.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-late-heavy-dinners-they-affect-more-just-your-weight-472697</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:11:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hot Cocoa, Green Tea With Fatty Meals May Combat Negative Effects Of Stress: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hot-cocoa-green-tea-fatty-meals-may-combat-negative-effects-stress-study-472694 <description><![CDATA[The study investigated how flavanols, when consumed with fat, can help reduce the negative effects of fat on stress-related problems in endothelial function.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hot-cocoa-green-tea-fatty-meals-may-combat-negative-effects-stress-study-472694</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Nov 2024 04:43:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Links COVID-19 To Tumor Regression, Opens New Venue For Cancer Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-links-covid-19-tumor-regression-opens-new-venue-cancer-treatment-472692 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that RNA from the SARS-CoV-2 virus may trigger the development of immune cells with anti-cancer properties.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-links-covid-19-tumor-regression-opens-new-venue-cancer-treatment-472692</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Nov 2024 02:30:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Multistate E-Coli Outbreak Linked To Organic Carrots Claims One Life, Sickens Dozens: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multistate-e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-carrots-claims-one-life-sickens-dozens-cdc-472691 <description><![CDATA[The current multistate outbreak, identified since September, is linked to multiple brands of recalled organic bagged carrots, including whole and baby carrots sold by Grimmway Farms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multistate-e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-carrots-claims-one-life-sickens-dozens-cdc-472691</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Nov 2024 01:02:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Every Extra Hour Of Walking In Your 40's Adds Time To Lifespan: Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/every-extra-hour-walking-your-40s-adds-time-lifespan-study-suggests-472689 <description><![CDATA[The study found that on average, every extra hour of walking in your 40s adds around 3 hours (169 minutes) to lifespan.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/every-extra-hour-walking-your-40s-adds-time-lifespan-study-suggests-472689</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Nov 2024 05:17:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Screen Time Triggers Early Puberty, Rapid Bone Growth, Potentially Limiting Height: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-triggers-early-puberty-rapid-bone-growth-pottially-limiting-height-study-472687 <description><![CDATA[The results of the rat study highlight how exposure to screens from a very young age affects children's height and physical maturity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-triggers-early-puberty-rapid-bone-growth-pottially-limiting-height-study-472687</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:54:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Magnesium Bath Flakes For Muscle Recovery, Stress Relief And Skin Hydration]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-magnesium-bath-flakes-muscle-recovery-stress-relief-skin-Hydration-472655 <description><![CDATA[Whether you're looking for a natural way to support muscle recovery, reduce stress, or improve your skin's hydration, magnesium bath flakes are an accessible and effective option to explore.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-magnesium-bath-flakes-muscle-recovery-stress-relief-skin-Hydration-472655</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:57:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Fitness Belts To Support For Core Strength, Posture And Injury Prevention]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-fitness-belts-support-core-strength-posture-injury-prevention-472664 <description><![CDATA[Fitness belts enhance core stability, support proper posture, and prevent injury during heavy lifting. Ideal for weightlifters, they provide added security, ensuring safe movement while promoting balanced muscle engagement for improved performance.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-fitness-belts-support-core-strength-posture-injury-prevention-472664</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:55:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Florida City Leaders Vote to Eliminate Fluoride from Water Supply Because of RFK Jr.: 'I Can Get False Teeth If Needed']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-city-leaders-vote-eliminate-fluide-water-supply-because-rfk-jr-i-can-get-false-472683 <description><![CDATA[Government officials in Winter Haven City voted to eliminate fluoride from its water supply, citing Robert F. Kennedy, Jr.'s national campaign to remove it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-city-leaders-vote-eliminate-fluide-water-supply-because-rfk-jr-i-can-get-false-472683</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:19:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Walk For 10 Minutes After Every Hour Of Sitting To Reduce Blood Pressure, Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/walk-10-mines-after-every-hour-sitting-reduce-blood-Pressure-study-suggests-472681 <description><![CDATA[The study found that sitting for more than six hours per day during childhood and continuing the habit into adulthood can raise blood pressure by 4mmHg.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/walk-10-mines-after-every-hour-sitting-reduce-blood-Pressure-study-suggests-472681</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Nov 2024 03:10:33 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>