<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Gut Microbe And Heart Health: Study Says Intestinal Bacteria Can Cause Fatty Deposits In Arteries]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-microbe-heart-health-study-says-intestinal-bacteria-can-cause-fatty-deposits-arteries-470516 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that an increase in the number of a particular type of bacteria in the gut increases the risk of coronary atherosclerotic plaques or fatty deposits in arteries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-microbe-heart-health-study-says-intestinal-bacteria-can-cause-fatty-deposits-arteries-470516</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:55:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Hyperlactation Syndrome? Woman With Rare Condition Sets Guinness Record By Donating Breast Milk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-hyperlactation-syndrome-woman-rare-condition-sets-guinness-record-donating-breast-milk-470515 <description><![CDATA[Elisabeth Anderson-Sierra, a mother of two from Aloha, has saved the lives of thousands of premature babies by donating around 1,600 liters of her breastmilk over the past nine years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-hyperlactation-syndrome-woman-rare-condition-sets-guinness-record-donating-breast-milk-470515</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 01:40:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Could Carpal Tunnel Syndrome Signal Heart Failure? Study Finds Potential Link Between The Two]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-carpal-tunnel-syndrome-signal-heart-failure-study-finds-pottial-link- Between-two-470505 <description><![CDATA[Elderly patients with carpal tunnel syndrome are 39% more likely to develop heart failure compared with those without the condition, a recent study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-carpal-tunnel-syndrome-signal-heart-failure-study-finds-pottial-link- Between-two-470505</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jul 2023 05:17:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Deep Sleep To Control Diabetes: Study Uncovers How Brain Waves Regulate Blood Sugar Levels]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/deep-sleep-control-diabetes-study-uncovers-how-brain-waves-regulate-blood-sugar-levels-470504 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has found how deep-sleep brain waves at night regulate a person's insulin sensitivity, which determines blood sugar control the next day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/deep-sleep-control-diabetes-study-uncovers-how-brain-waves-regulate-blood-sugar-levels-470504</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jul 2023 02:38:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Deadly Scrub Typhus Bacteria Found In North Carolina; What To Know About The Infectious Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/deadly-scrub-typhus-bacteria-found-north-carolina-what-know-about-infectious-disease-470502 <description><![CDATA[Bacteria causing scrub typhus, a deadly form of typhus disease spread through chigger bites, have been detected for the first time in the U.S.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/deadly-scrub-typhus-bacteria-found-north-carolina-what-know-about-infectious-disease-470502</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jul 2023 01:42:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Return To Ancient Recipe: Study Says 2 Common Pantry Ingredients Can Fight Superbug Infections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/return-ancient-recipe-study-says-2-common-pantry-ingredients-can-fight-superbug-infections-470499 <description><![CDATA[As scientists race to find ways to tackle superbug infections, a recent study highlights the need to revisit the ancient recipes to treat infections caused by antibiotic-resistant strains of microbes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/return-ancient-recipe-study-says-2-common-pantry-ingredients-can-fight-superbug-infections-470499</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:41:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Man Develops Green Hairy Tongue; Know What Causes The Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-man-develops-green-hairy-tongue-know-what-c​​auses-condition-470497 <description><![CDATA[The man developed an abnormal coating on his tongue almost three weeks after he was treated for gum disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-man-develops-green-hairy-tongue-know-what-c​​auses-condition-470497</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:42:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[West Nile Fever: Dallas Reports First Human Case Of The Season; Know All About It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-fever-dallas-reports-first- human-case-season-know-all-about-it-470494 <description><![CDATA[The Dallas County Health and Human Services Department has confirmed a man was diagnosed with West Nile neuroinvasive disease, a severe form of the illness transmitted by mosquitos infected with the virus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-fever-dallas-reports-first- human-case-season-know-all-about-it-470494</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:49:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Is How Many Malaria Cases The US Records Every Year]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-how-many-malaria-cases-us-records-every-year-470491 <description><![CDATA[The United States has recently witnessed an uptick in malaria cases.]]></description><guid>https://www.medicaldaily.com/this-how-many-malaria-cases-us-records-every-year-470491</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:55:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Deadly Virus Is Spreading Across Europe; May Cause Future Pandemic, Says WHO]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-deadly-virus-spreading-across-europe-may-cause-future-pandemic-says-who-470490 <description><![CDATA[The warmed environment has been conducive to the expansion of the habitat of ticks that can carry and transmit the nairovirus that causes CCHF.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-deadly-virus-spreading-across-europe-may-cause-future-pandemic-says-who-470490</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 05:38:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Sleep Divorce? It Turns Out A Lot Americans Are Doing It, Survey Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-sleep-divorce-it-turns-out-lot-americans-are-doing-it-survey-finds-470487 <description><![CDATA[Over a third of Americans reported opting for "sleep divorce" to accommodate their bed partner.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-sleep-divorce-it-turns-out-lot-americans-are-doing-it-survey-finds-470487</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 05:36:01 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>