<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[COVID Is Making A Comeback. Is It Time To Worry?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-making-comeback-it-time-worry-470724 <description><![CDATA[While the pandemic, and the panic, are over, COVID-19 cases are rising across the U.S. prompting concern about a return to mass vaccination, masking and even lockdowns.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-making-comeback-it-time-worry-470724</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 05:35:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Air Pollution Greatest Global Threat To Human Health, Says Benchmark Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-greatest-global-threat- human-health-says-benchmark-study-470721 <description><![CDATA[If the world were to permanently reduce the pollutants to meet the WHO guideline limit, the average person would add 2.3 years onto his or her life expectancy, according to the data.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-greatest-global-threat- human-health-says-benchmark-study-470721</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 04:36:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiac Arrest: Study Says Warning Signs Can Be Different In Men And Women]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-arrest-study-says-warning-signs-can- Different-men-women-470719 <description><![CDATA[Shortness of breath is reportedly its most prominent symptom in women, while for men, it is chest pain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiac-arrest-study-says-warning-signs-can- Different-men-women-470719</guid><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 03:43:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can IBS Be A Warning Sign Of Parkinson's Disease? Study Says Certain Gut Conditions Elevate Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-ibs-warning-sign-parkinsons-disease-study-says-certain-gut-conditions-elevate-risk-470716 <description><![CDATA[The findings of the study indicate that digestive issues such as constipation, gastroparesis, dysphagia and IBS without diarrhea can increase the risk of Parkinson's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-ibs-warning-sign-parkinsons-disease-study-says-certain-gut-conditions-elevate-risk-470716</guid><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 01:21:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Night Shifts And Brain Health: Study Says Working Late Hours May Lead To Memory Loss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-shifts-brain-health-study-says-working-late-hours-may-lead-memory-loss-470715 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that working on night shifts can cause cognitive impairments and memory loss in middle-aged and older adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-shifts-brain-health-study-says-working-late-hours-may-lead-memory-loss-470715</guid><pubDate> Fri, 25 Aug 2023 04:43:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Do Fish Oil Supplements Work For Your Heart Health? Here's What Researchers Think]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/do-fish-oil-supplements-work-your-heart-health-heres-what-researchers-think-470712 <description><![CDATA[A new study says although most labels that sell the supplements claim heart health benefits, they lack scientific evidence to prove the efficacy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/do-fish-oil-supplements-work-your-heart-health-heres-what-researchers-think-470712</guid><pubDate> Fri, 25 Aug 2023 03:14:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[1 Billion People Will Have Osteoarthritis By 2050, Study Says; Know Symptoms, Steps To Prevent Progression]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/1-billion-people-will-have-osteoarthritis-2050-study-says-know-symptoms-steps-prevent-470711 <description><![CDATA[A study published in the Lancet Rheumatology journal suggests that 15% of people aged 30 and above currently experience osteoarthritis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/1-billion-people-will-have-osteoarthritis-2050-study-says-know-symptoms-steps-prevent-470711</guid><pubDate> Fri, 25 Aug 2023 01:02:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Lack Of Physical Activity In Childhood Increases Risk Of Heart Attacks, Strokes Later In Life: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lack-physical-activity-childhood-increases-risk-heart-attacks-中风-later-life-study-470710 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say the lack of physical activity in childhood raises heart attack risks later in life, even in those who grow up to have normal weight and blood pressure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lack-physical-activity-childhood-increases-risk-heart-attacks-中风-later-life-study-470710</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 04:26:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is MLD? Rare Genetic Condition Causes Dementia In 3-Year-Old]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-mld-rare-genic-condition-causes-dementia-3-year-old-470707 <description><![CDATA[A 3-year-old boy has lost his ability to walk and talk after he was diagnosed with metachromatic leukodystrophy. The condition could cause muscle wasting, weakness, loss of vision, issues with swallowing, paralysis and dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-mld-rare-genic-condition-causes-dementia-3-year-old-470707</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 03:32:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Don't Skip Vaccines: New Study Says Routine Shots May Protect You From Alzheimer's]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-skip-vaccines-new-study-says-routine-shots-may-protect-you-alzheimers-470705 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that people vaccinated against shingles, pneumococcus, tetanus and diphtheria, with or without an added pertussis vaccine, are at a 25% to 30% reduced risk of developing Alzheimer's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-skip-vaccines-new-study-says-routine-shots-may-protect-you-alzheimers-470705</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:19:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gut Health Revolution: Unveiling The Top 10 Probiotics Powerhouses Of 2023]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-health-revolution-unveiling-top-10-probiotics-powerhouses-2023-470459 <description><![CDATA[Embark on a gut health revolution as we unveil the top 10 probiotic powerhouses of 2023, offering insights into the world of digestive wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-health-revolution-unveiling-top-10-probiotics-powerhouses-2023-470459</guid><pubDate> Wed, 23 Aug 2023 04:49:59 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>