<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[From Increased Appetite To Reduced Inflammation, Study Reveals Health Benefits Of Cardamom]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/increased-appetite-reduced-inflammation-study-reveals-health-benefits-cardamom-470654 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that consuming at least eight to 10 cardamom pods every day can bring in the desired health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/increased-appetite-reduced-inflammation-study-reveals-health-benefits-cardamom-470654</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:09:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Blood Sugar Levels Even Without Diabetes Can Raise Risk Of Heart Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-blood-sugar-levels-even-without-diabetes-can-raise-risk-heart-disease-study-470653 <description><![CDATA[Elevated blood sugar levels in prediabetes patients increase the risk of heart diseases such as heart failure by 30% to 47%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-blood-sugar-levels-even-without-diabetes-can-raise-risk-heart-disease-study-470653</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Aug 2023 02:55:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are Girl Dinners Safe? Here's What Experts Have To Say About The Latest Food Trend]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-girl-dinners-safe-heres-what-experts-have-say-about-latest-food-trend-470652 <description><![CDATA[Health experts believe girl dinners, the latest food trend on TikTok, can be healthy if approached with "balance in mind."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-girl-dinners-safe-heres-what-experts-have-say-about-latest-food-trend-470652</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Aug 2023 02:04:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Eris? Know All About The Fast-Spreading COVID-19 Variant]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-eris-know-all-about-fast-spreading-covid-19-variant-470648 <description><![CDATA[Although the public health risk posed by EG.5 is estimated to be low, the World Health Organization on Wednesday warned all nations to monitor the cases, while classifying it as a "variant of interest."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-eris-know-all-about-fast-spreading-covid-19-variant-470648</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Aug 2023 04:21:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hourglass Syndrome: Know What Happens When You Suck In Stomach For A Flat Tummy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hourglass-syndrome-know-what-happens-when-you-suck-stomach-flat-tummy-470646 <description><![CDATA[Experts strongly advise people to avoid the stomach-gripping habit as it can lead to health consequences over time.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hourglass-syndrome-know-what-happens-when-you-suck-stomach-flat-tummy-470646</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Aug 2023 03:15:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Essential Tremor Vs Parkinson's Disease: Know The Differences In Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/essential-tremor-vs-parkinsons-disease-know-differences-symptoms-470644 <description><![CDATA[Shaky hands or involuntary movements in the legs may not be always signs of Parkinson's disease. It may also be a sign of a less serious neurological condition called essential tremor.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/essential-tremor-vs-parkinsons-disease-know-differences-symptoms-470644</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Aug 2023 01:33:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Albinism: Researchers Explain What Leads To Spontaneous Eye Movement In People With The Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/albinism-researchers-explain-what-leads-spontaneous-eye-movement-people-condition-470643 <description><![CDATA[In addition to the noticeable changes in appearance, people with albinism often face difficulties in their vision. They might not see things as clearly as others.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/albinism-researchers-explain-what-leads-spontaneous-eye-movement-people-condition-470643</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Aug 2023 06:36:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Low Levels Of Vitamin K Linked To Poor Lung Health; Know Signs Of Deficiency]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-levels-vitamin-k-linked-poor-lung-health-know-signs-deficiency-470641 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that people with inadequate levels of vitamin K suffer from asthma, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) and wheezing.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-levels-vitamin-k-linked-poor-lung-health-know-signs-deficiency-470641</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Aug 2023 03:54:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Life's Little Joys Like Coffee, Music Can Boost Brain Power: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lifes-little-joys-like-coffee-music-can-boost-brain-power-study-470639 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say activities like sipping coffee and listening to your favorite music help to boost brain power.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lifes-little-joys-like-coffee-music-can-boost-brain-power-study-470639</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Aug 2023 02:51:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Long-Term Use Of Popular Acid Reflux Drugs May Increase Risk Of Dementia; Know Alternative Strategies]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-term-use-popular-acid-reflux-drugs-may-increase-risk-dementia-know-alternative-strategies-470638 <description><![CDATA[People who take proton pump inhibitors (PPI) for treating acid reflux every day for four-and-a-half years or more are at a 33% increased risk of developing dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-term-use-popular-acid-reflux-drugs-may-increase-risk-dementia-know-alternative-strategies-470638</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Aug 2023 01:09:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Freshly Made Pizza A Good Choice For People With Rheumatoid Arthritis, Researchers Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/freshly-made-pizza-good-choice-people-rheumatoid-arthritis-researchers-say-470636 <description><![CDATA[If prepared with fresh ingredients and in a perfect balance of carbs, protein and fats, pizza can be a nutritious choice for people with rheumatoid arthritis, a study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/freshly-made-pizza-good-choice-people-rheumatoid-arthritis-researchers-say-470636</guid><pubDate> Wed, 09 Aug 2023 04:20:02 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>