<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Is Ketamine For Depression Safe And Effective? Elon Musk Says It's A 'Better Option']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ketamine-depression-safe- effective-elon-musk-says-its-better-option-470349 <description><![CDATA[Elon Musk has told people he is taking small doses of ketamine to treat depression, a report claims.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ketamine-depression-safe- effective-elon-musk-says-its-better-option-470349</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 05:41:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[NHS Doctor Reveals The Correct Way Of Pooping For A 'Truly Wonderful Dump']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nhs-doctor-reveals- Correct-way-pooping-truly-wonderful-dump-470346 <description><![CDATA[A doctor in the United Kingdom shared with his over 5.1 million TikTok followers the proper and comfortable method of bowel movement.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nhs-doctor-reveals- Correct-way-pooping-truly-wonderful-dump-470346</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 05:36:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mpox Resurgence Expected As More People Step Out With Less Clothing On This Summer: Expert]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-resurgence-expected-more-people-step-out-less-clothing-this-summer-expert-470338 <description><![CDATA[Experts brace for the resurgence of mpox infections this summer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-resurgence-expected-more-people-step-out-less-clothing-this-summer-expert-470338</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:04:49 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Expert Reveals Commonly Missed Signs Of Dementia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-reveals-commonly-missed-signs-dementia-470337 <description><![CDATA[There are subtle signs and symptoms of dementia that could go unnoticed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-reveals-commonly-missed-signs-dementia-470337</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:00:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Paralyzed After COVID-19 Infection Speaks Out, Happy To Be Back On His Feet A Year Later]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-paralyzed-after-covid-19-infection-speaks-out-happy-back-his-feet-year-later-470341 <description><![CDATA[Lenny LaMarre is just one of the millions affected by complications and lingering symptoms of COVID-19.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-paralyzed-after-covid-19-infection-speaks-out-happy-back-his-feet-year-later-470341</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:54:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Designed To Be A 'Bioweapon,' Wuhan Researcher Claims]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-Designed-bioweapon-wuhan-researcher-claims-470343 <description><![CDATA[A Wuhan researcher has come out to claim that SARS-CoV-2 was designed to be a "bioweapon."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-Designed-bioweapon-wuhan-researcher-claims-470343</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:43:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People With This Blood Group May Be More Prone To Contracting COVID-19]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-this-blood-group-may-more-prone-contracting-covid-19-470334 <description><![CDATA[Early speculation on blood group A's increased susceptibility to COVID-19 receives support from a recent study published in the journal Blood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-this-blood-group-may-more-prone-contracting-covid-19-470334</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 05:14:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[It's All In Your Mind? Study Says Boost From Morning Coffee May Be A Placebo]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/its-all-your-mind-study-says-boost-morning-coffee-may-placebo-470332 <description><![CDATA[Researchers evaluated if the alertness associated with morning coffee is from caffeine or from the experience of drinking it and found that drinking coffee could have more of a placebo effect.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/its-all-your-mind-study-says-boost-morning-coffee-may-placebo-470332</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:12:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[HDL Vs LDL: Know The Difference Between Good And Bad Cholesterol]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/hdl-vs-ldl-know-difference- Between-good-bad-cholesterol-470329 <description><![CDATA[High levels of cholesterol can lead to conditions such as stroke, heart disease, diabetes and hypertension.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hdl-vs-ldl-know-difference- Between-good-bad-cholesterol-470329</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:23:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Malaria Outbreak In Texas And Florida; First Cases Detected In 2 Decades]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-florida-grapple-malaria-outbreak-first-cases-Detected-two-decades-470326 <description><![CDATA[Texas and Florida face a malaria threat as locally acquired cases emerge after a 20-year hiatus, raising concerns nationwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-florida-grapple-malaria-outbreak-first-cases-Detected-two-decades-470326</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:22:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Erectile Dysfunction Can Be A Warning Sign Of Heart Attack; Ways To Prevent It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/erectile-dysfunction-can-warning-sign-heart-attack-ways-prevent-it-470325 <description><![CDATA[A person who has ED but without any obvious symptoms is recommended to be screened for heart disease. The link between ED and heart disease is that both conditions can be caused due to narrowing of arteries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/erectile-dysfunction-can-warning-sign-heart-attack-ways-prevent-it-470325</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:22:18 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>