<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Obesity Affects Sperm Count: Study Uncovers Brain Mechanism Behind Fertility Decline]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-affects-sperm-count-study-uncovers-brain-mechanism-behind-fertility-decline-471991 <description><![CDATA[The researchers discovered in a mice study that obesity causes chronic changes in the brain, which affects sperm count.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-affects-sperm-count-study-uncovers-brain-mechanism-behind-fertility-decline-471991</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jul 2024 01:55:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Endometriosis Raises Risk Of Ovarian Cancer, Severe Types Most Vulnerable: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-raises-risk-ovarian-cancer-severe-types-most-vulnerable-study-471988 <description><![CDATA[Individuals with severe forms of endometriosis, such as deep infiltrating endometriosis or ovarian endometriomas, face a staggering 9.7-fold increase in the likelihood of developing ovarian cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-raises-risk-ovarian-cancer-severe-types-most-vulnerable-study-471988</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:17:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Frequent Childhood Relocations Linked To 40% Higher Risk Of Depression In Adulthood]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/frequent-childhood-relocations-linked-40-higher-risk-depression-adulthood-471986 <description><![CDATA[Individuals who often move before age 15 are over 40% more likely to be diagnosed with depression in adulthood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/frequent-childhood-relocations-linked-40-higher-risk-depression-adulthood-471986</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jul 2024 03:06:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Get Consistent Sleep: Study Says Irregular Pattern Raises Diabetes Risk By 34%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/get-consistent-sleep-study-says-irregular-pattern-raises-diabetes-risk-34-471983 <description><![CDATA[A study highlights the significance of maintaining regular sleep patterns for preventing type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/get-consistent-sleep-study-says-irregular-pattern-raises-diabetes-risk-34-471983</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jul 2024 02:03:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Best Form Of Daily Commute For Physical And Mental Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-form-daily-commute-physical-mental-health-471981 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that active daily travel, such as walking or cycling to work, is one of the most practical and sustainable methods to boost daily physical activity, reaping significant health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-form-daily-commute-physical-mental-health-471981</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Jul 2024 04:34:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Poop Frequency Matter? Study Identifies 'Goldilocks Zone' For Long-Term Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-poop-Frequency-matter-study-identizes-goldilocks-zone-long-term-health-471978 <description><![CDATA[A study revealed that both frequent and infrequent bowel movements can have long-term health implications.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-poop-Frequency-matter-study-identizes-goldilocks-zone-long-term-health-471978</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Jul 2024 03:39:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Should You Exercise Before Bed? Here's What Study Suggests For Better Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/should-you-exercise-before-bed-heres-what-study-suggests-better-sleep-471976 <description><![CDATA[A new study found that incorporating resistance exercise "activity breaks" at night can improve sleep duration.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/should-you-exercise-before-bed-heres-what-study-suggests-better-sleep-471976</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:26:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Transforming Young Minds: How Dr. Abbey Is Revolutionizing ADHD Treatment Without Medication]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/transforming-young-minds-how-dr-abbey-revolutionizing-adhd-treatment-without-medication-471973 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Abbey's company has refined over forty types of interventions into a proprietary system that transforms the lives of children with ADHD.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/transforming-young-minds-how-dr-abbey-revolutionizing-adhd-treatment-without-medication-471973</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:45:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Antibiotics Use In Childhood Elevates Asthma Risk; Study Identifies Gut Molecule With Protective Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antibiotics-use-childhood-elevates-asthma-risk-study-identizes-gut-molecule-protective-effects-471972 <description><![CDATA[The study identified a molecule called IPA, produced by gut bacteria, that shows promise as a dietary supplement in the future to prevent asthma development in children at risk of the disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/antibiotics-use-childhood-elevates-asthma-risk-study-identizes-gut-molecule-protective-effects-471972</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Jul 2024 02:51:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Maintaining Blood Pressure Below 120 mmHg Protects From Late-Life Dementia: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maintaining-blood-Pressure-below-120-mmhgprotects-late-life-dementia-study-471971 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that lowering systolic blood pressure below the clinically safe threshold of 120 mmHg over time may slightly reduce an individual's risk of developing dementia, particularly among Black and Latino groups.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maintaining-blood-Pressure-below-120-mmhgprotects-late-life-dementia-study-471971</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Jul 2024 01:49:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Insufficient And Excessive Sleep May Harm Blood Vessels Of Diabetes Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/insufficient-excessive-sleep-may-harm-blood-vessels-diabetes-病人-471968 <description><![CDATA[The study noted that short sleep duration is tied to a 2.6 times higher risk of microvascular disease, while long sleep duration is linked to a 2.3 times increased risk of the same condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/insufficient-excessive-sleep-may-harm-blood-vessels-diabetes-病人-471968</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:57:31 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>