<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[9/11 First Responders At Elevated Risk Of Early Onset Dementia, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-11-first-responders-elevated-risk-early-onset-dementia-study-says-471853 <description><![CDATA[There is a higher likelihood of developing dementia before reaching the age of 65 in the first responders to the 9/11 site who experienced severe exposure to toxic debris in contrast to minimally exposed responders or those who utilized personal protective equipment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-11-first-responders-elevated-risk-early-onset-dementia-study-says-471853</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 03:24:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Reduce TV Watching And Get Off The Couch: Study Reveals Secret To Healthy Aging]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reduce-tv-watching-get-off-couch-study-reveals-secret-healthy-aging-471852 <description><![CDATA[Swapping just one hour of daily TV watching for light physical activity at home can improve the odds of reaching a healthy age of 70 or beyond by 8%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reduce-tv-watching-get-off-couch-study-reveals-secret-healthy-aging-471852</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:56:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Levels Of Toxic Cancer-Causing Ethylene Oxide Detected In Louisiana: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-有毒-癌症-导致-乙烯-氧化物-检测到-路易斯安那-报告-471850 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that the air in the industrialized stretch of southeast Louisiana dubbed "cancer alley" has 20 times higher concentrations of carcinogenic ethylene oxide than previously expected.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-有毒-癌症-导致-乙烯-氧化物-检测到-路易斯安那-报告-471850</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jun 2024 03:47:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra-Processed Plant Food Raises Risk Of Heart Diseases, Related Deaths: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-plant-food-raises-risk-heart-diseases-lated-deaths-study-471848 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that ultra-processed plant-based foods do not offer health benefits and are actually linked to an increased risk of heart disease and heart-related mortality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-plant-food-raises-risk-heart-diseases-lated-deaths-study-471848</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jun 2024 02:34:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder Awareness Month: Eliminate Stigma As Expert Unveils Facts And Myths]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/post-traumatic-stress-disorder-awareness-month-eliminate-stigma-expert-unveils-facts-myths-471846 <description><![CDATA[Post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) is a frequently misunderstood mental health condition, often unfairly seen as a sign of weakness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/post-traumatic-stress-disorder-awareness-month-eliminate-stigma-expert-unveils-facts-myths-471846</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jun 2024 01:30:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Planetary Health Diet? Study Says It May Reduce Premature Death By 30%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-planetary-health-diet-study-says-it-may-reduce-premature-death-30-471844 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered that adhering to a healthy, sustainable diet, termed the planetary health diet, can help preserve the environment and lower the risk of premature death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-planetary-health-diet-study-says-it-may-reduce-premature-death-30-471844</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jun 2024 03:58:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hospitalizations With Seizures, Loss Of Consciousness Linked To Microdosing Chocolate Bars, FDA Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospitalizations-seizures-loss-thought-linked-microdosing-chocolate-bars-fda-warns-471842 <description><![CDATA[FDA has issued a warning after six people were hospitalized across four states following the consumption of Diamond Shruumz-brand's microdosing chocolate bars.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospitalizations-seizures-loss-thought-linked-microdosing-chocolate-bars-fda-warns-471842</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jun 2024 03:17:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Best Time To Exercise For Reducing Blood Sugar Levels]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-time-exercise-reducing-blood-sugar-levels-471841 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now identified the optimal time to exercise for reducing blood sugar levels in sedentary adults struggling with overweight and obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-time-exercise-reducing-blood-sugar-levels-471841</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jun 2024 01:27:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Omega-3 Supplements Now Have A Vegan Option; Here's Why You Need To Take Them Daily]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-supplements-now-have-vegan-option-heres-why-you-need-take-them-daily-471839 <description><![CDATA[Omega-3 is known for cognitive advantages like improving brain development, enhancing mental performance, and lowering the risk of neurodegenerative disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-supplements-now-have-vegan-option-heres-why-you-need-take-them-daily-471839</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:26:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Use Of Social Media Photo Filters Raises Muscle Dysmorphia In Young Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/use-social-media-photo-filters-raises-muscle-dysmorphia-young-adults-study-471838 <description><![CDATA[The use of social media photo filters has a strong association with increased symptoms of muscle dysmorphia, a mental health condition characterized by excessive obsession with muscularity and leanness, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/use-social-media-photo-filters-raises-muscle-dysmorphia-young-adults-study-471838</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:01:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Planning A Trip Abroad? Here's How To Reduce Risk Of Yellow Fever]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-trip-abroad-heres-how-reduce-risk-yellow-fever-471837 <description><![CDATA[If tropical destinations such as South America or Africa are on your itinerary, know all about yellow fever and learn essential tips to minimize your risk of contracting the infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-trip-abroad-heres-how-reduce-risk-yellow-fever-471837</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:30:37 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>