<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[It's All In Your Mind? Study Says Boost From Morning Coffee May Be A Placebo]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/its-all-your-mind-study-says-boost-morning-coffee-may-placebo-470332 <description><![CDATA[Researchers evaluated if the alertness associated with morning coffee is from caffeine or from the experience of drinking it and found that drinking coffee could have more of a placebo effect.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/its-all-your-mind-study-says-boost-morning-coffee-may-placebo-470332</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:12:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[HDL Vs LDL: Know The Difference Between Good And Bad Cholesterol]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/hdl-vs-ldl-know-difference- Between-good-bad-cholesterol-470329 <description><![CDATA[High levels of cholesterol can lead to conditions such as stroke, heart disease, diabetes and hypertension.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hdl-vs-ldl-know-difference- Between-good-bad-cholesterol-470329</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:23:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Malaria Outbreak In Texas And Florida; First Cases Detected In 2 Decades]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-florida-grapple-malaria-outbreak-first-cases-Detected-two-decades-470326 <description><![CDATA[Texas and Florida face a malaria threat as locally acquired cases emerge after a 20-year hiatus, raising concerns nationwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-florida-grapple-malaria-outbreak-first-cases-Detected-two-decades-470326</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:22:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Erectile Dysfunction Can Be A Warning Sign Of Heart Attack; Ways To Prevent It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/erectile-dysfunction-can-warning-sign-heart-attack-ways-prevent-it-470325 <description><![CDATA[The link between ED and heart disease is that both conditions can be caused due to narrowing of arteries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/erectile-dysfunction-can-warning-sign-heart-attack-ways-prevent-it-470325</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:22:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Ways Your Limbs Are Signaling That You Have Cholesterol]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-ways-your-limbs-are-signaling-that-you-have-cholesterol-470323 <description><![CDATA[Cholesterol symptoms include cold feet, cramps and delayed wound healing.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-ways-your-limbs-are-signaling-that-you-have-cholesterol-470323</guid><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:06:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Leads To Long-Term Decline In Men's Sperm Quality, Reveals Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-leads-long-term-decline-mens-sperm-quality-reveals-study-470321 <description><![CDATA[Even mild COVID-19 infection could impact the quality of semen, according to the researchers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-leads-long-term-decline-mens-sperm-quality-reveals-study-470321</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:12:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Ozempic Rival Drugs Could Be Cheaper, More Effective]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-ozempic-rival-drugs-could-cheaper-more- effective-470316 <description><![CDATA[Two new obesity drugs displayed promising results in clinical trials.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-ozempic-rival-drugs-could-cheaper-more- effective-470316</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:04:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Long COVID: Scientists Present New Insights, Potential Solutions]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-covid-scientists-present-new-insights-pottial-solutions-470319 <description><![CDATA[Millions of individuals continue to grapple with the devastating effects of long COVID.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-covid-scientists-present-new-insights-pottial-solutions-470319</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 21:57:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mpox Transmission 'Remains At Low Pace' In Many Countries: WHO]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-transmission-remains-low-pace-many-countries-who-470317 <description><![CDATA[The World Health Organization has released a new update on the mpox outbreak.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-transmission-remains-low-pace-many-countries-who-470317</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 21:50:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Advancements in Practice: Modern Chiropractic Clinic Services in the 21st Century]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/advancements-practice-modern-chiropractic-clinic-services-21st- century-470312 <description><![CDATA[In today's dynamic healthcare environment, the importance of staying abreast with modern advancements has never been more critical.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/advancements-practice-modern-chiropractic-clinic-services-21st- century-470312</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:34:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Charting the Course: Innovations and Treatments in the Field of Orthopaedics]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/charting-course-innovations-treatments-field-orthopaedics-470311 <description><![CDATA[Orthopaedics, a medical speciality focused on the musculoskeletal system, is a cornerstone of healthcare services worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/charting-course-innovations-treatments-field-orthopaedics-470311</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:30:59 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>