<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一个</language><item><title><![CDATA[Study Finds Two Common Gynecological Disorders Linked To Increased Risk Of Early Death]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-two-common-gynecological-disorders-linked-increased-risk-early-death-472720 <description><![CDATA[The study found that individuals with endometriosis were 31% more likely to die prematurely (before age 70) compared to those without these disorders]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-two-common-gynecological-disorders-linked-increased-risk-early-death-472720</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Nov 2024 05:44:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Fitness May Lower Dementia Risk, Even For Those With Genetic Predisposition, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardioangiography-fitness-may-lower-dementia-risk-even-those-genic-predisposition-study-finds-472718 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that in those with a moderate to high genetic risk of dementia, high cardiovascular fitness reduced their risk of developing dementia by 35%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardioangiography-fitness-may-lower-dementia-risk-even-those-genic-predisposition-study-finds-472718</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Nov 2024 03:51:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Chemical Identified In U.S. Tap Water, Scientists Urge Investigation Into Its Toxicity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-chemical-identified-us-tap-water-scientists-urge-investigation-its-toothity-472715 <description><![CDATA[The chemical byproduct formed during water purification with chloramine is now officially named chloronitramide anion.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-chemical-identified-us-tap-water-scientists-urge-investigation-its-toothity-472715</guid><pubDate> Fri, 22 Nov 2024 01:50:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Woman Who Briefly Died After Rare Delivery Room Complication Has No Memory of Giving Birth to Triplets]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-woman-who-briefly-died-after-rare-delivery-room-complication-has-no-memory-giving-birth-472712 <description><![CDATA[A Texas woman retained no memory of giving birth to triplets, including the 48 to 72 hours leading up to the delivery, after being clinically dead for about 45 minutes post-birth.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-woman-who-briefly-died-after-rare-delivery-room-complication-has-no-memory-giving-birth-472712</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Nov 2024 16:04:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Yoga Mats: Enhance Your Practice With Comfort, Stability And Style]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-yoga-mats-enhance-your-practice-comfort-stability-style-472654 <description><![CDATA[Finding the right yoga mat can elevate your practice, providing stability, comfort, and peace of mind. With so many options, it's essential to consider your specific needs to enhance your experience on the mat.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-yoga-mats-enhance-your-practice-comfort-stability-style-472654</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Nov 2024 12:56:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Diagnosing Diabetes At Younger Age Increases Dementia Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diagnosing-diabetes-younger-age-increases-dementia-risk-study-472709 <description><![CDATA[With each year earlier a person is diagnosed with type 2 diabetes, their risk of developing dementia rises by 1.9%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diagnosing-diabetes-younger-age-increases-dementia-risk-study-472709</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Nov 2024 02:08:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are BPA Alternatives Safe? Study Finds BPF And BPS May Pose Health Risks]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-bpa-alternatives-safe-study-finds-bpf-bps-may-pose-health-risks-472708 <description><![CDATA[New research reveals that BPF (bisphenol F)and BPS (bisphenol s), commonly used as BPA substitutes, may pose health risks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-bpa-alternatives-safe-study-finds-bpf-bps-may-pose-health-risks-472708</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Nov 2024 01:26:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Postpartum Depression Rates Doubled In A Decade, Prevalence 'High And Rising' In U.S.: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/postpartum-depression-rates-doubled-decade-prevalence-high-rising-us-study-472706 <description><![CDATA[The prevalence significantly rose from 9.4 percent in 2010 to 19 percent in 2021, with higher rates observed particularly among individuals with elevated pre-pregnancy body mass index.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/postpartum-depression-rates-doubled-decade-prevalence-high-rising-us-study-472706</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:58:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Pills For Cardiovascular Diseases? They May Also Protect Against Dementia, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-pills-cardioangio-diseases-they-may-also-protect-against-dementia-study-says-472703 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that long-term use of cardiovascular drugs, especially when used in combination, may offer protection against dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-pills-cardioangio-diseases-they-may-also-protect-against-dementia-study-says-472703</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Nov 2024 04:55:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is 'Aeronutrients'? Researchers Say You Can Breathe In Nutrients And Vitamins]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-aero Nutritions-researchers-say-you-can-breathe- Nutritions-vitamins-472700 <description><![CDATA[A recent study investigated the concept of "aeronutrients" and the mechanisms by which they are absorbed for human health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-aero Nutritions-researchers-say-you-can-breathe- Nutritions-vitamins-472700</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Nov 2024 03:08:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Avoid Late, Heavy Dinners: They Affect More Than Just Your Weight]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-late-heavy-dinners-they-affect-more-just-your-weight-472697 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that having heavy meals late in the evening can have harmful effects, even for those without weight issues.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-late-heavy-dinners-they-affect-more-just-your-weight-472697</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:11:51 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>