<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA[Sad Songs Have Positive Effects On A Person's Well-Being, Study Suggests]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/sad-songs-have-positive-effects-persons-well-being-study-suggests-470017 <description><![CDATA[Recent research suggests that sad music fosters a sense of connection and has a positive impact on one's mental well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sad-songs-have-positive-effects-persons-well-being-study-suggests-470017</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 06:10:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Loneliness Takes Toll On Cancer Survivors' Health, Increases Risk of Mortality: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneliness-takes-toll-cancer-survivors-health-increases-risk-mortality-study-470014 <description><![CDATA[The study recommends the screening of loneliness in cancer survivors and offering social support to address their specific needs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneliness-takes-toll-cancer-survivors-health-increases-risk-mortality-study-470014</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 04:54:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Cancer Survivor Month: Tips To Reduce Risk Of Recurrence]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-cancer-survivor-month-tips-reduce-risk-recurrence-470015 <description><![CDATA[The journey of a cancer survivor does not end with the successful treatment of the disease. Cancer survivors need to adopt certain changes in their lifestyle to prevent the recurrence of the disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-cancer-survivor-month-tips-reduce-risk-recurrence-470015</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 04:23:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gardening, Dancing, and Brisk Walks Can Reduce Diabetes Risk by 75%, Study Shows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gardening-dancing-brisk-walks-can-reduce-diabetes-risk-75-study-shows-470010 <description><![CDATA[Vigorous-intensity physical activities like running, cycling, and heavy gardening that make you breathe heavily can alleviate the chances of developing diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gardening-dancing-brisk-walks-can-reduce-diabetes-risk-75-study-shows-470010</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 03:24:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hormone Replacement Therapy: Study Says Taking Oral Estrogen Increases Risk Of Hypertension]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hormone-replacement-therapy-study-says-taking-oral-estrogen-increases-risk-hypertension-470012 <description><![CDATA[Women taking estrogen pills as part of their menopausal hormone therapy are at a greater risk of developing hypertension, a recent study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hormone-replacement-therapy-study-says-taking-oral-estrogen-increases-risk-hypertension-470012</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 02:32:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Switching Carbs With Protein Might Reduce Mortality Risk In People With Chronic Kidney Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/switching-carbs-protein-might-reduce-mortality-risk-people-chronic-kidney-disease-470008 <description><![CDATA[The study has disproved the popular notion that a high-protein diet is harmful to people with chronic kidney disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/switching-carbs-protein-might-reduce-mortality-risk-people-chronic-kidney-disease-470008</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:09:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Environment Day 2023: Why Are Microplastics So Dangerous? How To Avoid Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-environment-day-2023-why-are-microplastics-so-dangerous-how-avoid-them-470005 <description><![CDATA[The small plastic particles are found in everyday items such as food storage containers, baby bottles, nail polish, acrylic paint, gum, toys and cutting boards.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-environment-day-2023-why-are-microplastics-so-dangerous-how-avoid-them-470005</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:15:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['More Than Skin Deep': Study Reveals How Psoriasis Inflammation Leads To Other Related Disorders]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-skin-deep-study-reveals-how-psoriasis-inflammation-leads-other-related-disorders-470003 <description><![CDATA[The latest study aimed at developing objective diagnostic measures to predict severe psoriasis and to identify patients who are at higher risk of developing related disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-skin-deep-study-reveals-how-psoriasis-inflammation-leads-other-related-disorders-470003</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 04:54:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily Lung Cancer Pill After Surgery Slashes Death Risk By Half, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-lung-cancer-pill-after-surgery-slashes-death-risk-half-study-finds-470001 <description><![CDATA[Osimertinib slashed the risk of death by 51% compared to placebo.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-lung-cancer-pill-after-surgery-slashes-death-risk-half-study-finds-470001</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 03:34:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Adolescence Could Be The Best Time To Treat Schizophrenia, Autism]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adolescence-could-best-time-treat-schizophrenia-autism-469999 <description><![CDATA[A study showed that adolescence is the best time to treat conditions such as schizophrenia and autism, both characterized by dysfunctioning of the dopamine system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adolescence-could-best-time-treat-schizophrenia-autism-469999</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 02:24:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Blue Monday: Study Says Serious Heart Attacks More Common At Start Of Working Week]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blue-monday-study-says-serious-heart-attacks-more-common-start-working-week-469998 <description><![CDATA[The chances of getting a severe form of heart attack, called STEMI, on a Monday were 13% greater than on other days of the week, the study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blue-monday-study-says-serious-heart-attacks-more-common-start-working-week-469998</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 01:38:03 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>