<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Kieran Slevin On AI And Its Potential In Pain Detection And Patient Care]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/dr-kieran-slevin-ai-its-潜在-疼痛-检测-病人-护理-471618 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Kieran Slevin is keeping a close eye on artificial intelligence (AI), a tool not only with myriad applications across the healthcare landscape but one rapidly proving invaluable in delivering optimum patient care levels.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/dr-kieran-slevin-ai-its-潜在-疼痛-检测-病人-护理-471618</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Apr 2024 16:13:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Swapping Red Meat With Forage Fish Could Prevent 750,000 Deaths Annually In 2050: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/swapping-red-meat-forage-fish-could-prevent-750000-deaths-annually-2050-study-471615 <description><![CDATA[Incorporating forage fish or prey fish such as herring, sardines, and anchovies into diets could also potentially lower the prevalence of disability caused by diet-related diseases, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/swapping-red-meat-forage-fish-could-prevent-750000-deaths-annually-2050-study-471615</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Apr 2024 04:09:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Got Anger Issues? Researchers Suggest To Pen Down Your Feelings And Discard Paper]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-anger-issues-researchers-suggest-pen-down-your-feelings-discard-paper-471617 <description><![CDATA[Do you struggle with anger management issues? Researchers now say all you need to do is write down your feelings on a piece of paper and discard it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-anger-issues-researchers-suggest-pen-down-your-feelings-discard-paper-471617</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:09:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Finds The Best Time To Exercise For Heart Health Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-best-time-exercise-heart-health-benefits-471614 <description><![CDATA[The lowest risk of premature death and cardiovascular disease-related mortality were seen in those who did the majority of their aerobic moderate to vigorous physical activity between 6 p.m. and midnight.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-best-time-exercise-heart-health-benefits-471614</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Apr 2024 01:34:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 5 Baby Milk Formulas: Nutrient-Rich Options to Support Your Little One's Growth and Development]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-baby-milk-formulas- Nutrition-rich-options-support-your-little-ones-growth-development-471612 <description><![CDATA[When it comes to your baby's nutrition, it is best to consider only the best when it comes to formula milk]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-baby-milk-formulas- Nutrition-rich-options-support-your-little-ones-growth-development-471612</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:28:52 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Cold Plunge Tub 2024: Top 5 Picks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cold-plunge-tub-2024-top-5-picks-471610 <description><![CDATA[Here are our top picks for cold plunge tubs that are decently priced and worth the money.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cold-plunge-tub-2024-top-5-picks-471610</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:40:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Shake Up Your Nutrition: The Top 7 Meal Replacement Shakes For Busy Lifestyles]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/shake-your-nutrition-top-7-meal-replacement-shakes-busy-lifestyles-471609 <description><![CDATA[Meal replacement shakes are designed to replace either your breakfast, lunch, or dinner, which are perfect for people on the go or on their wellness journey.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/shake-your-nutrition-top-7-meal-replacement-shakes-busy-lifestyles-471609</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:40:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top Mouthwash Brands For A Fresh And Healthy Smile: Your Ultimate Guide To Oral Care]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-mouthwash-brands-fresh-healthy-smile-your-ultimate-guide-oral-care-471608 <description><![CDATA[Choosing the right mouthwash plays a pivotal role in oral care routine, and the options explored in this guide offer diverse benefits tailored to individual preferences.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-mouthwash-brands-fresh-healthy-smile-your-ultimate-guide-oral-care-471608</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:39:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Hyaluronic Acid Serums For 2024: Unlock Radiant Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hyaluronic-acid-serums-unlock-radiant-skin-471596 <description><![CDATA[Drops of the best hyaluronic acids will be enough to give you that glowing skin that will give you that confidence every single time.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-hyaluronic-acid-serums-unlock-radiant-skin-471596</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 08:08:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Botulism-Like Illness In Illinois: Officials Suspect Links To Fake Botox Injections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/botulism-like-illness-illinois-officials-suspect-links-fake-botox-injections-471606 <description><![CDATA[The illnesses were reported in two people who received fake Botox or a similar, possibly counterfeit products in LaSalle County, health officials said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/botulism-like-illness-illinois-officials-suspect-links-fake-botox-injections-471606</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 04:39:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Accelerated Aging Raises Cancer Risk In Young Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/accelerated-aging-raises-cancer-risk-young-adults-study-471604 <description><![CDATA[The researchers suggest that their discoveries open the door for future interventions to slow biological aging that could be a new avenue for cancer prevention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/accelerated-aging-raises-cancer-risk-young-adults-study-471604</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Apr 2024 03:03:50 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>