<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Staying Up To Date With COVID-19 Vaccinations Boosts Protection For Nursing Home Residents]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/staying-date-covid-19-vaccinations-boosts-protection-nursing-home-residents-470274 <description><![CDATA[A new study looked into the effectiveness of the COVID-19 vaccines among nursing home residents.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/staying-date-covid-19-vaccinations-boosts-protection-nursing-home-residents-470274</guid><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:09:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Origins: US Intelligence Report On Wuhan Lab Yields Inconclusive Evidence]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-origins-us-intelligence-report-wuhan-lab-yields-inconclusive-evidence-470272 <description><![CDATA[The report found no direct evidence linking the COVID-19 origin to the Wuhan laboratory.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-origins-us-intelligence-report-wuhan-lab-yields-inconclusive-evidence-470272</guid><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:04:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Scientists Identify COVID-Like Langya Virus As Potential Future Threat]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-identify-covid-like-langya-virus-pottial-future-threat-470269 <description><![CDATA[Experts may have found another potentially dangerous virus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-identify-covid-like-langya-virus-pottial-future-threat-470269</guid><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:00:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What's EU.1.1? CDC Tracks More Distant Descendant Of XBB.1.5 COVID Variant]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/whats-eu11-cdc-tracks-more-distant-descendant-xbb15-covid-variant-470266<description><![CDATA[The CDC is monitoring multiple new SARS-CoV-2 variants.]]></description><guid>https://www.medicaldaily.com/whats-eu11-cdc-tracks-more-distant-descendant-xbb15-covid-variant-470266</guid><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jun 2023 19:57:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Everything About Eye Twitching: Causes Of The Condition And Precautions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/everything-about-eye-twitching-causes-condition-precautions-470264 <description><![CDATA[The underlying cause of eye twitching is the accidental misfiring of neurons responsible for stimulating the eyelid muscles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/everything-about-eye-twitching-causes-condition-precautions-470264</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 06:23:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Health Benefits Of Fermented Food; Ways To Include Them In Diet]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-benefits-fermented-food-ways-include-them-diet-470263 <description><![CDATA[Fermented foods are gaining popularity in recent years, not just for their flavor and aroma but for their nutritional value and health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-benefits-fermented-food-ways-include-them-diet-470263</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 04:14:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even 'Safe' Levels Of Air Pollution Can Negatively Impact Brain Development: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-safe-levels-air-pollution-can-negatively-impact-brain-development-study-470258 <description><![CDATA[The study emphasizes the need for regulators to consider brain health, along with respiratory and cardiometabolic health, while setting air quality standards.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-safe-levels-air-pollution-can-negatively-impact-brain-development-study-470258</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 03:04:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Poo Transplant' May Benefit People With Advanced Liver Disease; Clinical Trial Begins]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poo-transplant-may-benefit-people-advanced-liver-disease-clinical-trial-begins-470261 <description><![CDATA[The relatively unconventional way of treatment involves patients consuming capsules containing freeze-dried feces from a healthy donor. They contain microorganisms needed for a healthy digestive system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/poo-transplant-may-benefit-people-advanced-liver-disease-clinical-trial-begins-470261</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 02:14:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cure For Baldness In Skin Moles? Scientists Discover New Mechanism For Stimulating Hair Growth]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cure-baldness-skin-moles-scientists-discover-new-mechanism-stimulate-hair-growth-470257 <description><![CDATA[According to the researchers, the mechanism by which aged or senescent cells in the skin moles make significant hair growth offers a road map for developing new molecular therapies to treat baldness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cure-baldness-skin-moles-scientists-discover-new-mechanism-stimulate-hair-growth-470257</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:15:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[E-Cigarette Sales Surge As Study Raises Concerns Regarding Youth Appeal]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-香烟-sales-surge-study-reports-concerns-regarding-youth-appeal-470256 <description><![CDATA[There's been a significant increase in monthly e-cigarette sales in the U.S.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/e-香烟-sales-surge-study-reports-concerns-regarding-youth-appeal-470256</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:54:06 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Spike Prompts CDC To Issue Warning For Summer Travel Season]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-spike-prompts-cdc-issue-warning-summer-travel-season-470255 <description><![CDATA[The public health agency emphasized the importance of receiving two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella (MMR) vaccine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-spike-prompts-cdc-issue-warning-summer-travel-season-470255</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:47:40 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>