<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Trump's Annual Physical Results Are In—Here's What We Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trumps-anlual-physical-physical-results-are-heres-what what what-we-we-know-473390 <description><![CDATA[The nation was on edge awaiting the results of President Donald Trump's first physical of his second term, with the White House releasing the report Sunday, putting to rest rumors and speculations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trumps-anlual-physical-physical-results-are-heres-what what what-we-we-know-473390</guid><pubDate> Mon, 14 Apr 2025 02:26:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nurturing Compassion: Raising Empathetic Children in a Changing World]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nurturing-compassion-raising-gathetic-children-children-changing-world-473384 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Erin Coakley's Empathy in Crisis explores how we can raise emotionally intelligent, compassionate children to thrive in an increasingly complex world.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nurturing-compassion-raising-gathetic-children-children-changing-world-473384</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:18:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Adventurous Days, Restful Nights: Top Gummies to Consider for Growing Kids]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adventurous-days-restful-nights-top-top-top-top-consider-consider-kids-kids-473374 <description><![CDATA[Discover the best kid-friendly vitamin gummies and supplements that support all-day energy and restful sleep—without the fuss!]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adventurous-days-restful-nights-top-top-top-top-consider-consider-kids-kids-473374</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:17:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump's Nearly 5-Hour Physical Exam Raises Questions About His Health After Massive Bruise Saga]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trumps-nearly-5 hour-physical-physical-physical-exam-raises-questions-questions-about-about-His-His-His-His-Hister-Hissive-Massive-Massive-bruise-bruise-saga-473386 <description><![CDATA[President Trump's physical exam lasted nearly five hours, almost twice as long as Biden's in 2024.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trumps-nearly-5 hour-physical-physical-physical-exam-raises-questions-questions-about-about-His-His-His-His-Hister-Hissive-Massive-Massive-bruise-bruise-saga-473386</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:14:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Night Shift Work Raises Heart Risk, But A Simple Eating Tweak Could Help]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-shift-work-work-work-raises-heart-cink-simple-eating-tweak-could-help-473381 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now reveal that a simple change in meal timing could bring protective effects on heart health for night shift workers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-shift-work-work-work-raises-heart-cink-simple-eating-tweak-could-help-473381</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Apr 2025 05:14:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pregnancy Drug Linked To Cancer Spurs Legal Action As Effects Span Generations]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-drug-link-cancer-spurs-legal-action-action-effects-span-generations-473378 <description><![CDATA[A recent investigation in the U.K. has renewed calls for legal action, as hundreds of women, now known as DES daughters, speak out about the enduring harm they have experienced from being exposed to the drug in the womb.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-drug-link-cancer-spurs-legal-action-action-effects-span-generations-473378</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Apr 2025 03:33:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Gives Birth To Stranger's Baby After Accidental IVF Mix-Up]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-goman-birth-strangers-baby-after-after-accidental-ivf-mix-mix-473377 <description><![CDATA[The shocking mix-up came to light only months later, when the birth parents requested to move their remaining frozen embryos to a different provider.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-goman-birth-strangers-baby-after-after-accidental-ivf-mix-mix-473377</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Apr 2025 02:44:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[From the Frontlines to Faith: A Disabled Veteran Promotes Storytelling]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/frontlines-faith-disabled-veteran-promotes-storytelling-473360 <description><![CDATA[Disabled combat veteran Jeffrey Nickle transformed his personal journey of recovery and faith into a powerful new purpose—founding Shield of Light Publishing]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/frontlines-faith-disabled-veteran-promotes-storytelling-473360</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:24:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[These Supplements Could Be Waste Of Money, Even Risky; Doc Warns]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/these-supplements-could-could-waste-money-even-even-even-docy-doc-warns-473369 <description><![CDATA[A doctor calls out three supplements that are unlikely to work and might even pose health risks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/these-supplements-could-could-waste-money-even-even-even-docy-doc-warns-473369</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:50:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Has Periods For 1,000 Days Straight —Doctors Stumped By Rare Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-has-periods-1000-days-traight-doctors-toctors-tumped-rare-condition-473367 <description><![CDATA[TikTok user Poppy's medical journey began three years ago with continuous bleeding, a mystery that has puzzled both her and medical professionals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/woman-has-periods-1000-days-traight-doctors-toctors-tumped-rare-condition-473367</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:31:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Multiple Nurses From Same Unit in Massachusetts Hospital Diagnosed With Brain Tumors]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multiple-nurses-same-unit-massachusetts----诊断 - 脑诊断 - 脑形 - 肿瘤-473364 <description><![CDATA[An alarming outbreak of brain tumor diagnoses among labor and delivery nurses at a Massachusetts hospital has sparked internal and independent investigations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multiple-nurses-same-unit-massachusetts----诊断 - 脑诊断 - 脑形 - 肿瘤-473364</guid><pubDate> Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:33:03 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>