<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[The Art And Science Of Facial Reconstruction With Dr. Artur Carandell]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/art-science-facial-reconstruction-dr-artur-carandell-471428 <description><![CDATA[A distinguished cranio-maxillo-facial surgeon, Dr. Carandell has over 15 years of experience in public hospitals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/art-science-facial-reconstruction-dr-artur-carandell-471428</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:40:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Innovation At Heart: The Role Of Technology In Advancing US Cardiac Care]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/innovation-heart-role-technology-advancing-us-cardiac-care-471427 <description><![CDATA[In honor of US Heart Month, a look at how technologies like SHL Telemedicine's SmartHeart® have the potential to revolutionize cardiac care in America.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/innovation-heart-role-technology-advancing-us-cardiac-care-471427</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:31:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Effective Strategies for Parenting a Child with ADHD from Dr. Kyle Daigle's Book]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ effective-strategies-parenting-child-adhd-dr-kyle-daigles-book-471425 <description><![CDATA[In his book, Dr. Daigle emphasizes the importance of understanding the multifaceted risk factors for early intervention and the support of ADHD.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ effective-strategies-parenting-child-adhd-dr-kyle-daigles-book-471425</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:20:56 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID Vaccines Linked To Slight Increase In Heart And Brain Issues: Large-Scale Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-vaccines-linked-slight-increase-heart-brain-issues-large-scale-study-471420 <description><![CDATA[The researchers cautioned that the study found only associations with adverse health effects and it does not prove that these issues are caused by the vaccines.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-vaccines-linked-slight-increase-heart-brain-issues-large-scale-study-471420</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Feb 2024 03:43:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Excess Vitamin B3 Affect Heart Health? Here's What Researchers Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-excess-vitamin-b3-affect-heart-health-heres-what-researchers-say-471422 <description><![CDATA[A recent study found that taking excessive quantities of the essential B vitamin, niacin could raise the risk of heart disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-excess-vitamin-b3-affect-heart-health-heres-what-researchers-say-471422</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Feb 2024 03:29:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women Reap Greater Benefits Than Men With Same Level Of Exercise: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-reap-greater-benefits-men-same-level-exercise-study-471418 <description><![CDATA[Regular exercise reduces the risk of early death or fatal cardiovascular events more significantly for women than men, and women gain greater benefits even with less effort, the study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-reap-greater-benefits-men-same-level-exercise-study-471418</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:51:44 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Stay Focused? Experts Say Protein-Rich Breakfast Enhances Satiety, Improves Concentration]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-stay-focused-experts-say- Protein-rich-breakfast-enhances-satiety-improves-471415 <description><![CDATA[Struggling to stay focused during the day? Maybe it's time to reconsider your breakfast choices.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-stay-focused-experts-say- Protein-rich-breakfast-enhances-satiety-improves-471415</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Feb 2024 04:04:44 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Approves First Drug To Treat Food Allergies: Here's What You Need To Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-approves-first-drug-treat-food-allergies-heres-what-you-need-know-471413 <description><![CDATA[Xolair, a medication initially designed for asthma, has been approved for treating food allergies to prevent severe reactions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-approves-first-drug-treat-food-allergies-heres-what-you-need-know-471413</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Feb 2024 01:54:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Antidepressants During Pregnancy Can Affect Fetal Brain Development: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-antidepressants-during-pregnancy-can-affect-fetal-brain-development-study-471412 <description><![CDATA[The use of antidepressants, particularly fluoxetine, could affect the development of the prefrontal cortex of the infant's brain, potentially raising the risk of mental health disorders later in their life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-antidepressants-during-pregnancy-can-affect-fetal-brain-development-study-471412</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:53:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Vaccination Or Booster During Pregnancy Protects Infants For 6 Months: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-vaccination-booster-during-pregnancy-protects-infants-6-months-study-471410 <description><![CDATA[The findings of the study underscore the importance of getting vaccinated against COVID-19 during pregnancy to ensure that infants are born with strong protection until they are old enough to be vaccinated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-vaccination-booster-during-pregnancy-protects-infants-6-months-study-471410</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Feb 2024 02:30:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mouthwash Use May Improve Blood Sugar Levels In Some Diabetic Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mouthwash-use-may-improve-blood-sugar-levels-some-diabetic-病人-study-471408 <description><![CDATA[Researchers believe that if patients who are likely to respond well to antiseptic mouthwash could be identified, it would be an easy-to-use treatment for people with periodontic-linked diseases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mouthwash-use-may-improve-blood-sugar-levels-some-diabetic-病人-study-471408</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:18:55 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>