<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA['Heart-In-A-Box': Innovative Transplant Method Deemed Safe, Could Expand Donor Pool]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-box-innovative-transplant-method-deemed-safe-could-expand-donor-pool-470069 <description><![CDATA[With the help of the device, doctors can revive and evaluate donor hearts that have stopped beating, determining their suitability for transplantation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-box-innovative-transplant-method-deemed-safe-could-expand-donor-pool-470069</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 06:05:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Nutrient Found In Protein Supplements May Help Add Years To Your Life]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-nutrient-found-protein-supplements-may-help-add-years-to-your-life-470066 <description><![CDATA[A new study shows taurine, a nutrient produced naturally in our bodies and also found in protein supplements, could potentially slow down the aging process.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-nutrient-found-protein-supplements-may-help-add-years-to-your-life-470066</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 04:46:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Viruses like SARS-CoV-2 Can Cause Brain Cells To Fuse, Trigger Chronic Neurological Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viruses-like-sars-cov-2-can-cause-brain-cells-fuse-trigger-chronic-neurological-symptoms-470063 <description><![CDATA[The findings of a recent study offer potential insight into the persistence of neurological symptoms following viral infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viruses-like-sars-cov-2-can-cause-brain-cells-fuse-trigger-chronic-neurological-symptoms-470063</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 02:39:47 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How To Prevent Tick- And Mosquito-Borne Diseases]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-to-prevent-tick-mosquito-borne-diseases-470062 <description><![CDATA[The CDC has shared tips on how to prevent diseases spread by ticks and mosquitoes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-to-prevent-tick-mosquito-borne-diseases-470062</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 21:04:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experimental Drug For Marijuana Addiction Demonstrates Potential In New Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-drug-marijuana-addiction-demonstrates-potential-new-study-470061<description><![CDATA[The drug is aimed at treating cannabis use disorder.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-drug-marijuana-addiction-demonstrates-potential-new-study-470061</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:57:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Moderna Plans Human Trials For Mpox Vaccine In Summer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/modern-plans-human-trials-pox-vaccine-summer-470059 <description><![CDATA[A new clinical trial for Moderna's mpox vaccine is underway.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/modern-plans-human-trials-pox-vaccine-summer-470059</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:52:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Jamie Foxx's Hospitalization Not Linked To COVID-19 Vaccine, Actor's Rep Clarifies]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/jamie-foxxs-hospitalization-not-linked-covid-19-vaccine-actors-rep-clarifies-470057 <description><![CDATA[Jamie Foxx's rep insisted his condition was not triggered by the COVID-19 vaccine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/jamie-foxxs-hospitalization-not-linked-covid-19-vaccine-actors-rep-clarifies-470057</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:48:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Menopause And Long COVID: Implications For Women's Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-menopause-covid-implications-women-health-470054<description><![CDATA[Menopause and long COVID may have similar symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-menopause-covid-implications-women-health-470054</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:35:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[China Could See COVID-19 Waves Every 6 Months: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/china-could-see-covid-19-waves-every-6-months-4 <description><![CDATA[Researchers predict recurring infection cycles every six months in China.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/china-could-see-covid-19-waves-every-6-months-4</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:30:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Brain Tumor Day: Warning Signs That You Should Not Ignore]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-brain-tumor-day-warning-signs-that-you-should-not-ignore-470051 <description><![CDATA[World Brain Tumor Day is marked every year on June 8 to raise awareness about the need for early detection and timely treatment of the condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-brain-tumor-day-warning-signs-that-you-should-not-ignore-470051</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 03:59:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Wildfire Smoke Affects Your Health And Tips To Stay Safe]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-wildfire-smoke-affects-your-health-tips-stay-safe-470048 <description><![CDATA[As the smoke from Canadian wildfires blows through the U.S. East Coast, millions of people are forced to stay indoors due to poor air quality alerts.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-wildfire-smoke-affects-your-health-tips-stay-safe-470048</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:42:42 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>