<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[7 Healthy Lifestyle Habits To Prevent Depression; Researchers Say Sleep Is The Most Important Factor]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/7-healthy-lifestyle-habits-prevent-depression-researchers-say-sleep-most-important-factor-470778 <description><![CDATA[Getting a good night's sleep has a significant impact, as it can reduce the risk of depression by 22%, a team from the University of Cambridge and Fudan University has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/7-healthy-lifestyle-habits-prevent-depression-researchers-say-sleep-most-important-factor-470778</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 02:44:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Keto Diet May Lead To Weight Loss, Improve Fertility In Women With PCOS: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keto-diet-may-improve-weight-loss-fertility-women-pcos-study-470777 <description><![CDATA[Researchers evaluated data from seven clinical trials and found significant improvements in weight loss, fertility and testosterone levels in women who followed the ketogenic diet for at least 45 days.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keto-diet-may-improve-weight-loss-fertility-women-pcos-study-470777</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 01:24:26 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Key Ingredient That's NOT In Your Toothpaste]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-ingredient-thats-not-your-toothpaste-470769 <description><![CDATA[Discover the essential missing component in your toothpaste, unraveling the mystery of its absence.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-ingredient-thats-not-your-toothpaste-470769</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:44:38 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 8 Best Teeth Whitening Solutions For 2023]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-8-best-teeth-whitening-solutions-2023-470756 <description><![CDATA[Explore the most effective teeth whitening solutions of 2023 and unveil your brightest smile with our expert recommendations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-8-best-teeth-whitening-solutions-2023-470756</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 23:37:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pregnant Women Exposed To Air Pollution May Give Birth To Smaller Babies, Study Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnant-women-expose-air-pollution-may-give-birth-smaller-babies-study-warns-470767 <description><![CDATA[The study highlights the importance of reducing pollution and increasing green spaces in residential areas for the health of future generations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnant-women-expose-air-pollution-may-give-birth-smaller-babies-study-warns-470767</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 03:44:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Peptic Ulcer? Know Causes, Symptoms Of The Condition Bruce Springsteen Is Being Treated For]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-peptic-ulcer-know-causes-symptoms-condition-bruce-springsteen-being-treatment-470765 <description><![CDATA[Peptic ulcers are open sores with severe pain that develop on the inner lining of the digestive tract when the digestive acids attack the stomach and small intestine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-peptic-ulcer-know-causes-symptoms-condition-bruce-springsteen-being-treatment-470765</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:28:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Irisin Treat Alzheimer's? Study Says Exercise-Induced Hormone May Help Combat The Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-irisin-treat-alzheimers-study-says-exercise-induced-hormone-may-help-combat-disease-470764 <description><![CDATA[The latest study has shown how irisin, an exercise-induced muscle hormone, can help in the potential treatment of Alzheimer's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-irisin-treat-alzheimers-study-says-exercise-induced-hormone-may-help-combat-disease-470764</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 01:26:41 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Climate Change Worsening Heatwaves, Air Quality: UN]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/climate-change-worsening-heatwaves-air-quality-un-470762 <description><![CDATA[Climate change is driving more intense and more frequent heatwaves, which in turn generate a "witch's brew" of pollutants, threatening the health of humans and all living things, the UN warned Wednesday.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/climate-change-worsening-heatwaves-air-quality-un-470762</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 04:43:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breast Cancer And Pregnancy: Study Explains Why Older First-Time Moms Are At Higher Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-pregnancy-study-explains-why-older-first-time-moms-are-higher-risk-470760 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say pregnancy could provide a "double whammy" for breast cancer as it induces a rapid expansion of breast cells for breastfeeding.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-pregnancy-study-explains-why-older-first-time-moms-are-higher-risk-470760</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 03:17:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Substance Abuse Causes Intellectual Disability Even If Only One Parent Has The Issue, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/substance-abuse-causes-intellectual-disability-even-if-only-one-parent-has-issue-study-says-470759 <description><![CDATA[The risk of intellectual disability in children was more than two times higher when the father or mother was diagnosed with abuse disorder before or during pregnancy, irrespective of which parent had the diagnosis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/substance-abuse-causes-intellectual-disability-even-if-only-one-parent-has-issue-study-says-470759</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 02:57:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Childhood Obesity Awareness Month: Tips To Promote Healthy Weight In Your Kids]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-childhood-obesity-awareness-month-tips-promote-healthy-weight-your-kids-470757 <description><![CDATA[Families can do a lot to help children tackle obesity, especially by inculcating healthy lifestyle habits in them from a young age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-childhood-obesity-awareness-month-tips-promote-healthy-weight-your-kids-470757</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 01:15:11 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>