<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh</language><item><title><![CDATA[First Saliva-Based Pregnancy Tests: Everything To Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-saliva-based-pregnancy-tests-everything-know-470246 <description><![CDATA[Salistick detects pregnancy by identifying a hormone called human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG), which is present in the body of a pregnant person.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-saliva-based-pregnancy-tests-everything-know-470246</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:37:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Highly Targeted Electrical Brain Stimulation May Improve Blood Flow In Stroke Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/highly-targeted-electrical-brain-stimulation-may-improve-blood-flow-中风-病人-study-470243 <description><![CDATA[The new treatment involves placing a series of electrodes across the scalp of the patient and delivering a weak inhibitory form of electrical current to the part of the brain suffering from low blood flow.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/highly-targeted-electrical-brain-stimulation-may-improve-blood-flow-中风-病人-study-470243</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 03:38:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Feeling Tired All The Time? Possible Causes And Solutions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/feeling-tired-all-time-possible-causes-solutions-470242 <description><![CDATA[Feeling "tired all the time" (TATT) without known reasons can be an indication of an underlying health issue that needs immediate attention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/feeling-tired-all-time-possible-causes-solutions-470242</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 03:00:45 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How To Overcome Your Sleep Debt And Reclaim Energy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-overcome-your-sleep-debt-reclaim-your-energy-470240 <description><![CDATA[Not getting enough sleep can translate into a multitude of issues, including weight gain, lack of focus, tiredness, a haze of confusion, and even depression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-overcome-your-sleep-debt-reclaim-your-energy-470240</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 02:45:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Omega-3 Fatty Acids Slow The Progression Of Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-fatty-acids-slow-progression-amyotropic-terior-sclerosis-study-470239 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that omega-3 acids, especially the type found in flaxseeds, walnuts, chia seeds, canola oil and soybean oil, can slow down the progression of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-fatty-acids-slow-progression-amyotropic-terior-sclerosis-study-470239</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 01:03:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC To Investigate Swine Flu Case That Killed 42-Year-Old Woman In Brazil]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-investigate-fatal-swine-flu-case-brazil-470236 <description><![CDATA[The fatality resulted from an H1N1 variant spreading among pigs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-investigate-fatal-swine-flu-case-brazil-470236</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:34:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mpox Cases Surge Globally, Sparking Vaccine Access Concerns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-cases-surge-globally-sparking-vaccine-access-concerns-470234<description><![CDATA[Experts expressed concerns over the spread of mpox worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-cases-surge-globally-sparking-vaccine-access-concerns-470234</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:30:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[California Student Sues University For Class Ban After Refusing COVID-19 Vaccine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-student-sues-university-class-ban-after-refusing-covid-19-vaccine-470232 <description><![CDATA[The student got barred from attending in-person classes after refusing the vaccine and other COVID-19 regulations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-student-sues-university-class-ban-after-refusing-covid-19-vaccine-470232</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:24:09 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctors Worry As Ozempic Causes Spike In ER Visits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctors-worry-ozempic-causes-spike-er-visits-470230 <description><![CDATA[The famous diabetes drug for weight loss reportedly comes with serious side effects.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctors-worry-ozempic-causes-spike-er-visits-470230</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:13:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[20% Of Women Who Need Fertility Treatment Can Get Pregnant Naturally Later: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20-women-who-need-fertility-treatment-can-get-pregnant-naturally-later-study-470228 <description><![CDATA[One in five women who had IVF treatment conceived naturally during their subsequent pregnancy, according to a study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/20-women-who-need-fertility-treatment-can-get-pregnant-naturally-later-study-470228</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 05:32:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exercise Can Increase Stroke Risk In People With Blocked Arteries, Study Shows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-can-increase-中风-risk-people-blocked-arteries-study-shows-470225 <description><![CDATA["It substantially increases the shear stress at the stenosis zone, which may cause the stenosis to rupture. This ruptured plaque may then flow to the brain and its blood supply, causing ischemic stroke," the study's lead author says.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-can-increase-中风-risk-people-blocked-arteries-study-shows-470225</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:26:27 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>