<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Women Who Take Infertility Treatment At Higher Risk Of Stroke In The Year Following Delivery: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-who-take-infertility-treatment-higher-risk-中风-year-following-delivery-study-470738 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that participants who took infertility treatment were at 66% higher risk of getting hospitalized for a stroke within 12 months of delivery when compared to others who spontaneously conceived.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-who-take-infertility-treatment-higher-risk-中风-year-following-delivery-study-470738</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Sep 2023 01:04:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Blood Cancer Medication May Unlock HIV Cure, Researchers Find]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-cancer-medication-may-unlock-hiv-cure-researchers-find-470736 <description><![CDATA[The drug in question is called venetoclax, and it can be repurposed and used to address HIV infection, as per the researchers behind the study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-cancer-medication-may-unlock-hiv-cure-researchers-find-470736</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Sep 2023 06:07:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Higher Levels Of Metal Seen In Blood And Urine Of Marijuana Users: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-levels-metal-seen-blood-urine-marijuana-users-study-470734 <description><![CDATA[Cadmium and lead remain in the body for quite a long time, according to study lead author Tiffany Sanchez.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-levels-metal-seen-blood-urine-marijuana-users-study-470734</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Sep 2023 04:23:40 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Breathe Easy, Feel Better: The Best Air Humidifier Of 2023]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/breathe-easy-feel-better-best-air-humidifier-2023-470733 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top air humidifier of 2023 that promises to enhance your well-being by promoting optimal air moisture levels.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breathe-easy-feel-better-best-air-humidifier-2023-470733</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:27:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teen Boys Who Smoke Pass On Damaged Genes To Future Offsprings: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen-boys-who-smoke-pass-damaging-genes-future-offsprings-study-470731 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that smoking in the teenage years causes DNA changes in the sperm, which lead to alterations in the DNA of their future babies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teen-boys-who-smoke-pass-damaging-genes-future-offsprings-study-470731</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 04:13:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Strive For A Balanced Diet: Study Says Extreme Dietary Habits Involving Carbs And Fats Affect Longevity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strive-balanced-diet-study-says-extreme-dietary-habits-involving-carbs-fats-affect-longevity-470729 <description><![CDATA[The key to longevity is following a balanced diet rather than putting the body through extreme dietary habits involving carbs and fats, according to a new study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/strive-balanced-diet-study-says-extreme-dietary-habits-involving-carbs-fats-affect-longevity-470729</guid><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:58:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Key To Longevity? Women Who Maintain Body Weight After 60 Likely To Live Longer, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-longevity-women-who-maintain-body-weight-after-60-likely-live-longer-says-study-470728 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has found that maintaining a steady weight after the age of 60 could bring "exceptional longevity" in women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-longevity-women-who-maintain-body-weight-after-60-likely-live-longer-says-study-470728</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 04:26:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Flu Shots: Importance, Right Time To Get Them; Expert Debunks Common Misconceptions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-shots-importance-right-time-get-them-expert-debunks-common-misconceptions-470727 <description><![CDATA[Flu season is around the corner, so health officials are reminding people to get vaccinated at the right time to get the maximum protection against the influenza virus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-shots-importance-right-time-get-them-expert-debunks-common-misconceptions-470727</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:59:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Collagen Peptides Enhance Active Lifestyle and Beauty]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/collagen-peptides-enhance-active-lifestyle-beauty-470687 <description><![CDATA[Discover how collagen peptides can synergistically amplify an active lifestyle while promoting enhanced beauty in this enlightening article.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/collagen-peptides-enhance-active-lifestyle-beauty-470687</guid><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:17:57 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 10 Best Collagen Products Of 2023]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-collagen-products-2023-470684 <description><![CDATA[Explore the finest collagen products of 2023 with our curated list of the top 10, designed to rejuvenate and enhance your skincare and wellness routine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-collagen-products-2023-470684</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 23:49:59 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stay At Ease: The 8 Baby Monitors With Advanced Features For Safety]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-ease-8-baby-monitors-advanced-features-safety-470615 <description><![CDATA[Explore a comprehensive list of eight cutting-edge baby monitors designed to ensure utmost safety and convenience, offering advanced features for peace of mind.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-ease-8-baby-monitors-advanced-features-safety-470615</guid><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 22:31:39 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>