<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Guillain-Barre Syndrome 'More Common Than Expected' In RSV Vaccinated Older Adults: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/guillain-barre-syndrome-more-common-expected-rsv-vaccinated-older-adults-cdc-471805 <description><![CDATA[While the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) and the officials from the CDC continue to investigate the risks, the current recommendation is to continue the vaccine as "the estimated benefits of RSV vaccination continued to outweigh potential risks."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/guillain-barre-syndrome-more-common-expected-rsv-vaccinated-older-adults-cdc-471805</guid><pubDate> Fri, 31 May 2024 03:39:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Flavonoids Reduce Type 2 Diabetes Risk, Study Identifies Food With Maximum Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flavonoids-reduce-type-2-diabetes-risk-study-identizes-food-maximum-benefits-471803 <description><![CDATA[Increasing the daily intake of flavonoid-rich foods by one serving could reduce the risk of type 2 diabetes by 6%, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flavonoids-reduce-type-2-diabetes-risk-study-identizes-food-maximum-benefits-471803</guid><pubDate> Fri, 31 May 2024 02:47:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Girls In US Getting Periods Earlier, Taking Longer To Regularize Cycles]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/girls-us-getting-periods-earlier-takeing-longer-regularize-cycles-471799 <description><![CDATA[The trend toward earlier menarche and longer time for menstrual regularity is more pronounced among Black, Hispanic, Asian, and mixed-race participants.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/girls-us-getting-periods-earlier-takeing-longer-regularize-cycles-471799</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 May 2024 04:15:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Looking For Key To Slow Aging? Study Suggests Embracing A Heart-Healthy Lifestyle]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/looking-key-slow-aging-study-suggests-embracing-heart-healthy-lifestyle-471798 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now say that adopting a heart-healthy lifestyle could be the key to slowing down biological aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/looking-key-slow-aging-study-suggests-embracing-heart-healthy-lifestyle-471798</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 May 2024 02:28:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Suicide And Homicide Risks Peak At Night, Disrupted Sleep A Contributing Factor: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/suicide-homicide-risks-peak-night-disrupted-sleep-contributing-factor-study-471796 <description><![CDATA[Nocturnal wakefulness, age, alcohol use, and relationship conflicts are major contributing factors to increased risk of suicides and homicides.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/suicide-homicide-risks-peak-night-disrupted-sleep-contributing-factor-study-471796</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 May 2024 01:30:32 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fastbraces: The Science Of Alveolar Bone Remodeling]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/fastbraces-science-alveolar-bone-remodeling-471794 <description><![CDATA[Fastbraces sets itself apart from traditional orthodontic treatments through its focus on pretreatment assessments, which use predictive parameters to ensure effective treatments.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fastbraces-science-alveolar-bone-remodeling-471794</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 May 2024 16:28:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Navigating The World Of Non-Surgical Facial Rejuvenation With Dr. Saba Motakef]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/navigating-world-non-surgical-facial-rejuvenation-dr-saba-motakef-471793 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Motakef's expertise lies in customizing treatments to suit each patient's unique anatomy and aesthetic preferences.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/navigating-world-non-surgical-facial-rejuvenation-dr-saba-motakef-471793</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 May 2024 16:22:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Advancing Safety and Innovation in Plastic Surgery: The Fulcrum Aesthetics Experience]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/advancing-safety-innovation- Plastic-surgery-fulcrum-aesthetics-experience-471791 <description><![CDATA[Fulcrum Aesthetics offers a full spectrum of aesthetic services—from non-invasive treatments like injectables to complex surgical procedures.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/advancing-safety-innovation- Plastic-surgery-fulcrum-aesthetics-experience-471791</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 May 2024 16:17:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Binge Eating Tops U.S. Eating Disorders, Study Says It Lasts Longer Than Expected]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/binge-eating-tops-us-eating-disorders-study-says-it-lasted-longer-expected-471789 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that achieving full remission from binge eating disorder can take several years, with relapses being common.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/binge-eating-tops-us-eating-disorders-study-says-it-lasted-longer-expected-471789</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 May 2024 03:41:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Introducing Peanuts In Infancy Cuts Allergy Risk In Adolescence: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/introducing-peanuts-infancy-cuts-allergy-risk-adolescent-study-471788 <description><![CDATA[Early introduction of peanut products can reduce the incidence of peanut allergy in adolescence by 71%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/introducing-peanuts-infancy-cuts-allergy-risk-adolescent-study-471788</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 May 2024 03:23:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Child's Exposure To Air Pollution In Womb Raises Mental Health Risks During Adolescence]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-exposure-to-air-pollution-womb-raises-mental-health-risks-during-adolescent-471787 <description><![CDATA[The study investigated how air and noise pollution during pregnancy impact a child's mental health at different stages of development, such as early childhood and adolescence.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-exposure-to-air-pollution-womb-raises-mental-health-risks-during-adolescent-471787</guid><pubDate> Wed, 29 May 2024 02:20:22 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>