<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[90% Of US Adults At Risk Of Heart Disease, At Various Stages of CKM Syndrome: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/90-us-adults-risk-heart-disease-various-stages-ckm-syndrome-study-471724 <description><![CDATA[A shocking majority of U.S. adults are at an early, middle, or late stage of cardiovascular, kidney, and metabolic (CKM) syndrome, a new study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/90-us-adults-risk-heart-disease-various-stages-ckm-syndrome-study-471724</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 May 2024 04:51:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra Processed Food Linked To Early Death, Study Identifies Items With Highest Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-linked-early-death-study-identizes-items-highest-risk-471723 <description><![CDATA[Researchers noted that not all ultra-processed products have the same risk, and not all products call for restricted usage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-linked-early-death-study-identizes-items-highest-risk-471723</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 May 2024 02:42:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Olive Oil In Diet Reduces Risk Of Death From Dementia: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/olive-oil-diet-reduces-risk-death-dementia-study-471721 <description><![CDATA[Daily consumption of at least 7 g of olive oil was linked to a 28% reduced risk of death from dementia-related illnesses.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/olive-oil-diet-reduces-risk-death-dementia-study-471721</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 May 2024 02:09:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Potentially Cancerous Air Detected In Car Interiors, Study Warns]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/pottially-cancerous-air-Detected-car-interiors-study-warns-471720 <description><![CDATA[According to a study, flame retardants used in car seats to meet an outdated federal flammability standard raise the risk of exposure to potentially cancerous air, particularly in summer when temperatures are high.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pottially-cancerous-air-Detected-car-interiors-study-warns-471720</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 May 2024 04:56:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sedentary Lifestyle In Childhood Linked To Progressing Heart Enlargement, Light Activity Reverses Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sedentary-lifestyle-childhood-linked-progressing-heart-enlargement-light-activity-reverses-risk-471718 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that a sedentary lifestyle in childhood increases the risk of progressing left ventricular hypertrophy, a heart enlargement condition that raises the likelihood of heart attacks, stroke, and premature death in adulthood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sedentary-lifestyle-childhood-linked-progressing-heart-enlargement-light-activity-reverses-risk-471718</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 May 2024 03:36:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Maternal Mental Health Month: Expert Shares Tips To Support Someone Going Through Postpartum Depression]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maternal-mental-health-month-expert-shares-tips-support-someone-going-through-postpartum-471717 <description><![CDATA[Although a common and treatable mental health condition, postpartum depression is often stigmatized, and many women hesitate to seek help, fearing that they will be branded as a "bad mother."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maternal-mental-health-month-expert-shares-tips-support-someone-going-through-postpartum-471717</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 May 2024 02:05:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unhealthy Levels Of Nitrogen Dioxide In Households With Gas Or Propane Stoves: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unhealthy-levels-nitrogen-dioxide-households-gas-propane-stoves-study-471715 <description><![CDATA[People living in households with gas or propane stoves breathe in unhealthy levels of nitrogen dioxide, with the increased levels linked to around 50,000 cases of pediatric asthma, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unhealthy-levels-nitrogen-dioxide-households-gas-propane-stoves-study-471715</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 May 2024 05:15:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Simple Nature-Based Activity Can Improve Students' Mental Health, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-nature-based-activity-can-improve-students-mental-health-says-study-471714 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that engaging in five 30-minute sessions of bird-watching every week could improve mental well-being and reduce psychological distress among college students.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-nature-based-activity-can-improve-students-mental-health-says-study-471714</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 May 2024 04:06:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ancient Grains Help Improve Blood Sugar, Cholesterol Levels In Diabetes Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ancient-grains-help-improve-blood-sugar-cholesterollevels-diabetics-患者-study-471712 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that oats, brown rice, and millet could improve various diabetes markers such as insulin levels, fasting blood sugar, and Hemoglobin A1C and are associated with improved cholesterol levels indicating better heart health in diabetes patients.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ancient-grains-help-improve-blood-sugar-cholesterollevels-diabetics-患者-study-471712</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 May 2024 01:47:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Harnessing Nature's Power: The 7 Best Tongkat Ali Supplements]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/harnessing-natures-power-7-best-tongkat-ali-supplements-471700 <description><![CDATA[Discover the benefits of Tongkat Ali with these supplements that harness nature's power to boost testosterone levels and enhance men's vitality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/harnessing-natures-power-7-best-tongkat-ali-supplements-471700</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 11:16:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Metformin Reduces COVID-19 Hospitalizations, Long COVID: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-reduces-covid-19-hospitalizations-long-covid-study-471710 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that metformin can reduce the amount of COVID-19 virus in the body and lower the risk of viral rebound.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-reduces-covid-19-hospitalizations-long-covid-study-471710</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 03:50:11 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>