<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Teens At Risk Of Exposure To Toxic Lead And Uranium From Frequent Vaping: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-risk-exposure-token-uranium-frequent-vaping-study-471694 <description><![CDATA[Teenagers who frequently vape may face increased exposure to harmful metals like lead and uranium, which could potentially impact brain and organ development adversely, a study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-risk-exposure-token-uranium-frequent-vaping-study-471694</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Apr 2024 04:20:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Reveals Ideal Duration You May Stand, Sit, Sleep, And Exercise For Optimal Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-ideal-duration-you-may-stand-sit-sleep-exercise-optimal-health-471693 <description><![CDATA[The researchers have identified the ideal number of hours you should spend standing, sitting, sleeping, and engaging in physical activities for optimal heart health and diabetic control.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-ideal-duration-you-may-stand-sit-sleep-exercise-optimal-health-471693</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:38:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Lifestyle At 40 Adds 5 Years To Life, Offsets Genetic Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-lifestyle-40-adds-5-years-life-offsets-genic-risk-study-471691 <description><![CDATA[People with a strong genetic risk of shorter lifespans could add almost 5.5 years to their lives if they adopt a healthy lifestyle at 40, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-lifestyle-40-adds-5-years-life-offsets-genic-risk-study-471691</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Apr 2024 02:15:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Top 8 Tanning Oils: Achieved a Sun-Kissed Skin with these Nourishing and Bronzing Formulas]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-8-tanning-oils-achieved-sun-kissed-skin-these-nourishing-bronzing-formulas-471671 <description><![CDATA[With so many choices out there to achieve a sun-kissed skin, here are our top 8 picks for you to decide on, whichever on this list is your next summer buddy!]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-8-tanning-oils-achieved-sun-kissed-skin-these-nourishing-bronzing-formulas-471671</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:23:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Women Diagnosed With HIV After 'Vampire Facial' At Unlicensed New Mexico Spa: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/3-women-diagnosed-hiv-after-vampire-facial-unlicensed-new-mexico-spa-cdc-471687 <description><![CDATA[Although HIV transmission from contaminated blood through unsterile injection is a well-known risk, the cluster marks the first known case of transmission during a cosmetic injection procedure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/3-women-diagnosed-hiv-after-vampire-facial-unlicensed-new-mexico-spa-cdc-471687</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:04:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Positive Childhood Experiences Linked To Reduced Risk Of Anxiety, Depression In Teens: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/positive-childhood-experiences-linked-reduced-risk-anxiety-depression-teens-study-471689 <description><![CDATA[Adults who experienced four or more adverse childhood experiences are four times more likely to experience depression and low life satisfaction, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/positive-childhood-experiences-linked-reduced-risk-anxiety-depression-teens-study-471689</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:46:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Not Getting Enough Sleep? Expert Offers Tips To Manage Stress For Improved Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-getting-enough-sleep-expert-offers-tips-manage-stress-improved-sleep-471685 <description><![CDATA[Inadequate sleep is not just about feeling tired or sluggish; it can also lead to serious long-term consequences.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-getting-enough-sleep-expert-offers-tips-manage-stress-improved-sleep-471685</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Apr 2024 01:55:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Acid Reflux Drugs Linked To Increased Risk Of Migraines: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/acid-reflux-drugs-linked-increased-risk-migraines-study-471683 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found higher odds of migraine or severe headache linked to the use of acid-suppression therapy, including proton pump inhibitors (PPIs), H2 receptor antagonists (H2RAs), and generic antacids.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/acid-reflux-drugs-linked-increased-risk-migraines-study-471683</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Apr 2024 04:30:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[USDA Updates School Meals To Limit Added Sugar For First Time]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/usda-updates-school-meals-limit-added-sugar-first-time-471681 <description><![CDATA[Flavored milk such as chocolate milk will still be available in elementary cafeterias but with limited added sugar.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/usda-updates-school-meals-limit-added-sugar-first-time-471681</guid><pubDate> Thu, 25 Apr 2024 03:01:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bird Flu Virus In Pasteurized Milk: FDA Says Commercial Supply Safe To Drink]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-virus-pasteurized-milk-fda-says-commercial-supply-safe-drink-471680 <description><![CDATA[The remnants of the bird flu virus found in pasteurized milk are not the same as the infectious virus and currently do not pose any elevated risk, the FDA said in an update.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-virus-pasteurized-milk-fda-says-commercial-supply-safe-drink-471680</guid><pubDate> Thu, 25 Apr 2024 02:07:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dengue Fever During Pregnancy Affects Infant's Health For First 3 Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dengue-fever-during-pregnancy-affects-infants-health-first-3-years-study-471678 <description><![CDATA[Children whose mothers contracted dengue fever during pregnancy faced a 27% higher likelihood of hospitalization from birth to age three, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dengue-fever-during-pregnancy-affects-infants-health-first-3-years-study-471678</guid><pubDate> Wed, 24 Apr 2024 04:00:15 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>