<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[High Temperature, Humidity During Pregnancy May Affect Child's Blood Pressure: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-temporal-humidity-during-pregnancy-may-affect-childs-blood-Pressure-study-471261 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that prenatal exposure to higher humidity was associated with a faster increase in systolic and diastolic blood pressure, and a higher temperature was linked to a slower increase in systolic blood pressure in childhood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-temporal-humidity-during-pregnancy-may-affect-childs-blood-Pressure-study-471261</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:14:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eat More Tomatoes: Study Says They May Reduce Risk Of High Blood Pressure]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eat-more-tomatoes-study-says-they-may-reduce-risk-high-blood-Pressure-471257 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that eating tomatoes helps manage high blood pressure and may even prevent developing hypertension in older adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eat-more-tomatoes-study-says-they-may-reduce-risk-high-blood-Pressure-471257</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:02:21 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Blood Pressure Monitors In 2024: For Precise Readings And Peace Of Mind]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-blood-Pressure-monitors-precise-readings-peace-mind-471255 <description><![CDATA[Monitoring blood pressure at home is a valuable tool for managing hypertension, a condition affecting millions globally.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-blood-Pressure-monitors-precise-readings-peace-mind-471255</guid><pubDate> Fri, 12 Jan 2024 04:41:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Blood Donor Month: Expert Debunks Misconceptions About Blood Donation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-blood-donor-month-expert-debunks-misconceptions-about-blood-donation-471254 <description><![CDATA[National Blood Donor Month holds special significance this year, as the country faces an emergency shortage, with donations reaching an all-time low in the past two decades.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-blood-donor-month-expert-debunks-misconceptions-about-blood-donation-471254</guid><pubDate> Fri, 12 Jan 2024 02:36:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Winter Foods To Boost Immunity: Expert Offers Tips To Fight Off Cold And Flu]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/winter-foods-boost-immunity-expert-offers-tips-fight-off-cold-flu-471249 <description><![CDATA[Healthy eating should be the focus throughout the year. Still, specific care should be given in winter, when cold, flu and other viruses are more prevalent, says Bonnie Taub-Dix, a registered dietitian and nutritionist from Long Island.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/winter-foods-boost-immunity-expert-offers-tips-fight-off-cold-flu-471249</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Jan 2024 06:36:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Happens When Your Blood Sugar Gets Too Low? Know Ways To Fix It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-happens-when-your-blood-sugar-gets-too-low-know-ways-fix-it-471248 <description><![CDATA[Hypoglycemia is a medical condition that occurs when the blood sugar level is lower than the normal range (below 70 mg/dL).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-happens-when-your-blood-sugar-gets-too-low-know-ways-fix-it-471248</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:58:18 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vegetarian Diet May Help Reduce Risk, Severity Of COVID-19 Infection: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vegetarian-diet-may-help-reduce-risk-severity-covid-19-infection-study-471247 <description><![CDATA[People on a predominantly plant-based or vegetarian diet were at a lower risk (39%) of getting COVID-19 infection compared to omnivores.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vegetarian-diet-may-help-reduce-risk-severity-covid-19-infection-study-471247</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:04:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excessive Screen Time In Kids Under 2 Linked To Issues With Sensory Processing: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-kids-under-2-linked-issues-sensory-processing-study-471246 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed a connection between excessive TV or video exposure in children under two and issues related to sensory processing.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-kids-under-2-linked-issues-sensory-processing-study-471246</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Jan 2024 03:31:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Know What You Drink: Study Says One Liter Of Bottled Water Contains 240,000 Plastic Particles]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-what-you-drink-study-says-one-liter-bottled-water-contains-240000- Plastic-articles-471245 <description><![CDATA[A person consumes around 240,000 of tiny plastic particles from one liter of bottled water, a new study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-what-you-drink-study-says-one-liter-bottled-water-contains-240000- Plastic-articles-471245</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Jan 2024 02:16:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Donate Blood, Make A Life-Or-Death Difference: Red Cross Urges Action Amid Emergency Shortage]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/donate-blood-make-life-death-difference-red-cross-urges-action-amid-emergency-shortage-471244 <description><![CDATA[The number of people donating blood through the American Red Cross has fallen by about 40% in the past two decades, the agency said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/donate-blood-make-life-death-difference-red-cross-urges-action-amid-emergency-shortage-471244</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:04:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Portable EKG Machines For Heart Monitoring 2024: The Heartbeat Companion]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-portable-ekg-machines-heart-monitoring-2024-heartbeat-companion-471243 <description><![CDATA[Understanding your heart's rhythm can be empowering, and portable EKG machines offer a convenient way to do just that.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-portable-ekg-machines-heart-monitoring-2024-heartbeat-companion-471243</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Jan 2024 07:03:36 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>