<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Looking Forward To A Healthier, Happier 2024? Combining Mindfulness With Exercise May Help]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/looking-forward-healthier-happier-2024-combining-mindativity-exercise-may-help-471230 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found life changes that combine physical activity and mindfulness can help enhance mood and improve mental health and well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/looking-forward-healthier-happier-2024-combining-mindativity-exercise-may-help-471230</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:03:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Surge In Scabies Cases In UK Amid Acute Treatment Shortage; Know Signs, Steps To Prevent Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surge-scabies-cases-uk-amid-acute-treatment-shortage-know-signs-steps-prevent-infection-471229 <description><![CDATA[The shortage of treatment drugs can lead to rapid spread of infection, causing a public health crisis, health officials warn.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surge-scabies-cases-uk-amid-acute-treatment-shortage-know-signs-steps-prevent-infection-471229</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jan 2024 02:50:44 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Adolescent Obesity Linked To Early Chronic Kidney Disease; Even Those With High-Normal BMI At Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-adolescent-linked-chronic-kidney-disease-study-says-even-those-high-normal-bmi-risk-471228 <description><![CDATA[Researchers observed that the risk of chronic kidney disease is high even for those seemingly healthy teens with high-normal BMI.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-adolescent-linked-chronic-kidney-disease-study-says-even-those-high-normal-bmi-risk-471228</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:47:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Legionnaires' Disease? 1 Dead, Another Hospitalized In New Hampshire; Know All About The Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-legionnaires-disease-1-dead-another-hospitalized-new-hampshire-know-all-about-condition-471227 <description><![CDATA[Legionnaires' disease is a serious type of pneumonia caused by Legionella bacteria. The bacteria enter the lungs through inhalation or accidental swallowing of water droplets.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-legionnaires-disease-1-dead-another-hospitalized-new-hampshire-know-all-about-condition-471227</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jan 2024 06:12:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Quit Smoking? Study Says Cytisine Doubles Chances Of Successful Cessation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-quit-smoking-study-says-cytisine-doubles-chances-successful-cessation-471226 <description><![CDATA[Cytisine increases the chances of smoking cessation by more than twofold compared to a placebo. It might be more effective than nicotine replacement therapy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-quit-smoking-study-says-cytisine-doubles-chances-successful-cessation-471226</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:00:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Long COVID: Study Says Synbiotic Drug That Alters Gut Microbiome Relieves Multiple Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-covid-study-says-synbiotic-drug-that-alters-gut-microbiome-relieves-multiple-symptoms-471225 <description><![CDATA[The results of the trial indicate that the drug could help alleviate symptoms such as fatigue, gastrointestinal upset, difficulty in concentration, memory loss and general unwellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-covid-study-says-synbiotic-drug-that-alters-gut-microbiome-relieves-multiple-symptoms-471225</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:44:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Standing Burns More Calories Than Sitting; Know Ways To Incorporate It Into Your Routine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stand-burns-more-calories-sitting-know-ways-incorporate-it-your-routine-471224 <description><![CDATA[Standing may not work as a weight loss strategy, but studies say it can help burn more calories than sitting.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stand-burns-more-calories-sitting-know-ways-incorporate-it-your-routine-471224</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Jan 2024 06:02:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fasting-Mimicking Diet Provides Unique Cardiovascular Benefits: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fasting-mimicking-diet-provides-unique-cardioangio-benefits-study-471223 <description><![CDATA[Fasting-mimicking diet provides unique cardiovascular benefits compared to the Mediterranean diet, which is associated with reduced risk of heart disease, a new study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fasting-mimicking-diet-provides-unique-cardioangio-benefits-study-471223</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Jan 2024 03:02:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Smart Insulin' Injection Regulates Glucose Levels For A Week, Could Be A Breakthrough In Diabetes Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smart-insulin-injection-regulates-glucose-levels-week-could-breakthrough-diabetes-treatment-471222 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have developed a new type of "smart insulin" that could potentially transform the future of diabetes treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smart-insulin-injection-regulates-glucose-levels-week-could-breakthrough-diabetes-treatment-471222</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Jan 2024 01:03:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Feeling Uneasy After A Heavy Meal? Here Are 5 Drinks To Aid Digestion]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/feeling-uneasy-after-heavy-meal-here-are-5-drinks-aid-digestion-471221 <description><![CDATA[To reduce gas trouble and improve digestion, here are some drinks that you can try out.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/feeling-uneasy-after-heavy-meal-here-are-5-drinks-aid-digestion-471221</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Dec 2023 06:03:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Owning A Pet Could Slow Cognitive Decline In Older Adults Living Alone: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/owning-pet-could-slow-cognitive-decline-older-adults-living-alone-study-471220 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that pet ownership was associated with slower rates of decline in verbal memory and fluency among those living alone.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/owning-pet-could-slow-cognitive-decline-older-adults-living-alone-study-471220</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Dec 2023 01:59:08 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>