<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[World Sleep Day: Here's What Happens When You Don't Get Enough Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-sleep-day-here-what-happens-when-you-dont-get-enough-sleep-471512 <description><![CDATA[During this World Sleep Day, it's crucial to understand the importance of sleep and know the consequences of inadequate sleep.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-sleep-day-here-what-happens-when-you-dont-get-enough-sleep-471512</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Mar 2024 02:48:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Animal Vs Plant Protein: Study Suggests The Better Choice For Quality Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/animal-vs-plant- Protein-study-suggests-better-choice-quality-sleep-471510 <description><![CDATA[Researchers of a recent study investigated how protein intake impacts sleep quality and identified the superior protein source that could improve sleep.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/animal-vs-plant- Protein-study-suggests-better-choice-quality-sleep-471510</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Mar 2024 01:21:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Spending Quality Time With A Dog Can Reduce Stress, Improve Concentration: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spending-quality-time-dogs-can-reduce-stress-improve-concentration-study-471509 <description><![CDATA[The study analyzed how various types of interactions with dogs can affect human brainwave patterns.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spending-quality-time-dogs-can-reduce-stress-improve-concentration-study-471509</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Mar 2024 05:18:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tapeworm Found In Man's Brain From Eating Undercooked Bacon: Know Risks Of Neurocysticercosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tapeworm-found-mans-brain-eating-undercooked-bacon-know-risks-neurocysticercosis-471508 <description><![CDATA[A 52-year-old man in Florida with severe migraines was diagnosed with neurocysticercosis after doctors discovered tapeworm larvae in his brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tapeworm-found-mans-brain-eating-undercooked-bacon-know-risks-neurocysticercosis-471508</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:37:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Blood Donor's Diet May Trigger Allergic Reactions In Recipients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-donors-diet-may-trigger-allergic-reactions-recipients-study-471507 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found an interesting link between a donor's diet before blood donation and allergic transfusion reactions (ATRs) in recipients, particularly among children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-donors-diet-may-trigger-allergic-reactions-recipients-study-471507</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:50:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Top 5 Cod Liver Oil Supplements: A Nutrient-Rich Addition To Your Wellness Routine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-cod-liver-oil-supplements- Nutrition-rich-addition-to-your-wellness-routine-471488 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top 5 cod liver oil supplements to boost your well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-cod-liver-oil-supplements- Nutrition-rich-addition-to-your-wellness-routine-471488</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:20:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Medications Help Cut Risk Of Premature Death In ADHD Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/medications-help-cut-risk-of-premature-death-adhd-病人-study-471506 <description><![CDATA[The latest study included 148,000 individuals in Sweden who were diagnosed with ADHD. The researchers noted that starting ADHD medications reduced their overall mortality risk, particularly from unnatural causes such as accidents and drug overdose.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/medications-help-cut-risk-of-premature-death-adhd-病人-study-471506</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:58:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People With Persisting, Worsening Metabolic Syndrome At Higher Risk Of Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-persisting-worsening-metabolic-syndrome-high-risk-cancer-study-471505 <description><![CDATA[The findings of the study suggest that managing metabolic syndrome could be an effective strategy to reduce cancer risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-persisting-worsening-metabolic-syndrome-high-risk-cancer-study-471505</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:00:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Depression Affects Heart Health: Study Says Women At Greater Risk Than Men]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-affects-heart-health-study-says-women-at-greater-risk-but-471504 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that depression raised the risk for heart disease by 39 percent in men, while the risk was 64 percent in women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-affects-heart-health-study-says-women-at-greater-risk-but-471504</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Mar 2024 01:47:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Folic Acid Fortified Table Salt Could Prevent Life-Threatening Birth Defects: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/folic-acid-fortified-table-salt-could-prevent-life-throne-birth-defects-study-471503 <description><![CDATA[The researchers hope that the use of folic acid-fortified salt could potentially prevent up to 50 percent of global spina bifida cases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/folic-acid-fortified-table-salt-could-prevent-life-throne-birth-defects-study-471503</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Mar 2024 04:16:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Activity Tracking Wrist-Worn Device Could Detect Alzheimer's Disease Early: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/activity-tracking-wrist-worn-device-could-detect-alzheimers-disease-early-study-471501 <description><![CDATA[With over 6 million Americans impacted by Alzheimer's across all age groups, the researchers hope their innovative approach could help identify the condition promptly, enabling early intervention for timely help and support.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/activity-tracking-wrist-worn-device-could-detect-alzheimers-disease-early-study-471501</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:47:52 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>