<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Young Mom Diagnosed With Stage 4 Breast Cancer Weeks After Clear Mammogram Reveals Overlooked Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/young-mom-diagnosed-stage-4-breast-cancer-weeks-after-clear-mammogram-reveals-overlooked-symptoms-472815 <description><![CDATA[The 31-year-old nurse and mother from New Jersey received the news of stage 4 breast cancer diagnosis, weeks after her mammogram cleared her of the disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/young-mom-diagnosed-stage-4-breast-cancer-weeks-after-clear-mammogram-reveals-overlooked-symptoms-472815</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Dec 2024 01:34:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Celebrity Blamed for Convincing Young Mom to Undergo Fatal Butt Lift Surgery: 'There Was No Changing Her Mind']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/celebrity-blamed-convincing-young-mom-undergo-fatal-butt-lift-surgery-there-was-no-changing-her-472814 <description><![CDATA[Demi Agoglia, 26-year-old UK mother of three, died tragically after undergoing a high risk cosmetic procedure she saw a celebrity advertise on social media.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/celebrity-blamed-convincing-young-mom-undergo-fatal-butt-lift-surgery-there-was-no-changing-her-472814</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Dec 2024 18:55:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Doctor Forced to Delete TikTok Helping Undocumented Immigrants Get Healthcare After Governor Threatens to Defund Children's Hospital]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doctor-forced-delete-tiktok-helping-undocumented-immigrants-get-healthcare-after-governor-472811 <description><![CDATA[A Texas doctor was forced to delete their TikTok about getting undocumented immigrants healthcare after the governor threatened to defund a children's hospital.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doctor-forced-delete-tiktok-helping-undocumented-immigrants-get-healthcare-after-governor-472811</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Dec 2024 16:05:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Munib Ahmad: Elevating Hair Transplantation Via Artistry And Precision]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-munib-ahmad-elevating-hair-transplantation-via-artistry- precision-472809 <description><![CDATA[Hair restoration is deeply personal because it affects how clients perceive themselves and how others perceive them. Dr. Ahmad helps individuals regain confidence by delivering exceptional results, often transforming their personal and professional lives.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-munib-ahmad-elevating-hair-transplantation-via-artistry- precision-472809</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Dec 2024 15:35:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Health Workers Get Farmer Drunk, Trick Him Into Unwanted Vasectomy Weeks Before Marriage: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-workers-get-farmer-drunk-trick-him-unwanted-vascision-weeks-before-marriage-report-472807 <description><![CDATA[An Indian man who had been set to get married in about a month was allegedly manipulated into getting a vasectomy, resulting in the launch of a state government investigation into the incident.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-workers-get-farmer-drunk-trick-him-unwanted-vascision-weeks-before-marriage-report-472807</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Dec 2024 15:01:48 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dermatologist Warns: Laptops And Heating Pads May Cause Permanent Skin Damage; Know About Toasted Skin Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dermatographer-warns-laptops-heating-pads-may-cause-permanent-skin-damage-know-about-toasted-skin-472804 <description><![CDATA[For those who carelessly leave heat pads on high all night, or rest a warm laptop on the lap, a board-certified dermatologist issues a warning that these seemingly harmless routines might lead to permanent skin damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dermatographer-warns-laptops-heating-pads-may-cause-permanent-skin-damage-know-about-toasted-skin-472804</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Dec 2024 01:20:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Got A Test Tomorrow? Take A Brisk Walk Now To Boost Your Memory]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-test-tomorrow-take-brisk-walk-now-boost-your-memory-472803 <description><![CDATA[A new study reveals that moderate to vigorous physical activity on one day can improve your performance on memory tests the following day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/got-test-tomorrow-take-brisk-walk-now-boost-your-memory-472803</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Dec 2024 04:08:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[From Night Sweats To Changes In Bowel Habits: Colorectal Cancer Survivor Reflects On Red Flags He Overlooked]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-sweats-changes-bowel-habits-colorectal-cancer-survivor-reflects-red-flags-he-overlooked-472802 <description><![CDATA["Don't risk your life by waiting to see a doc. Early screening could save you and your family," Joe Faratzis, a colorectal cancer survivor said sharing his story on TikTok.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/night-sweats-changes-bowel-habits-colorectal-cancer-survivor-reflects-red-flags-he-overlooked-472802</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Dec 2024 02:22:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Reverse The Clock: This Simple Exercise Thrice A Week Can Make You 8 Years Younger]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reverse-clock-this-simple-exercise-thrice-week-can-make-you-8-years-younger-472799 <description><![CDATA[The weights you lift at the gym might be lifting years off your biological age too, suggests a recent study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/reverse-clock-this-simple-exercise-thrice-week-can-make-you-8-years-younger-472799</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:25:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Understanding Different Types Of Coughs: Remedies And When To Seek Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/understanding- Different-types-coughs-remedies-when-seek-treatment-472795 <description><![CDATA[It's important to know when to manage a cough at home and when to seek professional care.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/understanding- Different-types-coughs-remedies-when-seek-treatment-472795</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Dec 2024 04:33:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Not All Sweets Do Harm: Here's How Different Sugar Sources Affect Cardiovascular Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-all-sweets-do-harm-heres-how- Different-sugar-sources-affect-cardioangio-health-472792 <description><![CDATA[A recent study found that while fizzy drinks significantly raise your risk of stroke, heart failure, and atrial fibrillation, occasional sweet treats may not do much harm.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/not-all-sweets-do-harm-heres-how- Different-sugar-sources-affect-cardioangio-health-472792</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Dec 2024 02:29:30 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>