<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Coffee, Soda Or Wine? Dentist's Reveals Drink That Stains Your Teeth Most]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/coffee-soda-wine-dentists-reveals-drink-that-stains-your-teeth-most-472971 <description><![CDATA[In a viral TikTok experiment, a California-based dentist unveiled the unexpected culprit behind tooth stains, and the surprising results left him "shocked.']]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/coffee-soda-wine-dentists-reveals-drink-that-stains-your-teeth-most-472971</guid><pubDate> Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:40:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Dismiss Bad Memories? Never Skip A Good Night's Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-dismiss-bad-memories-never-skip-good-nights-sleep-472969 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that sleep deprivation could be the culprit behind your mind's inability to lock away unwanted memories.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-dismiss-bad-memories-never-skip-good-nights-sleep-472969</guid><pubDate> Mon, 13 Jan 2025 02:40:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Shocking Reveal: Protein Powders May Contain Cancer-Causing Toxic Metals, Here're Products At Highest Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/shocking-reveal- Protein-powders-may-contain-cancer-causing-毒-金属-herere-products-highest-472968 <description><![CDATA[A recent report revealed that 47% of protein powders investigated contained heavy metals, at levels that exceeded government food safety regulations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/shocking-reveal- Protein-powders-may-contain-cancer-causing-毒-金属-herere-products-highest-472968</guid><pubDate> Mon, 13 Jan 2025 01:00:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Doctor Accused of Being High During Surgeries Loses License After Testing Positive for Cocaine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doctor-accused-being-high-during-surgeries-loses-license-after-testing-positive-cocaine-472965 <description><![CDATA[A Houston urologist lost his medical license after testing positive for cocaine and kratom amid allegations of performing surgeries while impaired.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-doctor-accused-being-high-during-surgeries-loses-license-after-testing-positive-cocaine-472965</guid><pubDate> Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:49:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Virginia Woman Forced to Raise Money for Prosthetic Hand After Insurance Refuses to Cover It Despite Doctor Recommendation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virginia-woman-forced-raise-money-prosthetic-hand-after-insurance-refuses-cover-it-despite-472962 <description><![CDATA[Elisabeth Foley, a Virginia mother who lost her hand in a shark attack, is turning to crowdfunding after her insurance company denied coverage for a $73,000 prosthetic her doctors recommended.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virginia-woman-forced-raise-money-prosthetic-hand-after-insurance-refuses-cover-it-despite-472962</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 18:21:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Thousands of Doctors Come Out Against Letting RFK Jr. Become Health Secretary: 'He Is Actively Dangerous']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/thousands-doctors-come-out-against-letting-rfk-jr-become-health-secretary-he-actively-472959 <description><![CDATA[More than 15,000 doctors are urging the Senate to vote against confirming Robert F. Kennedy Jr. as the Secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/thousands-doctors-come-out-against-letting-rfk-jr-become-health-secretary-he-actively-472959</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:25:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Baby Hygiene Made Easy: Here's What We Think of Papablic's 4-in-1 Bottle Washer That Does It All]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/baby-hygiene-made-easy-heres-what-we-think-papablics-4-1-bottle-cleaner-that-does-it-all-472947 <description><![CDATA[Instead of juggling scrubbing brushes, sterilizers, and drying racks, this all-in-one system takes care of everything in one compact package]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/baby-hygiene-made-easy-heres-what-we-think-papablics-4-1-bottle-cleaner-that-does-it-all-472947</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 12:49:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Beyond Bleeding: The Best Period Tracker Isn't Just For Tracking Periods]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-bleeding-best-period-tracker-isnt-just-tracking-periods-472946 <description><![CDATA[If you're looking for more tools to understand how your cycle-related experiences impact your mental and physical health, you'll need an app that goes beyond just bleeding]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-bleeding-best-period-tracker-isnt-just-tracking-periods-472946</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 12:48:56 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Juice From This 'Underappreciated' Berry May Help You Lose Weight, Improve Metabolic Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/juice-this-underappreciated-berry-may-help-you-lose-weight-improve-metabolic-health-472956 <description><![CDATA[Researchers are now turning to these dark purple berries from the elder tree, native to Europe, as a promising tool for weight management and metabolic health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/juice-this-underappreciated-berry-may-help-you-lose-weight-improve-metabolic-health-472956</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 05:04:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Shares A Rare Side Effect Of GLP-1 Weight Loss Drugs, Ways To Break A Stall]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-shares-rare-side-effect-glp-1weight-loss-drugs-ways-break-stall-472953 <description><![CDATA[As more people turn to these weight loss solutions, it's important to understand not only how to use them effectively but also to stay alert to even the rare side effects that could arise.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-shares-rare-side-effect-glp-1weight-loss-drugs-ways-break-stall-472953</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 03:23:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Two Common Drinks And Bowel Cancer: One Reduces Risk By 17%, The Other Raises It By Similar Amount]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/two-common-drinks-bowel-cancer-one-reduces-risk-17-other-raises-it-similar-amount-472950 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that drinking a glass of milk reduces the risk of bowel cancer by nearly a fifth, while drinking a glass of wine could elevate the risk by 15%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/two-common-drinks-bowel-cancer-one-reduces-risk-17-other-raises-it-similar-amount-472950</guid><pubDate> Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:29:30 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>