<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Reports Human Case Of Bird Flu Linked To Cattle Contact]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-reports- human-case-bird-flu-linked-cattle-contact-471564 <description><![CDATA[This is the second human case of avian influenza in the U.S. and the first one tied to a recent outbreak among dairy cows in Texas.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-reports- human-case-bird-flu-linked-cattle-contact-471564</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Apr 2024 01:40:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tuberculosis Infection Linked To Increased Risk Of Various Cancers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tuberculosis-infection-linked-increased-risk-various-cancers-study-471563 <description><![CDATA[The study found that those with current or previous TB infection are more likely to have a diagnosis of a variety of cancers, including lung, blood, gynecological, and colorectal cancers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tuberculosis-infection-linked-increased-risk-various-cancers-study-471563</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Apr 2024 03:50:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Much Should You Workout To Prevent Obesity? Study Says It Depends On Your Genetics]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-much-should-you-workout-prevent-obesity-study-says-it-depends-your-genics-471561 <description><![CDATA[The daily step count required for a person with a higher genetic risk of obesity is more than those with moderate or low genetic risk, the study found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-much-should-you-workout-prevent-obesity-study-says-it-depends-your-genics-471561</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Apr 2024 03:07:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Being Moderately Overweight Lowers Cardiovascular Death Risk In Older Adults With Diabetes: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-moderately-overweight-lowers-cardioangio-death-risk-older-adults-diabetes-study-471559 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now identified the ideal weight for adults with type 2 diabetes to minimize their risk of death from cardiovascular disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-moderately-overweight-lowers-cardioangio-death-risk-older-adults-diabetes-study-471559</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Apr 2024 01:35:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Know All About Seasonal Allergies: Expert Tips To Reduce Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-all-about-seasonal-allergies-expert-tips-reduce-symptoms-471558 <description><![CDATA[Early diagnosis and taking suitable precautions can help people effectively manage seasonal allergies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-all-about-seasonal-allergies-expert-tips-reduce-symptoms-471558</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Mar 2024 04:30:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 5 Ultimate Body Detox: A Comprehensive Guide to Cleansing And Revitalizing Your System]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-ultimate-body-detox-compressive-guide-cleansing-revitalizing-your-system-471489<description><![CDATA[Clean and revitalize your system with these top 5 ultimate body detox aids.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-5-ultimate-body-detox-compressive-guide-cleansing-revitalizing-your-system-471489</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:30:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Popcorn Brain? Expert Tips To Cut Screen Time, Improve Focus]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-popcorn-brain-expert-tips-cut-screen-time-improve-focus-471557 <description><![CDATA[The term "popcorn brain" comes from the constantly fleeting state of mind, where thoughts jump from one to another just like the popping of popcorn kernels.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-popcorn-brain-expert-tips-cut-screen-time-improve-focus-471557</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Mar 2024 03:08:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Protect Sleep, Feel Younger: Study Says Feeling Sleepy Can Make You Feel A Decade Older]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/protect-sleep-feel-younger-study-says-feeling-sleepy-can-make-you-feel-decade-older-471555 <description><![CDATA[A study has shown that feeling sleepy can make you feel up to a decade older, and just two nights of insufficient sleep can add more than four years to this perceived aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/protect-sleep-feel-younger-study-says-feeling-sleepy-can-make-you-feel-decade-older-471555</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Mar 2024 01:25:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling With Insomnia? Study Recommends Consistent Exercise 2-3 Times Every Week]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-insomnia-study-recommends-consistently-exercising-2-3-times-every-week-471553 <description><![CDATA[The study not only underscores the significance of exercise but also highlights the importance of maintaining consistency in physical activity over time.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-insomnia-study-recommends-consistently-exercising-2-3-times-every-week-471553</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Mar 2024 04:24:53 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Frequent Reuse Of Frying Oil Linked To Brain Damage, Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/frequent-reuse-frying-oil-linked-brain-damage-study-suggests-471551 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted higher levels of neurodegeneration in rats that consumed reheated oil and their offspring compared to rats on a normal diet.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/frequent-reuse-frying-oil-linked-brain-damage-study-suggests-471551</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:47:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Migraine Raises Stroke Risk In Young Adults Similar To Traditional Factors: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/migraine-raises-中风-risk-young-adults-similar-traditional-factors-study-471549 <description><![CDATA[The study found significant associations between migraines, blood clotting disorders, kidney failure, autoimmune diseases, and malignancy, and the occurrence of strokes in young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/migraine-raises-中风-risk-young-adults-similar-traditional-factors-study-471549</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:21:21 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>