<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Endometriosis Awareness Month: Dispel Myths With Expert Insights On The Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-awareness-month-dispel-myths-expert-insights-condition-471495 <description><![CDATA[During this Endometriosis Awareness Month, understand the condition better from an expert who dispels common myths around it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/endometriosis-awareness-month-dispel-myths-expert-insights-condition-471495</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Mar 2024 01:45:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Levels Of Cancer-Causing Benzene Detected In Some Acne Products: Independent Lab Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-of-cancer-causing-苯-Detected-some-acne-products-independent-lab-report-471493 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found unacceptably high levels of benzene in numerous prescription and over-the-counter benzoyl peroxide products when they were stored or handled at high temperatures.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-levels-of-cancer-causing-苯-Detected-some-acne-products-independent-lab-report-471493</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Mar 2024 03:55:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Virus Lingers In The Body More Than A Year After Infection: Studies]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-virus-lingers-body-more-years-after-infection-studies-4 <description><![CDATA[The studies showed that COVID antigens lingered in the blood up to 14 months after infection and more than two years in tissue samples of people who had the infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-virus-lingers-body-more-years-after-infection-studies-4</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:56:49 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People At High Risk Of Obesity In Middle Age If Parents Were Obese: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-high-risk-of-obesity-middle-age-if-parents-were-obese-study-471490 <description><![CDATA[People whose parents both experienced obesity in middle age are six times more likely to live with obesity during the same life stage, and the risk of developing obesity triples when one parent is living with the condition.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-high-risk-of-obesity-middle-age-if-parents-were-obese-study-471490</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:21:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Refined Carbs Affect Your Looks? Chronic Consumption Linked To Reduced Facial Attractiveness: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-refined-carbs-affect-your-looks-chronic-conspiration-linked-reduced-facial-attractiveness-471487 <description><![CDATA[Beyond the known health risks of refined carbs, a new study reveals that persistent consumption may diminish facial attractiveness in both men and women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-refined-carbs-affect-your-looks-chronic-conspiration-linked-reduced-facial-attractiveness-471487</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:58:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking 10,000 Steps A Day Cut Cardiovascular Risk Despite Sedentary Lifestyle: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-10000-steps-day-cut-cardioangio-risk-despite-sedentary-lifestyle-study-471486 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now reveal that by clocking in 10,000 daily steps, you can still cut down the cardiovascular risk and risk of early death even if you are sedentary for the rest of the day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-10000-steps-day-cut-cardioangio-risk-despite-sedentary-lifestyle-study-471486</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Mar 2024 02:03:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Kidney Month: Expert Reveals Dietary Habits For Preventing And Managing Kidney Diseases]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-kidney-month-expert-reveals-dietary-habits-preventing-managing-kidney-diseases-471485 <description><![CDATA[During this National Kidney Month, an expert reveals how dietary habits can help prevent kidney diseases and manage their progression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-kidney-month-expert-reveals-dietary-habits-preventing-managing-kidney-diseases-471485</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:53:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Artificially Sweetened Drinks Increase Risk Of Irregular Heartbeat: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking-artificially-sweetened-beverages-raises-risk-of-irregular-heartbeat-study-471483 <description><![CDATA[Drinking two or more liters of artificially sweetened beverages weekly elevates the risk of atrial fibrillation by 20%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking-artificially-sweetened-beverages-raises-risk-of-irregular-heartbeat-study-471483</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Mar 2024 04:24:45 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Parrot Fever Outbreak In Europe Kills 5: Know All About Psittacosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/parrot-fever-outbreak-europe-kills-5-know-all-about-psittacosis-471482 <description><![CDATA[The WHO reported a sudden increase in psittacosis infections over the past year, with the disease persisting and continuing to spread in Europe.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/parrot-fever-outbreak-europe-kills-5-know-all-about-psittacosis-471482</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:09:32 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Less Than 5 Hours Of Daily Sleep Raises Diabetes Risk Despite Healthy Eating: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-5-hours-daily-sleep-raises-diabetes-risk-despite-healthy-eating-study-471481 <description><![CDATA[The diabetes risk from chronic sleep deprivation cannot be compensated by healthy eating alone, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-5-hours-daily-sleep-raises-diabetes-risk-despite-healthy-eating-study-471481</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Mar 2024 01:17:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Dies From Vitamin D Overdose: Know The Risks Of Excessive Supplement Intake]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-die-vitamin-d-overdose-know-risks-excessive-supplement-intake-471480 <description><![CDATA[Although a necessary vitamin, when taken in excess, Vitamin D can cause toxicity and lead to potential kidney damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-die-vitamin-d-overdose-know-risks-excessive-supplement-intake-471480</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Mar 2024 04:36:53 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>