<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Exposure To Air Pollution During Pregnancy Quadruples Postpartum Depression Risk Up To 3 Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-air-pollution-during-pregnancy-quadruples-postpartum-depression-risk-3-years-study-472348 <description><![CDATA[The latest study revealed that pollution during pregnancy nearly quadruples the risk of postpartum depression, with this heightened risk lasting for up to three years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-air-pollution-during-pregnancy-quadruples-postpartum-depression-risk-3-years-study-472348</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Sep 2024 02:52:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Doses Of ADHD Drugs Linked To More Than 5 Times Risk Of Psychosis: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-dose-adhd-drugs-linked-more-5-times-risk-psychosis-study-472345 <description><![CDATA[Taking high doses of medications for ADHD, particularly amphetamines is linked to more than five times the risk of developing psychosis or mania.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-dose-adhd-drugs-linked-more-5-times-risk-psychosis-study-472345</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Sep 2024 02:06:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Orthopedic Knee And Leg Pillows For Pain Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-orthopedic-knee-leg-pillows-pain-relief-472299 <description><![CDATA[A knee pillow is specifically designed to promote spinal alignment. It can prevent your back from arching too much and make side sleeping comfortable.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-orthopedic-knee-leg-pillows-pain-relief-472299</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:59:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Children's Screen Time Mirrors Parents', Excessive Use Affects Language Skills: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childrens-screen-time-mirrors-parents-excessive-use-affects-language-skills-study-472340 <description><![CDATA[The study found that kids' screen habits closely mirror those of their parents and excessive screen use in the family can negatively impact children's language development.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childrens-screen-time-mirrors-parents-excessive-use-affects-language-skills-study-472340</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Sep 2024 05:03:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dry Eyes? Laughter May Be The Best Medicine, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dry-eyes-laughter-may-best-medicine-says-study-472337 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that laughter could be a safe, low-cost remedy for those struggling with dry eyes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dry-eyes-laughter-may-best-medicine-says-study-472337</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Sep 2024 03:15:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Suicide Prevention Week: Expert Insights On Ways To Help People Battling Suicidal Thoughts]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/suicide-prevention-week-expert-insights-ways-help-people-battle-suicidal-thoughts-472335 <description><![CDATA[In recognition of Suicide Prevention Week, an expert shares valuable insights on recognizing the warning signs and supporting those struggling with suicidal thoughts, which could potentially save lives.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/suicide-prevention-week-expert-insights-ways-help-people-battle-suicidal-thoughts-472335</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:08:32 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Cooling Towels To Help Your Regulate Body Temperature]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cooling-towels-help-your-regulate-body-Temperature-472310 <description><![CDATA[A cooling towel works by absorbing the heat from the skin surface and dissipating it into the environment. Cooling towels offer refreshing chill that lasts for hours and keeps your body cool. These can be easily folded and tossed into a bag and carried anywhere.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cooling-towels-help-your-regulate-body-Temperature-472310</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:17:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Baby Carriers To Simplify Your Life, Boost Child's Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-baby-riers-simplify-your-life-boost-childs-health-472304 <description><![CDATA[You might see more parents using sling bags and carriers to carry their babies these days, but babywearing is far from just a modern trend. It is an ancient practice ingrained across several cultures, valued for its many benefits, from convenience for parents and caregivers to improved health and mood for children. Beyond the practical advantages of baby carriers, here we explore their safety and health benefits for children and highlight top choices available in the market, to help you find the perfect one for your needs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-baby-riers-simplify-your-life-boost-childs-health-472304</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:07:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Resistance Bands For Every Workout: Top Picks To Boost Your Fitness Routine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-resistance-bands-every-workout-top-picks-boost-your-fitness-routine-472320 <description><![CDATA[Resistance bands help target multiple muscle groups, improve strength, flexibility, and endurance.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-resistance-bands-every-workout-top-picks-boost-your-fitness-routine-472320</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:05:13 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peptides And Dermatological Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/peptides-dermatological-research-472328 <description><![CDATA[Peptides are composed of two or more amino acids linked by peptide bonds. Research indicates that they may play diverse roles within an organism, ranging from signaling molecules to structural components.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/peptides-dermatological-research-472328</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:23:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Asthma Linked To Miscarriage And Fertility Issues In Women: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/asthma-linked-miscarriage-fertility-issues-women-study-472325 <description><![CDATA[As the findings suggest that the severity of asthma can impact fertility, the researchers stress the importance of effective asthma control to improve reproductive outcomes in women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/asthma-linked-miscarriage-fertility-issues-women-study-472325</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Sep 2024 02:47:15 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>