<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Air Pollution Affects Life Even Before Conception; Study Says It Cuts IVF Odds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-affects-life-even-before-conception-study-says-it-cuts-ivf-odds-471940 <description><![CDATA[Exposure to fine particulate matter before egg retrieval (oocyte retrieval) in IVF can reduce live birth odds by around 40%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-affects-life-even-before-conception-study-says-it-cuts-ivf-odds-471940</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Jul 2024 01:12:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Americans Are Sleeping Less: Chronic Insomnia Affects 1 In 8, Survey Reports]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-are-sleeping-less-chronic-insomnia-affects-1-8-survey-reports-471937 <description><![CDATA[According to the survey report around 12% of adults in the U.S., equivalent to one in eight have been diagnosed with chronic insomnia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-are-sleeping-less-chronic-insomnia-affects-1-8-survey-reports-471937</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:18:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Skipping 10 Bacon Slices Weekly Could Save Thousands Of Lives In US: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skipping-10-bacon-slices-weekly-could-save-thousands-lives-us-study-471935 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now reveal that cutting out just 10 slices of bacon each week could significantly reduce thousands of deaths from cardiovascular disease, diabetes, and colorectal cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/skipping-10-bacon-slices-weekly-could-save-thousands-lives-us-study-471935</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:51:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Brain-Eating Amoeba Kills 3: Know About Highly Fatal Naegleria Fowleri Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-brain-eating-amoeba-kills-3-know-about-highly-fatal-naegleria-fowleri-infection-471932 <description><![CDATA[Three children, including a 5-year-old, have succumbed to an infection from a rare brain-eating amoeba in India in the past two months.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-brain-eating-amoeba-kills-3-know-about-highly-fatal-naegleria-fowleri-infection-471932</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:19:43 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Bans Food Additive Found In Sports Drinks, Sodas Citing Safety Concerns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-bans-food-additive-found-sports-drinks-sodas-citing-safety-concerns-471928 <description><![CDATA[FDA revoked the authorization for the use of brominated vegetable oil, a common food additive used in sports drinks and sodas, citing safety concerns.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-bans-food-additive-found-sports-drinks-sodas-citing-safety-concerns-471928</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Jul 2024 03:20:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stay Healthy In 20s: Inflammation In Young Adulthood May Reduce Cognitive Skills Later]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-healthy-20s-inflammation-young-adulthood-may-reduce-cognitive-skills-later-471931 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say it is important to stay healthy and stress-free in your 20s for better cognitive health in midlife.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-healthy-20s-inflammation-young-adulthood-may-reduce-cognitive-skills-later-471931</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Jul 2024 03:10:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Toxic Metals Like Arsenic And Lead Detected In Tampons]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/有毒-金属-类似-砷-铅-检测到-tampons-471926 <description><![CDATA[This discovery emerged from an analysis of 30 tampons across 14 different brands, during which 16 metals were tested: arsenic, barium, calcium, cadmium, cobalt, chromium, copper, iron, manganese, mercury, nickel, lead, selenium, strontium, vanadium, and zinc.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/有毒-金属-类似-砷-铅-检测到-tampons-471926</guid><pubDate> Thu, 04 Jul 2024 01:38:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Diet At 40 Decides Quality Of Life At 70, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-diet-40-decides-quality-life-70-says-study-471925 <description><![CDATA[The researchers discovered that maintaining a healthy diet in midlife could pave the way for a high-quality life at 70.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-diet-40-decides-quality-life-70-says-study-471925</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jul 2024 03:52:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Kisunla? Know All About New FDA-Approved Drug For Alzheimer's Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-kisunla-know-all-about-new-fda-approved-drug-alzheimers-disease-471924 <description><![CDATA[Kisunla manufactured by Eli Lilly could significantly slow cognitive decline in people with early symptomatic Alzheimer's disease, according to results of the company's clinical trials.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-kisunla-know-all-about-new-fda-approved-drug-alzheimers-disease-471924</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jul 2024 02:46:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bacterial Contamination Detected In Tattoo And Permanent Makeup Inks, Study Cautions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bacterial-contamination-Detected-tattoo-permanent-makeup-inks-study-cautions-471921 <description><![CDATA[A new study found that 35% of tattoo and permanent makeup inks sold across the U.S. are contaminated with bacteria.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bacterial-contamination-Detected-tattoo-permanent-makeup-inks-study-cautions-471921</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jul 2024 02:01:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Discover How Angelina Fabian Utilizes The Power Of The 9 Centers Of The Human Design System For Self-Empowerment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/discover-how-angelina-fabian-utilizes-power-9-centers- human-design-system-self-empowerment-471919 <description><![CDATA[The Human Design System intertwines ancient wisdom with modern science, offering new insights into how we think, feel, and act. It serves as a map that decodes our unique behaviors, desires, and paths to personal healing.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/discover-how-angelina-fabian-utilizes-power-9-centers- human-design-system-self-empowerment-471919</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:52:06 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>