<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Robitussin Cough Syrups Recalled Due To Microbial Contamination]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/robitussin-cough-syrups-recalled-due-microbial-contamination-471314 <description><![CDATA[The distributors have been notified and provided with instructions for the return of all recalled products.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/robitussin-cough-syrups-recalled-due-microbial-contamination-471314</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jan 2024 03:03:56 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Should You Put The Toilet Lid Up Or Down While Flushing? Here's What A Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/should-you-put-toilet-lid-down-while-flushing-heres-what-study-says-471312 <description><![CDATA[The research team examined the spread of viral particles during toilet flushing in both scenarios — while the lids were open and closed. The study was conducted both in household and public toilets.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/should-you-put-toilet-lid-down-while-flushing-heres-what-study-says-471312</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:44:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dealing With Menopause Symptoms? Cold Water Swimming Could Alleviate Anxiety, Mood Swings And Hot Flushes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dealing-menopause-symptoms-cold-water-swimming-could-alleviate-anxiety-mood-swings-hot-flushes-471306 <description><![CDATA[To know the effects of cold water swimming on women's health and well-being, researchers surveyed 1,114 women, 785 of whom were going through menopause.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dealing-menopause-symptoms-cold-water-swimming-could-alleviate-anxiety-mood-swings-hot-flushes-471306</guid><pubDate> Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:58:54 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 During Pregnancy Triples Odds Of Respiratory Illness In Children; Risk Lower In Vaccinated Expectant Mothers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-during-pregnancy-triples-odds-respiratory-illness-children-risk-lower-vaccinated-471304 <description><![CDATA[Researchers behind a new study looked into the relationship between maternal COVID-19 vaccination and respiratory illness in infants using a longitudinal cohort of mother-infant pairs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-during-pregnancy-triples-odds-respiratory-illness-children-risk-lower-vaccinated-471304</guid><pubDate> Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:52:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Chocolate-Coated Insulin Pills Replace Needles? Animal Study Shows Promising Results For Diabetes Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-chocolate-coated-insulin-pills-replace-needles-animal-study-suggests-promising-results-471302 <description><![CDATA[Good news might be on the horizon for people with diabetes, as a swallowable insulin pill tucked in a piece of chocolate might replace painful insulin shots in the future.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-chocolate-coated-insulin-pills-replace-needles-animal-study-suggests-promising-results-471302</guid><pubDate> Wed, 24 Jan 2024 04:38:52 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[More Than 150 Infants, Pregnant Women Given Incorrect RSV Vaccine, CDC Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-150-infants-pregnant-women-given-in Correct-rsv-vaccine-cdc-says-471301 <description><![CDATA[According to reports, there have been 25 cases of accidental administration of Pfizer (Abrsyvo) or GSK (Arexvy) RSV vaccines to children below two and 128 cases of mistaken administration of the GSK RSV vaccine (Arexvy) to pregnant women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-150-infants-pregnant-women-given-in Correct-rsv-vaccine-cdc-says-471301</guid><pubDate> Wed, 24 Jan 2024 03:25:58 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unintentional Weight Loss Could Be Warning Sign Of Cancer, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unintentional-weight-loss-could-warning-sign-cancer-says-study-471299 <description><![CDATA[A recent study found that participants who lost over 10% of their body weight in the past two years were at a greater risk of developing cancer in the subsequent 12 months compared to those who did not have weight loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unintentional-weight-loss-could-warning-sign-cancer-says-study-471299</guid><pubDate> Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:55:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Energy Drinks Linked To Disturbed Sleep: Study Says Even Once A Month Consumption Raises Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/energy-drinks-linked-disturbed-sleep-study-says-even-once-month-conspiration-raises-risk-471298 <description><![CDATA[The research revealed that even occasional intake of energy drinks, such as once a month, could affect one's quality of sleep.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/energy-drinks-linked-disturbed-sleep-study-says-even-once-month-conspiration-raises-risk-471298</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Jan 2024 03:55:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Expert Insights On Intermittent Fasting: Know Health Benefits, Potential Side Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-insights-intermittent-fasting-know-health-benefits-pottial-side-effects-471297 <description><![CDATA[Discover insights from an expert about the fasting diet, its potential health benefits and possible side effects.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-insights-intermittent-fasting-know-health-benefits-pottial-side-effects-471297</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:13:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Best Protein Powders Of 2024: Powerful Nutrition To Fuel Your Fitness Journey]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-powders-powerful-nutrition-fuel-your-fitness-journey-471296 <description><![CDATA[Join the countless individuals who have embraced the benefits of protein powder as a key component in their journey toward a healthier and more balanced lifestyle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-powders-powerful-nutrition-fuel-your-fitness-journey-471296</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:34:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Secret To Healthy Aging? Study Identifies Foods That Reduce Risk Of Chronic Illnesses In Women]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/secret-healthy-aging-study-identizes-foods-that-reduce-risk-chronic-illnesses-women-471295 <description><![CDATA[Ladies, are you curious to know the secret to healthy aging? Your middle-age diet can influence your future health, a recent study suggests.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/secret-healthy-aging-study-identizes-foods-that-reduce-risk-chronic-illnesses-women-471295</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jan 2024 04:23:51 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>