<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Quit Smoking? Study Says Cytisine Doubles Chances Of Successful Cessation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-quit-smoking-study-says-cytisine-doubles-chances-successful-cessation-471226 <description><![CDATA[Cytisine increases the chances of smoking cessation by more than twofold compared to a placebo. It might be more effective than nicotine replacement therapy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/want-quit-smoking-study-says-cytisine-doubles-chances-successful-cessation-471226</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:00:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Long COVID: Study Says Synbiotic Drug That Alters Gut Microbiome Relieves Multiple Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-covid-study-says-synbiotic-drug-that-alters-gut-microbiome-relieves-multiple-symptoms-471225 <description><![CDATA[The results of the trial indicate that the drug could help alleviate symptoms such as fatigue, gastrointestinal upset, difficulty in concentration, memory loss and general unwellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-covid-study-says-synbiotic-drug-that-alters-gut-microbiome-relieves-multiple-symptoms-471225</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:44:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Standing Burns More Calories Than Sitting; Know Ways To Incorporate It Into Your Routine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stand-burns-more-calories-sitting-know-ways-incorporate-it-your-routine-471224 <description><![CDATA[Standing may not work as a weight loss strategy, but studies say it can help burn more calories than sitting.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stand-burns-more-calories-sitting-know-ways-incorporate-it-your-routine-471224</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Jan 2024 06:02:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fasting-Mimicking Diet Provides Unique Cardiovascular Benefits: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fasting-mimicking-diet-provides-unique-cardioangio-benefits-study-471223 <description><![CDATA[Fasting-mimicking diet provides unique cardiovascular benefits compared to the Mediterranean diet, which is associated with reduced risk of heart disease, a new study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fasting-mimicking-diet-provides-unique-cardioangio-benefits-study-471223</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Jan 2024 03:02:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Smart Insulin' Injection Regulates Glucose Levels For A Week, Could Be A Breakthrough In Diabetes Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smart-insulin-injection-regulates-glucose-levels-week-could-breakthrough-diabetes-treatment-471222 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have developed a new type of "smart insulin" that could potentially transform the future of diabetes treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/smart-insulin-injection-regulates-glucose-levels-week-could-breakthrough-diabetes-treatment-471222</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Jan 2024 01:03:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Feeling Uneasy After A Heavy Meal? Here Are 5 Drinks To Aid Digestion]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/feeling-uneasy-after-heavy-meal-here-are-5-drinks-aid-digestion-471221 <description><![CDATA[To reduce gas trouble and improve digestion, here are some drinks that you can try out.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/feeling-uneasy-after-heavy-meal-here-are-5-drinks-aid-digestion-471221</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Dec 2023 06:03:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Owning A Pet Could Slow Cognitive Decline In Older Adults Living Alone: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/owning-pet-could-slow-cognitive-decline-older-adults-living-alone-study-471220 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that pet ownership was associated with slower rates of decline in verbal memory and fluency among those living alone.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/owning-pet-could-slow-cognitive-decline-older-adults-living-alone-study-471220</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Dec 2023 01:59:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[An Alternative Approach To Treat Obesity? Scientists Develop Vibrating, Ingestible Capsule That Makes You Feel Full]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alternative-approach-treat-obesity-scientists-develop-vibrating-ingestible-capsule-that-makes-471219 <description><![CDATA[The new capsule could emerge as a minimally invasive and cost-effective way to treat obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alternative-approach-treat-obesity-scientists-develop-vibrating-ingestible-capsule-that-makes-471219</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:10:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Zombie Deer Disease: Know All About The Fatal Infection As Scientists Fear It May Jump To Humans]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/zombie-deer-disease-know-all-about-fatal-infection-scientists-fear-it-may-jump- humans-471218 <description><![CDATA[Although no cases have yet been reported in humans, scientists share concerns that the infection with no cure may jump to humans, which they should be prepared for.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/zombie-deer-disease-know-all-about-fatal-infection-scientists-fear-it-may-jump- humans-471218</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Dec 2023 03:02:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hospital Admissions For Pediatric RSV Far Higher Than Omicron Or Flu: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospital-admissions-pediatric-rsv-far-higher-omicron-flu-study-471217 <description><![CDATA[The study showed that in children, the hospitalization rate was highest for RSV (81.7%), while it was only 31.5% for omicron and 27.7% for influenza.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospital-admissions-pediatric-rsv-far-higher-omicron-flu-study-471217</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Dec 2023 02:20:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Year's Resolutions: Here Are Some Practical Goals You Can Set For A Healthy 2024]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-years-resolutions-here-are-some-practical-goals-you-can-set-healthy-2024-471202 <description><![CDATA[Although resolutions are easy to make, most often, they fail within weeks as the spirit and excitement of the New Year fade. Setting achievable, specific and measurable goals can help you stick to your resolutions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-years-resolutions-here-are-some-practical-goals-you-can-set-healthy-2024-471202</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Dec 2023 08:23:01 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>