<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医药日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Tips To Take Care Of Your Eyes While Traveling]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tips-take-care-your-eyes-while-traveling-470179 <description><![CDATA[Taking good care of the eyes can make travel more enjoyable.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tips-take-care-your-eyes-while-traveling-470179</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 03:34:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Vaginal Seeding? Rubbing Mom's Vaginal Fluids On C-Section Babies May Improve Their Neurodevelopment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-vaginal-seeding-rubbing-moms-vaginal-fluids-c-section-babies-may-improve-their-470175 <description><![CDATA[To instill disease-fighting properties in babies, the mother's vaginal fluid is smeared on the newborn with the help of a cotton swab to recreate the scenario of them being born through the vaginal canal.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-vaginal-seeding-rubbing-moms-vaginal-fluids-c-section-babies-may-improve-their-470175</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:39:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Sickle Cell Awareness Day: Risk Factors, Complications Of Genetic Blood Disorder]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-sickle-cell-awareness-day-risk-factors-complications-genetic-blood-disorder-470177 <description><![CDATA[The theme for this year's World Sickle Cell Awareness Day is "Building and Strengthening Global Sickle Cell Communities, Formalizing New-born Screening and Knowing your Sickle Cell Disease Status."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-sickle-cell-awareness-day-risk-factors-complications-genetic-blood-disorder-470177</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:38:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Does Magnesium Deficiency Affect Health? Watch Out For Signs]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-does-magnesium-deficiency-affect-health-watch-out-signs-470174 <description><![CDATA[From supporting muscle and nerve function to energy production, regulation of blood pressure and enzyme reactions, magnesium is essential for staying fit and healthy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-does-magnesium-deficiency-affect-health-watch-out-signs-470174</guid><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:29:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mounting Evidence Points To Wuhan Lab As Source Of COVID-19 Outbreak]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mounting-evidence-points-wuhan-lab-source-covid-19-outbreak-470173 <description><![CDATA[U.S. taxpayer funds might have been allocated to the controversial Wuhan laboratory before the pandemic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mounting-evidence-points-wuhan-lab-source-covid-19-outbreak-470173</guid><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:59:37 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[North Korea Faces Severe Food Crisis Amid Ongoing COVID-19 Measures]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/north-korea-faces-severe-food-crisis-amid-ongoing-covid-19-measures-470171 <description><![CDATA[North Korea reportedly faces its most severe food crisis since the 1990s famine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/north-korea-faces-severe-food-crisis-amid-ongoing-covid-19-measures-470171</guid><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:51:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[West Nile Virus Cases Reported Across Multiple States, Health Officials Urge Vigilance]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-virus-cases-reported-across-multiple-states-health-officials-urge-vigilance-470169 <description><![CDATA[There has been an alarming uptick in West Nile virus cases in the country.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/west-nile-virus-cases-reported-across-multiple-states-health-officials-urge-vigilance-470169</guid><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:46:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Florida Could Be The Epicenter Of Mpox Summer Outbreak: Report]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-could-epicenter-mpox-summer-outbreak-report-470167 <description><![CDATA[Recent data point to Florida being at the highest risk of seeing the most mpox cases this summer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/florida-could-epicenter-mpox-summer-outbreak-report-470167</guid><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:43:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[China's Omission Of Cremation Data Raises Questions About COVID-19 Impact]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chinas-omission-cremation-data-raises-questions-about-covid-19-impact-470166 <description><![CDATA[The absence of data suggested that the number of excess deaths could be significant.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chinas-omission-cremation-data-raises-questions-about-covid-19-impact-470166</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:44:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Reveals Alarming Mortality Rates For COVID-Associated Fungal Infections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-alarming-mortality-rates-covid-associated-fungal-infections-470164 <description><![CDATA[A study uncovered alarming mortality rates among people who had COVID-associated fungal infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-alarming-mortality-rates-covid-associated-fungal-infections-470164</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:41:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Gut Bacteria Could Be Causing Endometriosis, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-gut-bacteria-could-causing-endometriosis-study-says-470163 <description><![CDATA[Research suggests antibiotics could target the bacteria associated with gut bacteria, affecting 10% of women and girls worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-gut-bacteria-could-causing-endometriosis-study-says-470163</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:38:59 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>