<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Improving Gut Health May Help Slow Progression Of HIV: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/improving-gut-health-may-help-slow-progression-hiv-study-470567 <description><![CDATA[The study has revealed that the root cause of HIV progression and the key to recovery could be gut health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/improving-gut-health-may-help-slow-progression-hiv-study-470567</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 01:10:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[MIND Diet May Enhance Focus, Cognitive Performance In Young Students: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mind-diet-may-enhance-focus-cognitive-performance-young-students-study-470564 <description><![CDATA[The MIND diet improves focus and brain health in students while preventing cognitive decline in older adults, researchers say.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mind-diet-may-enhance-focus-cognitive-performance-young-students-study-470564</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 05:55:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[8 Healthy Lifestyle Habits That Could Add More Than 20 Years To Your Life]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-healthy-lifestyle-habits-that-c​​ould-add-more-20-years-your-life-470561 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has specifically identified eight lifestyle habits that when adopted by the middle ages, can improve longevity by more than 20 years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-healthy-lifestyle-habits-that-c​​ould-add-more-20-years-your-life-470561</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 04:41:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[An Unusual Type Of Red Wine Can Improve Skin Elasticity, Slow Aging, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unusual-type-red-wine-can-improve-skin-elasticity-slow-aging-study-finds-470560 <description><![CDATA[Drinking dealcoholized muscadine wine may help improve elasticity and make the skin look younger.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unusual-type-red-wine-can-improve-skin-elasticity-slow-aging-study-finds-470560</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 02:16:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Allergic March? Study Says Kids With Eczema May Develop More Allergies As They Grow]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-allergic-march-study-says-kids-eczema-may-develop-more-allergies-they-grow-470558 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say the development of allergies in kids follow a predictable pattern, called an "allergic march."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-allergic-march-study-says-kids-eczema-may-develop-more-allergies-they-grow-470558</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 01:31:08 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Omega-3 Fatty Acid Linked To Lower Risk Of Age-Related Hearing Loss, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-fatty-acid-linked-lower-risk-age-lated-hearing-loss-study-finds-470556 <description><![CDATA[New research shows that higher levels of docosahexaenoic acid may help reduce hearing challenges in older adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-fatty-acid-linked-lower-risk-age-lated-hearing-loss-study-finds-470556</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 04:51:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Olive Oil For Brain Health? Study Says It Could Lower Risk Of Death From Dementia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/olive-oil-brain-health-study-says-it-could-lower-risk-death-dementia-470555 <description><![CDATA[A new study shows that olive oil is not just beneficial for the heart but can also improve brain health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/olive-oil-brain-health-study-says-it-could-lower-risk-death-dementia-470555</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:57:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Extreme Heat Affects People With Underlying Health Conditions; Tips To Protect Yourself]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-extreme-heat-affects-people-underlying-health-conditions-tips-protect-yourself-470553 <description><![CDATA[Although heat-related illnesses can affect anyone, people with underlying health conditions such as diabetes, cardiac issues and skin disorders need to take extra precautions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-extreme-heat-affects-people-underlying-health-conditions-tips-protect-yourself-470553</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 01:57:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Customers of xNARA Report 98% success – The Truth Behind its Product]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/customers-xnara-report-98-success-truth-behind-its-product-470551 <description><![CDATA[MarketsandMarkets estimates that, in the US, dietary supplements will claim a $167.5 billion market in 2023.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/customers-xnara-report-98-success-truth-behind-its-product-470551</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:13:18 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Extreme Heat Straining Health Systems: WHO]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/extreme-heat-straining-health-systems-who-470548 <description><![CDATA[Experts have blamed the heatwaves on climate change, driven by the burning of fossil fuels releasing the greenhouse gas carbon dioxide into the atmosphere. The UN's WMO weather agency has said repeated high overnight temperatures are a particular health risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/extreme-heat-straining-health-systems-who-470548</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 06:53:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sydney's Former HIV Epicentre Close To Ending Transmission: Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sydneys-former-hiv-epicentre-close-ending-transmission-research-470547 <description><![CDATA[A study announced at the AIDS conference said people on antiretrovirals who have low but detectible levels of HIV have almost zero risk of sexually transmitting the virus to others.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sydneys-former-hiv-epicentre-close-ending-transmission-research-470547</guid><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 06:51:23 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>