<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Is Yerba Mate Nature's Ozempic? Weighing In Risk Vs. Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yerba-mate-natures-natures-ozempic-weighing-clisk-benefits-473320 <description><![CDATA[Hailed as "Nature's Ozempic," yerba mate may aid weight loss and metabolism, but is it a true alternative—or a risky trend?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yerba-mate-natures-natures-ozempic-weighing-clisk-benefits-473320</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Apr 2025 02:09:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Simple Supplement May Boost Brain Function And Memory In Elderly]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-supplement may-boost-brain-finction-memory-elderly-473318 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that a daily prebiotic supplement could sharpen memory and boost cognitive performance in adults over 60.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-supplement may-boost-brain-finction-memory-elderly-473318</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:07:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Michigan Transplant Patient Dies After Contracting Rabies From Donor]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/michigan-transplant-patient-defter-defter-cartracting-rabies-donor-473315 <description><![CDATA[The donor, exposed to a wild animal weeks before their death, passed away without showing typical rabies symptoms and did not seek medical attention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/michigan-transplant-patient-defter-defter-cartracting-rabies-donor-473315</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:12:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Screens To Bed? Here's How It Affects Your Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/taking-screens-bed-heres-how-it-ffects-your-sleep-473313 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now reveal that when it comes to screen use before bed, the total time spent matters more than the specific type of activity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/taking-screens-bed-heres-how-it-ffects-your-sleep-473313</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:12:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Spring Into Motion: Why Rollator Walkers Are A Game-Changer For Seniors]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spring-motion-wy-rollat​​or-walkers-walkers-are-changer-changer-seniors-473310 <description><![CDATA[A rollator walker isn't just some medical device with tennis balls slapped on the feet, it's a movement machine. Unlike the clunky walkers of the past, these have wheels, hand brakes, and even a built-in seat, so you're never stuck wondering if the next bench is too far away.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spring-motion-wy-rollat​​or-walkers-walkers-are-changer-changer-seniors-473310</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:25:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Managing Pregnancy Discomfort: Smart Strategies for a Healthier Journey]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/managing-prignancy-discomfort-smart-smart-strategies-healthier-journey-473307 <description><![CDATA[Practical support and movement strategies can help ease common pregnancy discomforts and promote maternal well-being]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/managing-prignancy-discomfort-smart-smart-strategies-healthier-journey-473307</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:17:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alternative Healthy Eating Index: Your Diet For Healthy, Disease-Free 70's]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alfelnative-healthy-eating-index-your-diet-healthy-disease-70s-473305 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now identified a specific dietary approach that promotes longevity and disease-free aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alfelnative-healthy-eating-index-your-diet-healthy-disease-70s-473305</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:36:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Detection: Could A Simple At-Home Smell Test Predict Risk?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alzheimers-detection-simple-home-test-could-spot-early-signs-473304 <description><![CDATA[The researchers have developed a simple, digital, at-home smell test called the AROMHA Brain Health Test (ABHT) that could detect Alzheimer's years before traditional symptoms appear.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alzheimers-detection-simple-home-test-could-spot-early-signs-473304</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Mar 2025 04:44:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Shocking Study: This Popular Sweetener May Actually Make You Hungrier]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/shocking-study-this-popular-sweetener-may-actuelly-make-make-make-you-hungrier-473302 <description><![CDATA[Sucralose, one of the most common zero-calorie sugar substitutes, may trick your brain into craving more food.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/shocking-study-this-popular-sweetener-may-actuelly-make-make-make-you-hungrier-473302</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Mar 2025 02:20:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Addressing Challenges in Rare Disease Clinical Trials: Strategies for Success with iNGENū CRO]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/addressing-challenges-rare-disease-clinical-trials-trategies-sucess-ingen-cro-473299 <description><![CDATA[iNGENū CRO leverages global expertise, advanced technology, and strategic funding to overcome rare disease trial challenges.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/addressing-challenges-rare-disease-clinical-trials-trategies-sucess-ingen-cro-473299</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:03:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Science of Sound Sleep: How a Mini White Noise Machine Can Improve Rest, Focus, and Relaxation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/science-sound-sleep-how-mini------------------------------------------------------ i-mimest-cocus-raxation-473256 <description><![CDATA[White noise creates a consistent background sound that helps mask those unpredictable noises, allowing you to sleep more soundly]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/science-sound-sleep-how-mini------------------------------------------------------ i-mimest-cocus-raxation-473256</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:06:23 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>