<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新新闻</description><language>看</language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Pregnancy Pillows for Comfort, Support, and a Restful Sleep]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-pillows-comfort-support-support-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep---------- <description><![CDATA[Choosing the best pregnancy pillow involves considering shape, material, size, and ease of maintenance. Look for options providing full-body support, hypoallergenic materials, versatile sizes, and washable covers for optimal comfort.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-pillows-comfort-support-support-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep-sleep----------</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:19:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Finger Exercisers for Strength and Rehabilitation: Enhance Dexterity and Grip]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-finger-exercisers-sgent-rength-rehabilitation-enhance-dexterity-gexterity-gexterity-gexterity-gexterity-gexter-gexter-Grip-grip-grip-grip-grip-grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip <description><![CDATA[Finger exercisers improve hand strength, dexterity, and aid rehabilitation. They enhance grip, relieve stress, and prevent injuries. Ideal for athletes, musicians, and recovery, they come in various forms with adjustable resistance.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-finger-exercisers-sgent-rength-rehabilitation-enhance-dexterity-gexterity-gexterity-gexterity-gexterity-gexter-gexter-Grip-grip-grip-grip-grip-grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip-Grip</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:19:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Blister Bandages for Comfort, Protection, and Quick Healing]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-blister-bandages-comfort-protection-protection-quick-quick-healing-472696 <description><![CDATA[Blister Bandages are more than just a temporary fix—they are a vital tool for maintaining foot health and comfort. By understanding the types, uses, and selection criteria, you can ensure your feet remain protected and pain-free, whether you're walking, running, or exploring new terrains. Investing in quality blister pads is a small step towards a more comfortable and active lifestyle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-blister-bandages-comfort-protection-protection-quick-quick-healing-472696</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:18:18 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling with Muscle Pain? Try These Proven Oils &amp; Supplements for Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-muscle-pain-try-try-troven-iolf-soilf-supleief-relief-473184 <description><![CDATA[From soothing essential oils to nutrient-rich supplements that support recovery, there are plenty of science-backed options to help ease soreness and keep you moving]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/struggling-muscle-pain-try-try-troven-iolf-soilf-supleief-relief-473184</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:06:49 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Majority of US Baby Food Products Do Not Meet Nutrition Guidelines, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/majority-us-baby-food-products-do-no-meet-meet-guition-guition-guition-guition-guition-guition-guition-guidelines-guidelines-study-study-finds-4 <description><![CDATA[A new study found that 60% of the baby foods in the United States don't meet nutritional guidelines set by the World Health Organization.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/majority-us-baby-food-products-do-no-meet-meet-guition-guition-guition-guition-guition-guition-guition-guidelines-guidelines-study-study-finds-4</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:04:36 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eyeing A Sunny State For Retirement? You Might Experience Accelerated Aging]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eyeing-shunny-state-tate-retirement-you-might-experience-aceleration-acelerated-aging-4 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that living in hotter environments may accelerate the aging process.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eyeing-shunny-state-tate-retirement-you-might-experience-aceleration-acelerated-aging-4</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 04:53:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Know Your Breast Cancer Risk: Here Are States With Highest Risk For Young Woman]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-your-your-your-your-cancer-here-are-sher------------------------- your-are-are-are-are-are-tars-wight-wight-wight-young-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-Woman-Woman-Woman <description><![CDATA[A recent study has identified the states with highest and lowest risks of breast cancer in the U.S.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-your-your-your-your-cancer-here-are-sher------------------------- your-are-are-are-are-are-tars-wight-wight-wight-young-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-woman-Woman-Woman-Woman</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 02:50:58 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Belly Fat Protect Your Brain Health? It Depends—Here's Who Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-belly-protect-your-brain-he-he-he-he dippersheres-who-beenfits-473180 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that belly fat may support brain health earlier in life, however, this protective effect diminishes with age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-belly-protect-your-brain-he-he-he-he dippersheres-who-beenfits-473180</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Feb 2025 01:31:20 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Utah Set to Eliminate Fluoride in Water After RFK Calls Cavity Fighter 'Industrial Waste']]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/utah-set-eliminate-fluoride-water-after-rfk-cavity-cavity-cavity-cavity-cavity-fighter-fighter-waste-473177777777777 <description><![CDATA[Utah may become the first U.S. state to ban the addition of fluoride to public drinking water, following the passage of a bill by the state Senate on Friday.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/utah-set-eliminate-fluoride-water-after-rfk-cavity-cavity-cavity-cavity-cavity-fighter-fighter-waste-473177777777777</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:17:30 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Says Measles Outbreak Is 'Not Unusual' Despite Texas Child Marking First Death in a Decade]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rfk-jr-says-measles爆发not-not-uspite-dspite-dspite-texas-child-mark-marking-deph-dept-dept-deptecade-decade-decade-473174 <description><![CDATA[Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. acknowledged the measles outbreak in Texas on Wednesday, emphasizing that the US sees multiple outbreaks each year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rfk-jr-says-measles爆发not-not-uspite-dspite-dspite-texas-child-mark-marking-deph-dept-dept-deptecade-decade-decade-473174</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:10:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unvaccinated Child Becomes First in a Decade to Die of Measles as Texas Outbreak Grows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unvacined-child-becomes-first decade-decade-die-measles-texas爆炸爆发-4 <description><![CDATA[A measles outbreak in rural West Texas has claimed the life of an unvaccinated child, marking the first U.S. measles-related death since 2015.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unvacined-child-becomes-first decade-decade-die-measles-texas爆炸爆发-4</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:01:54 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>