<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Golfers More Vulnerable To Skin Cancer Than Others, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/golfers-more-vulnerable-skin-cancer-others-study-says-470624 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say golfers face a nearly 250% higher risk of developing skin cancer than non-players.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/golfers-more-vulnerable-skin-cancer-others-study-says-470624</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 05:27:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Aroma To Boost Memory? Study Says Exposure To Fragrances During Sleep Can Improve Brain Function]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aroma-boost-memory-study-says-exposure-fragrances-during-sleep-can-improve-brain-function-470621 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found infusing aroma in the bedrooms of older adults for two hours each night resulted in significant improvements in their memory.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aroma-boost-memory-study-says-exposure-fragrances-during-sleep-can-improve-brain-function-470621</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:07:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleeping Late, Oversleeping During Weekends Could Be Harmful For Your Gut Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleeping-late-oversleeping-during-weekends-could-harmful-your-gut-health-470619 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found a link between "social jet lag" and gut health. It shows irregular sleep patterns can harm gut health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleeping-late-oversleeping-during-weekends-could-harmful-your-gut-health-470619</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 02:50:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Beer Tanning: Expert Warns Viral Trend Could Lead To Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beer-tanning-expert-warns-viral-trend-could-lead-cancer-470617 <description><![CDATA[As beer tanning is gaining popularity on social media, a health expert cautions people about the skin damage it can bring along.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beer-tanning-expert-warns-viral-trend-could-lead-cancer-470617</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 01:13:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Success Stories: Inspiring Testimonials of Med Students Who Achieved Residency Dreams with Dr. Michael Everest]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/success-stories-inspiring-testimonials-med-students-who-achieved-residency-dreams-dr-michael-470612 <description><![CDATA[Securing a medical residency position is a dream countless aspiring doctors cherish.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/success-stories-inspiring-testimonials-med-students-who-achieved-residency-dreams-dr-michael-470612</guid><pubDate> Sun, 06 Aug 2023 22:16:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Simple Yoga May Prevent Memory Loss In Women At Risk Of Alzheimer's: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-yoga-may-prevent-memory-loss-women-risk-alzheimers-study-470608 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that Kundalini yoga can be used as a preventive technique to ward off Alzheimer's in aging women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-yoga-may-prevent-memory-loss-women-risk-alzheimers-study-470608</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Aug 2023 04:22:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Flea-Borne Typhus Led To 3 Deaths In LA County; Know Symptoms, Ways To Prevent Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flea-borne-typhus-led-3-deaths-la-county-know-symptoms-ways-prevent-disease-470607 <description><![CDATA[Although rarely fatal, flea-borne typhus was associated with three deaths in Los Angeles County last year, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flea-borne-typhus-led-3-deaths-la-county-know-symptoms-ways-prevent-disease-470607</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Aug 2023 02:55:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mothers' Diet During Pregnancy Can Protect Brain Health Of Her Grandchildren; Researchers Explain How]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mothers-diet-during-pregnancy-can-protect-brain-health-her-grandchildren-researchers-explain-how-470606 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that a woman's diet during early pregnancy, especially the consumption of apples and herbs, can protect the brain health of her children and grandchildren.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mothers-diet-during-pregnancy-can-protect-brain-health-her-grandchildren-researchers-explain-how-470606</guid><pubDate> Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:56:49 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 10 Best Air Purifiers Of 2023]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-air-purifiers-2023-470590 <description><![CDATA[Discover the top-rated air purifiers of 2023, featuring cutting-edge technology and exceptional performance to ensure cleaner and healthier indoor air.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-10-best-air-purifiers-2023-470590</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:42:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[8 Best Eye Health Supplements: How These Essential Nutrients Support, Improve Vision]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-best-eye-health-supplements-how-这些-essential- Nutritions-support-improve-vision-470589 <description><![CDATA[Whether you are looking to preserve your vision or address specific eye concerns, these carefully curated supplements are here to enhance and protect your eyesight in the year 2023.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/8-best-eye-health-supplements-how-这些-essential- Nutritions-support-improve-vision-470589</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:11:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hookworms Can Improve Insulin Resistance In Diabetes Patients, Clinical Trial Shows]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hookworms-can-improve-insulin-resistance-diabetes-病人-clinical-tri-shows-470605 <description><![CDATA[A human trial that involves infecting people with live hookworms has proven beneficial for patients at risk of type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hookworms-can-improve-insulin-resistance-diabetes-病人-clinical-tri-shows-470605</guid><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:10:01 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>