<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Your Cells Inherit Energy From Mother; Study Offers Insights On Mitochondrial Disorders]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-cells-inherit-energy-mother-study-offers-insights-mitochondrial-disorders-472522 <description><![CDATA[The researchers discovered that humans inherit the DNA inside their mitochondria from their mothers alone, with all traces of their father's mitochondrial genome destroyed the moment sperm joins the egg.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-cells-inherit-energy-mother-study-offers-insights-mitochondrial-disorders-472522</guid><pubDate> Fri, 11 Oct 2024 01:26:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Residency Success: Key Tools and Strategies Residents Medical Provides for Aspiring Doctors Facing OSCE and Beyond]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/residency-success-key-tools-strategies-residents-medical-provides-aspiring-doctors-faceing-osce-472521 <description><![CDATA[Residents Medical gives international doctors that fair chance by offering personalized guidance, test preparation help, educational resources, and even real-world clinical placements to help maximize medical graduates' chances of securing a residency.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/residency-success-key-tools-strategies-residents-medical-provides-aspiring-doctors-faceing-osce-472521</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:38:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI-Powered Automation: The Lifeline Reviving Physicians' Shrinking Revenues]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-powered-automation-lifeline-reviving-physicals-shrinking-revenues-472519 <description><![CDATA[Unlike traditional manual processes, AI-powered solutions can drastically improve efficiency in the medical billing cycle. AI can identify patterns in denied claims, correct common errors, and even predict the likelihood of claim approval.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ai-powered-automation-lifeline-reviving-physicals-shrinking-revenues-472519</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:34:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Doubles Risk Of Heart Attacks, Strokes For Up To Three Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-doubles-risk-heart-attacks-中风-三年-study-472517 <description><![CDATA[The cardiovascular risk is significantly higher for those hospitalized with severe COVID and individuals with a preexisting history of heart disease, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-doubles-risk-heart-attacks-中风-三年-study-472517</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Oct 2024 03:04:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eating Less Extends Lifespan, But Those With Least Weight Loss Have Maximum Benefits: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-less-extends-lifespan-those-least-weight-loss-have-maximum-benefits-study-472516 <description><![CDATA[Researchers explored how eating less could extend lifespan and discovered that those who experienced the least weight loss while eating less had the greatest longevity benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-less-extends-lifespan-those-least-weight-loss-have-maximum-benefits-study-472516</guid><pubDate> Thu, 10 Oct 2024 01:35:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Weighing Machines For Accurate Health Tracking: Top Features To Consider]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-weighing-machines-accurate-health-tracking-top-features-consider-472461 <description><![CDATA[Investing in a weighing machine can be a significant step towards achieving your health and fitness goals. By understanding the different types of scales available and considering your individual needs, you can choose the right machine to help you monitor your weight and body composition effectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-weighing-machines-accurate-health-tracking-top-features-consider-472461</guid><pubDate> Wed, 09 Oct 2024 15:17:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Indoor Air Purifiers To Remove Pollutants, Smoke And Other Allergens]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-indoor-air-purifiers-remove-pollutants-smoke-other-allergens-472456 <description><![CDATA[Long-term exposure to air pollutants such as fine particulate matter increases the risk of respiratory illnesses, cardiovascular diseases, and cancers. In 2020, household air pollution was responsible for an estimated 3.2 million deaths per year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-indoor-air-purifiers-remove-pollutants-smoke-other-allergens-472456</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Oct 2024 13:55:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Screen Use In 9- And 10-Year-Olds Elevates Risk Of Depression, Anxiety, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/screen-use-9-10-year-olds-elevates-risk-depression-anxiety-study-says-472514 <description><![CDATA[The study found that each additional hour of screen time correlated with a 10% increase in depressive symptoms, a 7% increase in conduct symptoms, and a 6% increase in somatic symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/screen-use-9-10-year-olds-elevates-risk-depression-anxiety-study-says-472514</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Oct 2024 04:13:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Warns: These Incorrect Arm Positions Often Lead To Overestimated Blood Pressure Readings]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-warns-these-in Correct-arm-positions-often-lead-overestimated-blood-Pressure-readings-472511 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that incorrect positioning often leads to inflated blood pressure readings, potentially misdiagnosing millions of Americans with hypertension.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-warns-these-in Correct-arm-positions-often-lead-overestimated-blood-Pressure-readings-472511</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Oct 2024 02:43:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eggs Or Toast? Breakfast For Weight Loss Depends On Your Gender]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eggs-toast-breakfast-weight-loss-depends-your-gender-472510 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered that when it comes to breaking down meals after fasting for hours, men respond better to carbs, while women manage fat more effectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eggs-toast-breakfast-weight-loss-depends-your-gender-472510</guid><pubDate> Tue, 08 Oct 2024 01:16:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fall-Proof Your Health: Essential Household Items For A Wellness Boost]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fall-proof-your-health-essential-household-items-wellness-boost-472503 <description><![CDATA[Simple practices such as dressing for the weather, using a humidifier, and taking time to de-stress will enhance your body's resilience during the fall season]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fall-proof-your-health-essential-household-items-wellness-boost-472503</guid><pubDate> Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:03:00 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>