<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Evolution of Psychedelic Therapy in Mental Health and Spirituality]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/evolution-psychedelic-therapy-mental-health-spirituality-471665 <description><![CDATA[Matt Zemon's work contributes to the broader discussion on mental health treatment, the use of psychedelics in ceremonial contexts, and the acceptance of alternative therapies.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/evolution-psychedelic-therapy-mental-health-spirituality-471665</guid><pubDate> Sat, 20 Apr 2024 04:48:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Thatch.ai's Game-Changing Healthcare Solutions Empower Workforce Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/thatchais-game-changing-healthcare-solutions-empower-workforce-wellness-471663 <description><![CDATA[Rooted in the fundamental belief of equalizing access to quality healthcare, Thatch is on a mission to simplify and personalize the healthcare journey for employees across diverse industries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/thatchais-game-changing-healthcare-solutions-empower-workforce-wellness-471663</guid><pubDate> Sat, 20 Apr 2024 04:44:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Best Korean Sunscreens For 2024: Build Your Dream Skincare Regimen]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-korean-sunscreens-build-your-dream-skincare-regimen-471624 <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of Korean sunscreen, where skincare meets innovation! Let's explore why the best Korean sunscreens are taking the beauty world by storm, offering a powerful shield against harmful UV rays while keeping your skin feeling pampered.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-korean-sunscreens-build-your-dream-skincare-regimen-471624</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:52:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salmonella Infections Linked To Contaminated Basil Sold At Trader Joe's, CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-infections-linked-contaminate-basil-sold-trader-joes-cdc-warns-471659 <description><![CDATA[The CDC has received reports of 12 Salmonella infections in seven states.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-infections-linked-contaminate-basil-sold-trader-joes-cdc-warns-471659</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:05:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Surge in Newborn Syphilis Cases Prompts Call For More Screening During Pregnancy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surge-newborn-syphilis-cases-prompts-call-more-screening-during-pregnancy-471657 <description><![CDATA[As per the updated recommendation from ACOG, pregnant individuals should be screened for syphilis three times during pregnancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/surge-newborn-syphilis-cases-prompts-call-more-screening-during-pregnancy-471657</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:50:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Metabolic Health At Time Of Vaccination Decides Effectiveness Of Flu Shots: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-health-time-vaccination-decides-effectness-flu-shots-study-471655 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that switching obese mice to a healthy diet before flu vaccination completely protected them from a lethal dose of flu, despite their BMI (Body Mass Index). However, changing the diet after vaccination did not help.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-health-time-vaccination-decides-effectness-flu-shots-study-471655</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:23:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultimate Comfort and Protection: Knowing The Importance of Blister Patches]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultimate-comfort-protection-knowing-importance-blister-patches-471642 <description><![CDATA[We explore the significance of blister patches in alleviating discomfort and preventing further irritation caused by footwear among active individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultimate-comfort-protection-knowing-importance-blister-patches-471642</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:42:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hypertension Raises Uterine Fibroid Risk, Blood Pressure Medication Can Help Minimize It: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hypertension-raises-uterine-纤维瘤-风险-血液-压力-药物-can-help-minimize-it-study-471653 <description><![CDATA[Recent research has identified another risk linked to hypertension in women: an increased likelihood of developing uterine fibroids.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hypertension-raises-uterine-纤维瘤-风险-血液-压力-药物-can-help-minimize-it-study-471653</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Apr 2024 05:11:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Make Brains Work Hard At Job: Study Says It Guards Against Memory Issues Later]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/make-brains-work-hard-job-study-says-it-guards-against-memory-issues-later-471651 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that actively engaging your brain in your profession can lower your risk of experiencing memory and cognitive issues as you age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/make-brains-work-hard-job-study-says-it-guards-against-memory-issues-later-471651</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Apr 2024 03:41:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Quitting Smoking During Pregnancy Causes Weight Gain, But Benefits Outweigh: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quitting-smoking-during-pregnancy-causes-weight-gain-benefits-outweigh-study-471650 <description><![CDATA[The advantages of quitting outweigh the risks associated with ongoing smoking, such as stillbirths and premature deliveries, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quitting-smoking-during-pregnancy-causes-weight-gain-benefits-outweigh-study-471650</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Apr 2024 02:16:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[19 Botched Botox Cases Reported Across 9 States: CDC, FDA Investigate]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/19-botched-botox-cases-reported-across-9-states-cdc-fda-investigate-471648 <description><![CDATA[Officials said that all the incidents involved women who reported sick following the administration of counterfeit Botox injections of AbbVie or those who received injections from unlicensed or untrained individuals in non-healthcare environments.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/19-botched-botox-cases-reported-across-9-states-cdc-fda-investigate-471648</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Apr 2024 05:08:41 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>