<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Nighttime Exposure To Bright Light May Raise Diabetes Risk]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/nighttime-exposure-bright-light-may-raise-diabetes-risk-471901 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that exposure to light between 12:30 a.m. and 6 a.m., is linked to a 67% increased risk of developing diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nighttime-exposure-bright-light-may-raise-diabetes-risk-471901</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jun 2024 05:39:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teens Struggling With Mental Abilities Face Triple Risk Of Stroke By Age 50: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-struggling-mental-bility-face-triple-risk-中风-age-50-study-471900 <description><![CDATA[Teens with poor concentration, problem-solving, and learning abilities are at a heightened risk of early-onset stroke, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/teens-struggling-mental-bility-face-triple-risk-中风-age-50-study-471900</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jun 2024 05:31:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Protect Yourself With Updated COVID, Flu Vaccines Amid Surging Cases: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/protect-yourself-updated-covid-flu-vaccines-amid-surging-cases-cdc-471898 <description><![CDATA[The CDC recommends taking updated COVID and flu vaccines for the upcoming fall and winter seasons to protect against severe outcomes, including hospitalization and death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/protect-yourself-updated-covid-flu-vaccines-amid-surging-cases-cdc-471898</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:58:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sitting For Long? Drinking Coffee May Help Offset Mortality Risk]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/sitting-long-drinking-coffee-may-help-offset-mortality-risk-471895 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now suggest that drinking coffee might counteract the mortality risk linked to prolonged sitting.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sitting-long-drinking-coffee-may-help-offset-mortality-risk-471895</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jun 2024 05:22:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily Intake Of Multivitamins May Not Improve Longevity In Healthy Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-intake-multivitamins-may-not-improve-longevity-healthy-adults-study-471894 <description><![CDATA[A large-scale study revealed that for healthy adults, daily multivitamin intake does not extend longevity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-intake-multivitamins-may-not-improve-longevity-healthy-adults-study-471894</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jun 2024 05:08:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Active Lifestyle With Moderate Exercise May Reduce Risk Of ALS In Men: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/active-lifestyle-moderate-exercise-may-reduce-risk-als-men-study-471891 <description><![CDATA[Maintaining an active lifestyle with moderate physical activity and fitness may reduce the risk of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) in men, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/active-lifestyle-moderate-exercise-may-reduce-risk-als-men-study-471891</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jun 2024 04:01:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Warns Of Increased Risk Of Dengue Infections: Know Symptoms, Steps For Prevention]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-increased-risk-dengue-infections-know-symptoms-steps-prevention-471890 <description><![CDATA[Healthcare providers are advised to remain highly vigilant for dengue in patients presenting with fever and a recent travel history to regions with frequent or continuous dengue transmission.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-warns-increased-risk-dengue-infections-know-symptoms-steps-prevention-471890</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:55:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Oral Health Month: Dental Expert Shares Teeth Brushing Techniques For Radiant Smile]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-oral-health-month-dental-expert-shares-teeth-brushing-techniques-radiant-smile-471889 <description><![CDATA[During this National Oral Health Month, a leading dental expert shares the secrets to improved oral hygiene through effective teeth-brushing techniques.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-oral-health-month-dental-expert-shares-teeth-brushing-techniques-radiant-smile-471889</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:50:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People With Anxiety At Double Risk Of Parkinson's Disease: Study]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-anxiety-double-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-471888 <description><![CDATA[There is a two-fold increased risk of Parkinson's disease in the anxiety group compared to the control group, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-anxiety-double-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-471888</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:45 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Loneliness May Raise Risk Of Stroke In Older Adults]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-may-raise-risk-中风-older-adults-471887 <description><![CDATA[A study discovered that elderly adults who experienced chronic loneliness had a 56% higher risk of stroke compared to those who consistently reported not being lonely.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-may-raise-risk-中风-older-adults-471887</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:57:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Underweight Babies At Higher Risk Of Complications If They Develop Obesity: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/underweight-babies-higher-risk-complications-if-they-develop-obesity-study-471886 <description><![CDATA[According to the study results published in the journal eBiomedicine, children born underweight face greater health risks if they develop obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/underweight-babies-higher-risk-complications-if-they-develop-obesity-study-471886</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:45:06 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>