<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Diagnosing Diabetes At Younger Age Increases Dementia Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diagnosing-diabetes-younger-age-increases-dementia-risk-study-472709 <description><![CDATA[With each year earlier a person is diagnosed with type 2 diabetes, their risk of developing dementia rises by 1.9%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/diagnosing-diabetes-younger-age-increases-dementia-risk-study-472709</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Nov 2024 02:08:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are BPA Alternatives Safe? Study Finds BPF And BPS May Pose Health Risks]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-bpa-alternatives-safe-study-finds-bpf-bps-may-pose-health-risks-472708 <description><![CDATA[New research reveals that BPF (bisphenol F)and BPS (bisphenol s), commonly used as BPA substitutes, may pose health risks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-bpa-alternatives-safe-study-finds-bpf-bps-may-pose-health-risks-472708</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Nov 2024 01:26:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Postpartum Depression Rates Doubled In A Decade, Prevalence 'High And Rising' In U.S.: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/postpartum-depression-rates-doubled-decade-prevalence-high-rising-us-study-472706 <description><![CDATA[The prevalence significantly rose from 9.4 percent in 2010 to 19 percent in 2021, with higher rates observed particularly among individuals with elevated pre-pregnancy body mass index.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/postpartum-depression-rates-doubled-decade-prevalence-high-rising-us-study-472706</guid><pubDate> Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:58:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Pills For Cardiovascular Diseases? They May Also Protect Against Dementia, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-pills-cardioangio-diseases-they-may-also-protect-against-dementia-study-says-472703 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that long-term use of cardiovascular drugs, especially when used in combination, may offer protection against dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-pills-cardioangio-diseases-they-may-also-protect-against-dementia-study-says-472703</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Nov 2024 04:55:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is 'Aeronutrients'? Researchers Say You Can Breathe In Nutrients And Vitamins]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-aero Nutritions-researchers-say-you-can-breathe- Nutritions-vitamins-472700 <description><![CDATA[A recent study investigated the concept of "aeronutrients" and the mechanisms by which they are absorbed for human health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-aero Nutritions-researchers-say-you-can-breathe- Nutritions-vitamins-472700</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Nov 2024 03:08:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Avoid Late, Heavy Dinners: They Affect More Than Just Your Weight]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-late-heavy-dinners-they-affect-more-just-your-weight-472697 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that having heavy meals late in the evening can have harmful effects, even for those without weight issues.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/avoid-late-heavy-dinners-they-affect-more-just-your-weight-472697</guid><pubDate> Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:11:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hot Cocoa, Green Tea With Fatty Meals May Combat Negative Effects Of Stress: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hot-cocoa-green-tea-fatty-meals-may-combat-negative-effects-stress-study-472694 <description><![CDATA[The study investigated how flavanols, when consumed with fat, can help reduce the negative effects of fat on stress-related problems in endothelial function.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hot-cocoa-green-tea-fatty-meals-may-combat-negative-effects-stress-study-472694</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Nov 2024 04:43:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Links COVID-19 To Tumor Regression, Opens New Venue For Cancer Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-links-covid-19-tumor-regression-opens-new-venue-cancer-treatment-472692 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that RNA from the SARS-CoV-2 virus may trigger the development of immune cells with anti-cancer properties.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-links-covid-19-tumor-regression-opens-new-venue-cancer-treatment-472692</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Nov 2024 02:30:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Multistate E-Coli Outbreak Linked To Organic Carrots Claims One Life, Sickens Dozens: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multistate-e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-carrots-claims-one-life-sickens-dozens-cdc-472691 <description><![CDATA[The current multistate outbreak, identified since September, is linked to multiple brands of recalled organic bagged carrots, including whole and baby carrots sold by Grimmway Farms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multistate-e-coli-outbreak-linked-organic-carrots-claims-one-life-sickens-dozens-cdc-472691</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Nov 2024 01:02:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Every Extra Hour Of Walking In Your 40's Adds Time To Lifespan: Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/every-extra-hour-walking-your-40s-adds-time-lifespan-study-suggests-472689 <description><![CDATA[The study found that on average, every extra hour of walking in your 40s adds around 3 hours (169 minutes) to lifespan.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/every-extra-hour-walking-your-40s-adds-time-lifespan-study-suggests-472689</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Nov 2024 05:17:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Screen Time Triggers Early Puberty, Rapid Bone Growth, Potentially Limiting Height: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-triggers-early-puberty-rapid-bone-growth-pottially-limiting-height-study-472687 <description><![CDATA[The results of the rat study highlight how exposure to screens from a very young age affects children's height and physical maturity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-triggers-early-puberty-rapid-bone-growth-pottially-limiting-height-study-472687</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:54:33 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>