<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA['Long-Flu': People Hospitalized With Seasonal Influenza May Suffer Negative Health Effects Similar To Long-COVID]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-flu-people-hospitalized-seasonal-influenza-may-suffer-negative-health-effects-similar-471196 <description><![CDATA[The study showed that patients hospitalized with flu or COVID-19 had an increased risk of death, hospital readmission and issues to multiple organs in the months following the infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-flu-people-hospitalized-seasonal-influenza-may-suffer-negative-health-effects-similar-471196</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:12:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Many Mothers And Their Children Share Same Birthday Month; Here's Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/many-mothers-their-children-share-same-birthday-month-heres-why-471195 <description><![CDATA[A study suggests that women are more likely to have children in the same month as their birth, and births within immediate families tend to cluster within a given month.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/many-mothers-their-children-share-same-birthday-month-heres-why-471195</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:59:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Menstrual Cycles Intensify Suicidal Thoughts In People Struggling With Mental Health, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/menstrual-cycles-intensify-suicidal-thoughts-people-struggling-mental-health-study-says-471194 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that women with suicidal thoughts may face an increased risk of ideation or planning of suicide in the days around menstruation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/menstrual-cycles-intensify-suicidal-thoughts-people-struggling-mental-health-study-says-471194</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Dec 2023 23:32:08 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People Who Have Anxiety About Illnesses May Be At Greater Risk Of Death; Know Signs Of Hypochondriasis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-who-have-anxiety-about-illnesses-may-greater-risk-death-know-signs-hypochondriasis-471193 <description><![CDATA[Health anxiety, or hypochondriasis, is an extremely rare anxiety disorder that causes unrealistic fear in people about illnesses.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-who-have-anxiety-about-illnesses-may-greater-risk-death-know-signs-hypochondriasis-471193</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Dec 2023 06:22:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dengue Fever: Millions Infected Worldwide As Rising Temperatures Cause Virus To Flare]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dengue-fever-millions-infected-worldwide-rising-temporals-cause-virus-flare-471192 <description><![CDATA[Around five million cases of dengue fever and 5,500 deaths have been reported across 20 countries in 2023, the highest ever since record-keeping began in 1980.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dengue-fever-millions-infected-worldwide-rising-temporals-cause-virus-flare-471192</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Dec 2023 02:50:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fetal Alcohol Syndrome: Researchers Say Men Should Abstain From Drinking At Least 3 Months Before Conceiving]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fetal-alcohol-syndrome-researchers-say-men-should-abstain-drinking-least-3-months-before-471191 <description><![CDATA[The effect of paternal drinking on the sperm lasts much longer than expected, a new study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fetal-alcohol-syndrome-researchers-say-men-should-abstain-drinking-least-3-months-before-471191</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:52:59 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Holiday Heart Syndrome? Know Symptoms, Steps For Prevention]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-holiday-heart-syndrome-know-symptoms-steps-prevention-471190 <description><![CDATA[Holiday heart syndrome is a heart condition that causes atrial fibrillation or irregular heartbeat after excessive alcohol consumption or binge drinking.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-holiday-heart-syndrome-know-symptoms-steps-prevention-471190</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:42:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Respiratory Illnesses Surging In US; 15 States See 'High' Or 'Very High' Levels, CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/respiratory-illnesses-surge-us-15-states-see-high-very-high-levels-cdc-warns-471189 <description><![CDATA[The U.S Centers for Disease Control and Prevention warns of a surge in respiratory illnesses across the country, with 15 states facing "high" or "very high" levels of infections, including flu, COVID-19, RSV and common cold.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/respiratory-illnesses-surge-us-15-states-see-high-very-high-levels-cdc-warns-471189</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Dec 2023 02:42:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Siblings Of Dementia Patients May Face Risk Of Shortened Lifespan, Even If They Are Not Diagnosed]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/siblings-dementia-病人-may-face-risk-shortened-lifespan-even-if-they-are-not-diagnosed-471188 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that a combination of genetics and environmental factors reduces longevity in dementia patients. The same combination may shorten the lives of their siblings even without dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/siblings-dementia-病人-may-face-risk-shortened-lifespan-even-if-they-are-not-diagnosed-471188</guid><pubDate> Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:53:18 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Wasabi For Cognitive Health? Researchers Say It Could Improve Memory]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/wasabi-cognitive-health-researchers-say-it-could-improve-memory-471187 <description><![CDATA[In a trial conducted in a small group of healthy participants above the age of 60, researchers found a "significant improvement" in short-term and long-term memory with the use of a supplement containing 6-MSITC, the main bioactive compound found in wasabi.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/wasabi-cognitive-health-researchers-say-it-could-improve-memory-471187</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 06:06:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[WHO Warns Of Anthrax Outbreaks In 5 African Countries; Know Symptoms, Risk Factors Of Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/who-warns-anthrax-outbreaks-5-african-countries-know-symptoms-risk-factors-infection-471186 <description><![CDATA[Five countries in east and southern Africa are witnessing anthrax outbreaks, with more than 1,100 suspected cases and 20 related deaths reported this year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/who-warns-anthrax-outbreaks-5-african-countries-know-symptoms-risk-factors-infection-471186</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 02:34:51 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>