<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Metabolic Health At Time Of Vaccination Decides Effectiveness Of Flu Shots: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-health-time-vaccination-decides-effectness-flu-shots-study-471655 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that switching obese mice to a healthy diet before flu vaccination completely protected them from a lethal dose of flu, despite their BMI (Body Mass Index). However, changing the diet after vaccination did not help.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metabolic-health-time-vaccination-decides-effectness-flu-shots-study-471655</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:23:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultimate Comfort and Protection: Knowing The Importance of Blister Patches]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultimate-comfort-protection-knowing-importance-blister-patches-471642 <description><![CDATA[We explore the significance of blister patches in alleviating discomfort and preventing further irritation caused by footwear among active individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultimate-comfort-protection-knowing-importance-blister-patches-471642</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:42:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hypertension Raises Uterine Fibroid Risk, Blood Pressure Medication Can Help Minimize It: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hypertension-raises-uterine-纤维瘤-风险-血液-压力-药物-can-help-minimize-it-study-471653 <description><![CDATA[Recent research has identified another risk linked to hypertension in women: an increased likelihood of developing uterine fibroids.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hypertension-raises-uterine-纤维瘤-风险-血液-压力-药物-can-help-minimize-it-study-471653</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Apr 2024 05:11:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Make Brains Work Hard At Job: Study Says It Guards Against Memory Issues Later]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/make-brains-work-hard-job-study-says-it-guards-against-memory-issues-later-471651 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that actively engaging your brain in your profession can lower your risk of experiencing memory and cognitive issues as you age.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/make-brains-work-hard-job-study-says-it-guards-against-memory-issues-later-471651</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Apr 2024 03:41:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Quitting Smoking During Pregnancy Causes Weight Gain, But Benefits Outweigh: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quitting-smoking-during-pregnancy-causes-weight-gain-benefits-outweigh-study-471650 <description><![CDATA[The advantages of quitting outweigh the risks associated with ongoing smoking, such as stillbirths and premature deliveries, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/quitting-smoking-during-pregnancy-causes-weight-gain-benefits-outweigh-study-471650</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Apr 2024 02:16:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[19 Botched Botox Cases Reported Across 9 States: CDC, FDA Investigate]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/19-botched-botox-cases-reported-across-9-states-cdc-fda-investigate-471648 <description><![CDATA[Officials said that all the incidents involved women who reported sick following the administration of counterfeit Botox injections of AbbVie or those who received injections from unlicensed or untrained individuals in non-healthcare environments.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/19-botched-botox-cases-reported-across-9-states-cdc-fda-investigate-471648</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Apr 2024 05:08:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stress During Adolescence May Up The Risk Of Postpartum Depression In Adulthood: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-during-adolescent-may-risk-postpartum-depression-adulthood-study-471644 <description><![CDATA[Based on the findings of a rat study, researchers suggest that early life stress could contribute to the worsening of postpartum depression from a pathophysiological standpoint.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stress-during-adolescent-may-risk-postpartum-depression-adulthood-study-471644</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Apr 2024 03:48:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Junk Food Diet In Teens May Lead To Long-Term Memory Damage: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/junk-food-diet-teens-may-lead-long-term-memory-damage-study-471640 <description><![CDATA[A high-fat, high-sugar diet in teenagers may lead to long-term memory damage, according to the results of a rat study conducted by researchers from the University of Southern California.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/junk-food-diet-teens-may-lead-long-term-memory-damage-study-471640</guid><pubDate> Wed, 17 Apr 2024 01:58:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exercise Lowers Heart Disease Risk By Reducing Stress; Depression Patients At Greater Benefits: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-lowers-heart-disease-risk-reducing-stress-depression-fighters-greater-benefits-study-471639 <description><![CDATA[People with stress-related conditions such as depression reap the most cardiovascular benefits from physical activity, according to the latest study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exercise-lowers-heart-disease-risk-reducing-stress-depression-fighters-greater-benefits-study-471639</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Apr 2024 03:33:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong Reports First Human B Virus Case: Know All About Deadly Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hong-kong-reports-first- human-b-virus-case-know-all-about-deadly-infection-471637 <description><![CDATA[The monkey B virus is an extremely rare infection that could lead to severe brain damage or death in humans.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hong-kong-reports-first- human-b-virus-case-know-all-about-deadly-infection-471637</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Apr 2024 02:29:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pressure To Lose Weight In Teens Linked To 'Internalized' Weight Stigma Later: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-Pressure-teens-tied-internalized-weight-stigma-later-study-471635 <description><![CDATA[People who were bullied, teased, and pressured to lose weight during their teenage years by family and media may develop internalized weight stigma by the age of 31, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-Pressure-teens-tied-internalized-weight-stigma-later-study-471635</guid><pubDate> Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:48:33 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>