<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Best High-Quality Digital Stethoscope To Unlock The Pulse Of Perfection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-high-quality-digital-stethscope-unlock-pulse-perfection-470463 <description><![CDATA[The revolutionary EKO Digital Stethoscope combines cutting-edge technology with the trusted quality of the Littmann brand.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-high-quality-digital-stethscope-unlock-pulse-perfection-470463</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:47:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unveiling The 5 Perfect Gifts For Medical Professionals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unveiling-5-perfect-gifts-medical-professionals-470461 <description><![CDATA[Discover the ideal gift for medical professionals with this carefully curated selection of thoughtful and practical presents that express gratitude and appreciation for their dedicated service.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unveiling-5-perfect-gifts-medical-professionals-470461</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:57:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Gregory Crichlow on Life with Purpose and Fulfilling the Barbadian Dream Through His Work at AvantBlue]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-gregory-crichlow-life- Purpose-fulfilling-barbadian-dream-through-his-work-avantblue-470599 <description><![CDATA[In 2021, the average life expectancy decreased from 79 years in 2019 to only 77, registering the largest decrease over a two-year span since the 1920s.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dr-gregory-crichlow-life- Purpose-fulfilling-barbadian-dream-through-his-work-avantblue-470599</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:32:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rev Up Your Productivity: Stay Active At Work With These Top 5 Desk Pedal Devices]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rev-your-productivity-stay-active-work-这些-top-5-desk-pedal-devices-470392 <description><![CDATA[These 5 nifty devices offer a convenient solution to engage your body and mind, all from the comfort of your desk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rev-your-productivity-stay-active-work-这些-top-5-desk-pedal-devices-470392</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:16:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Lead Exposure Instills Criminal Instincts? Study Says People Exposed In Womb, Childhood Are At Higher Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lead-exposure-instils-criminal-instincts-study-says-people-expose-womb-childhood-are-higher-470596 <description><![CDATA[The latest study has found that lead exposure in the womb or in childhood increases the risk of criminal behavior in adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lead-exposure-instils-criminal-instincts-study-says-people-expose-womb-childhood-are-higher-470596</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 03:38:57 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kombucha Tea May Help Lower Blood Sugar Levels In Diabetes Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kombucha-tea-may-help-lower-blood-sugar-levels-diabetes-病人-470595 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that drinking a cup of kombucha daily for four weeks lowered average fasting blood glucose levels from 164 to 116 milligrams per deciliter in patients with type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kombucha-tea-may-help-lower-blood-sugar-levels-diabetes-病人-470595</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:03:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Leprosy Cases Surging In Florida; Know About The Symptoms, Treatment, How It Spreads]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/leprosy-cases-surging-florida-know-about-symptoms-treatment-how-it-spreads-470593 <description><![CDATA[According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), leprosy has become endemic in the southeastern United States.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/leprosy-cases-surging-florida-know-about-symptoms-treatment-how-it-spreads-470593</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:59:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch Out, Night Sweats May Be A Sign Of Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watch-out-night-sweats-may-sign-cancer-470587 <description><![CDATA[When night sweats happen very often even while sleeping in cool temperatures, it may be a sign of an underlying health condition such as cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watch-out-night-sweats-may-sign-cancer-470587</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 02:54:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Breastfeeding Week: Know The Problems Faced By Nursing Moms; Tips To Ease Discomforts]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-breastfeeding-week-know-problems-faced-nursing-moms-tips-ease-discomforts-470586 <description><![CDATA[Several issues during the initial stages of breastfeeding such as cracked nipples, breast engorgement and latching issues discourage mothers from continuing breastfeeding.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-breastfeeding-week-know-problems-faced-nursing-moms-tips-ease-discomforts-470586</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 01:43:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[2 Servings Of Strawberry Per Day Could Improve Heart And Brain Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/2-servings-strawberry-per-day-could-improve-heart-brain-health-470583 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has found that two servings of strawberries daily can improve heart and brain health and antioxidant capacity in older healthy adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/2-servings-strawberry-per-day-could-improve-heart-brain-health-470583</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 03:09:42 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Minutes Of Intense Daily Activity Could Reduce Cancer Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/4-minutes-intense-daily-activity-could-reduce-cancer-risk-study-470582 <description><![CDATA[For people who are unable to do regular exercise, even four minutes of intense physical activity daily could help cut down cancer risk by up to 32%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/4-minutes-intense-daily-activity-could-reduce-cancer-risk-study-470582</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 02:03:05 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>