<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Longer Breastfeeding Reduces Risk Of Asthma Via Healthy Microbiome In Gut, Nasal Cavity: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/longer-breastfeeding-reduces-risk-asthma-via-healthy-microbiome-gut-nasal-cavity-study-472408 <description><![CDATA[The researchers of the latest study underscore the importance of extended breastfeeding for respiratory health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/longer-breastfeeding-reduces-risk-asthma-via-healthy-microbiome-gut-nasal-cavity-study-472408</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 04:17:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Class Of Diabetes Drugs That Cuts Risk Of Dementia, Parkinson's Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-class-diabetes-drugs-that-c​​uts-risk-dementia-parkinsons-disease-472406 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that sodium-glucose cotransporter-2 (SGLT2) inhibitors may help reduce the risk of dementia and Parkinson's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-class-diabetes-drugs-that-c​​uts-risk-dementia-parkinsons-disease-472406</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:33:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fussy Eating In Toddlers Linked To Genetics, May Persist Into Early Adolescence: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fussy-eating-toddlers-linked-genics-may-persist-early-adolescent-study-472405 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that picky eating is largely influenced by genetics and children with such traits may continue the habit into early adolescence.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fussy-eating-toddlers-linked-genics-may-persist-early-adolescent-study-472405</guid><pubDate> Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:04:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Pulse Oximeters: Essential Tools For Monitoring Oxygen Levels And Heart Rate]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-pulse-oximeters-essential-tools-monitoring-oxygen-levels-heart-rate-472395 <description><![CDATA[Pulse oximeters are essential devices for monitoring blood oxygen saturation and heart rate. They are commonly used by individuals managing respiratory conditions, athletes tracking their performance, and those undergoing medical treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-pulse-oximeters-essential-tools-monitoring-oxygen-levels-heart-rate-472395</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:29:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Baby Strollers: Top Picks For Maximum Comfort And Safety On Every Stroll]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-baby-strollers-top-picks-maximum-comfort-safety-every-stroll-472351 <description><![CDATA[Strollers offer a range of benefits, including ensuring your child's safety and security while you stay busy, making baby transport easy and convenient, and providing extra storage for essentials. Many models, including jogging strollers, allow parents to exercise and enjoy the outdoors, and they are particularly useful for managing multiple children. With so many options available, choosing the right stroller can be overwhelming. This guide breaks down the benefits and offers tips to help you select the perfect stroller for comfort and convenience.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-baby-strollers-top-picks-maximum-comfort-safety-every-stroll-472351</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:26:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Neck Massager For Pain Relief: Effective Solutions For Soothing Muscle Tension And Stress]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-neck-massager-pain-relief- effective-solutions-soothing-muscle-tension-stress-472360 <description><![CDATA[Finding the right neck massager can make a significant difference in managing pain and relieving muscle tension. The best neck massagers are designed to target specific areas, offering effective solutions for alleviating neck pain, reducing stress, and improving overall comfort.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-neck-massager-pain-relief- effective-solutions-soothing-muscle-tension-stress-472360</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:23:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best White Noise Machines To Help You And Your Baby Sleep Peacefully]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-white-noise-machines-help-you-your-baby-sleep-peaceously-472359 <description><![CDATA[White Noise is essentially a type of broadband sound that has all the audible frequencies. Researchers claim that white noise helps people, including babies, fall asleep and improve the quality of their sleep.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-white-noise-machines-help-you-your-baby-sleep-peaceously-472359</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:19:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Balance Boards for Core Strength and Injury Prevention]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-balance-boards-core-strength-injury-prevention-472373 <description><![CDATA[Balance boards are tools for improving core strength, stability, and balance. They help enhance posture, prevent injuries, and improve athletic performance. Ideal for rehabilitation and fitness training, balance boards engage multiple muscle groups and improve coordination, making them a valuable addition to any exercise routine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-balance-boards-core-strength-injury-prevention-472373</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:16:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Acupuncture Pens For Targeted Pain Relief And Enhanced Wellness Therapy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-acupuncture-pens-targeted-pain-relief-enhanced-wellness-therapy-472358 <description><![CDATA[Acupuncture Pens provide needle-free acupuncture therapy, helping to relieve muscle tension, reduce pain, and enhance overall well-being. Ideal for at-home use, they offer a convenient way to target specific pain points and improve circulation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-acupuncture-pens-targeted-pain-relief-enhanced-wellness-therapy-472358</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:10:39 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Nurses Play A Key Role In Suicide Prevention]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-nurses-play-key-role-suicide-prevention-472404 <description><![CDATA[The rapport nurses develop with patients can play a crucial role in encouraging individuals to open up about their thoughts of self-harm.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-nurses-play-key-role-suicide-prevention-472404</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Sep 2024 14:59:35 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Are Medical Costs So High In The United States?]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-are-medical-costs-so-high-united-states-472402 <description><![CDATA[Administrative costs account for roughly 25% of total healthcare spending in the U.S. This includes expenses associated with billing, insurance processing, and compliance with regulations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/why-are-medical-costs-so-high-united-states-472402</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Sep 2024 14:20:08 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>