<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[World Stroke Day: Know Warning Signs, Steps To Prevent Brain Attack]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-行程-day-know-warning-signs-steps-prevent-brain-attack-471036 <description><![CDATA[This year's theme, "Together we are #Greater Than Stroke," focuses on preventing stroke by addressing the risk factors responsible for it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-行程-day-know-warning-signs-steps-prevent-brain-attack-471036</guid><pubDate> Sun, 29 Oct 2023 06:32:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Portfolio Diet? American Heart Association Recommends It To Reduce Heart Disease And Stroke Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-portfolio-diet-american-heart-association-recommends-it-reduce-heart-disease-中风-risk-471034 <description><![CDATA[A portfolio diet is a nutritional strategy that focuses on reducing LDL, or "bad" cholesterol, a leading risk factor for cardiovascular disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-portfolio-diet-american-heart-association-recommends-it-reduce-heart-disease-中风-risk-471034</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:56:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salmonella Outbreak In 22 States Linked To Fresh Diced Onions: Know Signs Of Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-22-states-linked-fresh-diced-onions-know-signs-of-infection-471032 <description><![CDATA[The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has issued a warning and recall notice for fresh diced onions linked to the outbreak.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-22-states-linked-fresh-diced-onions-know-signs-of-infection-471032</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Oct 2023 01:21:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[ADHD Awareness Month: Expert Dispels Common Misconceptions About The Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adhd-awareness-month-expert-dispels-common-misconceptions-about-condition-471029 <description><![CDATA[Attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder is often misunderstood and sometimes, people even fail to recognize it as a real disorder.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adhd-awareness-month-expert-dispels-common-misconceptions-about-condition-471029</guid><pubDate> Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:06:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Less Than 30 Minutes Of Daily Exercise May Offset Risk Of Death From Prolonged Sitting]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-30-minutes-daily-exercise-may-offset-risk-of-death-prolonged-sitting-471027 <description><![CDATA[Researchers suggest engaging in 20-25 minutes of physical activity every day could offset the death risk caused by a highly sedentary lifestyle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-30-minutes-daily-exercise-may-offset-risk-of-death-prolonged-sitting-471027</guid><pubDate> Wed, 25 Oct 2023 05:07:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Aerobic Exercise For Erectile Dysfunction? Study Says It Is Nearly As Effective As Viagra]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aerobic-exercise-erectile-dysfunction-study-says-it-nearly- effective-viagra-471025 <description><![CDATA[The participants who were given Viagra or Cialis showed an improvement of four to eight points on the IIEF-EF scale, while those on testosterone treatment improved by just two points.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/aerobic-exercise-erectile-dysfunction-study-says-it-nearly- effective-viagra-471025</guid><pubDate> Wed, 25 Oct 2023 03:03:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[E.Coli Outbreak In San Diego Leaves 7 Hospitalized: Know Symptoms, Causes Of Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ecoli-outbreak-san-diego-leaves-7-hospitalized-know-symptoms-causes-infection-471022 <description><![CDATA[Health officials said the outbreak has sickened at least 13 people in San Diego.  All cases were linked to dining at a local restaurant.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ecoli-outbreak-san-diego-leaves-7-hospitalized-know-symptoms-causes-infection-471022</guid><pubDate> Wed, 25 Oct 2023 01:38:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Heated Yoga For Depression? Study Says Symptoms Reduced In 2 Months With Around 10 Sessions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heated-yoga-depression-study-says-symptoms-reduced-2-months-around-10-sessions-471019 <description><![CDATA[The study indicates the possibility of using heated yoga as a viable treatment option for depression, as 44% of the participants who took up the sessions indicated signs of remission.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heated-yoga-depression-study-says-symptoms-reduced-2-months-around-10-sessions-471019</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:04:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Gut Fungi Linked To Severe COVID-19 Infection: Study Says They Cause Lasting Immune Changes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-gut-fungi-linked-to-severe-covid-19-infection-study-says-they-cause- permanent-immune-changes-471017 <description><![CDATA[Researchers identified that an abundance of fungi in the gut, particularly strains of Candida albicans yeast, could trigger an increase in immune cells, which could worsen lung damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-gut-fungi-linked-to-severe-covid-19-infection-study-says-they-cause- permanent-immune-changes-471017</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 02:43:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleeping Less Than 5 Hours Daily Raises Depression Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleeping-less-5-hours-daily-raises-depression-risk-while-reverse-chance-low-study-471016 <description><![CDATA[Sleeping less than five hours daily raises the risk of developing depression by 2.5 times, while the chance of developing poor sleep out of depression is only one-third, the study found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleeping-less-5-hours-daily-raises-depression-risk-while-reverse-chance-low-study-471016</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:53:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Preparing For Surgery? Study Suggests Walking Over 7,500 Steps Daily To Reduce Complications]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/preparing-surgery-study-suggests-walking-over-7500-steps-daily-reduce-complications-471013 <description><![CDATA[The study says walking more than 7500 steps daily during the preoperative period could cut the risk of complications by around half.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/preparing-surgery-study-suggests-walking-over-7500-steps-daily-reduce-complications-471013</guid><pubDate> Mon, 23 Oct 2023 05:14:04 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>