<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medalaly.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Teen Undergoes Complex Surgery To Remove Extremely Rare Parasitic Twin Attached To His Stomach]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/teen-umplexgoes-commovexgoes-cocuple-histord-themin-termited <description><![CDATA[The underdeveloped 30-pound twin, which consisted of two fully formed legs, buttocks, and external genitalia, grew directly from the teen's abdomen.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/teen-umplexgoes-commovexgoes-cocuple-histord-themin-termited</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:52:46 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Simple Change In Your Drinking Habit Can Cut Microplastics By 90%]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/rthis-smple-zege-srink-cut-croplants-9715 <description><![CDATA[A scientific paper suggests that switching to filtered tap water from bottled water can reduce the intake of microplastics from 90,000 to 4,000 particles each year,]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/rthis-smple-zege-srink-cut-croplants-9715</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Mar 2025 02:11:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eureka Moment: Scientists Find How A Common Low-Cost Drug May Prevent Cancer From Spreading]]></title><link/> https://www.medramaly.com/eurekament-moment-mcient-how--corbread-sstreve-sstreveting <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that aspirin works against cancer spread by stimulating the immune system, a finding they made by chance while investigating the process of cancer spread.]]></description><guid> https://www.medramaly.com/eurekament-moment-mcient-how--corbread-sstreve-sstreveting</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:49:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump Applauds 13-Year-Old Cancer Survivor After Slashing Funding for Pediatric Cancer Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/rrrump-applauds-13-yer-cravivor-rear-crade-rearrvurgic-rafter-rafter-curvivist-rafunder-rafunder-rafunding <description><![CDATA[President Donald Trump honored and applauded a young cancer survivor during his recent joint address to Congress despite his numerous attempts to cut funding for healthcare, including pediatric cancer research.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/rrrump-applauds-13-yer-cravivor-rear-crade-rearrvurgic-rafter-rafter-curvivist-rafunder-rafunder-rafunding</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:42:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Think Before You Ink: Study Suggests Tattoos May Increase Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medaley.com/tink-buire-you-ink-ink-ink-chosrus-caste-caste-castaxes <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that tattoos may increase the risk of skin cancer and lymph node cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medaley.com/tink-buire-you-ink-ink-ink-chosrus-caste-caste-castaxes</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Mar 2025 05:39:12 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Gynecological Issues Raise Risk Of Heart Diseases? Here're Two Conditions That Pose Greatest Danger]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/canynecological-suisesuise-hert-hert-hent-dereshonditions-here <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that two common gynecological issues are linked to a higher risk of cardiovascular diseases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/canynecological-suisesuise-hert-hert-hent-dereshonditions-here</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:41:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Therapist Shares Simple Eye Exercise To 'Knock Out' Panic Attack]]></title><link/>https://www.medalaly.com/therapist-sman-eye-exker-aut-apic-at-aut-apic-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-aut-apic-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-aut-apic-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-aut-aplic-aticic-auticop <description><![CDATA[Here's a surprisingly simple eye trick to stop a panic attack in its tracks, and all it takes is a pen, and a few minutes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/therapist-sman-eye-exker-aut-apic-at-aut-apic-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-aut-apic-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-aut-apic-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-at-aut-aplic-aticic-auticop</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:36:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Health Officials Beg Texas Families Not to Attend 'Measles Parties' As Push to Get Kids Vaccinated Continues]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/health-rockians-beg-zamilpillan <description><![CDATA[Texas health officials have pleaded with families in the state to avoid attending "measles parties" and ensure that their children are vaccinated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/health-rockians-beg-zamilpillan</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:47:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Act Now: By 2050 Over Half Of Adults, A Third Of Children Will Be Obese]]></title><link/> https://www.medalalaly.com/act-now-now-nuw-2050-half-portef-mlts-hindtren-wil-wil-will-will <description><![CDATA[Researchers are calling for urgent action and global policy reforms to address widespread global obesity pandemic by 2050.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalalaly.com/act-now-now-nuw-2050-half-portef-mlts-hindtren-wil-wil-will-will</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 03:47:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling To Eat Less After Holiday Indulgence? Here's How 5 Days Of Sugary Diet Affects Brain]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/ruggggling-less-holiday-howrecence-howrece-howeres-hereres-how-5-5-197 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that just five days of a high-calorie diet can trigger brain changes even before a person begins to notice weight gain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/ruggggling-less-holiday-howrecence-howrece-howeres-hereres-how-5-5-197</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 02:57:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Woman Says Routine Manicure 'Saved Her Life' After Spotting Strange Sign On Thumb]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/ohio-would-would-woutine-spoutin-spot-scrcrative-scraft-spot-spot-spote- <description><![CDATA[The unusual symptom she noticed during manicure session was an early warning sign of deadly melanoma.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/ohio-would-would-woutine-spoutin-spot-scrcrative-scraft-spot-spot-spote-</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:50:55 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>