<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>恩</language><item><title><![CDATA[China's Omission Of Cremation Data Raises Questions About COVID-19 Impact]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chinas-omission-of-cremation-data-raises-questions-about-covid-19-impact-470166 <description><![CDATA[The absence of data suggested that the number of excess deaths could be significant.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chinas-omission-of-cremation-data-raises-questions-about-covid-19-impact-470166</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:44:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Reveals Alarming Mortality Rates For COVID-Associated Fungal Infections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-alarming-mortality-rates-of-covid-associated-fungal-infections-470164 <description><![CDATA[A study uncovered alarming mortality rates among people who had COVID-associated fungal infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-reveals-alarming-mortality-rates-of-covid-associated-fungal-infections-470164</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:41:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Gut Bacteria Could Be Causing Endometriosis, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-gut-bacteria-could-cause-endometriosis-study-says-470163 <description><![CDATA[Research suggests antibiotics could target the bacteria associated with gut bacteria, affecting 10% of women and girls worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-gut-bacteria-could-cause-endometriosis-study-says-470163</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:38:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Overdose Deaths: Men In The US At Higher Risk Than Women, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/overdose-deaths-but-us-higher-risk-women-says-study-470156 <description><![CDATA[Men are 2-3 times more likely to die from drug overdose than women, according to Icahn School of Medicine and the U.S.  National Institute on Drug Abuse.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/overdose-deaths-but-us-higher-risk-women-says-study-470156</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:38:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fresh Veggies Day: 5 Healthy Greens To Include In Your Diet]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fresh-veggies-day-5-healthy-greens-include-your-diet-470160 <description><![CDATA[Fresh Veggies Day is observed on June 16 every year to encourage people to increase their daily intake of fresh vegetables and to recognize their nutritional role in boosting human health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fresh-veggies-day-5-healthy-greens-include-your-diet-470160</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:55:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Light Exercise After Concussion Reduces Healing Time: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/light-exercise-after-concussion-reduces-healing-time-study-470158 <description><![CDATA[The athletes who do light exercise within 48 hours of a concussion are more likely to resolve the symptoms than those who do not exercise.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/light-exercise-after-concussion-reduces-healing-time-study-470158</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 01:50:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Screen Time Might Damage Your Skin; Tips To Protect You From Blue Light]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/screen-time-might-damage-your-skin-tips-protect-you-blue-light-470154 <description><![CDATA[Limiting screen time and using sunscreens indoors can help reduce the damage caused by blue lights.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/screen-time-might-damage-your-skin-tips-protect-you-blue-light-470154</guid><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:25:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[China Faces Biowarfare Allegations Following Coronavirus Research Lab Exposé]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/china-faces-biowarfare-allegations-following-coronavirus-research-lab-expose-470153 <description><![CDATA[China faces renewed allegations suggesting a laboratory leak caused the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/china-faces-biowarfare-allegations-following-coronavirus-research-lab-expose-470153</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 23:24:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New COVID-19 Vaccine Update To Target Latest Variants, Here's Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-covid-19-vaccine-update-target-latest-variants-here-why-4<description><![CDATA[A vaccine overhaul is set to happen this fall.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-covid-19-vaccine-update-target-latest-variants-here-why-4</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 21:19:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eating Earlier In The Day: A Game-Changer For Blood Sugar Control?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-earlier-day-game-changer-blood-sugar-control-470147 <description><![CDATA[Consuming meals earlier in the day could be good for diabetic people.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-earlier-day-game-changer-blood-sugar-control-470147</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 21:13:51 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mpox Vaccination Amid Resurgence: Who Are Eligible?]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/pox-vaccination-amid-resurgence-who-are-eligible-470145 <description><![CDATA[Not everyone is eligible for the mpox vaccine, according to public health officials.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pox-vaccination-amid-resurgence-who-are-eligible-470145</guid><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:59:33 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>