<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Elderly Man Awarded Historic Damages After Clinic Allegedly Injects Him with Unnecessary 'Invasive' Penis Shots That Did Irreparable Harm]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/elderly-man-awarded-historic-damages-after-clinic-allegedly-injects-him-unnecessary-pressive-472743 <description><![CDATA[An elderly New Mexico man has been awarded $412 million after a men's health clinic treated his erectile dysfunction with "invasive penile shots" that caused irreversible damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/elderly-man-awarded-historic-damages-after-clinic-allegedly-injects-him-unnecessary-pressive-472743</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:27:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Menopause Treatment Tablets Could Affect Heart Health: Here's What Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-menopause-treatment-tablets-could-affect-heart-health-heres-what-study-says-472742 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that hormone replacement therapy (HRT) tablets containing both estrogen and progestogen may increase the risk of heart disease and blood clots in menopausal women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-menopause-treatment-tablets-could-affect-heart-health-heres-what-study-says-472742</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:32:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Food Additive May Affect Intestine, Raise Risk Of Diabetes: Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-food-additive-may-affect-intestine-raise-risk-diabetes-study-finds-472739 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that carrageenan(E407), a common food additive used as an emulsifier and thickening agent, is linked to an increased risk of diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-food-additive-may-affect-intestine-raise-risk-diabetes-study-finds-472739</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:55:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump Pick for Public Health Chief Opposed COVID Lockdown, Wanted People to Get Infected on Purpose]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trump-pick-public-health-chief-opposed-covid-lockdown-wanted-people-get-infected- Purpose-472736 <description><![CDATA[Donald Trump has appointed a health economist who published an open letter slamming the COVID-19 lockdown while promoting "herd immunity" to lead the NIH.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trump-pick-public-health-chief-opposed-covid-lockdown-wanted-people-get-infected- Purpose-472736</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Nov 2024 10:16:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Going To Bed At Different Times? Researchers Link It To Higher Risk Of Heart Attacks, Strokes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/going-bed- Different-times-researchers-link-it-higher-risk-heart-attacks-lines-472734 <description><![CDATA[The study found that individuals with irregular sleep patterns had a 26% higher risk of experiencing a major cardiovascular event compared to those with a regular sleep-wake cycle, while those with moderately irregular sleep patterns were 8% more likely to face the same risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/going-bed- Different-times-researchers-link-it-higher-risk-heart-attacks-lines-472734</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Nov 2024 01:53:49 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Reports First Case Of Locally Acquired Dengue This Year: Here's What To Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-reports-first-case-locally-acquired-dengue-this-year-heres-what-know-472733 <description><![CDATA[Since 2013, Texas has reported 665 dengue cases, including 40 locally acquired infections. This year, however, marks the state's highest annual case count since 2002.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/texas-reports-first-case-locally-acquired-dengue-this-year-heres-what-know-472733</guid><pubDate> Wed, 27 Nov 2024 01:19:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vaping Affects Circulation With Immediate Effects, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaping-affects-circulation-immediate-effects-study-finds-472731 <description><![CDATA[The study found that while vaping exposes users to fewer toxic chemicals than cigarettes, it still affects circulation and overall health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vaping-affects-circulation-immediate-effects-study-finds-472731</guid><pubDate> Tue, 26 Nov 2024 02:30:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Finds Widely Prescribed Thyroid Drug Linked To Bone Loss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-widely-prescribed-steroid-drug-linked-bone-loss-472728 <description><![CDATA[Researchers are raising concerns about levothyroxine, the second most commonly prescribed thyroid medication for older adults in the U.S., as new findings link its use to bone loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-widely-prescribed-steroid-drug-linked-bone-loss-472728</guid><pubDate> Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:06:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Meditation Cushions For Comfort, Support And Mindful Practice]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-meditation-cushions-comfort-support-mindful-practice-472686 <description><![CDATA[Meditation cushions enhance comfort, support posture, and improve mindfulness by elevating hips and aligning the spine. They are customizable, portable, and versatile, fostering deeper meditation and making extended sessions more enjoyable.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-meditation-cushions-comfort-support-mindful-practice-472686</guid><pubDate> Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:00:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Miscarrying Texas Mother Becomes Latest Woman to Die As Doctors Risk 99-Year Prison Sentence for Administering Life-Saving Drug]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/miscarrying-texas-mother-becomes-latest-woman-die-doctors-risk-99-year-prison-sentence-472726 <description><![CDATA[A Texas woman became the third to die as a result of the state's abortion ban when legislation prevented a doctor from administering life-saving care.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/miscarrying-texas-mother-becomes-latest-woman-die-doctors-risk-99-year-prison-sentence-472726</guid><pubDate> Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:47:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Finds Daily Dose Of Vitamin B3 Reduces Inflammation In COPD Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-daily-dose-vitamin-b3-reduces-inflammation-copd-病人-472723 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that taking vitamin B3 could reduce lung inflammatory biomarkers by up to 63%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-finds-daily-dose-vitamin-b3-reduces-inflammation-copd-病人-472723</guid><pubDate> Mon, 25 Nov 2024 02:09:38 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>