<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Can Refined Carbs Affect Your Looks? Chronic Consumption Linked To Reduced Facial Attractiveness: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-refined-carbs-affect-your-looks-chronic-conspiration-linked-reduced-facial-attractiveness-471487 <description><![CDATA[Beyond the known health risks of refined carbs, a new study reveals that persistent consumption may diminish facial attractiveness in both men and women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-refined-carbs-affect-your-looks-chronic-conspiration-linked-reduced-facial-attractiveness-471487</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:58:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking 10,000 Steps A Day Cut Cardiovascular Risk Despite Sedentary Lifestyle: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-10000-steps-day-cut-cardioangio-risk-despite-sedentary-lifestyle-study-471486 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now reveal that by clocking in 10,000 daily steps, you can still cut down the cardiovascular risk and risk of early death even if you are sedentary for the rest of the day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-10000-steps-day-cut-cardioangio-risk-despite-sedentary-lifestyle-study-471486</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Mar 2024 02:03:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Kidney Month: Expert Reveals Dietary Habits For Preventing And Managing Kidney Diseases]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-kidney-month-expert-reveals-dietary-habits-preventing-managing-kidney-diseases-471485 <description><![CDATA[During this National Kidney Month, an expert reveals how dietary habits can help prevent kidney diseases and manage their progression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-kidney-month-expert-reveals-dietary-habits-preventing-managing-kidney-diseases-471485</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:53:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Artificially Sweetened Drinks Increase Risk Of Irregular Heartbeat: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking-artificially-sweetened-beverages-raises-risk-irregular-heartbeat-study-471483 <description><![CDATA[Drinking two or more liters of artificially sweetened beverages weekly elevates the risk of atrial fibrillation by 20%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking-artificially-sweetened-beverages-raises-risk-irregular-heartbeat-study-471483</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Mar 2024 04:24:45 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Parrot Fever Outbreak In Europe Kills 5: Know All About Psittacosis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/parrot-fever-outbreak-europe-kills-5-know-all-about-psittacosis-471482 <description><![CDATA[The WHO reported a sudden increase in psittacosis infections over the past year, with the disease persisting and continuing to spread in Europe.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/parrot-fever-outbreak-europe-kills-5-know-all-about-psittacosis-471482</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:09:32 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Less Than 5 Hours Of Daily Sleep Raises Diabetes Risk Despite Healthy Eating: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-5-hours-daily-sleep-raises-diabetes-risk-despite-healthy-eating-study-471481 <description><![CDATA[The diabetes risk from chronic sleep deprivation cannot be compensated by healthy eating alone, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/less-5-hours-daily-sleep-raises-diabetes-risk-despite-healthy-eating-study-471481</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Mar 2024 01:17:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Dies From Vitamin D Overdose: Know The Risks Of Excessive Supplement Intake]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-dies-vitamin-d-overdose-know-risks-excessive-supplement-intake-471480 <description><![CDATA[Although a necessary vitamin, when taken in excess, Vitamin D can cause toxicity and lead to potential kidney damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-dies-vitamin-d-overdose-know-risks-excessive-supplement-intake-471480</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Mar 2024 04:36:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleep Apnea Raises Risk Of Memory And Thinking Problems: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-apnea-raises-risk-memory-thinking-problems-study-471479 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that individuals with symptoms of sleep apnea are approximately 50% more prone to reporting memory or cognitive issues compared to those without such symptoms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sleep-apnea-raises-risk-memory-thinking-problems-study-471479</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Mar 2024 02:13:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Lifestyle Determines Drug Effectiveness; Smoking, Alcohol Use, Obesity Key Factors: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lifestyle-determines-drug-effectness-smoking-alcohol-use-obesity-key-factors-study-471478 <description><![CDATA[Your lifestyle choices decide how well a medication works for you, findings of a new study reveal.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lifestyle-determines-drug-effectness-smoking-alcohol-use-obesity-key-factors-study-471478</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:57:42 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exposure To BPA Linked To Gut Microbiome, Childhood Obesity: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-bpa-linked-gut-microbiome-childhood-obesity-study-471477 <description><![CDATA[The researchers identified that normal-weight children had more unique bacteria taxa, which may help degrade BPA.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-bpa-linked-gut-microbiome-childhood-obesity-study-471477</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Mar 2024 03:25:49 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Obesity Day: Here's How To Promote Healthy Lifestyle In Overweight Children]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-obesity-day-heres-how-promote-healthy-lifestyle-overweight-children-471476 <description><![CDATA[On this World Obesity Day, know ways to promote a healthy lifestyle to tackle obesity in children.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-obesity-day-heres-how-promote-healthy-lifestyle-overweight-children-471476</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:08:01 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>