<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Early Menstruation Linked To Heightened Risk Of Type 2 Diabetes Later In Life: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-menstruation-linked-heightened-risk-type-2-diabetes-later-life-study-471170 <description><![CDATA[The study also suggests that girls who start menstruation before the age of 10 or younger, are at an increased risk of having a stroke before the age of 65.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-menstruation-linked-heightened-risk-type-2-diabetes-later-life-study-471170</guid><pubDate> Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:19:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Skin Flooding? Here's What An Expert Says About The Extreme Hydration Technique]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-skin-flooding-heres-what-expert-says-about-extreme-Hydration-technique-471168 <description><![CDATA[Skin flooding is a skincare technique that promises an instant, radiant boost to the skin by layering multiple hydrating products.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-skin-flooding-heres-what-expert-says-about-extreme-Hydration-technique-471168</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:54:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bee&amp;You Rhinapi Nasal Spray: Your Gateway To Natural Nasal Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/beeyou-rhinapi-nasal-spray-your-gateway-natural-nasal-wellness-471157 <description><![CDATA[This nasal spray adopts a holistic approach to wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/beeyou-rhinapi-nasal-spray-your-gateway-natural-nasal-wellness-471157</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:40:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 6 Personalized Meal Plan Services: Tailor Your Diet For A Healthier And Happier You]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-6-personalized-meal-plan-services-tailor-your-diet-healthier-happier-you-471098 <description><![CDATA[Let's delve into the top six personalized meal planning and delivery services that combine convenience and customization.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-6-personalized-meal-plan-services-tailor-your-diet-healthier-happier-you-471098</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:39:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Yogurt For Mental Health? Study Uncovers How Fermented Food May Prevent Depression, Anxiety]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yogurt-mental-health-study-uncovers-how-fermented-food-may-prevent-depression-anxiety-471166 <description><![CDATA[A team of researchers has identified how bacteria in fermented foods such as yogurt can help manage stress and prevent depression and anxiety.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/yogurt-mental-health-study-uncovers-how-fermented-food-may-prevent-depression-anxiety-471166</guid><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 04:36:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Grief Awareness Week: Experts Share Tips To Support Someone Grieving]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-grief-awareness-week-experts-share-tips-support-someone-grieving-471164 <description><![CDATA[Many times, people genuinely want to help someone in grief, but a lack of knowledge about the process and uncertainty on how to communicate effectively can hold them back from offering support. This week, let's get some valuable insights from experts on how to help someone who is grieving.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-grief-awareness-week-experts-share-tips-support-someone-grieving-471164</guid><pubDate> Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:31:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[International Day Of Persons With Disabilities: Myths And Facts About Disability]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-day-persons-disability-myths-facts-about-disability-471161 <description><![CDATA[On this International Day of Persons with Disabilities, know some facts about disabilities, that will help us understand the lives of people with impairments and acknowledge their daily challenges.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/international-day-persons-disability-myths-facts-about-disability-471161</guid><pubDate> Sun, 03 Dec 2023 06:36:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World AIDS Day: Know Signs, Stages Of HIV And Steps for Prevention]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-aids-day-know-signs-stages-hiv-steps-prevention-471163 <description><![CDATA[World AIDS Day targets to address one of the most pressing global public health challenges, which currently has no cure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-aids-day-know-signs-stages-hiv-steps-prevention-471163</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Dec 2023 03:24:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Reports 'Large Uptick' In Child Pneumonia Cases; Officials Say Outbreak Not Linked To China]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-reports-large-uptick-child-pneumonia-cases-officials-say-outbreak-not-linked-china-471159 <description><![CDATA[A total of 142 cases of pediatric pneumonia have been reported in Warren County, surpassing the county average, the Ohio Department of Health revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-reports-large-uptick-child-pneumonia-cases-officials-say-outbreak-not-linked-china-471159</guid><pubDate> Fri, 01 Dec 2023 01:25:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New 'Prescription Tool' For Postpartum Depression? Study Says Moderate Aerobic Exercise Helps In Prevention, Treatment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-prescription-tool-postpartum-depression-study-says-moderate-aerobic-exercise-helps-471155 <description><![CDATA[Engaging in aerobic exercise sessions 3-4 times per week, each lasting approximately 35-45 minutes, showed significant efficacy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-prescription-tool-postpartum-depression-study-says-moderate-aerobic-exercise-helps-471155</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Nov 2023 03:57:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[7 Healthy Lifestyle Recommendations To Cut Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/7-healthy-lifestyle-recommendations-cut-cancer-risk-471153 <description><![CDATA[A study found that greater adherence to lifestyle recommendations made by the World Cancer Research Fund/American Institute for Cancer Research (WCRF/AICR) was associated with reduced overall cancer risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/7-healthy-lifestyle-recommendations-cut-cancer-risk-471153</guid><pubDate> Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:52:40 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>