<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Fluoride Exposure During Pregnancy Increases Risk of Neurobehavioral Issues In Toddlers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluide-exposure-during-pregnancy-increases-risk-neurobehavioral-issues-toddlers-study-471757 <description><![CDATA[Children with more prenatal fluoride exposure experienced issues such as emotional reactivity, somatic complaints including headaches and stomachaches, anxiety, and symptoms linked to autism.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluide-exposure-during-pregnancy-increases-risk-neurobehavioral-issues-toddlers-study-471757</guid><pubDate> Tue, 21 May 2024 01:42:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Take Breaks From Keto: Study Says Long-Term Consumption Accelerates Organ Aging]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-breaks-keto-study-says-long-term-conspiration-accelerates-organ-aging-471756 <description><![CDATA[A continuous long-term ketogenic diet may induce senescence, the accumulation of aged cells in normal tissues, affecting the health of heart and kidney function in particular, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-breaks-keto-study-says-long-term-conspiration-accelerates-organ-aging-471756</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:53 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Changes In Your Nail Color May Signal Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/changes-your-nail-color-may-signal-cancer-risk-471755 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now recommend nail screening in patients with a personal or family history of melanoma or other potential BAP1-associated malignancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/changes-your-nail-color-may-signal-cancer-risk-471755</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 May 2024 02:49:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Just One Hour On Social Media Doubles Risk Of Smoking, Vaping Among Youth: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/just-one-hour-social-media-doubles-risk-smoking-vaping-among-youth-study-471754 <description><![CDATA[While spending as little as one hour on social media could double the risk of smoking and vaping, those likely to be glued to social media with more than seven hours of daily use could face triple the risk, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/just-one-hour-social-media-doubles-risk-smoking-vaping-among-youth-study-471754</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 May 2024 01:14:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mediterranean Diet Lowers Anxiety And Stress In Elderly Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mediterranean-diet-lowers-anxiety-stress-elderly-adults-study-471752 <description><![CDATA[The study found that in addition to promoting physical health, the Mediterranean diet could also play a significant role in improving mental wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mediterranean-diet-lowers-anxiety-stress-elderly-adults-study-471752</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 May 2024 03:42:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Men At Higher Risk Of Diabetic Complications Than Women: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/men-higher-risk-diabetic-complications-women-study-471751 <description><![CDATA[Men are at higher risk of developing complications from diabetes than women, regardless of the duration for which they have had type 1 or type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/men-higher-risk-diabetic-complications-women-study-471751</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 May 2024 01:54:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Planning To Lose Weight? Here's A Technique Recommended For Men]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-lose-weight-heres-technique-recommished-men-471749 <description><![CDATA[A simple intervention technique that involves receiving text messages with cash incentives could improve men's chances of losing weight by around four times, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-lose-weight-heres-technique-recommished-men-471749</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 May 2024 08:03:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Infertility Treatment Doubles Risk Of Heart Disease Within Year After Delivery: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/infertility-treatment-doubles-risk-heart-disease-within-year-after-delivery-study-471748 <description><![CDATA[The increased risk was most pronounced in the month following the delivery, particularly in those patients who experienced dangerously high blood pressure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/infertility-treatment-doubles-risk-heart-disease-within-year-after-delivery-study-471748</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 May 2024 02:14:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure Drugs More Than Double Risk Of Bone Fractures In Elderly: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-Pressure-drugs-more-double-risk-bone-fractures-elderly-study-471747 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that patients with dementia, those with systolic blood pressure above 139, people with diastolic blood pressure above 79, or those with no recent use of blood pressure medication have at least triple the fracture risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-Pressure-drugs-more-double-risk-bone-fractures-elderly-study-471747</guid><pubDate> Thu, 16 May 2024 01:32:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Severe Obesity In Childhood Halves Life Expectancy, Weight Loss Brings Back Decades: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/severe-obesity-childhood-halfs-life-expectancy-weight-loss-brings-back-decades-study-471745 <description><![CDATA[A child with severe obesity at age 4 has only a life expectancy of 39 if the individual does not lose weight. However, losing weight could add decades back to their lives, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/severe-obesity-childhood-halfs-life-expectancy-weight-loss-brings-back-decades-study-471745</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 May 2024 03:50:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[C-Section Doubles Risk Of Measles Vaccine Failure; Study Recommends Taking 2 Doses]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/c-section-doubles-risk-measles-vaccine-failure-study-recommends-take-2-doses-471743 <description><![CDATA[To have robust protection against measles, children born with C-sections should receive two doses of the vaccination, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/c-section-doubles-risk-measles-vaccine-failure-study-recommends-take-2-doses-471743</guid><pubDate> Wed, 15 May 2024 03:09:02 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>