<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Vegetarian Diet May Help Reduce Risk, Severity Of COVID-19 Infection: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vegetarian-diet-may-help-reduce-risk-severity-covid-19-infection-study-471247 <description><![CDATA[People on a predominantly plant-based or vegetarian diet were at a lower risk (39%) of getting COVID-19 infection compared to omnivores.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vegetarian-diet-may-help-reduce-risk-severity-covid-19-infection-study-471247</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:04:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excessive Screen Time In Kids Under 2 Linked To Issues With Sensory Processing: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-kids-under-2-linked-issues-sensory-processing-study-471246 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed a connection between excessive TV or video exposure in children under two and issues related to sensory processing.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-screen-time-kids-under-2-linked-issues-sensory-processing-study-471246</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Jan 2024 03:31:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Know What You Drink: Study Says One Liter Of Bottled Water Contains 240,000 Plastic Particles]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-what-you-drink-study-says-one-liter-bottled-water-contains-240000- Plastic-articles-471245 <description><![CDATA[A person consumes around 240,000 of tiny plastic particles from one liter of bottled water, a new study has revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-what-you-drink-study-says-one-liter-bottled-water-contains-240000- Plastic-articles-471245</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Jan 2024 02:16:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Donate Blood, Make A Life-Or-Death Difference: Red Cross Urges Action Amid Emergency Shortage]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/donate-blood-make-life-death-difference-red-cross-urges-action-amid-emergency-shortage-471244 <description><![CDATA[The number of people donating blood through the American Red Cross has fallen by about 40% in the past two decades, the agency said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/donate-blood-make-life-death-difference-red-cross-urges-action-amid-emergency-shortage-471244</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:04:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Portable EKG Machines For Heart Monitoring 2024: The Heartbeat Companion]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-portable-ekg-machines-heart-monitoring-2024-heartbeat-companion-471243 <description><![CDATA[Understanding your heart's rhythm can be empowering, and portable EKG machines offer a convenient way to do just that.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-portable-ekg-machines-heart-monitoring-2024-heartbeat-companion-471243</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Jan 2024 07:03:36 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Novel Antibiotic To Treat Drug-Resistant Bacteria? Zosurabalpin Shows Promising Results In Mice]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/novel-antibiotic-treat-drug-pressive-bacteria-zosurabalpin-shows-promising-results-mice-471242 <description><![CDATA[The novel antibiotic, Zosurabalpin, shows promising results in treating highly drug-resistant strains of Carbapenem-resistant Acinetobacter baumannii (CRAB) in mouse models.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/novel-antibiotic-treat-drug-pressive-bacteria-zosurabalpin-shows-promising-results-mice-471242</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:46:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Flu And COVID-19 Infections Continue To Surge After Holiday Season: CDC]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-covid-19-infections-continue-surge-after-holiday-season-cdc-471241 <description><![CDATA[Respiratory infections continue to surge in the U.S. after the holiday season. High or very high levels of respiratory illnesses were reported in 38 states last week, according to CDC.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flu-covid-19-infections-continue-surge-after-holiday-season-cdc-471241</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:49:42 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Male Contraception: Novel Product With Lasting Effects, Reversibility Like IUDs Shows Positive Results In Human Trial]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/male-contraception-novel-product-having-effects-reversibility-like-iuds-shows-positive-results-471240 <description><![CDATA[The new product, named ADAM and developed by Contraline, has a hydrogel insert, which when injected into the sperm duct could reduce sperm motility and concentration similar to that of a vasectomy. However, unlike vasectomy, the contraception is fully reversible.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/male-contraception-novel-product-having-effects-reversibility-like-iuds-shows-positive-results-471240</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Jan 2024 01:24:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best-Selling Toilet Seats For Seniors In 2024: Comfort With Safety]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best- sell-toilet-seats-seniors-2024-elevate-your-comfort-471239 <description><![CDATA[Discover top-rated toilet seats for seniors, with adjustable heights, handles, and essential safety features for a secure and accessible bathroom experience.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best- sell-toilet-seats-seniors-2024-elevate-your-comfort-471239</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:42:00 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Dark Spot Removers 2024:  The Ultimate Guide To Flawless Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-dark-spot-removers-2024-ultimate-guide-flawless-skin-471237 <description><![CDATA[Here, we explore the five best dark spot removers for 2024, examining their ingredients, possible benefits, and feedback from users.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/5-best-dark-spot-removers-2024-ultimate-guide-flawless-skin-471237</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jan 2024 04:37:47 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is There A Link Between Early Rising And Anorexia? Researchers Say 'Yes']]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/there-link- Between-early-rising-anorexia-researchers-say-yes-471238 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found a bidirectional association between anorexia nervosa and morning chronotype - the natural inclination of the body to wake up and sleep early.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/there-link- Between-early-rising-anorexia-researchers-say-yes-471238</guid><pubDate> Fri, 05 Jan 2024 04:34:14 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>