<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>母亲</title><link/>https：/www.was.com.com<description>在救世主上</description><language>曾是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Common Artificial Sweetener In Diet Sodas May Raise Risk Of Heart Attacks, Strokes]]></title><link/> Histops：/wow - 名称。 <description><![CDATA[Results of a recent mice trial revealed that mice fed with aspartame had increased inflammation and "larger and more fatty plaques" in their arteries, two main factors that could raise the risk of cardiovascular diseases.]]></description><guid> Histops：/wow - 名称。</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:37:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman Loses Sight After Parasites Burrow Into Eyes: Common Mistake While Swimming To Blame]]></title><link/> httops：/wow。 <description><![CDATA[The woman lost her eyesight to acanthamoeba keratitis, a rare infection caused by parasites burrowing into her cornea and permanently damaging her right eye.]]></description><guid> httops：/wow。</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:16:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman's Skin Turns Yellow, Develops Flu-Like Symptoms Before Shocking Terminal Diagnosis]]></title><link/> htts：/wow。 Borpos 4 73143。 <description><![CDATA[When the 38-year-old developed strange flu-like symptoms and noticed her skin turning yellow, little did she imagine that it would lead to a devastating diagnosis.]]></description><guid> htts：/wow。 Borpos 4 73143。</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:17:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Hospitalized With Fever, Recurrent Falls Diagnosed With Rare Infection Linked To Lake Swimming In Iowa]]></title><link/> https：/wows。 <description><![CDATA[The man's mysterious symptoms left doctors puzzled for days until they diagnosed him with a potentially fatal Legionnaires' disease, linked to his vacation swimming in an Iowa lake.]]></description><guid> https：/wows。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Feb 2025 04:47:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Feeling Groggy After A Full Night's Sleep? A Doctor Explains Simple Math To Find Your Ideal Bedtime]]></title><link/> https：/wow。 <description><![CDATA[You get a full night's sleep but still wake up feeling groggy, while a short nap leaves you feeling refreshed. Ever wondered why?]]></description><guid> https：/wow。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:51:36 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Autistic 3-Year-Old Speaks First Words Days After Starting Inexpensive Generic Drug Given For Chemo Patients]]></title><link/> https：/wowing系列 - 二十阶段-731313333。 <description><![CDATA[The parents of a nonverbal autistic boy in Arizona vouch for the drug after their son spoke his first words just days after taking it.]]></description><guid> https：/wowing系列 - 二十阶段-731313333。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 19 Feb 2025 01:22:48 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Water Allergy Causes Excruciating Pain For Woman—From Drinking To Showering, She Shares Her Daily Struggle]]></title><link/> htts：/wowl <description><![CDATA[An extremely rare condition called aquagenic urticaria makes the life of the young mother a daily struggle.]]></description><guid> htts：/wowl</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Feb 2025 04:45:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Popular Diet Pattern Effective For Many May Be Harmful For Teens: Here's How]]></title><link/> htts：// wowing。 <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that long-term intermittent fasting affected insulin production in young mice.]]></description><guid> htts：// wowing。</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Feb 2025 03:15:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Drives To Hospital Feeling Unwell, Hours Later Develops Hallucinations, Seizures: He's Now Battling Rare 'Brain On Fire' Disease]]></title><link/> htts：/wowling <description><![CDATA[The 48-year-old from California was diagnosed with Anti-NMDA Encephalitis, also known as "Brain on Fire" disease, an auto-immune condition where the body attacks the brain.]]></description><guid> htts：/wowling</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Feb 2025 01:26:29 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Craving Sugary Treat After Meals? Here's Why You Always Have Room For Dessert]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/craving-sugary-treat-ter-meals-heres-heres-why---------------------------------------------- <description><![CDATA[In a recent study researchers explain how "dessert stomach" is linked to the brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/craving-sugary-treat-ter-meals-heres-heres-why----------------------------------------------</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Feb 2025 03:40:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Taste Predict Early Death? If You Can't Sense These Two Flavors, Your Risk May Be High]]></title><link/> httops：/wownical。 <description><![CDATA[A recent study found that people who lose their sense of taste have a 47% higher risk of early death.]]></description><guid> httops：/wownical。</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Feb 2025 02:19:37 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>