<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[A 9-Year-Old Girl Raised $30K for a Prosthetic Arm After Being Denied Coverage. Then She Gave It All Away to Help Someone Else]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-year-old-girl-raised-30k-prosthetic-arm-after-being-denied-coverage-then-she-gave-it-all-472858 <description><![CDATA[A young girl is using her GoFundMe donations to pay for two other limb-different kids whose insurance claims for prosthetic arms were denied.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-year-old-girl-raised-30k-prosthetic-arm-after-being-denied-coverage-then-she-gave-it-all-472858</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Dec 2024 10:31:19 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Jobs That Save Lives? People In Certain Professions May Be At Reduced Risk Of Alzheimer's Death]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/jobs-that-save-lives-people-certain-professions-may-reduced-risk-alzheimers-death-472857 <description><![CDATA[Professions requiring constant navigation, such as taxi and ambulance drivers, might be at an advantage as a recent study found these workers have a reduced risk of death from Alzheimer's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/jobs-that-save-lives-people-certain-professions-may-reduced-risk-alzheimers-death-472857</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Dec 2024 02:50:35 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mom Mistakes Bloating For Period Symptoms, Told She's Too Young—Then Diagnosed With Terminal Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mom-mistakes-bloating-period-symptoms-told-shes-too-youngthen-diagnosed-terminal-cancer-472855 <description><![CDATA[The 28-year-old mother diagnosed with terminal ovarian cancer urges women not to ignore symptoms like bloating, which she initially mistook for a sign of her period.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mom-mistakes-bloating-period-symptoms-told-shes-too-youngthen-diagnosed-terminal-cancer-472855</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:43:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Pills For Hot Flashes? FDA Issues Strongest Warning On A Menopausal Drug Linked To Serious Liver Injury]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-pills-hot-flashes-fda-issues-strongest-warning-menopausal-drug-linked-serious-liver-472853 <description><![CDATA[The FDA has issued its strongest safety alert, a boxed warning, on a menopausal drug linked to severe liver injury.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-pills-hot-flashes-fda-issues-strongest-warning-menopausal-drug-linked-serious-liver-472853</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Dec 2024 00:31:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Navneet Kaur Is Championing Regulatory Excellence In The Pharmaceutical Industry]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-navneet-kaur-championing-regulatory-excellence-pharmaceutical-industry-472852 <description><![CDATA[With an average of over 1,284 drugs recalled annually, the pharmaceutical industry demands vigilance. Quality control issues, ranging from incorrect labeling to contamination, can result in costly recalls, regulatory fines, and reputational damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-navneet-kaur-championing-regulatory-excellence-pharmaceutical-industry-472852</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:14:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Holiday Cheer: Thoughtful Christmas Gifts For A Vibrant 2024]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-holiday-cheer-thoughtful-christmas-gifts-vibrant-2024-472841 <description><![CDATA[This holiday season, give the gift of wellness and help your loved ones start the new year feeling their best]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-holiday-cheer-thoughtful-christmas-gifts-vibrant-2024-472841</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Dec 2024 14:10:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is What You Eat Fueling Colon Cancer? Researchers Caution About Ultra-Processed Foods And Seed Oils]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-you-eat-fueling-colon-cancer-researchers-caution-about-ultra-processed-foods-seed-oils-472851 <description><![CDATA[Colorectal cancer, once considered a disease of the elderly, is now spiking at an alarming rate among young people. The study cautions that food you choose today may either fuel colon cancer or help heal tumors in the future.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-you-eat-fueling-colon-cancer-researchers-caution-about-ultra-processed-foods-seed-oils-472851</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Dec 2024 03:23:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Warns: If You've 3 Or More Of These Sleep Issues, Check Your Stress Hormone]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-warns-if-youve-3-more-these-sleep-issues-check-your-stress-hormone-472848 <description><![CDATA[Do you often wake up in the middle of the night, find yourself drenched in sweat, or experience vivid dreams? These seemingly minor sleep issues could be your body's way of signaling a deeper problem, warns a doctor.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-warns-if-youve-3-more-these-sleep-issues-check-your-stress-hormone-472848</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Dec 2024 01:21:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Key Tech Innovations Transforming Clinical Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-key-tech-innovations-transforming-clinical-research-472847 <description><![CDATA[Tech is transforming the clinical research process, making trials faster and more patient-focused. Discover five innovations reshaping the field.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-key-tech-innovations-transforming-clinical-research-472847</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Dec 2024 19:40:21 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Paracetamol Safe? Regular Use In Older Adults May Lead To Ulcers, Heart, And Kidney Complications]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/paracetamol-safe-regular-use-older-adults-may-lead-ulcers-heart-kidney-complications-472845 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that frequent use of this common pain reliever may be linked to several serious complications, such as peptic ulcers, heart failure, hypertension, and chronic kidney disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/paracetamol-safe-regular-use-older-adults-may-lead-ulcers-heart-kidney-complications-472845</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Dec 2024 03:56:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Any Of These 5 Medications Daily? Doctor Cautions That They May Cause Dementia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-any-these-5-medications-daily-doctor-cautions-that-they-may-cause-dementia-472842 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Zain Hasan, a board-certified anesthesiologist in Los Angeles shared on TikTok five common medications including two over-the-counter drugs that if taken daily can raise the risk of dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-any-these-5-medications-daily-doctor-cautions-that-they-may-cause-dementia-472842</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Dec 2024 01:53:30 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>