<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[The Truth About Mushroom Coffee: Are There Any Health Benefits Or Side Effects?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/truth-about-mushroom-coffee-are-there-any-health-benefits-side-effects-470437 <description><![CDATA[Exploring the claims around mushroom coffee, the beverage that's been creating a buzz on social media.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/truth-about-mushroom-coffee-are-there-any-health-benefits-side-effects-470437</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 05:06:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Zoonoses Day: Know About Common Diseases That Spread From Animals To Humans]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-zoonoses-day-know-about-common-diseases-that-spread-animals- humans-470435 <description><![CDATA[World Zoonoses Day marks the day the first vaccine against rabies, a zoonotic disease, was developed by French microbiologist Louis Pasteur.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-zoonoses-day-know-about-common-diseases-that-spread-animals- humans-470435</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 03:52:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Maintaining Oral Hygiene May Be Good For Your Brain Health Too, Study Suggests]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maintaining-oral-hygiene-may-good-your-brain-health-too-study-suggests-470431 <description><![CDATA[While we often associate brain health with various factors, not many of use will consider the impact of dental care on our cognitive well-being.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maintaining-oral-hygiene-may-good-your-brain-health-too-study-suggests-470431</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 03:40:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dissolving Cardiac Device Monitor Gets FDA Approval; What To Know About The Device]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dissolving-cardiac-device-monitor-gets-fda-approval-what-know-about-device-470433 <description><![CDATA[The postage stamp-size electronic device, designed to outperform traditional cardiac devices such as pacemakers, dissolves harmlessly inside the body after the period of treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dissolving-cardiac-device-monitor-gets-fda-approval-what-know-about-device-470433</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 02:47:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fluctuating Cholesterol Linked To Increased Dementia Risk In Elderly: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluctuating-cholesterol-linked-increased-dementia-risk-elderly-study-470430 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that lipid variability – both increase or decrease in lipid levels – increases the risk of Alzheimer's and related dementias.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluctuating-cholesterol-linked-increased-dementia-risk-elderly-study-470430</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 01:27:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Nourishing Foods That Could Increase Your Chances Of Getting Pregnant]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-nourishing-foods-that-c​​ould-increase-your-chances-getting-pregnant-470428 <description><![CDATA[Here is a list of food choices recommended by experts that you can incorporate into your diet to optimize your chances of getting pregnant.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-nourishing-foods-that-c​​ould-increase-your-chances-getting-pregnant-470428</guid><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 01:12:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Triple Protection: Flu, COVID, RSV Vaccines To Help Prevent Resurgence Of Respiratory Illnesses This Fall]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/triple-protection-flu-covid-rsv-vaccines-help-prevent-resurgence-respiratory-illnesses-this-470425 <description><![CDATA[Three vaccines against respiratory illnesses are coming this fall.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/triple-protection-flu-covid-rsv-vaccines-help-prevent-resurgence-respiratory-illnesses-this-470425</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:12:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Shows Link Between Physical Activity And Quality Of Life In Older Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-shows-link- Between-physical-activity-quality-life-older-adults-470424 <description><![CDATA[The study highlighted the importance of encouraging older adults to stay active and minimize sedentary behavior.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-shows-link- Between-physical-activity-quality-life-older-adults-470424</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:07:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Benefits Of Daytime Napping For Brain Health: Study Reveals Fascinating Insights]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-daytime-napping-brain-health-study-reveals-fascinating-insights-470423 <description><![CDATA[Taking short naps during the day may have a positive impact on the brain.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/benefits-daytime-napping-brain-health-study-reveals-fascinating-insights-470423</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:04:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Being Overweight Not Directly Linked To Increased Mortality Risk, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-overweight-not-directly-linked-increased-mortality-risk-study-finds-470421 <description><![CDATA[A new study claims being overweight does not translate to a higher mortality risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/being-overweight-not-directly-linked-increased-mortality-risk-study-finds-470421</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 19:57:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Cortisol Levels: Know The Causes, Warning Signs Of Cushing Syndrome]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-cortisol-levels-know-causes-warning-signs-cushing-syndrome-470419 <description><![CDATA[High levels of cortisol can increase the risk of weight gain, anxiety, depression, headaches, diabetes, heart disease and memory and concentration problems.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-cortisol-levels-know-causes-warning-signs-cushing-syndrome-470419</guid><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 05:05:47 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>