<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[How Navneet Kaur Is Championing Regulatory Excellence In The Pharmaceutical Industry]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-navneet-kaur-championing-regulatory-excellence-pharmaceutical-industry-472852 <description><![CDATA[With an average of over 1,284 drugs recalled annually, the pharmaceutical industry demands vigilance. Quality control issues, ranging from incorrect labeling to contamination, can result in costly recalls, regulatory fines, and reputational damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/how-navneet-kaur-championing-regulatory-excellence-pharmaceutical-industry-472852</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:14:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Holiday Cheer: Thoughtful Christmas Gifts For A Vibrant 2024]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-holiday-cheer-thoughtful-christmas-gifts-vibrant-2024-472841 <description><![CDATA[This holiday season, give the gift of wellness and help your loved ones start the new year feeling their best]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-holiday-cheer-thoughtful-christmas-gifts-vibrant-2024-472841</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Dec 2024 14:10:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is What You Eat Fueling Colon Cancer? Researchers Caution About Ultra-Processed Foods And Seed Oils]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-you-eat-fueling-colon-cancer-researchers-caution-about-ultra-processed-foods-seed-oils-472851 <description><![CDATA[Colorectal cancer, once considered a disease of the elderly, is now spiking at an alarming rate among young people. The study cautions that food you choose today may either fuel colon cancer or help heal tumors in the future.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-you-eat-fueling-colon-cancer-researchers-caution-about-ultra-processed-foods-seed-oils-472851</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Dec 2024 03:23:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Warns: If You've 3 Or More Of These Sleep Issues, Check Your Stress Hormone]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-warns-if-youve-3-more-these-sleep-issues-check-your-stress-hormone-472848 <description><![CDATA[Do you often wake up in the middle of the night, find yourself drenched in sweat, or experience vivid dreams? These seemingly minor sleep issues could be your body's way of signaling a deeper problem, warns a doctor.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/doctor-warns-if-youve-3-more-these-sleep-issues-check-your-stress-hormone-472848</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Dec 2024 01:21:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Key Tech Innovations Transforming Clinical Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-key-tech-innovations-transforming-clinical-research-472847 <description><![CDATA[Tech is transforming the clinical research process, making trials faster and more patient-focused. Discover five innovations reshaping the field.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-key-tech-innovations-transforming-clinical-research-472847</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Dec 2024 19:40:21 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Paracetamol Safe? Regular Use In Older Adults May Lead To Ulcers, Heart, And Kidney Complications]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/paracetamol-safe-regular-use-older-adults-may-lead-ulcers-heart-kidney-complications-472845 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that frequent use of this common pain reliever may be linked to several serious complications, such as peptic ulcers, heart failure, hypertension, and chronic kidney disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/paracetamol-safe-regular-use-older-adults-may-lead-ulcers-heart-kidney-complications-472845</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Dec 2024 03:56:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Any Of These 5 Medications Daily? Doctor Cautions That They May Cause Dementia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-any-these-5-medications-daily-doctor-cautions-that-they-may-cause-dementia-472842 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Zain Hasan, a board-certified anesthesiologist in Los Angeles shared on TikTok five common medications including two over-the-counter drugs that if taken daily can raise the risk of dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-any-these-5-medications-daily-doctor-cautions-that-they-may-cause-dementia-472842</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Dec 2024 01:53:30 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New York Requires Health Insurers to Cover EpiPens as Cost of Life-Saving Device Skyrockets]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-york-requires-health-insurers-cover-epipens-cost-life- saving-device-skyrockets-472838 <description><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking move to combat rising healthcare costs, New York Governor Kathy Hochul signed a law mandating health insurers cover EpiPens as they surge in price.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-york-requires-health-insurers-cover-epipens-cost-life- saving-device-skyrockets-472838</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Dec 2024 18:21:03 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Child's Snoring Isn't Just A Noise, It's A Signal': Dentist Cautions Parents About Dangers Of Sleep Apnea]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childs-snoring-isnt-just-noise-its-signal-dentist-cautions-parents-about-dangers-sleep-472836 <description><![CDATA[Snoring in children might seem like an innocent quirk, but a California dentist warns it could signal a hidden health issue.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/childs-snoring-isnt-just-noise-its-signal-dentist-cautions-parents-about-dangers-sleep-472836</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Dec 2024 04:43:25 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[UCLA Student Sues Doctors, Claims She Was Misdiagnosed Of Gender Dysphoria, And 'Fast-Tracked' Into Transgender Surgery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ucla-student-sues-doctors-claims-she-was-misdiagnosed-gender-dysphoria-fast-tracked-472834 <description><![CDATA[The 20-year-old filed a lawsuit against multiple healthcare providers in California as she was reportedly misdiagnosed with gender dysphoria at age 12 and "fast-tracked onto a conveyor belt" of irreversible gender transition treatments.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ucla-student-sues-doctors-claims-she-was-misdiagnosed-gender-dysphoria-fast-tracked-472834</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Dec 2024 03:08:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are Babies In U.S. Sleeping Safely? Over 3,000 Infants Die Annually From Incorrect Sleep Positions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-babies-us-sleeping-safely-over-3000-infants-die-annually-in Correct-sleep-positions-472831 <description><![CDATA[Many of the sleep-related deaths such as those from accidental strangulation or sudden infant death syndrome (SIDS) could be prevented through safe sleep practices.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-babies-us-sleeping-safely-over-3000-infants-die-annually-in Correct-sleep-positions-472831</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Dec 2024 01:22:23 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>