<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Foundation For Mature Skin: Ultimate Guide For Flawless Complexion]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-foundation-mature-skin-ultimate-guide-flawless-complexion-471363 <description><![CDATA[Here are some of the best foundations that offer a natural finish, blend seamlessly with your skin tone, and provide long-lasting wear for a flawless complexion all day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-foundation-mature-skin-ultimate-guide-flawless-complexion-471363</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:09:42 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Eye Cream For Wrinkles In 2024: Say Goodbye To Those Fine Lines]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-eye-cream-wrinkles-say-goodbye-those-fine-lines-471362 <description><![CDATA[Here are some of the best eye creams that will help hydrate the delicate skin around the eyes and reduce the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-eye-cream-wrinkles-say-goodbye-those-fine-lines-471362</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Feb 2024 05:05:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[PCOS Patients At More Than 8-Fold Increased Risk Of Suicide Attempts: Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pcos-患者-more-8-fold-increased-risk-suicide-attempts-study-says-471361 <description><![CDATA[The findings of the study highlight the importance of routine monitoring of mental health and suicide risk in persons diagnosed with PCOS.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pcos-患者-more-8-fold-increased-risk-suicide-attempts-study-says-471361</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:38:41 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Are Happy Hormones? Ways To Naturally Improve Them In Your Body]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-are-happy-hormones-ways-naturally-improve-them-your-body-471360 <description><![CDATA[A certain group of hormones nicknamed "feel-good hormones" or "happy hormones" can shape your mood and make you feel happy. Know the natural ways to improve them in your body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-are-happy-hormones-ways-naturally-improve-them-your-body-471360</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:12:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Compression Socks For 2024: Elevate Your Comfort With All-Day Support]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-compression-socks-elevate-your-comfort-all-day-support-471358 <description><![CDATA[Discover the versatile benefits of compression socks, from alleviating ache to enhancing circulation during work, workouts, travel, and more.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-compression-socks-elevate-your-comfort-all-day-support-471358</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:31:02 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Eye Cream For Dark Circles In 2024: Revitalize Your Gaze]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-eye-cream-dark-circles-revitalize-your-gaze-471356 <description><![CDATA[Transform your tired eyes with our compilation of the top eye creams. These creams will help you diminish dark circles for a brighter, refreshed gaze.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-eye-cream-dark-circles-revitalize-your-gaze-471356</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:24:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Candida Auris Outbreak In Washington State: Know Signs, Risk Factors Of Deadly Fungal Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/candida-auris-outbreak-washington-state-know-signs-risk-factors-deadly-fungal-infection-471354 <description><![CDATA[Four people have tested positive for the infection since the beginning of the month in Washington state, officials said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/candida-auris-outbreak-washington-state-know-signs-risk-factors-deadly-fungal-infection-471354</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:12:13 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthy Diet In Infancy May Reduce Risk Of Inflammatory Bowel Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-diet-infancy-may-reduce-risk-profit-bowel-disease-study-471351 <description><![CDATA[What kids consume before the age of one could potentially determine their susceptibility to future illnesses.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/healthy-diet-infancy-may-reduce-risk-profit-bowel-disease-study-471351</guid><pubDate> Sat, 03 Feb 2024 04:30:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Fiber Supplements For 2024: Boost Your Digestive Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-fibre-supplements-boost-your-digestive-health-471353 <description><![CDATA[Discover the convenience and benefits in every dose of these fiber supplements.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-fibre-supplements-boost-your-digestive-health-471353</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Feb 2024 07:49:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily 3 Servings Of Kimchi Could Reduce Risk Of Obesity In Men: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-3-servings-kimchi-could-reduce-risk-obesity-men-study-471349 <description><![CDATA[The researchers explored if regular consumption of kimchi could cut the risk of overall obesity, and abdominal obesity, which is particularly harmful to health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-3-servings-kimchi-could-reduce-risk-obesity-men-study-471349</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Shampoo For Oily Hair In 2024: Say Goodbye To Grease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shampoo-oily-hair-say-goodbye-grease-471347 <description><![CDATA[Finding the best shampoo for oily hair may not be very easy, especially with the myriads of choices. Fortunately, we have compiled some of the best ones for you.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-shampoo-oily-hair-say-goodbye-grease-471347</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:24:36 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>