<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Lead Exposure Instills Criminal Instincts? Study Says People Exposed In Womb, Childhood Are At Higher Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lead-exposure-instils-criminal-instincts-study-says-people-expose-womb-childhood-are-higher-470596 <description><![CDATA[The latest study has found that lead exposure in the womb or in childhood increases the risk of criminal behavior in adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lead-exposure-instils-criminal-instincts-study-says-people-expose-womb-childhood-are-higher-470596</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 03:38:57 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kombucha Tea May Help Lower Blood Sugar Levels In Diabetes Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kombucha-tea-may-help-lower-blood-sugar-levels-diabetes-病人-470595 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that drinking a cup of kombucha daily for four weeks lowered average fasting blood glucose levels from 164 to 116 milligrams per deciliter in patients with type 2 diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kombucha-tea-may-help-lower-blood-sugar-levels-diabetes-病人-470595</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:03:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Leprosy Cases Surging In Florida; Know About The Symptoms, Treatment, How It Spreads]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/leprosy-cases-surging-florida-know-about-symptoms-treatment-how-it-spreads-470593 <description><![CDATA[According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), leprosy has become endemic in the southeastern United States.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/leprosy-cases-surging-florida-know-about-symptoms-treatment-how-it-spreads-470593</guid><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:59:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch Out, Night Sweats May Be A Sign Of Cancer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watch-out-night-sweats-may-sign-cancer-470587 <description><![CDATA[When night sweats happen very often even while sleeping in cool temperatures, it may be a sign of an underlying health condition such as cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watch-out-night-sweats-may-sign-cancer-470587</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 02:54:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Breastfeeding Week: Know The Problems Faced By Nursing Moms; Tips To Ease Discomforts]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-breastfeeding-week-know-problems-faced-nursing-moms-tips-ease-discomforts-470586 <description><![CDATA[Several issues during the initial stages of breastfeeding such as cracked nipples, breast engorgement and latching issues discourage mothers from continuing breastfeeding.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-breastfeeding-week-know-problems-faced-nursing-moms-tips-ease-discomforts-470586</guid><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 01:43:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[2 Servings Of Strawberry Per Day Could Improve Heart And Brain Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/2-servings-strawberry-per-day-could-improve-heart-brain-health-470583 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has found that two servings of strawberries daily can improve heart and brain health and antioxidant capacity in older healthy adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/2-servings-strawberry-per-day-could-improve-heart-brain-health-470583</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 03:09:42 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Minutes Of Intense Daily Activity Could Reduce Cancer Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/4-minutes-intense-daily-activity-could-reduce-cancer-risk-study-470582 <description><![CDATA[For people who are unable to do regular exercise, even four minutes of intense physical activity daily could help cut down cancer risk by up to 32%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/4-minutes-intense-daily-activity-could-reduce-cancer-risk-study-470582</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 02:03:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Insufficient Fiber Intake During Pregnancy Affects Baby's Brain Development: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/insufficient-fibre-intake-during-pregnancy-affects-babys-brain-development-study-470579 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that neurodevelopmental delays correlated with the amount of dietary fiber in the expectant mother's diet.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/insufficient-fibre-intake-during-pregnancy-affects-babys-brain-development-study-470579</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:48:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Rhabdomyolysis? Symptoms To Watch Out For After Intense Workouts]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-rhabdomyothesis-symptoms-watch-out-after-intense-workouts-470577 <description><![CDATA[While the condition can affect anyone out there, people like beginners who are pushing their limits without proper guidance, or athletes who are training way too much without proper rest are more at risk.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-rhabdomyothesis-symptoms-watch-out-after-intense-workouts-470577</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 05:35:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Meat Allergy From Tick Spit Is Getting Common, CDC Warns; Know Symptoms Of Alpha-Gal Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meat-allergy-tick-spit-getting-common-cdc-warns-know-symptoms-alpha-gal-syndrome-470575 <description><![CDATA[Around 110,000 suspected cases of alpha-gal syndrome have been identified in the U.S., but officials believe the actual number of cases might be more than 450,000.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meat-allergy-tick-spit-getting-common-cdc-warns-know-symptoms-alpha-gal-syndrome-470575</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 01:55:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Hepatitis Day: Types Of Liver Infections And Tips To Prevent Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-hepatitis-day-types-liver-infections-tips-prevent-them-470573<description><![CDATA[The theme for this year is "one life, one liver."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-hepatitis-day-types-liver-infections-tips-prevent-them-470573</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:35:23 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>