<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[A Step Closer To An Anti-Aging Pill? Harvard Researchers Find Age-Reversing Chemical Cocktails]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/step-closer-anti-aging-pill-harvard-researchers-find-age-reversing-chemical-cocktails-470521 <description><![CDATA[In what could be a groundbreaking discovery, researchers from Harvard have identified six chemical cocktails that they say can reverse the aging process in both human and mouse skin cells.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/step-closer-anti-aging-pill-harvard-researchers-find-age-reversing-chemical-cocktails-470521</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 03:56:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Man Thought Diabetes Caused Excessive Thirst Until He Tested His Eyes; Know Signs Of Pituitary Tumors]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-thought-diabetes-caused-excessive-thirst-until-he-tested-his-eyes-know-signs-pituitary-tumors-470520 <description><![CDATA[The man was diagnosed with a type of brain tumor – a germ cell tumor on his pituitary gland that interfered with water retention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/man-thought-diabetes-caused-excessive-thirst-until-he-tested-his-eyes-know-signs-pituitary-tumors-470520</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 02:51:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Failing Eyesight Signal Dementia? Study Says Vision Loss Is A Modifiable Risk Factor]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-failing-eyesight-signal-dementia-study-says-vision-loss-modulated-risk-factor-470518 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that vision loss has a significant association with dementia in the elderly.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-failing-eyesight-signal-dementia-study-says-vision-loss-modulated-risk-factor-470518</guid><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:58:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[10-Year-Old Diagnosed With 'Most Painful' Condition; Learn More About Complex Regional Pain Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/10-year-old-diagnosed-most-painful-condition-learn-more-about-complex-regional-pain-syndrome-470517 <description><![CDATA[Complex Regional Pain Syndrome (CRPS) is a relatively rare disorder, often dubbed the most painful condition known to mankind.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/10-year-old-diagnosed-most-painful-condition-learn-more-about-complex-regional-pain-syndrome-470517</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:21:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Gut Microbe And Heart Health: Study Says Intestinal Bacteria Can Cause Fatty Deposits In Arteries]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-microbe-heart-health-study-says-intestinal-bacteria-can-cause-fatty-deposits-arteries-470516 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that an increase in the number of a particular type of bacteria in the gut increases the risk of coronary atherosclerotic plaques or fatty deposits in arteries.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gut-microbe-heart-health-study-says-intestinal-bacteria-can-cause-fatty-deposits-arteries-470516</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:55:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Hyperlactation Syndrome? Woman With Rare Condition Sets Guinness Record By Donating Breast Milk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-hyperlactation-syndrome-woman-rare-condition-sets-guinness-record-donating-breast-milk-470515 <description><![CDATA[Elisabeth Anderson-Sierra, a mother of two from Aloha, has saved the lives of thousands of premature babies by donating around 1,600 liters of her breastmilk over the past nine years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-hyperlactation-syndrome-woman-rare-condition-sets-guinness-record-donating-breast-milk-470515</guid><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 01:40:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Could Carpal Tunnel Syndrome Signal Heart Failure? Study Finds Potential Link Between The Two]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-carpal-tunnel-syndrome-signal-heart-failure-study-finds-pottial-link- Between-two-470505 <description><![CDATA[Elderly patients with carpal tunnel syndrome are 39% more likely to develop heart failure compared with those without the condition, a recent study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/could-carpal-tunnel-syndrome-signal-heart-failure-study-finds-pottial-link- Between-two-470505</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jul 2023 05:17:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Deep Sleep To Control Diabetes: Study Uncovers How Brain Waves Regulate Blood Sugar Levels]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/deep-sleep-control-diabetes-study-uncovers-how-brain-waves-regulate-blood-sugar-levels-470504 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has found how deep-sleep brain waves at night regulate a person's insulin sensitivity, which determines blood sugar control the next day.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/deep-sleep-control-diabetes-study-uncovers-how-brain-waves-regulate-blood-sugar-levels-470504</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jul 2023 02:38:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Deadly Scrub Typhus Bacteria Found In North Carolina; What To Know About The Infectious Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/deadly-scrub-typhus-bacteria-found-north-carolina-what-know-about-infectious-disease-470502 <description><![CDATA[Bacteria causing scrub typhus, a deadly form of typhus disease spread through chigger bites, have been detected for the first time in the U.S.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/deadly-scrub-typhus-bacteria-found-north-carolina-what-know-about-infectious-disease-470502</guid><pubDate> Fri, 14 Jul 2023 01:42:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Return To Ancient Recipe: Study Says 2 Common Pantry Ingredients Can Fight Superbug Infections]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/return-ancient-recipe-study-says-2-common-pantry-ingredients-can-fight-superbug-infections-470499 <description><![CDATA[As scientists race to find ways to tackle superbug infections, a recent study highlights the need to revisit the ancient recipes to treat infections caused by antibiotic-resistant strains of microbes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/return-ancient-recipe-study-says-2-common-pantry-ingredients-can-fight-superbug-infections-470499</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:41:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ohio Man Develops Green Hairy Tongue; Know What Causes The Condition]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-man-develops-green-hairy-tongue-know-what-c​​auses-condition-470497 <description><![CDATA[The man developed an abnormal coating on his tongue almost three weeks after he was treated for gum disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ohio-man-develops-green-hairy-tongue-know-what-c​​auses-condition-470497</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:42:27 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>