<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Friend's Genetic Traits Can Influence Your Mental Health Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/friends-genic-traits-can-influence-your-mental-health-risk-study-472082 <description><![CDATA[The traits of your friends, particularly their genetic predisposition to mental health issues, can influence your mental health risks, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/friends-genic-traits-can-influence-your-mental-health-risk-study-472082</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:41:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Kangaroo Care For Preemies: Skin-To-Skin Cuddling Improves Neurodevelopment, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kangaroo-care-preemies-skin-skin-cuddling-improves-neurodevelopment-says-study-472080 <description><![CDATA[A study revealed that even small increases in the amount of skin-to-skin time with premature babies could make a measurable difference in their neurologic development in the first year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kangaroo-care-preemies-skin-skin-cuddling-improves-neurodevelopment-says-study-472080</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:14:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Watching Even 8 Minutes Of TikTok Glamorizing Disordered Eating Harms Body Image, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watching-even-8-minutes-tiktok-glamorizing-disordered-eating-harms-body-image-study-finds-472078 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that even short exposure to "pro-anorexia" content that glorifies extreme weight loss and restricted diet is sufficient to harm body image and affect women's mental health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watching-even-8-minutes-tiktok-glamorizing-disordered-eating-harms-body-image-study-finds-472078</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:09:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Secret To Cholesterol Control? Study Finds Corn Flour Blend Could Be A Game Changer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/secret-cholesterol-control-study-finds-corn-flour-blend-could-game-changer-472076 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that incorporating a blend of refined corn flour and corn bran can reduce LDL (low-density lipoprotein) cholesterol levels by 5% to 13.3% in just four weeks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/secret-cholesterol-control-study-finds-corn-flour-blend-could-game-changer-472076</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:34:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[EPA Issues Emergency Ban On Common Weedkiller Citing Risk To Unborn Babies]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/epa-issues-emergency-ban-common-weedkiller-citing-risk-unborn-babies-472073 <description><![CDATA[In the first emergency ban in nearly 40 years, the EPA has highlighted serious risks for unborn children from maternal exposure to DCPA.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/epa-issues-emergency-ban-common-weedkiller-citing-risk-unborn-babies-472073</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:46:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breakthrough Monthly Treatment May Boost Longevity, Vitality In Old Age: Mice Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakthrough-monthly-treatment-may-boost-longevity-vitality-old-age-mice-study-reveals-472070 <description><![CDATA[The new study offers promising insights into how we might be able to have both longevity and vitality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakthrough-monthly-treatment-may-boost-longevity-vitality-old-age-mice-study-reveals-472070</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:41:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Ashwagandha Supplements Of 2024 For Optimal Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-benefits-ashwagandha-ancient-herb-modern-pottial-472068 <description><![CDATA[Ashwagandha supplements, made from the Withania somnifera plant, come in capsules, powders, and extracts. They're commonly used to help reduce stress, boost physical performance, and enhance cognitive function. For the best results, choose high-quality products from reputable brands and consult a healthcare professional before starting any new supplement.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-benefits-ashwagandha-ancient-herb-modern-pottial-472068</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:32:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top Collagen Supplements Of 2024: Expert Picks For Radiant Skin And Joint Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/compressive-guide-collagen-supplements-472061 <description><![CDATA[Collagen is the most abundant protein in the human body, essential for maintaining the structure and elasticity of skin, bones, tendons, and cartilage. As we age, collagen production naturally decreases, leading to signs of aging like wrinkles and joint discomfort. This decline can be exacerbated by factors such as smoking and excessive sun exposure. To combat these effects, many people turn to collagen supplements, which can promote skin elasticity, improve joint health, and support overall wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/compressive-guide-collagen-supplements-472061</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:49:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[More Than 15 Million US Adults Consume Botanicals With Liver Harming Potential: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-15-million-us-adults-consume-botanicals-liver-harming-pottial-study-472066 <description><![CDATA[The researchers observed that the lack of regulations for botanicals often leads to discrepancies between product labels and actual ingredients, which can mislead consumers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-15-million-us-adults-consume-botanicals-liver-harming-pottial-study-472066</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:58:14 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Drinking From Plastic Water Bottles May Raise Blood Pressure: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking- Plastic-water-bottles-may-raise-blood-Pressure-study-472064 <description><![CDATA[The new study found that drinking from plastic bottles can cause microplastics to enter the bloodstream, potentially leading to increased blood pressure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drinking- Plastic-water-bottles-may-raise-blood-Pressure-study-472064</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:43:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Keto Diet 'May Not Suit Everyone': Study Says It Raises Cholesterol Levels, Disrupts Gut Bacteria]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keto-diet-may-not-suit-everyone-study-says-it-raises-cholesterol-levels-disrupts-gut-bacteria-472063 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noticed that the keto diet reduced glucose tolerance levels, altered gut microbiome composition, and raised cholesterol levels, particularly small and medium-sized low-density lipoprotein (LDL) particles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/keto-diet-may-not-suit-everyone-study-says-it-raises-cholesterol-levels-disrupts-gut-bacteria-472063</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:02:46 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>