<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Grapes For Eye Health: Study Says Regular Consumption Can Improve Macular Degeneration In Older Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/grapes-eye-health-study-says-regular-conspiration-can-improve-macular-degenesis-in-older-adults-470970 <description><![CDATA[Macular degeneration is a condition that results in blurred central vision, which is the leading cause of vision loss in older adults. It occurs when part of the retina, called the macula, that controls sharp, straight-ahead vision gets damaged with aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/grapes-eye-health-study-says-regular-conspiration-can-improve-macular-degenesis-in-older-adults-470970</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Oct 2023 05:13:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is CKM Syndrome? American Heart Association Says 1 In 3 Adults Are At Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-c​​km-syndrome-american-heart-association-says-1-3-adults-are-at-risk-470969 <description><![CDATA[The AHA has identified a new medical condition called cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic (CKM) syndrome, which reflects a strong link between cardiovascular disease, kidney disease, type 2 diabetes and obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-c​​km-syndrome-american-heart-association-says-1-3-adults-are-at-risk-470969</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Oct 2023 04:01:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Loneliness Raises Risk Of Parkinson's Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-raises-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-470967 <description><![CDATA[Loneliness, defined as a lack of meaningful social relationships or a sense of belonging, can raise the chances of a Parkinson's diagnosis by 37%, researchers say.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-raises-risk-parkinsons-disease-study-470967</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Oct 2023 01:01:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bird Flu Spreads To Seals In Washington; Here's What You Need To Know About H5N1 Avian Influenza]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-spreads-seals-washington-here-what-you-need-to-know-about-h5n1-avian-influenza-470965 <description><![CDATA[Several adult harbor seals in the Puget Sound region in Washington have tested positive for the H5N1 strain since September.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bird-flu-spreads-seals-washington-here-what-you-need-to-know-about-h5n1-avian-influenza-470965</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:35:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Rasmussen's Encephalitis? Doctors Disconnect Half Of 6-Year-Old's Brain To Prevent Progression Of Rare Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-rasmussens-encephalitis-doctors-disconnect-half-6-year-olds-brain-prevent-progression-470964 <description><![CDATA[Rasmussen's Encephalitis is a rare neurological disorder that can lead to loss of motor skills and speech, and eventual paralysis on one side of the body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-rasmussens-encephalitis-doctors-disconnect-half-6-year-olds-brain-prevent-progression-470964</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:10:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breast Cancer Awareness Month: Expert Shares Benefits Of Screenings, Self-Examination]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-awareness-month-expert-shares-benefits-of-screening-self-examination-470961 <description><![CDATA[Breast self-examinations can help detect cancer signs early. While doing so, it is important to understand what is normal for each person, a breast and gynecologic medical oncologist says.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breast-cancer-awareness-month-expert-shares-benefits-of-screening-self-examination-470961</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 02:16:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[RSV Prevention in Newborns: What do you need to know about Beyfortus?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rsv-prevention-newborns-what-do-you-need-to-know-about-beyfortus-470942 <description><![CDATA[New RSV monoclonal antibody treatment is now on the market. What do you need to know about RSV and this new treatment?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rsv-prevention-newborns-what-do-you-need-to-know-about-beyfortus-470942</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:15:06 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magnesium Deficiency: Know The Risk Factors, Warning Signs]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/magnesium-deficiency-know-risk-factors-warning-signs-470958 <description><![CDATA[If a person with a habitual poor intake loses magnesium or has reduced absorption due to medical conditions, it can cause long-term health complications.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/magnesium-deficiency-know-risk-factors-warning-signs-470958</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:51:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Treatment-Resistant Epilepsy: Experimental Drug May Reduce Seizures By More Than 50%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/treatment-pressive-epilepsy-experimental-drug-may-reduce-seizures-more-50-470957 <description><![CDATA[A study that examined the efficacy and safety of the new drug, XEN1101, revealed that it can reduce seizures by more than 50% in some patients with focal onset seizures. In some cases, it may even eliminate them altogether.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/treatment-pressive-epilepsy-experimental-drug-may-reduce-seizures-more-50-470957</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:03:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Buruli Ulcer? Know All About The Flesh-Eating Bacterial Infection As Cases Spike In Australia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-burn-ulcer-know-all-about-flesh-eating-bacterial-infection-cases-spike-australia-470955 <description><![CDATA[The infection typically affects the skin and sometimes, bones. If not properly treated, it may result in permanent deformity and disability.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-burn-ulcer-know-all-about-flesh-eating-bacterial-infection-cases-spike-australia-470955</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 01:20:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Mental Health Day: Look Out For These Signs To Detect Depression Early]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-mental-health-day-look-out-这些-signs-detect-depression-early-470953 <description><![CDATA[As we celebrate World Mental Health Day, here are some tips from an expert to detect early signs of depression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-mental-health-day-look-out-这些-signs-detect-depression-early-470953</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 05:37:31 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>