<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Heart Attacks Can Occur At Any Age: Factors Affecting Cardiovascular Health Of Young Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-attacks-can-occur-any-age-factors-affecting-cardioangio-health-young-adults-470284 <description><![CDATA[People are developing diabetes and hypertension, factors associated with heart attacks, much earlier than before.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-attacks-can-occur-any-age-factors-affecting-cardioangio-health-young-adults-470284</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 03:57:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are You A Mosquito Magnet? Here's Why Some People Get Bitten More Than Others]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-you-mosquito-magnet-heres-why-some-people-get-bitten-more-others-470281 <description><![CDATA[Ever wondered why mosquitoes have a knack for singling you out in a crowd?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-you-mosquito-magnet-heres-why-some-people-get-bitten-more-others-470281</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 03:00:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Loneliness Could Weaken Bone Quality In Men, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-could-weaken-bone-quality-men-study-says-470278 <description><![CDATA[A study conducted on mice showed that social isolation can lower bone density in males.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-could-weaken-bone-quality-men-study-says-470278</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 01:53:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Statin Alternative Bempedoic Acid Cuts Down Heart Attack Risk By 39%: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/statin-alternative-bempedoic-acid-cuts-down-heart-attack-risk-39-study-470276 <description><![CDATA[It is still important for people intolerant to statins to take alternative medication to reduce deaths from heart disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/statin-alternative-bempedoic-acid-cuts-down-heart-attack-risk-39-study-470276</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 01:16:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Staying Up To Date With COVID-19 Vaccinations Boosts Protection For Nursing Home Residents]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/staying-date-covid-19-vaccinations-boosts-protection-nursing-home-residents-470274 <description><![CDATA[A new study looked into the effectiveness of the COVID-19 vaccines among nursing home residents.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/staying-date-covid-19-vaccinations-boosts-protection-nursing-home-residents-470274</guid><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:09:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Origins: US Intelligence Report On Wuhan Lab Yields Inconclusive Evidence]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-origins-us-intelligence-report-wuhan-lab-yields-inconclusive-evidence-470272 <description><![CDATA[The report found no direct evidence linking the COVID-19 origin to the Wuhan laboratory.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/covid-19-origins-us-intelligence-report-wuhan-lab-yields-inconclusive-evidence-470272</guid><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:04:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Scientists Identify COVID-Like Langya Virus As Potential Future Threat]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-identify-covid-like-langya-virus-pottial-future-threat-470269 <description><![CDATA[Experts may have found another potentially dangerous virus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/scientists-identify-covid-like-langya-virus-pottial-future-threat-470269</guid><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:00:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What's EU.1.1? CDC Tracks More Distant Descendant Of XBB.1.5 COVID Variant]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/whats-eu11-cdc-tracks-more-distant-descendant-xbb15-covid-variant-470266<description><![CDATA[The CDC is monitoring multiple new SARS-CoV-2 variants.]]></description><guid>https://www.medicaldaily.com/whats-eu11-cdc-tracks-more-distant-descendant-xbb15-covid-variant-470266</guid><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jun 2023 19:57:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Everything About Eye Twitching: Causes Of The Condition And Precautions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/everything-about-eye-twitching-causes-condition-precautions-470264 <description><![CDATA[The underlying cause of eye twitching is the accidental misfiring of neurons responsible for stimulating the eyelid muscles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/everything-about-eye-twitching-causes-condition-precautions-470264</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 06:23:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Health Benefits Of Fermented Food; Ways To Include Them In Diet]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-benefits-fermented-food-ways-include-them-diet-470263 <description><![CDATA[Fermented foods are gaining popularity in recent years, not just for their flavor and aroma but for their nutritional value and health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/health-benefits-fermented-food-ways-include-them-diet-470263</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 04:14:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even 'Safe' Levels Of Air Pollution Can Negatively Impact Brain Development: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-safe-levels-air-pollution-can-negatively-impact-brain-development-study-470258 <description><![CDATA[The study emphasizes the need for regulators to consider brain health, along with respiratory and cardiometabolic health, while setting air quality standards.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/even-safe-levels-air-pollution-can-negatively-impact-brain-development-study-470258</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 03:04:55 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>