<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medalaly.com<description>最新消息</description><language>en </language><item><title><![CDATA[Alternative Healthy Eating Index: Your Diet For Healthy, Disease-Free 70's]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/alterricital-anexy-yex-yex-your-drie-deashe-dere-70707 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now identified a specific dietary approach that promotes longevity and disease-free aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/alterricital-anexy-yex-yex-your-drie-deashe-dere-70707</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:36:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Detection: Could A Simple At-Home Smell Test Predict Risk?]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/alzheimers-detection-simple-homple-homet-test-could-for Spot-Signs <description><![CDATA[The researchers have developed a simple, digital, at-home smell test called the AROMHA Brain Health Test (ABHT) that could detect Alzheimer's years before traditional symptoms appear.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/alzheimers-detection-simple-homple-homet-test-could-for Spot-Signs</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Mar 2025 04:44:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Shocking Study: This Popular Sweetener May Actually Make You Hungrier]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/shocking-study-this-this-meetener-meunner-maukener-maukner-maactiorner <description><![CDATA[Sucralose, one of the most common zero-calorie sugar substitutes, may trick your brain into craving more food.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/shocking-study-this-this-meetener-meunner-maukener-maukner-maactiorner</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Mar 2025 02:20:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Addressing Challenges in Rare Disease Clinical Trials: Strategies for Success with iNGENū CRO]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/addressing-challlen-clrre <description><![CDATA[iNGENū CRO leverages global expertise, advanced technology, and strategic funding to overcome rare disease trial challenges.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/addressing-challlen-clrre</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:03:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Science of Sound Sleep: How a Mini White Noise Machine Can Improve Rest, Focus, and Relaxation]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/sciencemix-sleep-how-how-min-jeine-mamprote-mellaxation-relaxation <description><![CDATA[White noise creates a consistent background sound that helps mask those unpredictable noises, allowing you to sleep more soundly]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/sciencemix-sleep-how-how-min-jeine-mamprote-mellaxation-relaxation</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:06:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Antibiotics For UTI Gets FDA Approval- First In 30 Years]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/new-antbiotics-uti-get-approval-first-3073297 <description><![CDATA[The FDA has approved a new antibiotic, Gepotidacin (Blujepa), for treating uncomplicated urinary tract infections (UTIs) in women and girls aged 12 and older.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/new-antbiotics-uti-get-approval-first-3073297</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:43:31 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Seasoning May Raise Risk Of Depression]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/common-hasoning-may-epcession-depression <description><![CDATA[A recent study has put a common seasoning, found in all types of cuisines, under scrutiny.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/common-hasoning-may-epcession-depression</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:01:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[28-Year-Old, 'Epitome Of Health,' Dies Of Heart Attack; Mom Blames One Habit]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/28-yer-yed-ld-dies-anticck-matck-mat-h​​abit-habit-marmes-marmes-habit <description><![CDATA[Her grieving mother is speaking out, blaming one surprising habit for her daughter's unexpected death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/28-yer-yed-ld-dies-anticck-matck-mat-h​​abit-habit-marmes-marmes-habit</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 01:48:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Body Measurement Could Predict Cancer Risk In Men]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/hat-body-masurement-could-coldcertcertcertance-certaking-certax-certak-certak-men <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that waist circumference in men may be a stronger predictor of cancer risk than Body Mass Index (BMI).]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/hat-body-masurement-could-coldcertcertcertance-certaking-certax-certak-certak-men</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:18:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[This Daily Drink Could Extend Your Life—Longevity Expert Reveals Best Time To Consume]]></title><link/> https://www.medaley.com/rthis-drink-culd-oxtended-extendedbity-exime-chizen-chind <description><![CDATA[A beverage that millions of people consume daily can add years to life if consumed at the right time.]]></description><guid> https://www.medaley.com/rthis-drink-culd-oxtended-extendedbity-exime-chizen-chind</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:03:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Meat Allergy Spreads As More Tick Species Linked To Alpha-Gal Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medalaly.com/rare-alre-spred-spred-spence-spence-spen-ll <description><![CDATA[Although alpha-gal syndrome has long been linked to the lone star tick, recent cases suggest other tick species in the U.S. may also be responsible, raising concerns about the allergy spreading to new regions.]]></description><guid> https://www.medalaly.com/rare-alre-spred-spred-spence-spence-spen-ll</guid><pubDate> Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:31:45 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>