<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Study Says Healthy Plant-Based Diet Can Reduce Risk Of Sleep Apnea]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-healthy-plant-based-diet-can-reduce-risk-sleep-apnea-471439 <description><![CDATA[People who eat a healthy plant-based diet rich in vegetables, fruits, whole grains, and nuts have a 19% less chance of having sleep apnea compared to those who eat an unhealthy diet.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-says-healthy-plant-based-diet-can-reduce-risk-sleep-apnea-471439</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:34:38 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Over Half The World Faces Risk Of Measles Outbreak: WHO]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-half-world-faces-risk-measles-outbreak-who-471438 <description><![CDATA[Over 61 million doses of MCV were postponed or missed during the COVID-19 pandemic, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-half-world-faces-risk-measles-outbreak-who-471438</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:25:31 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[October-Born Kids At Lower Flu Risk; Study Reveals Ideal Time For Influenza Vaccination]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/october-born-kids-lower-flu-risk-study-reveals-ideal-time-influenza-vaccination-471436 <description><![CDATA[A recent U.S.-based study discovered that children born in October are more likely to get vaccinated against the flu during the same month and are at a reduced risk of contracting influenza.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/october-born-kids-lower-flu-risk-study-reveals-ideal-time-influenza-vaccination-471436</guid><pubDate> Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:38:19 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Best Pillows For A Good Night's Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/6-best-pillows-good-nights-sleep-471423 <description><![CDATA[Ready to upgrade your sleep setup? Take a peek at our list of six top-notch pillows that'll have you snoozing in no time.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/6-best-pillows-good-nights-sleep-471423</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:38:22 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Guide To Prevention And Therapy Of Crohn's Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/compressive-guide-prevention-therapy-crohns-disease-471435 <description><![CDATA[Dr. Gilles R.G. Monif's book on Crohn's Disease helps readers understand the disease, empowering them to break free from its harmful effects on both their health and finances.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/compressive-guide-prevention-therapy-crohns-disease-471435</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:25:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nocturia: Know All About The Common Urological Symptom That Could Disrupt Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nocturia-know-all-about-common-urological-symptom-that-c​​ould-disrupt-sleep-471431 <description><![CDATA[Nocturia affects the sleep of approximately 50 million people in the United States. However, only 10 million people are diagnosed with it.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/nocturia-know-all-about-common-urological-symptom-that-c​​ould-disrupt-sleep-471431</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:16:34 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can't Exercise During The Week? Researchers Say 'Weekend Warrior' Workouts Bring Comparable Weight Loss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cant-exercise-during-week-researchers-say-weekend-warrior-workouts-bring-comparable-weight-loss-471433 <description><![CDATA[The study found that those who concentrate their exercise on one or two days a week can still achieve comparable weight loss to those who exercise regularly, as long as they meet the recommended goals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cant-exercise-during-week-researchers-say-weekend-warrior-workouts-bring-comparable-weight-loss-471433</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:08:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Healthy Lifestyle Habits Could Reduce Risk Of Developing Irritable Bowel Syndrome: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-healthy-lifestyle-habits-could-reduce-risk-development-irritable-bowel-syndrome-study-471430 <description><![CDATA[The researchers of the latest study evaluated how a combination of 5 healthy habits affected the onset of IBS.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-healthy-lifestyle-habits-could-reduce-risk-development-irritable-bowel-syndrome-study-471430</guid><pubDate> Wed, 21 Feb 2024 01:26:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Art And Science Of Facial Reconstruction With Dr. Artur Carandell]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/art-science-facial-reconstruction-dr-artur-carandell-471428 <description><![CDATA[A distinguished cranio-maxillo-facial surgeon, Dr. Carandell has over 15 years of experience in public hospitals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/art-science-facial-reconstruction-dr-artur-carandell-471428</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:40:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Innovation At Heart: The Role Of Technology In Advancing US Cardiac Care]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/innovation-heart-role-technology-advancing-us-cardiac-care-471427 <description><![CDATA[In honor of US Heart Month, a look at how technologies like SHL Telemedicine's SmartHeart® have the potential to revolutionize cardiac care in America.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/innovation-heart-role-technology-advancing-us-cardiac-care-471427</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:31:50 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Effective Strategies for Parenting a Child with ADHD from Dr. Kyle Daigle's Book]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ effective-strategies-parenting-child-adhd-dr-kyle-daigles-book-471425 <description><![CDATA[In his book, Dr. Daigle emphasizes the importance of understanding the multifaceted risk factors for early intervention and the support of ADHD.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ effective-strategies-parenting-child-adhd-dr-kyle-daigles-book-471425</guid><pubDate> Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:20:56 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>