<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Best Uses Of Kinesiology Tape: How This Elastic Sports Tape Can Enhance Performance And Recovery]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-uses-kinesiology-tape-how-this-elastic-sports-tape-can-enhance-performance-recovery-472344 <description><![CDATA[Kinesiology tape is a versatile tool that provides pain relief, muscle support, and improved circulation for a wide range of individuals. Whether you're an athlete looking to improve performance or someone recovering from an injury, kinesiology tape offers a non-invasive, effective way to promote healing and enhance mobility.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-uses-kinesiology-tape-how-this-elastic-sports-tape-can-enhance-performance-recovery-472344</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Sep 2024 15:32:38 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Water Flossers Of 2024 For A Cleaner, Healthier Smile]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-water-flowers-2024-cleaner-healthier-smile-472353 <description><![CDATA[Water flossers are an excellent addition to oral care routines, providing a more effective and gentler way to remove plaque and debris from between teeth and along the gum line compared to traditional flossing. They are especially beneficial for people with braces, implants, or sensitive gums. Whether you're looking for a compact option for travel or a powerful model for home use, there's a water flosser to suit every need and budget.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-water-flowers-2024-cleaner-healthier-smile-472353</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:25:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Body Posture Correctors To Help You Walk With Confidence And Ease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-body-posture- Correctors-help-you-walk-confidence-ease-472326 <description><![CDATA[Lower back pain affects around 619 million people worldwide and it is the leading cause of disability worldwide, according to a survey by National Centre for Health Statistics.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-body-posture- Correctors-help-you-walk-confidence-ease-472326</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:24:05 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Cervical Collars For Effective Neck Stabilization And Pain Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cervical-collars- effective-neck-stabilization-pain-relief-472342 <description><![CDATA[Cervical collars, or neck braces, are essential medical devices used to support and stabilize the cervical spine. They are commonly employed in the recovery from neck injuries, surgical procedures, and chronic neck conditions such as cervical spondylosis and whiplash.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-cervical-collars- effective-neck-stabilization-pain-relief-472342</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:22:33 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Foot Braces For Comfort And Support: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-foot-braces-comfort-support-compressive-guide-472322 <description><![CDATA[Discover the best foot braces to enhance comfort and support, whether for injury recovery or daily use. From ankle braces and compression sleeves to night splints and custom orthotics, this guide highlights key types and benefits. Find the perfect foot brace to alleviate pain, prevent injuries, and improve overall foot health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-foot-braces-comfort-support-compressive-guide-472322</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:17:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Ketone Strips: What's Ketosis And How To Measure And Use The Strips?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-ketone-strips-what-is-ketosis-how-to-measure-use-strips-472333 <description><![CDATA[In people who are diabetic, a high level of ketones in the urine can signal a dangerous condition known as diabetic ketoacidosis. Therefore, it is crucial for them to monitor their ketone levels regularly. People following a low-carb ketogenic diet should also consider taking this test.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-ketone-strips-what-is-ketosis-how-to-measure-use-strips-472333</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:13:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exposure To Air Pollution During Pregnancy Quadruples Postpartum Depression Risk Up To 3 Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-to-air-pollution-during-pregnancy-quadruples-risk-of-postpartum-depression-3-year-study-472348 <description><![CDATA[The latest study revealed that pollution during pregnancy nearly quadruples the risk of postpartum depression, with this heightened risk lasting for up to three years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-to-air-pollution-during-pregnancy-quadruples-risk-of-postpartum-depression-3-year-study-472348</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Sep 2024 02:52:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Doses Of ADHD Drugs Linked To More Than 5 Times Risk Of Psychosis: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-dose-adhd-drugs-linked-more-5-times-risk-of-psychosis-study-472345 <description><![CDATA[Taking high doses of medications for ADHD, particularly amphetamines is linked to more than five times the risk of developing psychosis or mania.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-dose-adhd-drugs-linked-more-5-times-risk-of-psychosis-study-472345</guid><pubDate> Fri, 13 Sep 2024 02:06:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Orthopedic Knee And Leg Pillows For Pain Relief]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-orthopedic-knee-leg-pillows-pain-relief-472299 <description><![CDATA[A knee pillow is specifically designed to promote spinal alignment. It can prevent your back from arching too much and make side sleeping comfortable.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-orthopedic-knee-leg-pillows-pain-relief-472299</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:59:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Children's Screen Time Mirrors Parents', Excessive Use Affects Language Skills: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-screen-time-mirrors-parents-excessive-use-affects-language-skills-study-472340 <description><![CDATA[The study found that kids' screen habits closely mirror those of their parents and excessive screen use in the family can negatively impact children's language development.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/children-screen-time-mirrors-parents-excessive-use-affects-language-skills-study-472340</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Sep 2024 05:03:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Dry Eyes? Laughter May Be The Best Medicine, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dry-eyes-laughter-may-be-best-medicine-says-study-472337 <description><![CDATA[The study suggests that laughter could be a safe, low-cost remedy for those struggling with dry eyes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dry-eyes-laughter-may-be-best-medicine-says-study-472337</guid><pubDate> Thu, 12 Sep 2024 03:15:33 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>