<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>母亲</title><link/>https：/www.was.com.com<description>在救世主上</description><language>曾是</language><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Hangover? Have This Before Drinks, Says Doctor]]></title><link/> htts：/wowing。 <description><![CDATA[Here's a simple trick to prevent the unpleasant aftermath of drinking alcohol.]]></description><guid> htts：/wowing。</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:51:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Have This Gut Healthy Snack Twice A Week, It Can Protect You From Aggressive Colorectal Cancer]]></title><link/> htts：/wowing。 <description><![CDATA[A new study discovered that a popular gut-healthy snack could offer protection against colorectal cancer, a finding that offers hope as cases rise, particularly among young adults.]]></description><guid> htts：/wowing。</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:45:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctor Warns: Avoid These Foods If You Take Medications, Eating This Fruit Can Even Be Toxic]]></title><link/>他的hetps：/wowling <description><![CDATA[A doctor now warns that certain food items can interfere with the absorption of medications, affecting their effectiveness, or in rare cases causing toxicity when combined with pills.]]></description><guid>他的hetps：/wowling</guid><pubDate> Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:40:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Want To Lose Weight? Nutritionist Shares Foods That Naturally Mimic Ozempic]]></title><link/> httops：/哇。 <description><![CDATA[A nutritionist shares 8 high-quality foods that naturally mimic the effects of Ozempic by boosting satiety, balancing blood sugar, reducing cravings, and helping make fat loss easier.]]></description><guid> httops：/哇。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Feb 2025 03:51:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[6-Year-Old's Weight Doubles In A Year, And Mom Thinks It's Lockdown Gain Before Fatal Cancer Diagnosis]]></title><link/> httops：/wowwow.damymical.com/senal-to-doubs-to-doubles-more-bindin-bebeing-being-bebeing-bebe-bibind-bindon-brange-bigina-bigina-beca-bebeing-being-being-being-being-bebeing-be be be be be be be be be bebeing-bebeing- - 边缘 - 阳性 - 阳性 - 边缘 - 边缘 - 阳性 - 阳性 - 阳性。 <description><![CDATA[The boy's mother now realizes his weight gain and other unusual signs were early warnings of cancer, and now shares his story to raise awareness about brain tumor symptoms.]]></description><guid> httops：/wowwow.damymical.com/senal-to-doubs-to-doubles-more-bindin-bebeing-being-bebeing-bebe-bibind-bindon-brange-bigina-bigina-beca-bebeing-being-being-being-being-bebeing-be be be be be be be be be bebeing-bebeing- - 边缘 - 阳性 - 阳性 - 边缘 - 边缘 - 阳性 - 阳性 - 阳性。</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:54:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Indiana Doctors Go To Court To Keep Terminated Pregnancy Reports From Being Released To The Public]]></title><link/> https：/wow.dalysicals.comdain-sodina-sodina-to-greet-greet-panding-pand-prince-prince-princes 4731000 <description><![CDATA[Two abortion providers in Indiana advocating against the release of individual terminated pregnancy reports have filed a lawsuit to keep the records private.]]></description><guid> https：/wow.dalysicals.comdain-sodina-sodina-to-greet-greet-panding-pand-prince-prince-princes 4731000</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:59:36 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is 'Lemonading'? When Life Gives You Lemons, Having This Personality Trait Helps]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-lemonading-when-life-gives-you-lemons-having-having-this-this-this-this-persallity-thrait-trait-helps-473097 <description><![CDATA[Researchers find scientific proof for the benefits of being playful during adversities.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-lemonading-when-life-gives-you-lemons-having-having-this-this-this-this-persallity-thrait-trait-helps-473097</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Feb 2025 04:49:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Woman With Rare Condition Suffers Constant Arousal, Multiple Orgasms: 'It's Pain, Not Pleasure,' Know More About PGAD]]></title><link/> httops:/wowling.damicy.com/sale-sweet-suffert-suffer-start-to-testins-to-ordins-ons-on- 4063. <description><![CDATA[The 36-year-old shares her story to raise awareness about this often misunderstood and stigmatized condition that has completely disrupted her life.]]></description><guid> httops:/wowling.damicy.com/sale-sweet-suffert-suffer-start-to-testins-to-ordins-ons-on- 4063.</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Feb 2025 01:37:43 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teen Dies From Rare Brain Tumor After Unusual Symptoms; Heartbroken Mom Urges Others To Recognize Signs]]></title><link/> httops：/wow。 - 风险和47309-Sorprick-State-Same-Orch。 <description><![CDATA[After years of battling the disease, the young girl passed away at the age of 16, and her heartbroken mother now raises awareness about the cancer, hoping that parents could spot the signs as soon as possible.]]></description><guid> httops：/wow。 - 风险和47309-Sorprick-State-Same-Orch。</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:41:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fat Or Carbs? Identical Twins Followed Different Diets For 12 Weeks; Results Will Surprise You]]></title><link/> hetps：/wowing <description><![CDATA[In a fascinating experiment, a pair of identical twins followed two different diets, one loaded with fat and the other with carbs, for 12 weeks. The results may surprise you.]]></description><guid> hetps：/wowing</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:22:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stuck On Your Weight Loss Journey? Here's Nutritionist's Cheat Code To Shed Pounds In 3 Months]]></title><link/> htts：/www。 <description><![CDATA[For those looking to kickstart their weight loss journey or those struggling along the way, here are some practical tips from a nutritionist.]]></description><guid> htts：/www。</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Feb 2025 05:18:39 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>