<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>是</language><item><title><![CDATA[14% Of U.S. Adults Have Inadequate Iron, Study Finds: Here's How to Spot Deficiency]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/14-us-adults-have-inadequate-iron-study-finds-heres-how-spot-deficiency-472463 <description><![CDATA[The study found that 14% of U.S. adults lack adequate iron, while 15% have functional iron deficiency, where their bodies can't properly use the iron they have.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/14-us-adults-have-inadequate-iron-study-finds-heres-how-spot-deficiency-472463</guid><pubDate> Fri, 27 Sep 2024 01:42:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exposure To Air Pollution During Pregnancy And Childhood Have Lasting Effects On Brain: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-air-pollution-during-pregnancy-childhood-have- permanent-effects-brain-study-472457 <description><![CDATA[Exposure to fine particles (PM2.5) and nitrogen oxides (NOx) during pregnancy and childhood can lead to significant changes in the microstructure of the brain's white matter, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-air-pollution-during-pregnancy-childhood-have- permanent-effects-brain-study-472457</guid><pubDate> Thu, 26 Sep 2024 07:04:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Myopia Affects 1 In 3 Children, Expected To Surge To 40% By 2050]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/myopia-affects-1-3-children-expected-surge-40-2050-472454 <description><![CDATA[Researchers believe that one of the possible reasons for the rise in near-sightedness may be the decrease in outdoor activities and an increase in screen time, particularly due to online classes during the pandemic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/myopia-affects-1-3-children-expected-surge-40-2050-472454</guid><pubDate> Thu, 26 Sep 2024 04:08:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Researchers Suggest Body Roundness Index As New Predictor Of Cardiovascular Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/researchers-suggest-body-roundness-index-new-predictor-cardioangio-risk-472453 <description><![CDATA[For adults older than 45, a higher body roundness index over six years suggests a greater risk of developing cardiovascular disease, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/researchers-suggest-body-roundness-index-new-predictor-cardioangio-risk-472453</guid><pubDate> Thu, 26 Sep 2024 01:48:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Medicine Balls To Boost Strength And Power]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-medicine-balls-boost-strength-power-472441 <description><![CDATA[Medicine balls are a dynamic, multifaceted tool that can improve power, stability, balance, and coordination. If you're aiming to increase performance or recover from injury, incorporating medicine ball exercises into your fitness routine can lead to significant benefits across multiple aspects of physical health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-medicine-balls-boost-strength-power-472441</guid><pubDate> Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:54:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Yoga Wheels For Flexibility, Balance And Strength]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-yoga-wheels-flexibility-balance-strength-472425 <description><![CDATA[Yoga wheels are more than just a trend; they are valuable tools that can significantly enhance your yoga practice. From improving flexibility and balance to deepening backbends and promoting mindfulness, the benefits of incorporating a yoga wheel are manifold. Whether you are new to yoga or a seasoned practitioner, exploring the use of a yoga wheel can lead to new insights, improved performance, and a more fulfilling practice.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-yoga-wheels-flexibility-balance-strength-472425</guid><pubDate> Wed, 25 Sep 2024 12:37:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Influenza During Pregnancy Raises Risk Of Seizures In Offspring: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/influenza-during-pregnancy-raises-risk-seizures-offspring-study-472447 <description><![CDATA[The study examined how a mother's influenza infection during pregnancy affected the risk of her child developing different types of seizures during childhood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/influenza-during-pregnancy-raises-risk-seizures-offspring-study-472447</guid><pubDate> Wed, 25 Sep 2024 06:14:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[EEE Declared 'Public Health Threat' After NY Man Dies From Mosquito-Borne Virus]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eee-declared-public-health-threat-after-ny-man-dies-mosquito-borne-virus-472445 <description><![CDATA[The NY Man's death marks the second EEE-related fatality in the U.S. this year after a New Hampshire resident succumbed to the virus last month.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eee-declared-public-health-threat-after-ny-man-dies-mosquito-borne-virus-472445</guid><pubDate> Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:05:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Prediabetes In Young Adults: Here's How It Affects Pregnancy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prediabetes-young-adults-heres-how-it-affects-pregnancy-472444 <description><![CDATA[The research team discovered that having prediabetes before conception more than doubles the risk of developing gestational diabetes in the first pregnancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/prediabetes-young-adults-heres-how-it-affects-pregnancy-472444</guid><pubDate> Wed, 25 Sep 2024 01:20:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Mouth Guards For Grinding Teeth At Night: Top Solutions For Bruxism Relief, Peaceful Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-mouth-guards-grinding-teeth-night-top-solutions-bruxism-relief-peaceful-sleep-472426 <description><![CDATA[This article explores the best mouthguards designed specifically for individuals who grind their teeth at night, a condition known as bruxism. It discusses the effectiveness of these guards in protecting teeth from damage, reducing jaw discomfort, and improving overall sleep quality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-mouth-guards-grinding-teeth-night-top-solutions-bruxism-relief-peaceful-sleep-472426</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:25:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Foam Rollers For Muscle Recovery, Flexibility And Injury Prevention]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-foam-rollers-muscle-recovery-flexibility-injury-prevention-472423 <description><![CDATA[Foam rollers are a versatile and affordable tool that can greatly benefit your fitness journey. By promoting faster recovery, enhancing flexibility, and preventing injuries, they help ensure that your muscles stay healthy and functional, whether you're training for a marathon or simply staying active.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-foam-rollers-muscle-recovery-flexibility-injury-prevention-472423</guid><pubDate> Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:24:17 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>