<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Hospitalization From Heart Diseases Raises Mental Health Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospitalization-heart-diseases-raises-mental-health-risk-study-472056 <description><![CDATA[The study highlights the heightened risk for mental health issues, including anxiety, depression, and self-harm, during the recovery years, especially within the first year after hospitalization for cardiovascular diseases.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospitalization-heart-diseases-raises-mental-health-risk-study-472056</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:17:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top Picks For Amino Acid Supplements In 2024: Boost Your Fitness Goals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-picks-amino-acid-supplements-2024-boost-your-fitness-goals-472052 <description><![CDATA[Amino acids are the building blocks of proteins, vital for muscle repair, hormone production and immune support. Of the 20 amino acids, nine are essential and must be obtained from foods like meat, fish, eggs, dairy, beans and nuts. A balanced intake of these nutrients is crucial for energy, tissue repair and overall health, making amino acids important for everyone, from athletes to those simply aiming to stay healthy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-picks-amino-acid-supplements-2024-boost-your-fitness-goals-472052</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:15:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Fish Oil Benefit Older Adult Brains? Here's What Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-fish-oil-benefit-older-adult-brains-heres-what-study-says-472048 <description><![CDATA[According to the study, omega-3 fatty acid use could benefit those with a genetic predisposition to Alzheimer's. However, researchers did not find significant benefits for all older adults in general.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-fish-oil-benefit-older-adult-brains-heres-what-study-says-472048</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Aug 2024 03:29:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Trying To Cut Calories? Skip The Dip With Your Chips]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trying-cut-calories-skip-dip-your-chips-472049 <description><![CDATA[Researchers discovered that when consumers pair chips with dip, their caloric intake shot up by 77% compared to just eating chips alone.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/trying-cut-calories-skip-dip-your-chips-472049</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Aug 2024 03:21:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Drug Could Cut Colorectal Cancer Risk In People With Unhealthy Lifestyle: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-drug-could-cut-colorectal-cancer-risk-people-unhealthy-lifestyle-study-472047 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that regular use of aspirin could slash colorectal cancer risk in people already at risk from unhealthy lifestyles.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/common-drug-could-cut-colorectal-cancer-risk-people-unhealthy-lifestyle-study-472047</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:13:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[One Step Closer To Hair Rejuvenation: The Best Ways To Deal With Hairloss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/one-step-closer-hair-rejuvenation-best-ways-deal-hairloss-472028 <description><![CDATA[For men, FDA-approved medications like Minoxidil, the generic for Rogaine®, offer a safe and effective solution for hair loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/one-step-closer-hair-rejuvenation-best-ways-deal-hairloss-472028</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Aug 2024 08:50:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cut Down On Processed Meat, Swap It With Nuts To Reduce Dementia Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-down-processed-meat-swap-it-nuts-reduce-dementia-risk-study-472045 <description><![CDATA[Recent research uncovers a concerning link between processed meat and an increased risk of dementia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-down-processed-meat-swap-it-nuts-reduce-dementia-risk-study-472045</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:51:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Many Cocoa Products Contain Toxic Heavy Metals, Higher Levels In Organic Chocolates: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/many-cocoa-products-contain-有毒-heavy-metals-higher-levels-organic-chocolates-study-472042 <description><![CDATA[Researchers cautioned that their findings do not mean consumers should completely avoid chocolates but enjoy them in moderation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/many-cocoa-products-contain-有毒-heavy-metals-higher-levels-organic-chocolates-study-472042</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:48:04 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gen X, Millennials At Higher Risk Of Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gen-x-millennials-higher-risk-cancer-study-472041 <description><![CDATA[The study found that 17 types of cancers, including breast, pancreatic, and gastric cancers, are rising in younger generations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/gen-x-millennials-higher-risk-cancer-study-472041</guid><pubDate> Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:50:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Loss Drugs With Semaglutide May Help Quit Smoking: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-semaglutide-may-help-quit-smoking-study-472038 <description><![CDATA[Semaglutide drugs such as Ozempic and Wegovy could help tobacco smokers quit smoking, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-semaglutide-may-help-quit-smoking-study-472038</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:16:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Chronic Cough Be Inherited? Here's What Studies Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-chronic-cough-inherited-heres-what-studies-say-472037 <description><![CDATA[Two separate studies have found that chronic cough may have a genetic component, and the condition particularly impacts middle-aged women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-chronic-cough-inherited-heres-what-studies-say-472037</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:38:44 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>