<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Reports Second Human Case Of Bird Flu In Michigan Dairy Worker]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-reports-second- human-case-bird-flu-michigan-dairy-worker-471772 <description><![CDATA[The CDC confirmed there is still no evidence of human-to-human transmission, and infection risk to the public remains low.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-reports-second- human-case-bird-flu-michigan-dairy-worker-471772</guid><pubDate> Thu, 23 May 2024 02:12:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Metformin Prevent Cancer? Study Links It To Reduced Blood Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-metformin-prevent-cancer-study-links-it-reduced-blood-cancer-risk-471768 <description><![CDATA[The surprising potential of metformin for cancer prevention emerged after researchers found an association between metformin use and a reduced risk of myeloproliferative neoplasms (MPN), a rare type of blood cancer that can progress to acute leukemia.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-metformin-prevent-cancer-study-links-it-reduced-blood-cancer-risk-471768</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 May 2024 04:37:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ex-Smokers Who Vape Still At High Risk Of Lung Cancer: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ex-smokers-who-vape-still-high-risk-lung-cancer-study-471766 <description><![CDATA[Ex-smokers who vape still face a high risk of lung cancer compared to those who quit nicotine completely.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ex-smokers-who-vape-still-high-risk-lung-cancer-study-471766</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 May 2024 02:45:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fish Oil Supplements May Raise Heart Disease, Stroke Risk In Healthy Individuals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fish-oil-supplements-may-raise-heart-disease-中风-risk-healthy-individuals-471764 <description><![CDATA[While fish oil supplements may slow disease progression and lower the risk of death in people with a history of cardiovascular diseases, they might increase the risk of first-time heart disease and stroke among healthy individuals.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fish-oil-supplements-may-raise-heart-disease-中风-risk-healthy-individuals-471764</guid><pubDate> Wed, 22 May 2024 01:29:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Exercise That Could Reduce Knee Pain, Risk Of Osteoarthritis ]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-exercise-that-c​​ould-reduce-knee-pain-risk-osteoarthritis-471761 <description><![CDATA[Regular bicycling could reduce the chances of frequent knee pain, radiographic osteoarthritis (ROA), and symptomatic radiographic osteoarthritis (SOA), the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-exercise-that-c​​ould-reduce-knee-pain-risk-osteoarthritis-471761</guid><pubDate> Tue, 21 May 2024 05:07:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Spike In Nightmares, Hallucinations Could Be Warning Signs Of Lupus: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spike-nightmares-hallucinations-could-warning-signs-lupus-study-471759 <description><![CDATA[A spike in nightmares and hallucinations could indicate the onset of autoimmune diseases such as lupus and signal an approaching disease flare, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/spike-nightmares-hallucinations-could-warning-signs-lupus-study-471759</guid><pubDate> Tue, 21 May 2024 03:17:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fluoride Exposure During Pregnancy Increases Risk of Neurobehavioral Issues In Toddlers: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluide-exposure-during-pregnancy-increases-risk-neurobehavioral-issues-toddlers-study-471757 <description><![CDATA[Children with more prenatal fluoride exposure experienced issues such as emotional reactivity, somatic complaints including headaches and stomachaches, anxiety, and symptoms linked to autism.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fluide-exposure-during-pregnancy-increases-risk-neurobehavioral-issues-toddlers-study-471757</guid><pubDate> Tue, 21 May 2024 01:42:16 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Take Breaks From Keto: Study Says Long-Term Consumption Accelerates Organ Aging]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-breaks-keto-study-says-long-term-conspiration-accelerates-organ-aging-471756 <description><![CDATA[A continuous long-term ketogenic diet may induce senescence, the accumulation of aged cells in normal tissues, affecting the health of heart and kidney function in particular, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/take-breaks-keto-study-says-long-term-conspiration-accelerates-organ-aging-471756</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:53 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Changes In Your Nail Color May Signal Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/changes-your-nail-color-may-signal-cancer-risk-471755 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now recommend nail screening in patients with a personal or family history of melanoma or other potential BAP1-associated malignancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/changes-your-nail-color-may-signal-cancer-risk-471755</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 May 2024 02:49:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Just One Hour On Social Media Doubles Risk Of Smoking, Vaping Among Youth: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/just-one-hour-social-media-doubles-risk-smoking-vaping-among-youth-study-471754 <description><![CDATA[While spending as little as one hour on social media could double the risk of smoking and vaping, those likely to be glued to social media with more than seven hours of daily use could face triple the risk, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/just-one-hour-social-media-doubles-risk-smoking-vaping-among-youth-study-471754</guid><pubDate> Mon, 20 May 2024 01:14:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mediterranean Diet Lowers Anxiety And Stress In Elderly Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mediterranean-diet-lowers-anxiety-stress-elderly-adults-study-471752 <description><![CDATA[The study found that in addition to promoting physical health, the Mediterranean diet could also play a significant role in improving mental wellness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mediterranean-diet-lowers-anxiety-stress-elderly-adults-study-471752</guid><pubDate> Fri, 17 May 2024 03:42:46 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>