<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Washing May Not Reduce Pesticides On Fruits, But Peeling Helps: Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/washing-may-not-reduce-pesticides-fruits-peeling-helps-says-study-472096 <description><![CDATA[Using a new imaging technique—surface-enhanced Raman spectroscopy (SERS)—researchers found that pesticides can penetrate beyond the peel and into the pulp layer of fruits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/washing-may-not-reduce-pesticides-fruits-peeling-helps-says-study-472096</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:21:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Neffy: Know All About First FDA Approved Nasal Spray To Treat Severe Allergic Reactions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neffy-know-all-about-first-fda-approved-nasal-spray-treat-severe-allergic-reactions-472095 <description><![CDATA[The new treatment, a needle-free alternative, could be used for managing severe allergic responses in children and adults, weighing at least 66 pounds, the FDA said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neffy-know-all-about-first-fda-approved-nasal-spray-treat-severe-allergic-reactions-472095</guid><pubDate> Mon, 12 Aug 2024 01:58:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sugar Substitute Erythritol Raises Risk Of Heart Attacks, Stroke: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sugar-substitute-erythritol-raises-risk-heart-attacks-中风-study-472093 <description><![CDATA[Adding more evidence to the increased risk associated with sugar substitutes, researchers of a recent study have identified that erythritol, a common low-calorie sweetener, could raise the risk of heart attacks and strokes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sugar-substitute-erythritol-raises-risk-heart-attacks-中风-study-472093</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Aug 2024 03:57:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Myths Busted: Expert Insights During Breastfeeding Awareness Month]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/myths-busted-expert-insights-during-breastfeeding-awareness-month-472090 <description><![CDATA[Misconceptions surrounding breastfeeding often discourage women from trying. During this Breastfeeding Awareness Month, an international board-certified lactation consultant shares the facts to help dispel these myths.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/myths-busted-expert-insights-during-breastfeeding-awareness-month-472090</guid><pubDate> Fri, 09 Aug 2024 02:08:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Friend's Genetic Traits Can Influence Your Mental Health Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/friends-genic-traits-can-influence-your-mental-health-risk-study-472082 <description><![CDATA[The traits of your friends, particularly their genetic predisposition to mental health issues, can influence your mental health risks, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/friends-genic-traits-can-influence-your-mental-health-risk-study-472082</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:41:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Kangaroo Care For Preemies: Skin-To-Skin Cuddling Improves Neurodevelopment, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kangaroo-care-preemies-skin-skin-cuddling-improves-neurodevelopment-says-study-472080 <description><![CDATA[A study revealed that even small increases in the amount of skin-to-skin time with premature babies could make a measurable difference in their neurologic development in the first year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kangaroo-care-preemies-skin-skin-cuddling-improves-neurodevelopment-says-study-472080</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:14:13 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Watching Even 8 Minutes Of TikTok Glamorizing Disordered Eating Harms Body Image, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watching-even-8-minutes-tiktok-glamorizing-disordered-eating-harms-body-image-study-finds-472078 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that even short exposure to "pro-anorexia" content that glorifies extreme weight loss and restricted diet is sufficient to harm body image and affect women's mental health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/watching-even-8-minutes-tiktok-glamorizing-disordered-eating-harms-body-image-study-finds-472078</guid><pubDate> Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:09:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Secret To Cholesterol Control? Study Finds Corn Flour Blend Could Be A Game Changer]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/secret-cholesterol-control-study-finds-corn-flour-blend-could-game-changer-472076 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that incorporating a blend of refined corn flour and corn bran can reduce LDL (low-density lipoprotein) cholesterol levels by 5% to 13.3% in just four weeks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/secret-cholesterol-control-study-finds-corn-flour-blend-could-game-changer-472076</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:34:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[EPA Issues Emergency Ban On Common Weedkiller Citing Risk To Unborn Babies]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/epa-issues-emergency-ban-common-weedkiller-citing-risk-unborn-babies-472073 <description><![CDATA[In the first emergency ban in nearly 40 years, the EPA has highlighted serious risks for unborn children from maternal exposure to DCPA.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/epa-issues-emergency-ban-common-weedkiller-citing-risk-unborn-babies-472073</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:46:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breakthrough Monthly Treatment May Boost Longevity, Vitality In Old Age: Mice Study Reveals]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakthrough-monthly-treatment-may-boost-longevity-vitality-old-age-mice-study-reveals-472070 <description><![CDATA[The new study offers promising insights into how we might be able to have both longevity and vitality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakthrough-monthly-treatment-may-boost-longevity-vitality-old-age-mice-study-reveals-472070</guid><pubDate> Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:41:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Ashwagandha Supplements Of 2024 For Optimal Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-benefits-ashwagandha-ancient-herb-modern-pottial-472068 <description><![CDATA[Ashwagandha supplements, made from the Withania somnifera plant, come in capsules, powders, and extracts. They're commonly used to help reduce stress, boost physical performance, and enhance cognitive function. For the best results, choose high-quality products from reputable brands and consult a healthcare professional before starting any new supplement.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/exploring-benefits-ashwagandha-ancient-herb-modern-pottial-472068</guid><pubDate> Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:32:21 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>