<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder Awareness Month: Eliminate Stigma As Expert Unveils Facts And Myths]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/post-traumatic-stress-disorder-awareness-month-eliminate-stigma-expert-unveils-facts-myths-471846 <description><![CDATA[Post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) is a frequently misunderstood mental health condition, often unfairly seen as a sign of weakness.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/post-traumatic-stress-disorder-awareness-month-eliminate-stigma-expert-unveils-facts-myths-471846</guid><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jun 2024 01:30:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Planetary Health Diet? Study Says It May Reduce Premature Death By 30%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-planetary-health-diet-study-says-it-may-reduce-premature-death-30-471844 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered that adhering to a healthy, sustainable diet, termed the planetary health diet, can help preserve the environment and lower the risk of premature death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-planetary-health-diet-study-says-it-may-reduce-premature-death-30-471844</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jun 2024 03:58:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hospitalizations With Seizures, Loss Of Consciousness Linked To Microdosing Chocolate Bars, FDA Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospitalizations-seizures-loss-thought-linked-microdosing-chocolate-bars-fda-warns-471842 <description><![CDATA[FDA has issued a warning after six people were hospitalized across four states following the consumption of Diamond Shruumz-brand's microdosing chocolate bars.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hospitalizations-seizures-loss-thought-linked-microdosing-chocolate-bars-fda-warns-471842</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jun 2024 03:17:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Best Time To Exercise For Reducing Blood Sugar Levels]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-time-exercise-reducing-blood-sugar-levels-471841 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now identified the optimal time to exercise for reducing blood sugar levels in sedentary adults struggling with overweight and obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-best-time-exercise-reducing-blood-sugar-levels-471841</guid><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jun 2024 01:27:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Omega-3 Supplements Now Have A Vegan Option; Here's Why You Need To Take Them Daily]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-supplements-now-have-vegan-option-heres-why-you-need-take-them-daily-471839 <description><![CDATA[Omega-3 is known for cognitive advantages like improving brain development, enhancing mental performance, and lowering the risk of neurodegenerative disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/omega-3-supplements-now-have-vegan-option-heres-why-you-need-take-them-daily-471839</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:26:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Use Of Social Media Photo Filters Raises Muscle Dysmorphia In Young Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/use-social-media-photo-filters-raises-muscle-dysmorphia-young-adults-study-471838 <description><![CDATA[The use of social media photo filters has a strong association with increased symptoms of muscle dysmorphia, a mental health condition characterized by excessive obsession with muscularity and leanness, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/use-social-media-photo-filters-raises-muscle-dysmorphia-young-adults-study-471838</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:01:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Planning A Trip Abroad? Here's How To Reduce Risk Of Yellow Fever]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-trip-abroad-heres-how-reduce-risk-yellow-fever-471837 <description><![CDATA[If tropical destinations such as South America or Africa are on your itinerary, know all about yellow fever and learn essential tips to minimize your risk of contracting the infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/planning-trip-abroad-heres-how-reduce-risk-yellow-fever-471837</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:30:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Viagra Improves Brain Blood Flow, Reduces Dementia Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viagra-improves-brain-blood-flow-reduces-dementia-risk-study-471836 <description><![CDATA[A study suggests Viagra could revolutionize the treatment and prevention of vascular dementia, a condition for which specific therapies are currently unavailable.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/viagra-improves-brain-blood-flow-reduces-dementia-risk-study-471836</guid><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:20:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Higher Stroke Risk For Women Overweight In Teenage Or Young Adult Years: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-行程-risk-women-overweight-teenage-young-adult-years-study-471835 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that having excess body weight at age 14 or 31 raises the risk of ischemic stroke in women by the age of 55.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/higher-行程-risk-women-overweight-teenage-young-adult-years-study-471835</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:45:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Xylitol Sweetener Linked To Increased Risk Of Heart Attacks, Stroke: Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/xylitol-sweetener-linked-increased-risk-heart-attacks-中风-study-finds-471833 <description><![CDATA[Xylitol, a natural sugar alcohol found in plants, is a sugar substitute used in candies, gums, baked goods, and toothpaste. ]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/xylitol-sweetener-linked-increased-risk-heart-attacks-中风-study-finds-471833</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jun 2024 03:27:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salmonella Outbreak Linked To Cucumbers Sickens 162 In 25 States, CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-cucumbers-sickens-162-25-states-cdc-warns-471831 <description><![CDATA[Salmonella outbreak linked to cucumbers sickened 162, resulting in 54 hospitalizations across 25 states.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-cucumbers-sickens-162-25-states-cdc-warns-471831</guid><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:06:33 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>