<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Dentures May Raise Risk Of Pneumonia; Tips To Keep Them Clean]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dentures-may-raise-risk-pneumonia-tips-keep-them-clean-470303 <description><![CDATA[Did you know that if you don't take care of your dentures, it can even lead to pneumonia?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dentures-may-raise-risk-pneumonia-tips-keep-them-clean-470303</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 03:32:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Intermittent Fasting Vs Energy Restriction: Study Says Both Yield Similar Weight Loss Outcomes]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intermittent-fasting-vs-energy-restriction-study-says-both-yield-similar-weight-loss-outcomes-470300 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say it is better to combine physical activities with intermittent fasting to lose weight effectively.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intermittent-fasting-vs-energy-restriction-study-says-both-yield-similar-weight-loss-outcomes-470300</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 03:10:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National HIV Testing Day: Types Of Tests, Why They Are Important]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-hiv-testing-day-types-tests-why-they-are-important-470301 <description><![CDATA[This year's theme for National HIV Testing Day, "Take the Test &amp; Take the Next Step" encourages people to get tested for HIV and helps them choose options to stay healthy regardless of their test results.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-hiv-testing-day-types-tests-why-they-are-important-470301</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 02:56:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Chronic Liver Diseases Affect Brain Health? Study Says They Can Reduce Cognitive Ability]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-liver-diseases-affect-brain-health-study-says-they-can-reduce-cognitive-ability-470297 <description><![CDATA[A new study suggests that liver fibrosis associated with chronic liver diseases can reduce cognitive ability and brain volume.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-liver-diseases-affect-brain-health-study-says-they-can-reduce-cognitive-ability-470297</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 01:24:27 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Virus Expert Says Japan Has Entered Ninth COVID Wave]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virus-expert-says-japan-has-entered-ninth-covid-wave-470295 <description><![CDATA[After easing countermeasures, Japan has seemingly entered its ninth wave of COVID-19 infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/virus-expert-says-japan-has-entered-ninth-covid-wave-470295</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 22:05:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Recent Mpox Cases Prompt Colorado To Launch Vaccination Campaign]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/recent-mpox-cases-prompt-colorado-launch-vaccination-campaign-470292<description><![CDATA[Colorado has initiated a new vaccination campaign amid the mpox resurgence.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/recent-mpox-cases-prompt-colorado-launch-vaccination-campaign-470292</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 22:00:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Promising Advances In Cancer Treatment: Vaccines As The Next Breakthrough]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/promising-advances-cancer-treatment-vaccines-next-breakthrough-470289 <description><![CDATA[Cancer vaccines could be the next breakthrough in the medical world.]]></description><guid>https://www.medicaldaily.com/promising-advances-cancer-treatment-vaccines-next-breakthrough-470289</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 21:52:16 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[9 Cats Die Due To Bird Flu In Poland Amid Outbreak]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-cats-die-due-bird-flu-poland-amid-outbreak-470286 <description><![CDATA[Poland reported nine feline deaths linked to the H5N1 bird flu virus.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/9-cats-die-due-bird-flu-poland-amid-outbreak-470286</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 21:42:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[High Coffee Consumption Increases Risk Of Abdominal Arterial Calcification In People With Hypertension: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-coffee-conspiration-increases-risk-abdominal-arterial-calcification-people-hypertension-470282 <description><![CDATA[While moderate coffee consumption is believed to reverse life-threatening diseases like metabolic syndrome, Parkinson's Disease (PD), type 2 diabetes and some cancers, excessive intake of caffeine can increase the risk of cardiovascular diseases in people with hypertension, researchers say.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/high-coffee-conspiration-increases-risk-abdominal-arterial-calcification-people-hypertension-470282</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:35:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Heart Attacks Can Occur At Any Age: Factors Affecting Cardiovascular Health Of Young Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-attacks-can-occur-any-age-factors-affecting-cardioangio-health-young-adults-470284 <description><![CDATA[People are developing diabetes and hypertension, factors associated with heart attacks, much earlier than before.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/heart-attacks-can-occur-any-age-factors-affecting-cardioangio-health-young-adults-470284</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 03:57:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are You A Mosquito Magnet? Here's Why Some People Get Bitten More Than Others]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-you-mosquito-magnet-heres-why-some-people-get-bitten-more-others-470281 <description><![CDATA[Ever wondered why mosquitoes have a knack for singling you out in a crowd?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/are-you-mosquito-magnet-heres-why-some-people-get-bitten-more-others-470281</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 03:00:17 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>