<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Your Diet At 40 Decides Quality Of Life At 70, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-diet-40-decides-quality-life-70-says-study-471925 <description><![CDATA[The researchers discovered that maintaining a healthy diet in midlife could pave the way for a high-quality life at 70.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-diet-40-decides-quality-life-70-says-study-471925</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jul 2024 03:52:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Kisunla? Know All About New FDA-Approved Drug For Alzheimer's Disease]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-kisunla-know-all-about-new-fda-approved-drug-alzheimers-disease-471924 <description><![CDATA[Kisunla manufactured by Eli Lilly could significantly slow cognitive decline in people with early symptomatic Alzheimer's disease, according to results of the company's clinical trials.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-kisunla-know-all-about-new-fda-approved-drug-alzheimers-disease-471924</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jul 2024 02:46:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Bacterial Contamination Detected In Tattoo And Permanent Makeup Inks, Study Cautions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bacterial-contamination-Detected-tattoo-permanent-makeup-inks-study-cautions-471921 <description><![CDATA[A new study found that 35% of tattoo and permanent makeup inks sold across the U.S. are contaminated with bacteria.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bacterial-contamination-Detected-tattoo-permanent-makeup-inks-study-cautions-471921</guid><pubDate> Wed, 03 Jul 2024 02:01:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Discover How Angelina Fabian Utilizes The Power Of The 9 Centers Of The Human Design System For Self-Empowerment]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/discover-how-angelina-fabian-utilizes-power-9-centers- human-design-system-self-empowerment-471919 <description><![CDATA[The Human Design System intertwines ancient wisdom with modern science, offering new insights into how we think, feel, and act. It serves as a map that decodes our unique behaviors, desires, and paths to personal healing.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/discover-how-angelina-fabian-utilizes-power-9-centers- human-design-system-self-empowerment-471919</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:52:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultrasonic Rhinoplasty: A Revolutionary New Procedure with Dr. Hani Sinno]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultrasonic-rhinoplasty-revolutionary-new-procedure-dr-hani-sinno-471918 <description><![CDATA[Ultrasonic rhinoplasty, a cutting-edge technique used by Montreal-based cosmetic surgeon Dr. Hani Sinno, dramatically reduces risks and recovery time, making the procedure more feasible for many.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultrasonic-rhinoplasty-revolutionary-new-procedure-dr-hani-sinno-471918</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:48:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Kids Get Less Severe COVID-19 Compared To Adults; Here's Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kids-get-less-severe-covid-19-compared-adults-heres-why-471915 <description><![CDATA[The researchers say children's frequent exposure to respiratory infections is responsible for their heightened innate immunity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/kids-get-less-severe-covid-19-compared-adults-heres-why-471915</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jul 2024 04:30:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is BMI Heritable? Study Says Obesity In Teens Raises Offspring's Risk Of Same]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bmi-heritable-study-says-obesity-teens-raises-offsprings-risk-same-471912 <description><![CDATA[The researchers have now found that obesity in adolescence can affect the risk of the same in future generations.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/bmi-heritable-study-says-obesity-teens-raises-offsprings-risk-same-471912</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:28:15 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Gain From Antidepressants Varies; Here Are Drugs With Least And Most Impact]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-gain-antidepressants-varies-here-are-drugs-least-most-impact-471911 <description><![CDATA[In a new study, researchers analyzed eight different first-line antidepressants and identified the drugs that lead to the most weight gain and the ones with relatively lesser impact.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-gain-antidepressants-varies-here-are-drugs-least-most-impact-471911</guid><pubDate> Tue, 02 Jul 2024 01:47:22 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Exposure To Air Pollution In Childhood Linked To Bronchitis Risk Later In Life: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-air-pollution-childhood-linked-bronchitis-risk-later-life-study-471909 <description><![CDATA[The study discovered that childhood exposure to air pollution is linked to lung issues during childhood, which in turn are consistently associated with respiratory problems in adulthood.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/exposure-air-pollution-childhood-linked-bronchitis-risk-later-life-study-471909</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Jul 2024 04:33:41 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Fathers' Intake Of Fish Oil Supplements May Lower Children's Obesity Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fathers-fish-oil-supplementation-may-lower-childs-obesity-risk-471906 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests fish oil supplementation in fathers as a "secret weapon" to combat the issue of childhood obesity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fathers-fish-oil-supplementation-may-lower-childs-obesity-risk-471906</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:22:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pre-Conception Calcium And Zinc Intake May Help Cut Hypertension Risk In Pregnancy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pre-conception-calcium-zinc-intake-may-help-cut-hypertension-risk-pregnancy-471904 <description><![CDATA[Recent research indicates that consuming high levels of calcium and zinc three months before conception can significantly lower the risk of hypertensive disorders during pregnancy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pre-conception-calcium-zinc-intake-may-help-cut-hypertension-risk-pregnancy-471904</guid><pubDate> Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:15:56 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>