<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Vitamin D For Heart Health? Study Says Supplements Can Cut Cardiovascular Risk In Elderly]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-heart-health-study-says-supplements-can-cut-cardioangiography-risk-elderly-470381 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found vitamin D supplementation could help prevent major cardiovascular events such as heart attacks in people above the age of 60.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/vitamin-d-heart-health-study-says-supplements-can-cut-cardioangiography-risk-elderly-470381</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:58:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Opioids May Not Be Effective In Treating Low Back And Neck Pain, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/opioids-may-not- effective-treating-low-back-neck-pain-study-finds-470378 <description><![CDATA[The study's findings indicate that opioids have minimal or negligible impact in addressing acute lower back pain. Researchers also express concerns about the potential risks associated with these medications.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/opioids-may-not- effective-treating-low-back-neck-pain-study-finds-470378</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:06:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Experimental Probiotic Could Help Reduce Mercury Absorption In Gut]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-probiotic-could-help-reduce-mercury-absorbation-gut-470380 <description><![CDATA[In the latest study, researchers developed a new probiotic bacteria that can express an enzyme to convert more absorbable forms of mercury into less absorbable forms.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/experimental-probiotic-could-help-reduce-mercury-absorbation-gut-470380</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 02:29:39 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[40% Of Young Women In US Have Iron Deficiency, Study Says; Know The Symptoms]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/40-young-women-us-have-iron-deficiency-study-says-know-symptoms-470376 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests a blood test to measure the body's iron reserves should be included in routine health checkups as 40% of American teenage girls and young women have low levels of iron.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/40-young-women-us-have-iron-deficiency-study-says-know-symptoms-470376</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:38:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Giving Birth Between Ages 23 And 32 Reduces Baby's Risk Of 'Non-Chromosomal Anomalies': Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/giving-birth- Between-ages-23-32-reduces-babys-risk-non-chromosomal-anomalies-study-470374 <description><![CDATA[Women older than 32 had a 15% higher chance of such births, while younger mothers had a 20% higher chance.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/giving-birth- Between-ages-23-32-reduces-babys-risk-non-chromosomal-anomalies-study-470374</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 06:03:40 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Foods With Low Glycemic Index To Control Blood Sugar Levels]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-foods-low-glycemic-index-control-blood-sugar-levels-470366 <description><![CDATA[Over 34 million people in the United States have diabetes--comprising 10.5% of the population.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/5-foods-low-glycemic-index-control-blood-sugar-levels-470366</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 04:57:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Intranasal Insulin Might Boost Cognition In Alzheimer's Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intranasal-insulin-might-boost-cognition-alzheimers-患者-study-470371 <description><![CDATA[The researchers conducted a meta-analysis of 29 studies involving 1,726 participants to examine the effect of intranasal insulin on cognitive function.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/intranasal-insulin-might-boost-cognition-alzheimers-患者-study-470371</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 04:13:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Water Fasting For Weight Loss: Study Reveals Limited Long-Term Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/water-fasting-weight-loss-study-reveals-limited-long-term-effects-470365 <description><![CDATA[A recent study from the University of Illinois Chicago reveals that although water fasting may lead to initial weight loss, the weight is quickly regained.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/water-fasting-weight-loss-study-reveals-limited-long-term-effects-470365</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 02:56:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Aspartame Cause Cancer? Know Which Products Contain The Artificial Sweetener As WHO Raises Concerns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-aspartame-cause-cancer-know-which-products-contain-artificial-sweetener-who-raises-concerns-470369 <description><![CDATA[After the safety review conducted by the World Health Organization's cancer research arm, the International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC), aspartame is likely to be classified as possibly carcinogenic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/does-aspartame-cause-cancer-know-which-products-contain-artificial-sweetener-who-raises-concerns-470369</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 02:25:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Loneliness More Dangerous Than Smoking In Diabetes Patients, Could Increase Heart Disease Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-more-dangerous-smoking-diabetes-病人-could-increase-heart-disease-risk-study-470364 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that loneliness, which refers to the quality of social interaction, has a significant impact on heart health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/loneiness-more-dangerous-smoking-diabetes-病人-could-increase-heart-disease-risk-study-470364</guid><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 01:01:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Canine Influenza Outbreak: Minnesota Cases Surge As Vaccines Run Low]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/canine-influenza-outbreak-minnesota-cases-surge-vaccines-run-low-470361 <description><![CDATA[Nearly 300 dogs are suspected to have been infected with canine influenza.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/canine-influenza-outbreak-minnesota-cases-surge-vaccines-run-low-470361</guid><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:51:05 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>