<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh</language><item><title><![CDATA[Weight Loss Drugs With Semaglutide May Help Quit Smoking: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-semaglutide-may-help-quit-smoking-study-472038 <description><![CDATA[Semaglutide drugs such as Ozempic and Wegovy could help tobacco smokers quit smoking, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/weight-loss-drugs-semaglutide-may-help-quit-smoking-study-472038</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:16:59 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Chronic Cough Be Inherited? Here's What Studies Say]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-chronic-cough-inherited-heres-what-studies-say-472037 <description><![CDATA[Two separate studies have found that chronic cough may have a genetic component, and the condition particularly impacts middle-aged women.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-chronic-cough-inherited-heres-what-studies-say-472037</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:38:44 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Don't Skip Breakfast: Study Reveals Children Who Miss It Regularly Are Less Happy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-skip-breakfast-study-reveals-children-who-miss-it-regularly-are-less-happy-472035 <description><![CDATA[Can the regularity of the morning meal affect happiness? The researchers discovered "a nearly linear relationship" between a higher frequency of eating breakfast and greater life satisfaction.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/dont-skip-breakfast-study-reveals-children-who-miss-it-regularly-are-less-happy-472035</guid><pubDate> Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:20:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cutting Out This Item From Your Diet Could Reverse Aging, New Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cutting-out-this-item-your-diet-could-reverse-aging-new-study-finds-472032 <description><![CDATA[Can an item in your diet turn back the biological clock? Researchers have now identified a specific item, which, when reduced, could potentially reverse the signs of aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cutting-out-this-item-your-diet-could-reverse-aging-new-study-finds-472032</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:32:38 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Expert Reveals Dangers Of UV Index Tanning Trend, Shares Tips To Protect Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-reveals-dangers-uv-index-tanning-trend-shares-tips-protect-skin-472029 <description><![CDATA[Chasing that perfect tan could be more harmful than you think. Know from an expert how tanning accelerates skin aging and increases the risk of skin cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-reveals-dangers-uv-index-tanning-trend-shares-tips-protect-skin-472029</guid><pubDate> Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:03:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[First Ever Deaths From Oropouche Virus: Know About Rare Illness, Life-Threatening Complications]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-ever-deaths-oropouche-virus-know-about-rare-illness-life-throne-complications-472027 <description><![CDATA[The world's first-ever deaths from the Oropouche virus have been reported in Brazil. The relatively unknown infection has no specific vaccines or medications for prevention and treatment.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/first-ever-deaths-oropouche-virus-know-about-rare-illness-life-throne-complications-472027</guid><pubDate> Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:46:36 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Creatine Supplements in 2024: A List Of Options To Support Your Exercise And Recovery Needs]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/writing-down-creatine-supplements-list-options-support-your-exercise-recovery-needs-472021 <description><![CDATA[Creatine provides numerous benefits, especially related to exercise. It aids the pathway from phosphocreatine to ATP, giving a vital energy boost crucial for performance, recovery, and muscle growth. Creatine supplements come in various forms, such as pills and drinks, but are most commonly found as powders, similar to whey protein or pre-workout supplements. Sports dietitians recommend creatine monohydrate, the most studied and 100% bioavailable form, ensuring full absorption and utilization by the body.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/writing-down-creatine-supplements-list-options-support-your-exercise-recovery-needs-472021</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jul 2024 14:39:06 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pesticide Use In Farms Poses Cancer Risk Similar To Smoking: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pesticide-use-farms-poses-cancer-risk-similar-smoking-study-472026 <description><![CDATA[The researchers caution that the effect of agricultural pesticide usage is comparable in magnitude to the effect of smoking.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pesticide-use-farms-poses-cancer-risk-similar-smoking-study-472026</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:46:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Obesity Raises Hospitalizations From Dengue In Children: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-raises-hospitalizations-dengue-children-study-472024 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have uncovered a significant link between obesity in children and increased likelihood of hospitalization due to dengue in a large-scale study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-raises-hospitalizations-dengue-children-study-472024</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:13:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[There's No Safe Level: Study Says Moderate Drinking Does Not Improve Longevity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/theres-no-safe-level-study-says-moderate-drinking-does-not-improve-longevity-472019 <description><![CDATA[The long-held notion that moderate alcohol consumption boosts longevity may be misleading, as researchers have found that no amount of alcohol is truly safe for health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/theres-no-safe-level-study-says-moderate-drinking-does-not-improve-longevity-472019</guid><pubDate> Thu, 25 Jul 2024 04:23:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[HIV Prevention: Trial Results Show Twice-Yearly Shots Offer 100% Protection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hiv-prevention-trial-results-show-twice-yearly-shots-offer-100-protection-472018 <description><![CDATA[Recent results from a phase 3 trial reveal that a twice-yearly injection of the drug to treat AIDS offers 100% efficacy in preventing new infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hiv-prevention-trial-results-show-twice-yearly-shots-offer-100-protection-472018</guid><pubDate> Thu, 25 Jul 2024 03:07:45 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>