<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Maternal Mental Health Month: Expert Shares Tips To Support Someone Going Through Postpartum Depression]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maternal-mental-health-month-expert-shares-tips-support-someone-going-through-postpartum-471717 <description><![CDATA[Although a common and treatable mental health condition, postpartum depression is often stigmatized, and many women hesitate to seek help, fearing that they will be branded as a "bad mother."]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/maternal-mental-health-month-expert-shares-tips-support-someone-going-through-postpartum-471717</guid><pubDate> Wed, 08 May 2024 02:05:10 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Unhealthy Levels Of Nitrogen Dioxide In Households With Gas Or Propane Stoves: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unhealthy-levels-nitrogen-dioxide-households-gas-propane-stoves-study-471715 <description><![CDATA[People living in households with gas or propane stoves breathe in unhealthy levels of nitrogen dioxide, with the increased levels linked to around 50,000 cases of pediatric asthma, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/unhealthy-levels-nitrogen-dioxide-households-gas-propane-stoves-study-471715</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 May 2024 05:15:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Simple Nature-Based Activity Can Improve Students' Mental Health, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-nature-based-activity-can-improve-students-mental-health-says-study-471714 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that engaging in five 30-minute sessions of bird-watching every week could improve mental well-being and reduce psychological distress among college students.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/simple-nature-based-activity-can-improve-students-mental-health-says-study-471714</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 May 2024 04:06:18 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ancient Grains Help Improve Blood Sugar, Cholesterol Levels In Diabetes Patients: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ancient-grains-help-improve-blood-sugar-cholesterollevels-diabetics-患者-study-471712 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that oats, brown rice, and millet could improve various diabetes markers such as insulin levels, fasting blood sugar, and Hemoglobin A1C and are associated with improved cholesterol levels indicating better heart health in diabetes patients.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ancient-grains-help-improve-blood-sugar-cholesterollevels-diabetics-患者-study-471712</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 May 2024 01:47:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Harnessing Nature's Power: The 7 Best Tongkat Ali Supplements]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/harnessing-natures-power-7-best-tongkat-ali-supplements-471700 <description><![CDATA[Discover the benefits of Tongkat Ali with these supplements that harness nature's power to boost testosterone levels and enhance men's vitality.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/harnessing-natures-power-7-best-tongkat-ali-supplements-471700</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 11:16:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Metformin Reduces COVID-19 Hospitalizations, Long COVID: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-reduces-covid-19-hospitalizations-long-covid-study-471710 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that metformin can reduce the amount of COVID-19 virus in the body and lower the risk of viral rebound.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/metformin-reduces-covid-19-hospitalizations-long-covid-study-471710</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 03:50:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tuberculosis Outbreak: 1 Dead, 9 Hospitalized In Long Beach; Officials Declare Health Emergency]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tuberculosis-outbreak-1-dead-9-hospitalized-long-beach-officials-declare-health-emergency-471709 <description><![CDATA[An investigation revealed that approximately 170 people have likely been exposed to TB.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tuberculosis-outbreak-1-dead-9-hospitalized-long-beach-officials-declare-health-emergency-471709</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 03:35:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Liver Patients Can Benefit By Going Meatless For Just One Meal, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/liver-病人-can-benefit-just-going-meatless-one-meal-says-study-471708 <description><![CDATA[Adults with permanent liver damage can lower the levels of harmful ammonia by substituting one meal with a vegan or vegetarian option, the study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/liver-病人-can-benefit-just-going-meatless-one-meal-says-study-471708</guid><pubDate> Fri, 03 May 2024 02:01:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Beauty from Within: Top 5 Collagen Powder Drinks To Boost and Improve Skin Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beauty-within-top-5-collagen-powder-drinks-boost-improve-skin-health-471706 <description><![CDATA[Discover the secret to radiant, youthful skin with collagen power drinks – the ultimate skincare booster packed with all the goodness your skin craves.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beauty-within-top-5-collagen-powder-drinks-boost-improve-skin-health-471706</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 15:56:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women Are 40% More At Risk Of Depression During Perimenopause: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-40-more-risk-depression-during-perimenopause-study-471705 <description><![CDATA[There is a 40% increased risk of depression at the perimenopausal stage compared to the premenopausal stage, a study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-40-more-risk-depression-during-perimenopause-study-471705</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 03:56:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Control Your Anger: Study Says It Damages Blood Vessel, Raising Heart Disease Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/control-your-anger-study-says-it-damages-blood-vessel-raise-heart-disease-risk-471704 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have found that a brief period of anger can damage your blood vessels and elevate the risk of heart disease and stroke.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/control-your-anger-study-says-it-damages-blood-vessel-raise-heart-disease-risk-471704</guid><pubDate> Thu, 02 May 2024 03:18:29 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>