<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Obesity Raises Hospitalizations From Dengue In Children: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-raises-hospitalizations-dengue-children-study-472024 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have uncovered a significant link between obesity in children and increased likelihood of hospitalization due to dengue in a large-scale study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-raises-hospitalizations-dengue-children-study-472024</guid><pubDate> Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:13:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[There's No Safe Level: Study Says Moderate Drinking Does Not Improve Longevity]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/theres-no-safe-level-study-says-moderate-drinking-does-not-improve-longevity-472019 <description><![CDATA[The long-held notion that moderate alcohol consumption boosts longevity may be misleading, as researchers have found that no amount of alcohol is truly safe for health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/theres-no-safe-level-study-says-moderate-drinking-does-not-improve-longevity-472019</guid><pubDate> Thu, 25 Jul 2024 04:23:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[HIV Prevention: Trial Results Show Twice-Yearly Shots Offer 100% Protection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hiv-prevention-trial-results-show-twice-yearly-shots-offer-100-protection-472018 <description><![CDATA[Recent results from a phase 3 trial reveal that a twice-yearly injection of the drug to treat AIDS offers 100% efficacy in preventing new infections.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/hiv-prevention-trial-results-show-twice-yearly-shots-offer-100-protection-472018</guid><pubDate> Thu, 25 Jul 2024 03:07:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Excess Fat In These Areas Raises Risk Of Alzheimer's And Parkinson's, Study Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-fat-these-areas-raises-risk-alzheimers-parkinsons-study-warns-472016 <description><![CDATA[The researchers have identified that body composition affects the risk of neurodegenerative diseases such as Alzheimer's and Parkinson's disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/excess-fat-these-areas-raises-risk-alzheimers-parkinsons-study-warns-472016</guid><pubDate> Thu, 25 Jul 2024 02:10:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Having High Systolic Blood Pressure Over Time Raises Stroke Risk, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/having-high-systolic-blood-Pressure-over-time-raises-中风-risk-says-study-472014 <description><![CDATA[Based on their findings, the researchers recommend that stroke prevention programs should address modifiable risk factors such as systolic blood pressure.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/having-high-systolic-blood-Pressure-over-time-raises-中风-risk-says-study-472014</guid><pubDate> Wed, 24 Jul 2024 04:16:14 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Floating Duck Syndrome: Study Explains How Underestimating Efforts Fuels Burnout]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/floating-duck-syndrome-study-explains-how-underestimating-efforts-fuels-burnout-472013 <description><![CDATA[The researchers believe that their findings offer a new explanation for why overcommitment and burnout occur in universities, workplaces, and homes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/floating-duck-syndrome-study-explains-how-underestimating-efforts-fuels-burnout-472013</guid><pubDate> Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:51:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Beyond Childhood: Expert Unmasks Hidden Struggles Of Adult ADHD]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-childhood-expert-unmasks-hidden-struggles-adult-adhd-472010 <description><![CDATA[In adults, ADHD may go unrecognized and undiagnosed, with symptoms masked or mistaken for other issues.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-childhood-expert-unmasks-hidden-struggles-adult-adhd-472010</guid><pubDate> Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:45:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Treatment For Male Pattern Baldness? Study Identifies Body Sugar That Holds Key]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-treatment-male-pattern-baldness-study-identizes-body-sugar-that-holds-key-472007 <description><![CDATA[The researchers noted that a naturally occurring sugar in the human body, known as 2-deoxy-D-ribose (2dDR), could stimulate hair growth.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-treatment-male-pattern-baldness-study-identizes-body-sugar-that-holds-key-472007</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Jul 2024 04:21:29 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Indian Teen Dies From Nipah Virus: Know About Deadly Infection With No Vaccine, Cure]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/indian-teen-dies-nipah-virus-know-about-deadly-infection-no-vaccine-cure-472005 <description><![CDATA[With no available vaccine or cure, the World Health Organization has classified Nipah as a priority pathogen due to its high potential to cause an epidemic.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/indian-teen-dies-nipah-virus-know-about-deadly-infection-no-vaccine-cure-472005</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Jul 2024 03:08:09 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eat More Fruits In Middle Age To Ward Off Depressive Symptoms Later, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eat-more-fruits-middle-ages-ward-off-depressive-symptoms-later-says-study-472002 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that individuals who consumed higher quantities of fruits earlier in life had a reduced risk of experiencing depressive symptoms as they aged.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eat-more-fruits-middle-ages-ward-off-depressive-symptoms-later-says-study-472002</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:59:02 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Fiber In Common Cereals That Aids Weight Loss]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-fibre-common-cereals-that-aids-weight-loss-472001 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have identified the type of fiber commonly found in oats and barley that shows significant potential for weight loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-fibre-common-cereals-that-aids-weight-loss-472001</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jul 2024 05:27:10 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>