<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Expert Insights On Intermittent Fasting: Know Health Benefits, Potential Side Effects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-insights-intermittent-fasting-know-health-benefits-pottial-side-effects-471297 <description><![CDATA[Discover insights from an expert about the fasting diet, its potential health benefits and possible side effects.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/expert-insights-intermittent-fasting-know-health-benefits-pottial-side-effects-471297</guid><pubDate> Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:13:15 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Best Protein Powders Of 2024: Powerful Nutrition To Fuel Your Fitness Journey]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-powders-powerful-nutrition-fuel-your-fitness-journey-471296 <description><![CDATA[Join the countless individuals who have embraced the benefits of protein powder as a key component in their journey toward a healthier and more balanced lifestyle.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best- Protein-powders-powerful-nutrition-fuel-your-fitness-journey-471296</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:34:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Secret To Healthy Aging? Study Identifies Foods That Reduce Risk Of Chronic Illnesses In Women]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/secret-healthy-aging-study-identizes-foods-that-reduce-risk-chronic-illnesses-women-471295 <description><![CDATA[Ladies, are you curious to know the secret to healthy aging? Your middle-age diet can influence your future health, a recent study suggests.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/secret-healthy-aging-study-identizes-foods-that-reduce-risk-chronic-illnesses-women-471295</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jan 2024 04:23:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Eating Dark Chocolate Linked To Reduced Risk Of Hypertension, Blood Clots: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-dark-chocolate-linked-reduced-risk-hypertension-blood-clots-study-471293 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now found an interesting link between the consumption of dark chocolate and reduced risk of essential hypertension and venous thromboembolism.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/eating-dark-chocolate-linked-reduced-risk-hypertension-blood-clots-study-471293</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jan 2024 02:09:52 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[California Norovirus Outbreak: Over 200 Cases Reported; Officials Warn To Avoid Eating Raw Oysters From Mexico]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-norovirus-outbreak-over-200-cases-reported-officials-warn-avoid-eating-raw-oysters-471292 <description><![CDATA[Health officials in Southern California have issued a warning to avoid eating raw oysters imported from certain areas of Mexico after more than 200 people got sick from suspected norovirus infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/california-norovirus-outbreak-over-200-cases-reported-officials-warn-avoid-eating-raw-oysters-471292</guid><pubDate> Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:36:34 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Happens To Your Body In Extreme Cold? Know Hypothermia Signs, Treatments]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-happens-your-body-extreme-cold-know-signs-treatments-hypothermia-471290 <description><![CDATA[Hypothermia, a dangerous condition that can occur when a person gets exposed to extreme cold climates, has the potential to lead to organ failure and even death.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-happens-your-body-extreme-cold-know-signs-treatments-hypothermia-471290</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jan 2024 03:33:09 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Energy Drinks Associated With Depression, ADHD, And Anxiety In Kids, Young Adults: Research]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/energy-drinks- Associated-depression-adhd-anxiety-kids-young-adults-research-471289 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has identified a series of health effects associated with energy drinks, including disrupted sleep, depression, suicide, ADHD, and anxiety, particularly in children and young adults.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/energy-drinks- Associated-depression-adhd-anxiety-kids-young-adults-research-471289</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:13:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Multivitamins For Memory Loss: Researchers Say Daily Intake Could Slow Cognitive Aging By Around 2 Years]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multivitamins-memory-loss-researchers-say-daily-intake-could-slow-cognitive-aging-around-2-years-471287 <description><![CDATA[A recent study suggests that daily supplementation of multivitamins could slow cognitive decline in older adults by around two years.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/multivitamins-memory-loss-researchers-say-daily-intake-could-slow-cognitive-aging-around-2-years-471287</guid><pubDate> Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:28:33 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Neurotechnology-Based RecoveriX Treatment Provides Safer Alternative To Medications For Stroke And MS Patients]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neurotechnology-based-recoverix-treatment-provides-safer-alternative-medications-中风-ms-471285 <description><![CDATA[Unlike most medications for stroke and MS on the market, recoveriX has been shown to aid in the rehabilitation of stroke and multiple sclerosis patients.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/neurotechnology-based-recoverix-treatment-provides-safer-alternative-medications-中风-ms-471285</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 12:10:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Antifungal Body Wash For 2024: Experience Healthy, Happy Skin]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-antifungal-body-wash-experience-healthy-happy-skin-471284 <description><![CDATA[We have compiled the list of best fungus body wash in the market today, and some things to consider while buying one.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/best-antifungal-body-wash-experience-healthy-happy-skin-471284</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 10:39:07 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Organic Castor Oils Of 2024: Nourish, Strengthen And Shine]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-organic-castor-oil-nourish-strengthen-shine-471278 <description><![CDATA[As a key ingredient in beauty routines, castor oil is celebrated for its ability to address various concerns, including dry skin, damaged hair, and even aiding in the maintenance of healthy lashes and brows.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/best-organic-castor-oil-nourish-strengthen-shine-471278</guid><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:16:23 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>