<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[Limiting Children's Screen Time To 3 Hours Weekly Boosts Mental Health In Days: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/limiting-childrens-screen-time-3-hours-weekly-boosts-mental-health-days-study-471964 <description><![CDATA[The mental health benefits from limiting screen time in kids will be observable in as little as two weeks, a new study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/limiting-childrens-screen-time-3-hours-weekly-boosts-mental-health-days-study-471964</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Jul 2024 04:40:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Four New Bird Flu Cases Confirmed In Colorado Poultry Workers]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/four-new-bird-flu-cases-confirmed-colorado-poultry-workers-471962 <description><![CDATA[Four new cases of bird flu have been confirmed among poultry workers in Colorado, bringing the total number of cases in the U.S. to nine since the current outbreak was first detected in 2022.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/four-new-bird-flu-cases-confirmed-colorado-poultry-workers-471962</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Jul 2024 04:12:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Lifestyle Changes Could Prevent Nearly Half Of Adult Cancer Deaths In US: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lifestyle-changes-could-prevent-nearly-half-adult-cancer-deaths-us-study-471959 <description><![CDATA[A new study suggests that lifestyle changes could avert approximately 40% of new cancer cases in adults aged 30 and above, and nearly half of all cancer-related deaths.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/lifestyle-changes-could-prevent-nearly-half-adult-cancer-deaths-us-study-471959</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:14:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Life Expectancy After Heart Attack: Study Says Women Lose More Years Compared To Men]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/life-expectancy-after-heart-attack-study-says-women-lose-more-years-compared-men-471956 <description><![CDATA[The study revealed that after heart attacks, women experience a greater life expectancy loss than men, and the effect was more significant in those with impaired cardiac function after their heart attack.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/life-expectancy-after-heart-attack-study-says-women-lose-more-years-compared-men-471956</guid><pubDate> Thu, 11 Jul 2024 03:08:47 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Breakthrough In Osteoporosis: Scientists Discover New Hormone That Builds Stronger Bones]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakthrough-osteoporosis-scientists-discover-new-hormone-that-builds-stronger-bones-471954 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a new hormone, a maternal brain hormone (CCN3) that could be a breakthrough in the treatment of osteoporosis.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/breakthrough-osteoporosis-scientists-discover-new-hormone-that-builds-stronger-bones-471954</guid><pubDate> Thu, 11 Jul 2024 02:46:26 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Delaying Diabetes By 4 Years Reduces Risks Of Death And Complication, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/delaying-diabetes-4-years-reduces-risks-death-complication-says-study-471951 <description><![CDATA[The researchers suggest that people who have impaired glucose tolerance (IGT) should consider making lifestyle interventions such as diet and exercise to effectively delay the onset of diabetes.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/delaying-diabetes-4-years-reduces-risks-death-complication-says-study-471951</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Jul 2024 04:19:24 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women More At Risk Of Anxiety, Depression Than Men After Surviving Cardiac Arrest: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-more-risk-anxiety-depression-men-after-surviving-cardiac-arrest-study-471948 <description><![CDATA[The research team made the findings after examining long-term socioeconomic and mental health outcomes among cardiac arrest survivors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/women-more-risk-anxiety-depression-men-after-surviving-cardiac-arrest-study-471948</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Jul 2024 03:09:56 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Colorado Confirms Rare Case Of Human Plague: Essential Facts, Safety Tips]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/colorado-confirms-rare-case- human-plague-essential-facts-safety-tips-471945 <description><![CDATA[Health officials in Colorado have confirmed a rare case of human plague, a potentially life-threatening disease transmitted from infected rodents.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/colorado-confirms-rare-case- human-plague-essential-facts-safety-tips-471945</guid><pubDate> Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:36:19 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Obesity Diagnosis Needs Change, Study Says Fat Distribution More Important Than BMI]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-diagnosis-needs-change-study-says-fat-distribution-more-important-bmi-471943 <description><![CDATA[The researchers of the latest study put forth a new framework for the diagnosis, staging, and management of obesity in adults that takes into account not just BMI but the way the body fat is distributed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/obesity-diagnosis-needs-change-study-says-fat-distribution-more-important-bmi-471943</guid><pubDate> Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:00:04 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[More Than Just Skin And Hair Rejuvenation: Here's Why Having A Reliable Collagen Supplement Matters]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-just-skin-hair-rejuvenation-heres-why-having-reliable-collagen-supplement-matters-471944 <description><![CDATA[Studies on collagen supplements like the NativePath Collagen Peptides show it can help you replace collagen that people usually start losing when they reach 30.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-just-skin-hair-rejuvenation-heres-why-having-reliable-collagen-supplement-matters-471944</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:18:57 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Study Identifies Lifestyle Habit Linked To Cognitive Decline In Older Adults]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-lifestyle-habit-linked-cognitive-decline-older-adults-471941 <description><![CDATA[Among lifestyle habits, researchers have now identified the key factor that has the most effect on the cognitive health of the elderly.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/study-identizes-lifestyle-habit-linked-cognitive-decline-older-adults-471941</guid><pubDate> Mon, 08 Jul 2024 02:25:17 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>