<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医药日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>在</language><item><title><![CDATA[World Environment Day 2023: Why Are Microplastics So Dangerous? How To Avoid Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-environment-day-2023-why-are-microplastics-so-dangerous-how-avoid-them-470005 <description><![CDATA[The small plastic particles are found in everyday items such as food storage containers, baby bottles, nail polish, acrylic paint, gum, toys and cutting boards.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-environment-day-2023-why-are-microplastics-so-dangerous-how-avoid-them-470005</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:15:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['More Than Skin Deep': Study Reveals How Psoriasis Inflammation Leads To Other Related Disorders]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-skin-deep-study-reveals-how-psoriasis-inflammation-leads-other-related-disorders-470003 <description><![CDATA[The latest study aimed at developing objective diagnostic measures to predict severe psoriasis and to identify patients who are at higher risk of developing related disorders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/more-skin-deep-study-reveals-how-psoriasis-inflammation-leads-other-related-disorders-470003</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 04:54:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily Lung Cancer Pill After Surgery Slashes Death Risk By Half, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-lung-cancer-pill-after-surgery-slashes-death-risk-half-study-finds-470001 <description><![CDATA[Osimertinib slashed the risk of death by 51% compared to placebo.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/daily-lung-cancer-pill-after-surgery-slashes-death-risk-half-study-finds-470001</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 03:34:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Adolescence Could Be The Best Time To Treat Schizophrenia, Autism]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adolescence-could-best-time-treat-schizophrenia-autism-469999 <description><![CDATA[A study showed that adolescence is the best time to treat conditions such as schizophrenia and autism, both characterized by dysfunctioning of the dopamine system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/adolescence-could-best-time-treat-schizophrenia-autism-469999</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 02:24:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Blue Monday: Study Says Serious Heart Attacks More Common At Start Of Working Week]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blue-monday-study-says-serious-heart-attacks-more-common-start-working-week-469998 <description><![CDATA[The chances of getting a severe form of heart attack, called STEMI, on a Monday were 13% greater than on other days of the week, the study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blue-monday-study-says-serious-heart-attacks-more-common-start-working-week-469998</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 01:38:03 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tacoma Woman Officially Arrested After Year-Long Refusal Of TB Treatment]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/tacoma-woman-officially-arrested-after-year-long-refusal-tb-treatment-469995 <description><![CDATA[After more than a year, the female patient was officially arrested and ordered to isolate.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tacoma-woman-officially-arrested-after-year-long-refusal-tb-treatment-469995</guid><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:05:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[US Adults Refusing COVID-19 Boosters After WHO Declared Pandemic Over]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/us-adults-refusing-covid-19-boosters-after-who-declared-pandemic-over-469993 <description><![CDATA[Many are declining the boosters even though authorities have warned of the risk of catching COVID-19 in the post-pandemic era.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/us-adults-refusing-covid-19-boosters-after-who-declared-pandemic-over-469993</guid><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jun 2023 23:59:48 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 3 Personalized Supplements You Must Take for Better Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-3-personalized-supplements-you-must-take-better-health-469992 <description><![CDATA[When it comes to taking care of our health, there are a lot of things we can do. Eating healthy, exercising regularly, and getting enough sleep are just a few examples. However, even these aren't enough to supply your body with all the nutrients it needs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/top-3-personalized-supplements-you-must-take-better-health-469992</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:07:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Servings Of Grapes A Day Increase Gut Bacteria, Boost Metabolic Function, Study Finds]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/3-servings-grapes-day-increases-gut-bacteria-boosts-metabolic-function-study-finds-469989 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that grapes can have a positive impact on gut health by increasing the abundance of beneficial gut bacteria, giving yet another reason to incorporate grapes into our dietary routine.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/3-servings-grapes-day-increases-gut-bacteria-boosts-metabolic-function-study-finds-469989</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 06:04:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA Finalizes Stricter Guidance On Inorganic Arsenic Levels in Apple Juice]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-finalizes-stricter-guidance-inorganic-arsenic-levels-apple-juice-469987 <description><![CDATA[The heavy presence of arsenic and lead in fruit juices is sometimes beyond the control of the manufacturers.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/fda-finalizes-stricter-guidance-inorganic-arsenic-levels-apple-juice-469987</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 05:01:35 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Awareness Month: 7 Ways To Keep Your Brain Healthy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alzheimers-awareness-month-7-ways-keep-your-brain-healthy-469984 <description><![CDATA[Every year, June is marked to increase awareness about the degenerative brain disorder that affects the lives of millions of people worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/alzheimers-awareness-month-7-ways-keep-your-brain-healthy-469984</guid><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:39:14 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>