<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Brushing Your Teeth Before Bedtime May Be Crucial For A Healthy Heart]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brushing-your-teeth-before-bedtime-may-crucial-healthy-heart-470408 <description><![CDATA[Multiple studies emphasize oral care's significance before and after surgery, but its potential connection to heart problems remains unexplored. The latest study focuses on this area.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/brushing-your-teeth-before-bedtime-may-crucial-healthy-heart-470408</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 05:51:21 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardiorespiratory Fitness Reduces Colon And Lung Cancer Risk: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiorespiratory-fitness-reduces-colon-lung-cancer-risk-study-470405 <description><![CDATA[The study showed that individuals with higher levels of cardiorespiratory fitness had a 2% lower risk of developing colon and lung cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cardiorespiratory-fitness-reduces-colon-lung-cancer-risk-study-470405</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 04:50:00 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Young Cancer Survivors May Be At Increased Risk Of Mental Disorders; Ways To Support Them]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/young-cancer-survivors-may-increased-risk-mental-disorders-ways-support-them-470403 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that young cancer survivors are at an increased risk of developing mental health disorders such as depression and anxiety.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/young-cancer-survivors-may-increased-risk-mental-disorders-ways-support-them-470403</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 03:26:12 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Smoothie Recipes To Ease Constipation]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/6-smoothie-recipes-ease-constipation-470402 <description><![CDATA[You can relieve constipation by seamlessly incorporating nutrient-rich smoothies into your daily diet.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/6-smoothie-recipes-ease-constipation-470402</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 03:06:30 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Decreased Sense Of Smell In Elderly May Increase Risk Of Depression, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/decreased-sense-smell-elderly-may-increase-risk-depression-study-says-470399 <description><![CDATA[The study evaluated factors that affect the relationship between olfaction and depression, including poor cognition and inflammation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/decreased-sense-smell-elderly-may-increase-risk-depression-study-says-470399</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 02:29:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Soups And Shakes Diet Safe For Nash, May Improve Advanced Fatty Liver Disease: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/soups-shakes-diet-safe-nash-may-improve-advanced-fatty-liver-disease-study-470397 <description><![CDATA[A new study has found that a soups and shakes diet can benefit people with non-alcoholic steatohepatitis (NASH).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/soups-shakes-diet-safe-nash-may-improve-advanced-fatty-liver-disease-study-470397</guid><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 01:02:58 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CDC Reveals How Many Americans Still Haven't Caught COVID-19]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-reveals-how-many-americans-still-havent-caught-covid-19-470395 <description><![CDATA[CDC estimates suggested a vast majority of Americans had developed antibodies against COVID-19.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cdc-reveals-how-many-americans-still-havent-caught-covid-19-470395</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 20:28:25 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Study Links COVID-19 Severity To Autoantibodies Against Blood Clotting]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-study-links-covid-19-severity-autoantibodies-against-blood-clotting-470394 <description><![CDATA[The study explored how a blood clotting regulator gene performed during COVID-19 infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-study-links-covid-19-severity-autoantibodies-against-blood-clotting-470394</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 20:24:28 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Auria: Pioneering Tear-Based Cancer Screening for Breast Abnormalities]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/auria-pioneering-tear-based-cancer-screening-breast-abnormalities-470388 <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer is one of the leading causes of cancer-related deaths among women worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/auria-pioneering-tear-based-cancer-screening-breast-abnormalities-470388</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 10:46:37 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Signs Of Depression May Linger Even After Joint Pain Subsides In Orthopedic Patients, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/signs-depression-may-linger-even-after-joint-pain-subsides-orthopedic-病人-study-says-470385 <description><![CDATA[A new study suggests that even when the physical pain subsides, it doesn't mean the mental health issues will improve.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/signs-depression-may-linger-even-after-joint-pain-subsides-orthopedic-病人-study-says-470385</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 05:46:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Older Adults in Warmer Regions Have Higher Risk of Severe Vision Impairment: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-warmer-regions-have-higher-risk-severe-vision-impairment-study-470384 <description><![CDATA[Living in counties with temperatures ranging from 50-54.99°F increases the likelihood of severe vision impairment by 14%, the recent study said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/older-adults-warmer-regions-have-higher-risk-severe-vision-impairment-study-470384</guid><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 05:19:06 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>