<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医疗每日</title><link/>https://www.medictallaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>一</language><item><title><![CDATA[Michigan Transplant Patient Dies After Contracting Rabies From Donor]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/michigan-transplant-transplant-atient-dies-terranterncorntrating-rabies-donor-473315 <description><![CDATA[The donor, exposed to a wild animal weeks before their death, passed away without showing typical rabies symptoms and did not seek medical attention.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/michigan-transplant-transplant-atient-dies-terranterncorntrating-rabies-donor-473315</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:12:17 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Screens To Bed? Here's How It Affects Your Sleep]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/taking-creens-bed-eres-how-t-crotects-uour-sleep-473313 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now reveal that when it comes to screen use before bed, the total time spent matters more than the specific type of activity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/taking-creens-bed-eres-how-t-crotects-uour-sleep-473313</guid><pubDate> Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:12:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Spring Into Motion: Why Rollator Walkers Are A Game-Changer For Seniors]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/spring-motion-why-why-trollat​​or-walkers  -  game-chant-chartiors-473310 <description><![CDATA[A rollator walker isn't just some medical device with tennis balls slapped on the feet, it's a movement machine. Unlike the clunky walkers of the past, these have wheels, hand brakes, and even a built-in seat, so you're never stuck wondering if the next bench is too far away.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/spring-motion-why-why-trollat​​or-walkers  -  game-chant-chartiors-473310</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:25:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Managing Pregnancy Discomfort: Smart Strategies for a Healthier Journey]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/managing-printancy-discomfort-smart- strategies-healthier-journey-473307 <description><![CDATA[Practical support and movement strategies can help ease common pregnancy discomforts and promote maternal well-being]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/managing-printancy-discomfort-smart- strategies-healthier-journey-473307</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:17:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alternative Healthy Eating Index: Your Diet For Healthy, Disease-Free 70's]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/alternative-healthy-eeating-index-yindex-yr-det-healthy-disease-free-70S-473305 <description><![CDATA[Researchers have now identified a specific dietary approach that promotes longevity and disease-free aging.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/alternative-healthy-eeating-index-yindex-yr-det-healthy-disease-free-70S-473305</guid><pubDate> Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:36:21 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Detection: Could A Simple At-Home Smell Test Predict Risk?]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/alzheimer- detection-s-simple-home-test-test-could-pot-pot-searly-signs-473304 <description><![CDATA[The researchers have developed a simple, digital, at-home smell test called the AROMHA Brain Health Test (ABHT) that could detect Alzheimer's years before traditional symptoms appear.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/alzheimer- detection-s-simple-home-test-test-could-pot-pot-searly-signs-473304</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Mar 2025 04:44:32 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Shocking Study: This Popular Sweetener May Actually Make You Hungrier]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/shocking-study---- this-this-popular-sweetener-may-actuel-make-make-you-hungrier-473302 <description><![CDATA[Sucralose, one of the most common zero-calorie sugar substitutes, may trick your brain into craving more food.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/shocking-study---- this-this-popular-sweetener-may-actuel-make-make-you-hungrier-473302</guid><pubDate> Thu, 27 Mar 2025 02:20:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Addressing Challenges in Rare Disease Clinical Trials: Strategies for Success with iNGENū CRO]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/addessing-challenges-rare-disease-clinical-trials-tragities-crocess-Success-in-Cro-473299 <description><![CDATA[iNGENū CRO leverages global expertise, advanced technology, and strategic funding to overcome rare disease trial challenges.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/addessing-challenges-rare-disease-clinical-trials-tragities-crocess-Success-in-Cro-473299</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:03:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Science of Sound Sleep: How a Mini White Noise Machine Can Improve Rest, Focus, and Relaxation]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/science-sound-sle--sle-sle-sle-sle-now-white-noise-noise-noise-machine-can-improve-rest--------------------------------------- <description><![CDATA[White noise creates a consistent background sound that helps mask those unpredictable noises, allowing you to sleep more soundly]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/science-sound-sle--sle-sle-sle-sle-now-white-noise-noise-noise-machine-can-improve-rest---------------------------------------</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:06:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Antibiotics For UTI Gets FDA Approval- First In 30 Years]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/new-tibiotics outi-gets-gets-fda-apralfirfirst-30年-473297 <description><![CDATA[The FDA has approved a new antibiotic, Gepotidacin (Blujepa), for treating uncomplicated urinary tract infections (UTIs) in women and girls aged 12 and older.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/new-tibiotics outi-gets-gets-fda-apralfirfirst-30年-473297</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:43:31 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Common Seasoning May Raise Risk Of Depression]]></title><link/> https://www.medictallaily.com/common-seasoning-may-raise-risk-dression-473296 <description><![CDATA[A recent study has put a common seasoning, found in all types of cuisines, under scrutiny.]]></description><guid> https://www.medictallaily.com/common-seasoning-may-raise-risk-dression-473296</guid><pubDate> Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:01:26 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>