<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Algae Oil? This Michelin-Starred Chef Vouched Cooking Oil May Be Healthier And Tastier Alternative]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-algae-oil-this-michelin-starred-chef-vouched-cooking-oil-may-healthier-tastier-alternative-472764 <description><![CDATA[For food enthusiasts and home cooks looking for a healthy cooking oil without compromising on flavor, algae oil could be an alternative.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-algae-oil-this-michelin-starred-chef-vouched-cooking-oil-may-healthier-tastier-alternative-472764</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:02:59 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Disorder Makes Patients Scream In Pain While Vomiting, Causes Teeth Loss: Cannabis-Linked Syndrome On Rise]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-disorder-makes-病人-scream-pain-while-vomiting-causes-teeth-loss-cannabis-linked-472761 <description><![CDATA[Cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome (CHS) is a relatively new term for the acute reaction to cannabis use, characterized by severe bouts of nausea, abdominal pain, and vomiting. Patients often scream and vomit due to the pain, a phenomenon referred to as 'scromiting.']]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-disorder-makes-病人-scream-pain-while-vomiting-causes-teeth-loss-cannabis-linked-472761</guid><pubDate> Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:51:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Your Drinking Water Safe? This Metal In Your Supply May Pose Cancer Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-drinking-water-safe-this-metal-your-supply-may-pose-cancer-risk-472760 <description><![CDATA[A recent study conducted in Texas found that even low levels of arsenic in water, below the regulatory threshold of 10 parts per billion, could pose health risks, including an increased risk of kidney cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/your-drinking-water-safe-this-metal-your-supply-may-pose-cancer-risk-472760</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Dec 2024 04:21:26 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Treating Appendicitis In Children: Which Is Better, Antibiotics Or Surgery?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/treating-appendicitis-children-which-better-antibiotics-surgery-472757 <description><![CDATA[Treatment with antibiotics is a safe, cost-effective alternative to laparoscopic appendectomy for pediatric uncomplicated appendicitis, a recent study revealed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/treating-appendicitis-children-which-better-antibiotics-surgery-472757</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Dec 2024 02:56:39 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Testosterone Really Fuel Sex Drive? It May Improve Courtship, Not Desire, Says Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-testosterone-really-fuel-sex-drive-it-may-improve-courtship-not-desire-says-study-472754 <description><![CDATA[The fluctuations in testosterone may not influence sexual desire as much as previously thought, suggest a recent study.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-testosterone-really-fuel-sex-drive-it-may-improve-courtship-not-desire-says-study-472754</guid><pubDate> Tue, 03 Dec 2024 00:49:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Depression May Trigger Severe Period Pain, Sleep Disturbances May Aggravate It: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-may-trigger-severe-period-pain-sleep-disturbances-may-aggravate-it-study-472753 <description><![CDATA[A recent study found that depression may actually trigger severe period pain, with sleep deprivation worsening its severity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/depression-may-trigger-severe-period-pain-sleep-disturbances-may-aggravate-it-study-472753</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:48:55 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Salmonella Outbreak Linked To Cucumbers Sickens Dozens Across 19 States: CDC Warns]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-cucumbers-sickens-dozens-across-19-states-cdc-warns-472752 <description><![CDATA[The current outbreak, linked to recalled cucumbers from SunFed Produce, LLC, has sickened 68 people, with 18 hospitalized across 19 states.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/salmonella-outbreak-linked-cucumbers-sickens-dozens-across-19-states-cdc-warns-472752</guid><pubDate> Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:57:34 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Redefining Women's Healthcare: Dr. Stephanie Efua Sobotie On Breaking Barriers And Building Sustainable Solutions]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/redefining-womens-healthcare-dr-stephanie-efua-sobotie-breaking-barriers-building-sustainable-472735 <description><![CDATA[As a family physician with a Certificate of Added Competence in obstetric surgical skills at Bow Trail Medical Clinic in Calgary and a clinical lecturer at the Cumming School of Medicine, Dr Sobotie continues to address healthcare accessibility challenges]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/redefining-womens-healthcare-dr-stephanie-efua-sobotie-breaking-barriers-building-sustainable-472735</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Nov 2024 14:53:17 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Cut Back On Ultra-Processed Foods: Researchers Say They May Trigger  Psoriasis]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-back-ultra-processed-foods-researchers-say-they-may-trigger-psoriasis-472748 <description><![CDATA[It's time to put that bag of processed snacks away, as a new study warns they may trigger psoriasis flare-ups.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/cut-back-ultra-processed-foods-researchers-say-they-may-trigger-psoriasis-472748</guid><pubDate> Fri, 29 Nov 2024 01:31:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Treatment For Asthma, COPD Flare-Ups: Single Dose Of Existing Antibody Injection May Cut Hospitalizations]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-treatment-asthma-copd-flare-ups-single-dose-existing-antibody-injection-may-cut-472745 <description><![CDATA[A recent trial revealed that a single injection of a monoclonal antibody, benralizumab, could be more effective than standard steroid tablets during asthma or COPD flare-ups.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-treatment-asthma-copd-flare-ups-single-dose-existing-antibody-injection-may-cut-472745</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Nov 2024 23:38:37 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Elderly Man Awarded Historic Damages After Clinic Allegedly Injects Him with Unnecessary 'Invasive' Penis Shots That Did Irreparable Harm]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/elderly-man-awarded-historic-damages-after-clinic-allegedly-injects-him-unnecessary-pressive-472743 <description><![CDATA[An elderly New Mexico man has been awarded $412 million after a men's health clinic treated his erectile dysfunction with "invasive penile shots" that caused irreversible damage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/elderly-man-awarded-historic-damages-after-clinic-allegedly-injects-him-unnecessary-pressive-472743</guid><pubDate> Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:27:25 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>