<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Is Classic Christmas Dinner Healthy? Researchers Say Some Side Dishes Offer Significant Health Benefits]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/classic-christmas-dinner-healthy-researchers-say-some-side-dishes-offer-significant-health-471204 <description><![CDATA[Researchers say traditional Christmas dinners can be healthy, particularly since some side dishes have significant health benefits.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/classic-christmas-dinner-healthy-researchers-say-some-side-dishes-offer-significant-health-471204</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 06:52:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 8 Companies Redefining Gut Health Supplements: Your Ultimate Guide]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-8-companies-redefining-gut-health-supplements-your-ultimate-guide-471158 <description><![CDATA[These companies are changing how we think about digestive wellness]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/partner/top-8-companies-redefining-gut-health-supplements-your-ultimate-guide-471158</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 04:40:12 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Holidays More Stressful Than Tax Season? Survey Says 79% Overlook Their Health Needs During Festive Period]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/holidays-more-stressful-tax-season-survey-says-79-overlook-their-health-needs-during-festive-471205 <description><![CDATA[Out of 1,000 adults who participated in the nationwide survey, 79% said they were so involved in creating special moments for others that they overlooked their own needs during the festive season.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/holidays-more-stressful-tax-season-survey-says-79-overlook-their-health-needs-during-festive-471205</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 04:09:27 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Early Life Diseases Linked To Lifetime Childlessness: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-life-diseases-linked-lifetime-childless-study-471203 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found a "significant" link between 74 early-life diseases and the risk of being childless throughout life.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/early-life-diseases-linked-lifetime-childless-study-471203</guid><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:56:06 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Americans Eat An Extra Meal Daily Through Snacking; Snacks Constitute Nearly Quarter Of Daily Caloric Intake]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-eat-extra-meal-daily-through-snacking-snacks-constitute-nearly-quarter-daily-caloric-471201 <description><![CDATA[On average, U.S. adults consume 400 to 500 calories a day in snacks, which is often much more than what they would eat for breakfast.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/americans-eat-extra-meal-daily-through-snacking-snacks-constitute-nearly-quarter-daily-caloric-471201</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:07:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Get Your Shots Immediately: CDC Warns Of 'Urgent Need' To Boost Vaccine Coverage As Respiratory Illnesses Surge]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/get-your-shots-immediately-cdc-warns-urgent-need-boost-vaccine-coverage-respiratory-illnesses-471200 <description><![CDATA[Low vaccination rates against influenza, COVID-19 and RSV, along with an increase in respiratory diseases, could pose a potential strain on the healthcare system, the CDC warned.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/get-your-shots-immediately-cdc-warns-urgent-need-boost-vaccine-coverage-respiratory-illnesses-471200</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 02:59:21 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Meal Timings Affect Cardiovascular Disease Risk; Here's The Best Time To Have Breakfast And Dinner]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meal-timings-affect-cardioangio-disease-risk-heres-best-time-have-breakfast-dinner-471199 <description><![CDATA[Researchers recommend adopting the habit of having early breakfast (by 8 a.m.) and dinner (8 p.m.) to prevent cardiovascular disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/meal-timings-affect-cardioangio-disease-risk-heres-best-time-have-breakfast-dinner-471199</guid><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:28:58 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Year, Better You: Revitalize Your Well-Being With These 17 Must-Have Products]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-year-better-you-revitalize-your-well-being-these-17-must-have-products-471197 <description><![CDATA[Here are seventeen must-have products to ensure your health care journey is successful and exhilarating.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/new-year-better-you-revitalize-your-well-being-these-17-must-have-products-471197</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Dec 2023 09:41:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA['Long-Flu': People Hospitalized With Seasonal Influenza May Suffer Negative Health Effects Similar To Long-COVID]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-flu-people-hospitalized-seasonal-influenza-may-suffer-negative-health-effects-similar-471196 <description><![CDATA[The study showed that patients hospitalized with flu or COVID-19 had an increased risk of death, hospital readmission and issues to multiple organs in the months following the infection.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/long-flu-people-hospitalized-seasonal-influenza-may-suffer-negative-health-effects-similar-471196</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:12:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Many Mothers And Their Children Share Same Birthday Month; Here's Why]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/many-mothers-their-children-share-same-birthday-month-heres-why-471195 <description><![CDATA[A study suggests that women are more likely to have children in the same month as their birth, and births within immediate families tend to cluster within a given month.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/many-mothers-their-children-share-same-birthday-month-heres-why-471195</guid><pubDate> Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:59:10 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Menstrual Cycles Intensify Suicidal Thoughts In People Struggling With Mental Health, Study Says]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/menstrual-cycles-intensify-suicidal-thoughts-people-struggling-mental-health-study-says-471194 <description><![CDATA[Researchers found that women with suicidal thoughts may face an increased risk of ideation or planning of suicide in the days around menstruation.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/menstrual-cycles-intensify-suicidal-thoughts-people-struggling-mental-health-study-says-471194</guid><pubDate> Thu, 14 Dec 2023 23:32:08 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>