<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Grief Takes A Toll On Your Body: Here's What To Know]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/grief-takes-toll-your-body-heres-what-know-471457 <description><![CDATA[While mental stress is commonly acknowledged in connection with grief, it is crucial to understand that grief can also present physical symptoms, including illnesses, fatigue, pain, and sleep disturbances.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/grief-takes-toll-your-body-heres-what-know-471457</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Feb 2024 02:40:14 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sunlight Affects Female Fertility? Study Says Moderate Exposure Improves Ovarian Reserve After 30]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sunlight-affects-female-fertility-study-says-moderate-exposure-improves-ovarian-reserve-after-30-471456 <description><![CDATA[The researchers say that moderate levels of sunlight exposure could improve ovarian reserve in women over the age of 30.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/sunlight-affects-female-fertility-study-says-moderate-exposure-improves-ovarian-reserve-after-30-471456</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Feb 2024 02:03:34 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Listening To Soothing Words While Asleep Calms Heart, Promotes Deeper Sleep: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/listening-soothing-words-while-asleep-calms-heart-promotes-deeper-sleep-study-471454 <description><![CDATA[The researchers found that listening to soothing words while sleeping can calm the heart and promote deeper sleep, in contrast to neutral words that have no impact on cardiac activity.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/listening-soothing-words-while-asleep-calms-heart-promotes-deeper-sleep-study-471454</guid><pubDate> Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:34:04 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Survey Reveals Increasing Headphone Usage Among Children; Experts Caution Parents On Health Risks]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/survey-reveals-increasing-headphone-usage-among-children-experts-caution-parents-health-risks-471452 <description><![CDATA[Researchers warn about the potential negative health hazards associated with noise exposure, including the risk of sleep disruption, heightened stress levels, and potential hearing loss.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/survey-reveals-increasing-headphone-usage-among-children-experts-caution-parents-health-risks-471452</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 04:21:45 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Drug-Free Treatment For Diabetes? Study Says Red Light Therapy Could Reduce Blood Sugar Levels]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-free-treatment-diabetes-study-says-red-light-therapy-could-reduce-blood-sugar-levels-471450 <description><![CDATA[A study has uncovered a potential drug-free treatment for diabetes, as researchers noted a significant reduction in blood sugar levels after a single session of a 15-minute red light therapy.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/drug-free-treatment-diabetes-study-says-red-light-therapy-could-reduce-blood-sugar-levels-471450</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:41:11 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Norovirus Cases Surge In Northeast: Know All About Highly Contagious Stomach Bug]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/norovirus-cases-surge-northeast-know-all-about-highly-contagious-stomach-bug-471448 <description><![CDATA[As per the CDC surveillance data, northeastern states have been particularly affected by a surge in norovirus cases in the past few weeks.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/norovirus-cases-surge-northeast-know-all-about-highly-contagious-stomach-bug-471448</guid><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 01:05:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stay Active, Stay Hydrated: The 5 Best Electrolyte Powder You Need]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-active-stay-Hydrated-5-best-electrolyte-powder-you-need-471424 <description><![CDATA[Seeking the ultimate electrolyte drink? Our curated list ensures you stay active and fully hydrated.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/stay-active-stay-Hydrated-5-best-electrolyte-powder-you-need-471424</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Feb 2024 13:53:42 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Tough And Reliable: A Comprehensive Review Of The Best Steel Toe Boot]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tough-reliable-compressive-review-best-steel-toe-boot-471417 <description><![CDATA[Workers are often exposed to heavy machinery, falling objects and sharp tools. Steel toe boots protect feet from these hazards.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/tough-reliable-compressive-review-best-steel-toe-boot-471417</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Feb 2024 13:23:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Air Pollution Linked To Higher Rate Of Cardiovascular Hospitalizations In Older Adults: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-linked-higher-rate-cardioangio-hospitalization-older-adults-study-471445 <description><![CDATA[The study found that lowering annual average PM2.5 levels from 7-8 μg/m3 to below 5 μg/ could decrease overall cardiovascular hospitalizations by 15%.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/air-pollution-linked-higher-rate-cardioangio-hospitalization-older-adults-study-471445</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:08:40 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Know Signs Of Heart Attack: How Are They Different In Men And Women?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-signs-heart-attack-how-are-they- Different-men-women-471443 <description><![CDATA[Heart attacks don't discriminate, which is why it is crucial to understand how the signs might vary between the genders.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-signs-heart-attack-how-are-they- Different-men-women-471443</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Feb 2024 02:18:24 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Children's Dental Health Month: Expert Urges Care For Baby Teeth For Lifelong Wellness]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-childrens-dental-health-month-expert-urges-care-baby-teeth-lifelong-wellness-471442 <description><![CDATA["Dental health better known as oral health is very important in kids because optimal oral health as a child will set you up for a lifetime health and wellness," says an expert during National Children's Dental Health Month.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-childrens-dental-health-month-expert-urges-care-baby-teeth-lifelong-wellness-471442</guid><pubDate> Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:28:24 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>