<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[WHO Warns Of Anthrax Outbreaks In 5 African Countries; Know Symptoms, Risk Factors Of Infection]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/who-warns-anthrax-outbreaks-5-african-countries-know-symptoms-risk-factors-infection-471186 <description><![CDATA[Five countries in east and southern Africa are witnessing anthrax outbreaks, with more than 1,100 suspected cases and 20 related deaths reported this year.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/who-warns-anthrax-outbreaks-5-african-countries-know-symptoms-risk-factors-infection-471186</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 02:34:51 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Chronic Fatigue Syndrome Affects 3.3 Million Adults In US, CDC Says; Know Symptoms, Treatment Options]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-fatigue-syndrome-affects-33-million-adults-us-cdc-says-know-symptoms-treatment-options-471185 <description><![CDATA[Myalgic encephalomyelitis, or chronic fatigue syndrome, is a serious, long-term multisystem illness that limits a person's activity due to fatigue.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/chronic-fatigue-syndrome-affects-33-million-adults-us-cdc-says-know-symptoms-treatment-options-471185</guid><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 01:02:48 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Owning A Cat Raises Risk Of Schizophrenia? Study Reveals A Mysterious Association Between The Two]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/owning-cat-raises-risk-schizophrenia-study-reveals-mysterious-association- Between-two-471184 <description><![CDATA[A research team from the University of Queensland in Australia reviewed 17 studies on the topic and found a 2.35 times higher likelihood of Schizophrenia in cat owners. However, the study did not take into account other potential contributing factors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/owning-cat-raises-risk-schizophrenia-study-reveals-mysterious-association- Between-two-471184</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:32:01 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever: Know Symptoms, Prevention Steps As CDC Warns Travelers To Mexico]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rocky-mountain-spotted-fever-know-symptoms-prevention-steps-cdc-warns-travelers-mexico-471182 <description><![CDATA[The CDC has issued a health alert warning travelers to Baja California, Mexico, about Rocky Mountain spotted fever, after five people from Southern California have been hospitalized with the infection since July.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rocky-mountain-spotted-fever-know-symptoms-prevention-steps-cdc-warns-travelers-mexico-471182</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:44:23 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Constipation Awareness Month: Expert Shares Tips To Ease Bowel Movement]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/constipation-awareness-month-expert-shares-tips-ease-bowel-movement-471181 <description><![CDATA[While occasional constipation is not a cause of concern and may be resolved with diet and lifestyle adjustments, some people might need additional support from over-the-counter fiber supplements, laxatives or prescription medication.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/constipation-awareness-month-expert-shares-tips-ease-bowel-movement-471181</guid><pubDate> Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:49:57 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Flaxseeds For Breast Cancer? Study Says Manipulating Gut Microbiota Using Them Could Reduce Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flaxseeds-breast-cancer-study-says-manipulated-gut-microbiota-using-them-could-reduce-risk-471180 <description><![CDATA[In a new study, researchers manipulated gut microbiota using flaxseeds and found it could be beneficial in the prevention of breast cancer.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/flaxseeds-breast-cancer-study-says-manipulated-gut-microbiota-using-them-could-reduce-risk-471180</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Dec 2023 03:32:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mpox Outbreak: CDC Issues Warning About New Variant As Cases Surge In 2 States]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-outbreak-cdc-issues-warning-about-new-variant-cases-surge-2-states-471179 <description><![CDATA[Clade I Monkeypox virus (MPXV), the mpox variant with a 10% fatality rate, is now spreading in DRC. Cases related to this subtype of Mpox virus have not been reported in the U.S.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/mpox-outbreak-cdc-issues-warning-about-new-variant-cases-surge-2-states-471179</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Dec 2023 03:16:16 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Over 4 Hours Of Smartphone Use Linked To Higher Stress, Substance Use In Teens: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-4-hours-smartphone-use-linked-higher-stress-substance-use-teens-study-471178 <description><![CDATA[Participants who used a smartphone for more than four hours per day had higher rates of stress, thoughts of suicide and substance use compared to those with lesser usage.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/over-4-hours-smartphone-use-linked-higher-stress-substance-use-teens-study-471178</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:22:05 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[People Above 50 May Have Accelerated Aging In At Least 1 Organ; A Blood Test Could Detect It]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-above-50-may-have-accelerated-aging-least-1-organ-blood-test-could-detect-it-471176 <description><![CDATA[Researchers now say around 18% of healthy adults above the age of 50 face accelerated aging in at least one of their organs.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/people-above-50-may-have-accelerated-aging-least-1-organ-blood-test-could-detect-it-471176</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Dec 2023 03:54:53 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Concordant Hypertension: Researchers Say Many Couples Share High Blood Pressure]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/concordant-hypertension-researchers-say-many- Couples-share-high-blood-Pressure-471174 <description><![CDATA[Although hypertension is more common in the U.S. and the U.K., the likelihood of a wife having blood pressure when married to a person with hypertension is more prevalent in China and India. Researchers believe it could be due to cultural factors.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/concordant-hypertension-researchers-say-many- Couples-share-high-blood-Pressure-471174</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Dec 2023 01:58:28 -0500</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can Diet Soda Consumption Affect Your Liver? Study Says Excessive Intake Linked To Risk Of MASLD]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-diet-soda-conspiration-affect-your-liver-study-says-excessive-intake-linked-risk-masld-471173 <description><![CDATA[Excessive consumption of diet soda could raise the risk of metabolic dysfunction-associated Steatotic liver disease (MASLD), the most common form of chronic liver disease.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/can-diet-soda-conspiration-affect-your-liver-study-says-excessive-intake-linked-risk-masld-471173</guid><pubDate> Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:25:46 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>