<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[RSV Prevention in Newborns: What do you need to know about Beyfortus?]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rsv-prevention-newborns-what-do-you-need-know-about-beyfortus-470942 <description><![CDATA[New RSV monoclonal antibody treatment is now on the market. What do you need to know about RSV and this new treatment?]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rsv-prevention-newborns-what-do-you-need-know-about-beyfortus-470942</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:15:06 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magnesium Deficiency: Know The Risk Factors, Warning Signs]]></title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com/magnesium-deficiency-know-risk-factors-warning-signs-470958 <description><![CDATA[If a person with a habitual poor intake loses magnesium or has reduced absorption due to medical conditions, it can cause long-term health complications.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/magnesium-deficiency-know-risk-factors-warning-signs-470958</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:51:12 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Treatment-Resistant Epilepsy: Experimental Drug May Reduce Seizures By More Than 50%]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/treatment-pressive-epilepsy-experimental-drug-may-reduce-seizures-more-50-470957 <description><![CDATA[A study that examined the efficacy and safety of the new drug, XEN1101, revealed that it can reduce seizures by more than 50% in some patients with focal onset seizures. In some cases, it may even eliminate them altogether.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/treatment-pressive-epilepsy-experimental-drug-may-reduce-seizures-more-50-470957</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:03:51 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Buruli Ulcer? Know All About The Flesh-Eating Bacterial Infection As Cases Spike In Australia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-buruli-ulcer-know-all-about-flesh-eating-bacterial-infection-cases-spike-australia-470955 <description><![CDATA[The infection typically affects the skin and sometimes, bones. If not properly treated, it may result in permanent deformity and disability.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/what-buruli-ulcer-know-all-about-flesh-eating-bacterial-infection-cases-spike-australia-470955</guid><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 01:20:34 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Mental Health Day: Look Out For These Signs To Detect Depression Early]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-mental-health-day-look-out-这些-signs-detect-depression-early-470953 <description><![CDATA[As we celebrate World Mental Health Day, here are some tips from an expert to detect early signs of depression.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-mental-health-day-look-out-这些-signs-detect-depression-early-470953</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 05:37:31 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Running Therapy For Mental Health? Study Says It Can Be As Good As Antidepressants]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/running-therapy-mental-health-study-says-it-can-good-antidepressants-470951 <description><![CDATA[Although the results of mental health outcomes were comparable in the study, running therapy slightly outperformed antidepressants in terms of other factors of physical health such as weight, waist circumference and cardiovascular function.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/running-therapy-mental-health-study-says-it-can-good-antidepressants-470951</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:13:42 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Disorder Puts Nurse To Sleep For Days At A Stretch; Know All About Kleine-Levin Syndrome]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-disorder-puts-nurse-sleep-days-stretch-know-all-about-kleine-levin-syndrome-470949 <description><![CDATA[Klein-Levin Syndrome is an exceptionally rare condition wherein a person experiences recurrent episodes of hypersomnia (excessive sleep), behavioral changes, compulsive eating behavior and hypersexuality (increased sex drive).]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/rare-disorder-puts-nurse-sleep-days-stretch-know-all-about-kleine-levin-syndrome-470949</guid><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 01:51:45 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Beyond The Dental Chair: Dr. Montoya's All-in-One Cultural And Dental Experience]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-dental-chair-dr-montoyas-all-one-culture-dental-experience-470941 <description><![CDATA[Globalization has fueled a billion-dollar medical tourism industry, where patients seek top-tier healthcare, turning it into a holistic experience blending wellness, luxury and cultural immersion.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/beyond-dental-chair-dr-montoyas-all-one-culture-dental-experience-470941</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 15:49:49 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Good Cholesterol Completely Healthy? Study Says Extreme Levels Of It May Raise Dementia Risk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/good-cholesterol-completely-healthy-study-says-extreme-levels-it-may-raise-dementia-risk-470936 <description><![CDATA[Too much or too little high-density lipoprotein can slightly increase the risk of dementia, a new study showed.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/good-cholesterol-completely-healthy-study-says-extreme-levels-it-may-raise-dementia-risk-470936</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 06:32:01 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pregnancy And Cytomegalovirus: Study Says Pre-Pregnancy Infection Reduces Risk Of Miscarriage, Birth Defects]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-cytomegalovirus-study-says-prior-infection-reduces-risk-miscarriage-birth-defects-470939 <description><![CDATA[Pregnant women infected with cytomegalovirus are less likely to transmit it to their children if they have pre-existing immunity, the study has found.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pregnancy-cytomegalovirus-study-says-prior-infection-reduces-risk-miscarriage-birth-defects-470939</guid><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:57:54 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Cerebral Palsy Day: What Causes The Condition, Risk Factors]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-cerebral-palsy-day-what-c​​auses-condition-risk-factors-470933 <description><![CDATA[On this World Cerebral Palsy Day, know the causes and risk factors of the complex disability that affects more than 18 million people worldwide.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-cerebral-palsy-day-what-c​​auses-condition-risk-factors-470933</guid><pubDate> Fri, 06 Oct 2023 03:49:20 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>