<rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.medicaldaily.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.medicaldaily.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>医学日报</title><link/>https://www.medicaldaily.com<description>最新消息</description><language>zh </language><item><title><![CDATA[Measles Cases In Wisconsin, Illinois: Know All About The Disease That Was Once Eliminated From US]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-cases-wisconsin-illinois-know-all-about-disease-that-was-once-eliminate-us-471001 <description><![CDATA[Health officials urge people to stay up to date on immunizations after a case of measles has been confirmed in each state.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/measles-cases-wisconsin-illinois-know-all-about-disease-that-was-once-eliminate-us-471001</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 03:25:52 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[National Liver Awareness Month: Experts Offer Dietary, Lifestyle Tips To Keep The Vital Organ Healthy]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-liver-awareness-month-experts-offer-dietary-lifestyle-tips-keep-vital-organ-healthy-471000 <description><![CDATA[Many liver conditions, including fatty liver, can be reversed if they are diagnosed and treated at an early stage. A healthy diet and lifestyle modifications are equally essential.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/national-liver-awareness-month-experts-offer-dietary-lifestyle-tips-keep-vital-organ-healthy-471000</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 01:38:23 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure Fluctuations May Be A Warning Sign Of Dementia]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-Pressure-fluctuations-may-warning-sign-dementia-470994 <description><![CDATA[Short-term fluctuations of blood pressure within a day, as well as over several days or weeks, are associated with impaired cognition, a study shows.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/blood-Pressure-fluctuations-may-warning-sign-dementia-470994</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 04:22:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Campylobacter Outbreak In Utah: Know All About The Infection Associated With Raw Milk]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/campylobacter-outbreak-utah-know-all-about-infection- Associated-raw-milk-470991 <description><![CDATA[Campylobacteriosis, an infection associated with drinking raw milk, has left at least 14 people sick in Utah, health officials said.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/campylobacter-outbreak-utah-know-all-about-infection- Associated-raw-milk-470991</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 03:13:55 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Know How Much Iron You Need, Symptoms Of Deficiency And When To Take Supplements]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-how-much-iron-you-need-symptoms-deficiency-when-take-supplements-470988 <description><![CDATA[Iron is indispensable for people of all ages – from pregnant women to young children, athletes and the elderly – as it plays a crucial role in the growth, development and proper functioning of the immune system.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/know-how-much-iron-you-need-symptoms-deficiency-when-take-supplements-470988</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:25:53 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Male Infertility: Experts Make 10 Recommendations To Improve Men's Reproductive Health]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/male-infertility-experts-make-10-recommendations-improve-mens-reproductive-health-470987 <description><![CDATA[Due to the lack of knowledge and limited clinical tools for diagnosis, male infertility is often overlooked.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/male-infertility-experts-make-10-recommendations-improve-mens-reproductive-health-470987</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:40:07 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Low Birth Weight Babies 4 Times More At Risk Of Developing Fatty Liver: Study]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-birth-weight-babies-4-times-more-risk-developmenting-fatty-liver-study-470984 <description><![CDATA[Children born with weight below 2.5 kg or 5 lbs 8 oz are at a higher risk of developing metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) in childhood, adolescence or young adulthood,]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/low-birth-weight-babies-4-times-more-risk-developmenting-fatty-liver-study-470984</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 02:57:50 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultra-Processed Food Can Be Addictive Like Nicotine, Alcohol; Study Says It Affects 14% Of Adults Globally]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-can-addictive-like-nicotine-alcohol-study-says-it-affects-14-adults-470981 <description><![CDATA[After analyzing 281 studies across 36 countries, a team of researchers estimated that 14% of adults and 12% of children have an addiction to ultra-processed food.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/ultra-processed-food-can-addictive-like-nicotine-alcohol-study-says-it-affects-14-adults-470981</guid><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 01:40:46 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[World Spine Day: Know How Bad Postures Affect Health, Ways To Improve]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-spine-day-know-how-bad-postures-affect-health-ways-improve-470978 <description><![CDATA[This year's theme, "Move Your Spine," aims to encourage people to stay active for better spine health.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/world-spine-day-know-how-bad-postures-affect-health-ways-improve-470978</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 04:32:20 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pumpkin Seeds: Here's How The Superfood Can Be Beneficial]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pumpkin-seeds-heres-how-superfood-can-beneficial-470975 <description><![CDATA[Toasted pumpkin seeds can be a nutritious and satisfying snack. They can be easily included in your everyday diet in the form of toppings in cereals, soups or salads.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/pumpkin-seeds-heres-how-superfood-can-beneficial-470975</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:57:11 -0400</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Key To Exceptional Longevity: Study Identifies Common Blood Traits Among People Who Live To 100]]></title><link/> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-exceptional-longevity-study-identizes-common-blood-traits-among-people-who-live-100-470974 <description><![CDATA[People who live to 100 years have lower measures of creatinine, glucose and uric acid in their blood compared to those with a comparatively shorter lifespan, researchers say.]]></description><guid> https://www.medicaldaily.com/key-exceptional-longevity-study-identizes-common-blood-traits-among-people-who-live-100-470974</guid><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 01:57:51 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>